English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP21
Harder!
Isn't that Mr. Han?
Halt.
Your Highness!
This jerk has no shame at all.
He had the audacity to approach
the gate of Princess Ying's residence.
He needs to be taught a lesson today.
What brings you here?
Your Highness!
I beg you to save Caiwei.
Han Shiyuan,
I have given you chances before.
You didn't cherish it yourself.
Now,
what do you have to offer me in return?
Your Highness!
As long as you are willing to save her,
Shiyuan's life
will belong to you.
From now on,
no matter what you ask me to do,
Shiyuan will never refuse.
Dare you still trouble Her Highness!
Enough!
You're the epitome of a true romantic,
putting your life on the line for her.
What a shame.
The poison in Yan Caiwei
was not administered by me.
I don't know how to save her either.
You wish to follow her in life and death,
then die elsewhere together
and spare my eyes.
Ms. Yang.
Throw him back to the Yan residence.
Don't let him die here.
Understood.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, Your Highness!
Prince Xian.
Yan Kuo is timid and
unfit for greater responsibilities,
while his daughters
are all quite capable.
However, with Yan Caiwei poisoned,
It's unclear if it was Princess Ying
or the work of Chen Huo'e.
If Yan Caiwei
were to die from this poison,
Princess Ying and Chen Huo'e
would be inextricably linked.
In fact,
it doesn't even matter whether it was her
Shen Du will certainly side with us
for the sake of his sister-in-law.
Even if Shen Du remains foolish
and doesn't align with us,
Princess Ying
wouldn't dare to trust him any longer.
Sir,
what have you been
hiding from me
all these years?
Your Highness.
your benevolence is well-known,
but great deeds require overlooking trifles.
A true leader is not soft when necessary.
You were born into the royal family,
and thus cannot escape
the intricacies of power and human nature.
Even the Her Majesty
had to navigate carefully in her time
to secure her position.
The late Crown Prince's death remain murky,
- and now the young emperor... - Insolent!
I may have spoken out of turn,
but I assure you,
my loyalty to Prince Xian
is as steadfast as the sun in the sky.
Sir,
over the years, you have
protected me with unwavering dedication,
and every action you've taken
has been to pave the way for my future.
I am fully aware of that.
However, I truly do not wish
to witness family members
turning against one another.
If it must come to that,
then I would rather forgo the regency.
Prince Xian,
you must not entertain
such thoughts!
You are the current Prince Xian.
In the future,
you'll undoubtedly rise to the position of
regent of our empire!
Everything I have done
has been in your best interests!
Your Highness!
Foolish!
Sir,
does the pursuit of power
truly warrant such an obsession?
Lord Shen!
Are you concerned about
my lady's?
Nonsense!
My Lord!
My remark was truly foolish.
However,
I seem to know
what my lady
was preoccupied with
all night at the Ministry of Justice.
Yesterday, Yan Mojie came to see me.
He asked me
to help him look through
the files at the headquarters.
I heard that Yan Caiwei
has been severely poisoned,
and it seems to be
Fire Moth Sect's infamous poison of
"co"
"coco"
"cocoon"
"cocoon poison"
Cocoon poison?
Yes.
The entire Yan residence
has been in chaos these past few days
because of this.
The Yan residence is in chaos?
How come I haven't heard a word?
Perhaps my lady didn't want to bother you?
Even Yan Mojie knows to seek your help
when something goes wrong.
How could she not know who to turn to?
Then my lady must have
her own connections.
I have heard that
my lady went to the palace today
to consult a healer.
It is said that
she even presented a recipe for an
antidote from the Imperial Inspectorate.
Rumor has it that
this was based on Chen Huo'e's
testimony during interrogation.
Imperial Inspectorate?
Chen Huo'e?
I have already inquired with
that healer.
He indicated that the antidote
is about eighty percent authentic,
but
there is a super rare
ingredient in it.
What ingredient?
It's a doppelganger's
blood
blood of
blood of heart.
Anyone here?
Are there no
living human beings in the Lai residence?
Lord Shen,
what kind of trickery
is Lai Luozhi trying to pull?
If you know it's a trick,
why be anxious?
You all stay put.
I'll go check in the back.
Lord Shen!
Ease your mind.
Chancellor Lai,
You've orchestrated such a show
just to lure me here.
What?
I'm already here.
Yet you're hiding and avoiding me.
This is not in line with
your usual style of
assertive presence.
I apologize for intruding upon a lady,
I was indeed rude.
This is your first visit to my residence,
and you're already chasing after a lady.
If this were to spread,
it would surely become a laughingstock.
Chancellor Lai,
enough with these
intimidating theatrics.
These flashy little tricks are
hardly worthy of The White Death's attention.
However, Lord Shen,
you've intruded into my residence,
so you owe me an explanation.
If I didn't come,
would you offer me the heart's blood
of a doppelganger?
What do you mean by that?
You intentionally poisoned Yan Caiwei
and had Yan Xing obtain the recipe,
which obviously implies you
possess the heart's blood of Chen Huo'e.
And you use it as a bait.
Lord Shen,
that was merely your conjecture.
I do not acknowledge a word of it.
However...
I happen to have
a vial of the heart's blood
of a doppelganger.
Lord Shen,
don't!
What's the matter?
Do you think my water is tainted,
or are you worried it might be poisonous?
I have always held you in high regard,
Lord Shen.
You've made quite the entrance,
storming into my residence.
If you can't make it out today,
or if you leave and
soon suffer from poisoning,
I would indeed have a hard time
explaining this to Her Majesty.
Where's the blood of the doppelganger?
It's right in your teacup.
You tricked him into drinking it?
You sealed the heart's blood of the
doppelganger in this teacup?
I specifically sought out
skilled craftsmen from Xichen
to create this
teacup for the heart's blood.
In fact,
the ingredient you're looking for
has always been right in front of you.
Yet you treat my residence
like a den of snakes and scorpions,
not even daring to drink a cup of tea.
Actually,
I am not someone
who is untrustworthy.
Isn't that so?
In this world,
the heart's blood of a doppelganger
is exceedingly rare.
This cup is a true work of art,
and it surely won't come without a price.
Chancellor Lai has orchestrated
such an elaborate scheme to draw me here.
What is it that you seek?
Speak plainly.
It's a relief to talk
to someone intelligent.
In truth,
I have no specific demands,
except that you, Lord Shen,
remember this favor of mine.
In the future,
you will surely repay it in double.
Then there's no other way,
but to see if you
truly love your wife.
To see if you are willing to
make an uncertain promise
to save your sister-in-law.
I have
taken up the offer.
Lord Shen,
I won't see you off.
I truly don't get it.
You planned this scheme meticulously,
first with the poisoning,
then providing the antidote,
asking me to show my face in front of him.
What exactly are you plotting?
You don't need to understand.
I don't need to understand?
Our entire family has sacrificed so much
for your so-called grand ambitions.
Haven't we given enough?
Now,
I don't even have the right
to ask a question?
It's my fault,
sister.
I was just anxious.
How could I not understand your suffering?
Everything I do
is to ensure that
all our sacrifices
will be rewarded appropriately.
Poisoning Yan Caiwei
can draw the attention of Prince Xian,
Princess Ying and the Imperial Guard,
creating suspicion among these parties.
This goal has already been achieved.
As for Shen Du,
he is indeed the hardest to deal with.
The Imperial Guard and Shen residence
are heavily guarded.
The spies inserted in
have all been removed.
Is Shen Du on Prince Xian's side?
No.
Shen Du has always
maintained neutrality.
He neither supports Prince Xian,
nor favors Princess Ying,
and he keeps his distance from me.
The more cautious he is
in maintaining balance,
the more the Her Majesty
trusts him,
which is increasingly unfavorable
for what we intend to do.
Then why not just kill him?
Or directly make demands of him?
Unknown promises are the most terrifying.
I want to instill in him
a sense of unease,
a sense of fear,
and a hesitation filled with doubt.
Once fear takes
root in his heart,
one day,
it will be more useful
than death itself.
Xing!
All the ingredients are ready.
We're just missing one,
the heart's blood of a doppelganger.
But over at Lord Zhang,
your father hit a snag.
As for Princess Ying,
Shiyuan got beaten.
I'm at my wit's end.
I beg you,
please think of another way!
- My Lady! - My Lady.
My lady, what are you doing?
Aren't you just pushing her?
She's already been trying to find a way,
and she's exhausted.
What more can she think of?
What about...
What about Lord Shen.
Silence!
Why should I?
Chen Huo'e
was killed by The White Death,
and the retribution has fallen on my girl.
Why shouldn't I
ask The White Death for help,
and let him figure something out?
Even if Caiwei once wronged him,
no matter what,
she is still his sister-in-law now!
- My lady! - What you said makes sense!
I'm late.
- Lord Shen! - No formalities.
Here is the missing ingredient,
the heart's blood of a doppelganger.
It's contained right in this teacup.
We're grateful to you for saving her life!
Please, rise.
Xing and I are one.
The affairs of the Yan residence
are also my responsibility.
This can't wait any longer.
Gratitude, Lord Shen!
I will take it to prepare the antidote.
Hurry, hurry!
Caiwei is saved!
Come on, come on!
Xing,
when will I finally be
your first choice
when you need help?
Xing!
It's alright now.
Can we really trust
Lai Luozhi's words?
Is the heart's blood he provided
reliable?
You can't fully trust
anyone's words.
Shen Du,
I have something important to tell you.
If I don't tell you now,
I might miss my chance in the future.
Do you know
what Lord Zhang's intention was
by insisting on marrying a girl
from the Yan Family to you?
Lord Zhang coerced my father,
arranging this marriage.
Originally, Caiwei was to marry you,
but I took her place.
Lord Zhang still expects me
to be his and the Prince Xian's eyes
within Shen residence.
But I've never truly assisted
Prince Xian's faction to harm you.
I know.
I believe you wouldn't harm me.
You know?
You really trust me?
Xing,
since you have never done anything
to harm me,
there's no need to feel guilty.
In the future, if you have
any doubts,
just come and ask me,
alright?
What are you doing?
Spit it out!
Spit it!
Come on!
Spit it out!
Hurry!
If you can test the antidote for your sister,
I can certainly do the same for you.
Who asked you to do that?
You...
I will use my internal energy
to spread the effect throughout my system.
If I remain unharmed
after a short while, your sister
can take the antidote with peace of mind.
Why were you being so foolish?
Testing the antidote for my sister
is a duty of blood relatives.
What's with you?
Do you feel any discomfort?
Your wounds have just healed.
How can you take such a risk?
After taking it,
do you feel any discomfort?
Anything?
Are you feeling unwell at all?
Say something!
I'm really fine.
Since Lai Luozhi was
trying to draw me in,
the item he offered should be authentic.
However, he clearly didn't foresee
that I would personally take the antidote.
Otherwise,
he might have actually included
something deadly in it.
Ouch!
It hurts!
Let me take a look.
I wasn't poisoned to death,
but I might just get beaten to death.
The antidote is fine.
Hurry and take it to your sister.
Hurry.
Here it comes, the antidote is here!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Don't worry,
she will regain consciousness soon.
It's already been two hours.
Mother...
Caiwei,
you're awake!
Mother...
Caiwei!
Caiwei, you're awake!
Xing...
Father...
Where is my love?
Caiwei!
My love!
What happened to you?
Father!
Princess Ying sent a gift box,
along with a note.
Princess Ying?
Read it!
I have heard that Mr. Han and Yan Caiwei
share a deep bond,
In life and death, they vow never to part.
This love, so fervent, so bright and pure.
The radiance of their affection,
akin to the blooms of the crabapple,
Moved by their devotion,
I too wish to see their love fulfilled,
For such passion should
not be denied by fate.
I bestow upon them a jade ornament,
May their love last, forever in harmony.
It seems that
Princess Ying
intends to
let Mr. Han go
and fulfill your happiness.
Xing,
are you feeling unwell?
No, not at all.
Why did Lai Luozhi do all these?
Poisoning and then supplying the antidote,
going in circles.
What is his purpose?
His target
may not be your sister,
but me.
He wants to set a trap
to hold something over you,
to grant you a favor.
Have you been threatened by him?
Or have you promised him anything?
Don't worry,
nothing happened.
Instead, it's your sister who has been
suffering this undeserved misfortune.
So,
pursuing justice with all your heart
and seeking the truth
can indeed bring unforeseen risks
to your loved ones.
However,
the path we choose
is destined to be
a thorny road, isn't it?
Since I have made this choice,
I will not regret it.
I must stay true to my heart
and do everything I can
to protect those around me.
Xing,
from now on, focus on
what you believe is right.
I will protect you
and ensure your family remains safe.
Shen Du...
Lord Shen!
What is it?
Are you sending my lady back
or heading to the Imperial Guard?
To the Shen residence.
Understood!
Earlier,
what did you want to ask me?
Nothing...
Nothing at all.
Shen Du.
You protect me,
help me,
support me...
Then in your heart
what am I
to you?
You...
You should get some rest.
I'll study for a bit.
Study?
The examination is coming up.
I made a commitment
in front of Her Majesty
and Lady Xu.
I'll take part in the exam as a scribe.
If I fail,
I won't even be able to
remain as a clerk.
Now that Caiwei's poison has been cured
and the Chen Huo'e case is resolved,
if I don't burn the midnight oil now,
I might fail the examination.
So tonight,
you've been in and out,
moving stuff around,
just to use my lighting to study?
Exactly!
You happen to like the light, right?
We could save the oil for several lamps!
Then I wish you
success in your examination
and may your wish come true.
Thank you for your kind words!
It's rare for you to take the initiative.
Is there some good news?
Well,
thank you.
Caiwei's poison has been cured.
Your recipe really worked.
Of course.
How could my recipe be fake?
I...
Have I ever deceived you?
You clearly...
Alright,
it's true that I've been
calling you "maskman" on my own.
I wouldn't say you've deceived me.
Anyway...
Anyway,
thank you.
Thank me?
A mere oral gratitude
might not be enough.
What do you want then?
You shouldn't be asking me this.
You should think carefully about
how you plan to show your gratitude.
Lu Chuichui?
Lu Chuichui!
I'm here.
Chui?
Chui!
Chui,
what's wrong?
Poker face...
I...
He...
I thought...
What happened?
It's nothing.
My feet are numb.
Your feet are numb?
You really scared me!
I thought
something bad had happened!
Poker face, poker face...
Can you take me home?
Come on, slowly.
What are you doing?
Didn't you say your feet are numb?
I'll carry you.
Poker face,
tell me,
if there's someone
who is usually extremely wicked,
hated by everyone,
but occasionally shows kindness
and genuinely helps others,
is he a good person?
Is he worth being friends with?
This is up to you.
You should ask yourself,
not others.
If
you believe that person is a friend
and that he is a good person,
and he also won't harm you,
Then he's surely worth befriending.
I should ask myself,
not others?
Chi,
by the time you receive this letter,
I will likely be participating
in the examination for female officials.
In this examination,
I have truly burned my bridges,
staking my future as a female official.
But I believe
I won't let down Her Majesty
or Lady Xu's trust in me.
I'll also honor
the help he has given me.
Oh my, Xing girl,
you are first place!
My Xing is the top scorer!
Oh my, that's fantastic, Xing!
You'll finally be promoted to scribe!
I'm about to have
an rank-eight friend looking out for me!
What about you?
Me?
Never mind about me.
Anyway, I already have
an rank-eight bestie.
I don't care if I fail!
- So happy. - Chui!
Chui!
You made the list!
You finally made the list!
This time,
I didn't spend any money
on tutors.
You made it entirely on your own merit!
Though it's the last place,
I am still proud of you!
My precious daughter!
Lord Shen,
my lady will be promoted to a scribe.
She will out rank even me.
Do you have issues with it?
Not at all!
I'm truly happy for my lady!
Let's go.
Father,
the order doesn't mention the Yans at all!
Did you check it thoroughly?
I've gone through it line by line,
and it doesn't mention us!
The order personally signed by Lord Zhang,
among the officials assigned for border duty,
doesn't mention the Yan Family!
That's fantastic!
Thank goodness, thank goodness!
Our Yan family has finally escaped this.
We've avoided a catastrophe!
Xing,
today our Yan Family is truly
blessed with two auspicious events!
Two fortunate events!
Let's treat ourselves to something nice.
Absolutely!
Good, good.
Mother!