[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP32]
I didn't plan to keep you
and Lady Shen here today.
No need to be so uptight.
However, I still want to offer you both
a piece of advice.
The criminals apprehended by the
Imperial Inspectorate aren't ones you can
simply exonerate at will.
You'd better consider carefully
which words to heed,
which words to report,
Some things
are best kept to yourself.
Don't bring trouble upon
yourself and your family.
What exactly is Lai Luozhi's intention?
Do you doubt Sun Tan's words?
Absolutely not.
It's just that the looming truth
is far too frightening.
It's genuinely unsettling.
But just as Lai Luozhi mentioned,
we were only speculating,
there's no concrete proof.
I'm afraid that for now,
it's difficult to take action against him.
And what about
Sun Tan's testimony?
I will, of course, report it honestly.
Xing,
gratitude!
Scribe Lu,
you honor us with your presence,
yet you're leaving without
so much as a greeting?
What's going on?
It appears you're scared of me again.
You...
Have you been
arresting a lot of officials lately?
Yes, that's true.
You and your
nosy friend
came to the Imperial Inspectorate
because of this, right?
What exactly are you trying to do?
You're not planning to
harm Yan Xing, are you?
That's really not fair.
You claimed I am your friend,
so why is your worry
solely about me hurting her
and not about
whether she might
sabotage my plans?
I don't consider people like you as friends.
I'm warning you,
you absolutely must not harm Yan Xing.
If anything
happens to her,
I will never forgive you!
Then we'll see
what her true intentions are.
You work at the Ministry of Justice,
so what were you doing at II?
And even entered the palace
to submit an appeal to Lady Xu?
Are you still having your guardsmen
keeping an eye on me?
Do you realize...
that the moment you stepped out of
the Imperial Inspectorate
with Sun Tan's testimony,
your head
was no longer safe on your shoulders?
But Sun Tan suspects that
Lai Luozhi is plotting to seize control of
the Gannan garrison and may even conspire
with nomadic tribes for sinister purposes.
With such crucial military intelligence,
shouldn't it be reported to Her Majesty?
Moreover,
you also want to save Sun Tan, right?
Sun Tan had been quite beneficial to us
in Gannan,
so, I want to save him for sure.
But I prefer you stay out of harm's way.
I understand your nature, and I'm not
trying to hinder your investigation.
However, moving forward,
you need to be more cautious.
Next time you face a challenge,
remember that your husband,
is the commander of the Imperial Guard.
I worry that I might bring you trouble.
If trouble was what I feared,
I wouldn't be marrying you.
My love,
what do you think Her Majesty
will decide after reviewing
Sun Tan's testimony?
I can't say for sure.
My actions today have truly
provoked Lai Luozhi.
I can't even discern
if I'm truly aiding Sun Tan
or inadvertently putting him in jeopardy.
As long as your conscience remains clear,
don't fret about what lies ahead.
Since you've allied with Yan Xing
and Xu Xiangren against me,
you must be fully aware
of the consequences
that await you.
However,
you still have a chance to survive.
if you provide me with a list
of the bandits Xu Xiangren
was associated with before
he became the Chief Inspector.
I assure you,
you can walk out of here alive,
and even secure
the position of the next Chief Inspector.
You want me to frame Chief?
Xu Xiangren
is quite a thorn to me.
Do you know how Xu Xiangren came to
hold the position of
the Chief Inspector?
Years ago, he made three bets
with the current queen
to steal treasures from the palace.
He actually succeeded in
taking treasures from
the heavily guarded palace.
Her Majesty recognized his talent,
which is why she allowed him
to succeed Chief Yuan.
With your capabilities,
how could you possibly take him on?
He's a tough nut to crack, but
it depends on what you use to break him.
All you need to do is provide the list,
and leave the rest
to the Imperial Inspectorate.
This should be easy for you,
and it's not really a betrayal,
is it?
Don't you aspire to become
the Chief Inspector who commands
all the delinquents?
I do...
I truly desire it!
The command token for
all the delinquents;
I genuinely want it!
I'll wait for your list.
What did you steal?
Stay out of my way!
Even thieves have their code of honor.
You stole
and then employed such a brutal move.
Today, I'll make you...
Don't hurt Tan!
Go! All of you!
Let Tan go!
We'll give you all our food!
Just run!
He stole things
just to feed all of you?
Tan is a good man.
If it weren't for him,
I would have starved to death.
Leave!
Don't hurt him, sir.
He is a good man.
Yeah, he is a good man.
Don't hit him.
From now on, stop stealing.
Just join me.
Quit pretending to be a good person!
You hardly look like
someone wealthy.
You might have stolen less than I have!
It's just that my skills aren't there yet.
Once I hone my skills, I'll even swipe
the treasures from the royal palace!
Sounds good.
Just you wait,
I'll go and steal
some treasures from the palace
to show you all!
Easy.
Did you really steal all these
from the palace?
I've made a promise to the queen
that from now on, I'll take the
position as the Chief Inspector
who commands all the delinquents
in the empire.
Join me,
and we'll all
be delinquents.
Being merely a delinquent isn't enough.
I aim to be a
Chief Inspector.
-Am I right?
-Yeah.
You are ambitious, good.
Then you'll need to find a way
to defeat me.
Get down.
Once I get stronger,
I will take you down!
Alright then.
Then I make you this promise:
If I ever meet my end,
the token of the Chief Inspector
will be yours to claim.
Fair enough.
I promise you,
I'll join the ranks of the Delinquents
until the day you take your last breath.
[I'm not dead yet,]
[and this token]
[is still waiting for you to claim it!]
But you're still alive,
how could I possibly take your token...
Xing,
the documents from the
Imperial Inspectorate are here for you.
I thought
Lai Luozhi would cause you trouble,
but seeing you alright today
puts my mind at ease.
Xing,
what does it say?
"Sun Tan took his own life out of guilt..."
He really is gone...
Lai Luozhi,
that bastard!
Xiangren,
I'm the one who caused Sun Tan's demise!
Chief anticipated you'd think this way,
so as soon as we received the news,
we rushed over.
What Sun Tan wanted to express has already
been conveyed through your memo.
He chose to end his life
partly to protect
the brothers in Gannan.
Also,
he must have wanted to keep me safe.
Brother,
rest in peace!
Xing!
Why were you drinking?
I got you.
Watch your step.
Was it because of Sun Tan?
Sun Tan is a genuine hero,
through and through.
I failed to keep him alive.
I originally
planned to plead for him today,
but it was too late.
Sun Tan's death is so unjust...
Here, read this.
A letter from Pan Chi.
Pan Chi...
You're still feeling jealous?
Seriously?
This is major!
It's concerning the incident of the Shens!
Look,
Pan Chi mentions that the granary's fire
involved the "Ignition Craft,"
Which suggests that the granary fire that
led to the conviction of the Shen Family,
was deliberately
ignited using Ignition Craft.
But the pattern on this jade pendant...
What's wrong?
This was from the wedding of
the late emperor and Her Majesty,
a pattern bestowed by the late emperor
to the Zhou Family.
The Zhou Family?
Is he implying that
the fire was set
by the Zhou Family?
[The one responsible for the deaths]
[of everyone in the Shen Family]
[has always been none other than]
[her, Zhou Xu.]
[The Zhou Family!]
That's a secret technique of the Fire Moth Sect.
How could it involve the Zhou Family?
Xing,
you should get some sleep now.
No!
I promised to help you
uncover the truth.
Now that we finally got
a lead,
how could it possibly be the Zhou Family?
Lord Shen,
here's a classified message from Gannan.
It contains the results
[of the autopsies of those]
[masked spectres in Gannan.]
[Those triangular puncture wounds]
[have been proved to be]
[a medium for a type of chronic poison]
[known as Ten-Day Grasp.]
[As the name suggests,]
[it means that after ten days of poisoning,]
[the King of Hell will collect the soul,]
[and the victim will succumb to the poison.]
Xing!
Xing.
The deceased have
triangular puncture wounds on their neck?
Yuan Niang...
Yuan Niang too!
Shen Du, do you recall
the day of the Royal Advisor's memorial?
I was arrested by you and Lai Luozhi.
I was actually on the mountain
investigating Yuan's case.
It was concluded as a crime of passion,
but while I was
organizing the files,
I discovered
that Yuan also had
triangular puncture wounds.
This indicates that Yuan
very likely also fell victim to
the Ten-Day Grasp.
Why would the Fire Moth Sect target her,
and even use a chronic toxin?
A common rural woman of the highlands
being targeted
and poisoned with a chronic toxin
only leaves one possibility:
she must have known
something she shouldn't have,
so needed to be silenced.
Look into it
to see if she has
any special identity
or other secrets.
Understood!
It seems that the granary
was indeed empty back then.
Using the Fire Moth Sect's Ignition Craft
to burn the granary
was to cover up the
fact that the granary was already empty.
This is likely
connected to Lai Luozhi.
And the Zhou Family...
Xing,
thank you!
It seems that
the forces behind the injustice done to my
Shen Family are deeply intertwined.
We should wait for the right moment.
Xing,
no matter what,
I hope nothing bad happens to you.
Shen Du.
What time is it?
Don't worry,
today is a day off.
You were drunk last night.
Pan Chi's letter...
It's quite useful.
The intricate network
behind the Shen Family's incident
is on the verge of exposure.
Thank you, my love.
Yuan!
The Ten-Day Grasp!
Jing Lin went to investigate.
Not only was she a rural woman from
the nearby mountains, but she was also
tasked with cleaning the Ming Hall.
Ming Hall?
The Royal Advisor used to
live in the Ming Hall.
But ever since he passed away,
everyone related to the Ming Hall
has disappeared without a trace.
Could all of this
be tied to the Royal Advisor's death?
Is it possible that he...
After delivering
his final prophecy,
he passed away shortly thereafter.
I once heard rumors
that his last prophecy
"The phoenix leading nine chicks, peace in the world"
and there is an unknown
second half to it.
So it seems that
the Royal Advisor's death
might be quite suspicious.
Could it be that
the Royal Advisor's death and Yuan's death
and the disappearance of those
connected to the Ming Hall
are all linked to that prophecy?
[My lady,]
[there's a decree from the palace,]
[stating that Her Majesty]
[wants to see you alone in the palace.]
I'm going with you.
Her Majesty
wants me to go alone.
Alright, Uncle Zhong,
I heard you!
Please have the messenger wait a moment;
I will get changed and go right away.
Yes!
Wait for me.
Be cautious,
and don't be impulsive.
Also,
never bring up
Sun Tan
and anything related to Lai Luozhi.
Do not mention the Shen Family...
Alright,
I'll keep those in mind.
How did you get
so chatty all of a sudden?
Lady Xu,
this isn't the path to the study chamber.
You won't be going there today.
She's waiting for you in her sleeping chamber.
Her Majesty' sleeping chamber?
Your Royal Highness.
Greetings, Your Royal Highness.
Please rise.
Emerald cake?
This is my
absolute favorite treat!
These days, my stomach can't handle much.
A half-piece would render me
unable to eat for the rest of the day,
a far cry from your youthful appetites.
Have a taste.
Emerald cakes
are exceptionally rare.
They're crafted from the tribute
glutinous rice from the Western Regions,
dried and ground into fine powder,
combined with lotus leaf powder.
The filling is even more elaborate.
Her Majesty
rarely bestows this upon others.
Why don't you give it a try
and see how it compares to others?
To my surprise, it's savory.
Whether it be pastries
or a person,
appearances can
be really
deceiving.
Aren't you the talkative one, huh?
Your Royal Highness.
Your Royal Highness,
winter is just around the corner.
Please stay warm and avoid getting sick.
You all just
view me as aged.
Your Royal Highness
is the empire's guardian star.
The people yearn for
your eternal life, to ensure your
continued guidance and protection.
Yan Xing,
do you know why
I summoned you?
Your Royal Highness, I am unaware.
I seek clarity
on certain issues.
One of which is the rumor
that the
late governor of Yingzhou,
Mo Qianzhi,
alleged that I was
behind the Shen Family incident.
Shen Du's allegiance to
Your Royal Highness is steadfast,
and I share that allegiance.
Stay calm,
rise and explain in detail.
Mo Qianzhi indeed made such claims,
but Shen Du has
served Your Royal Highness for so long.
He cannot be so easily misled.
Besides,
Mo Qianzhi was ensnared by
the deceit of wicked people,
leading him to embrace those claims.
Motivated by a desire to honor his mentor,
he was relentless in his pursuit of
the truth about the Shens' incident.
Unfortunately, he was misguided
and ended up as a
puppet for the Fire Moth Sect,
resulting in a huge mistake.
There's another issue.
They've been hidden in Yingzhou for years,
yet no whispers have escaped.
Could it be that they have
a presence elsewhere too?
Um...
There may well be such a presence,
but their
public identity is
unknown to us.
The Yingzhou incident serves as a precedent.
Mo Qianzhi met his end already,
might there not be
others like him to emerge?
Your Majesty is devoted to the people.
The people live in harmony and contentment.
There will surely not be more individuals
akin to Mo Qianzhi
appearing.
[Back in those days, I brought the]
[young emperor to attend court affairs,]
[which caused me countless accusations.]
How many truly understand
the helplessness I faced?
Everyone
wants to live a peaceful life.
But since we hold our positions,
we must shoulder the
responsibilities that come with them.
As the Empress Dowager,
I am well aware of the uncertain future.
But I have never given up.
With Qi (emperor) being so young,
as a woman in charge,
how many men would truly respect this?
But I will make them respect!
These years have been relatively stable.
I have not failed the late emperor's trust!
The grace of Your Royal Highness
is a shining example
for all the women of the empire.
And one more thing...
About the death of Sun Tan,
I know you were under pressure when you
submitted the petition to the palace.
But Sun Tan
still died under mysterious circumstances.
Do you believe
I am the one
allowing Lai Luozhi to act with impunity?
Your Royal Highness needs
to have Chancellor Lai oversee the officials.
It requires a display of great authority.
But I understand, no one is infallible;
who can be without faults?
If there are any complexities in the case,
I am willing to be a loyal subject
and speak candidly to correct any errors!
Excellent!
What a loyal and honest official!
Yan Xing's sharp and honest tongue
is something I cherish.
Do you know
that Lai Luozhi
visited me last night?
He spoke highly of your accomplishments.
He also told me to
make sure to put you to good use.
I am truly honored.
I have no connection with Lord Lai
and do not know
what Lord Lai's recommendation
entails.
I
do not seek any rewards or promotions.
I only wish to investigate cases,
to uncover the truth,
and bring justice to the deceased.
Alright, alright, you may rise.
How many times
have you knelt already?
Rise.
Come here.
Here,
take this.
Looking at you,
I am reminded of my younger days.
If you have some free time,
come to the palace more often
to chat with me.
Gratitude, Your Royal Highness.
Have you heard of Imperial Consort Shu?
The late emperor's
concubine from Nanlang?
I have heard a bit.
This was once the residence
bestowed to her by the late emperor.
There are rumors that she was killed
by the then-queen,
who is now the Empress Dowager,
in a struggle for favor.
In reality, she passed away
from longing for her homeland.
This palace
has added yet another tale of unfulfilled
heartbreak.
Now that you possess the
token to enter and exit the palace freely,
you should be able to grasp the depth
of the royal grace, which is as profound
as the sea, but also as heavy as a mountain.
I only feel anxious,
so please guide me, Lady Xu.
A few days ago, I helped you submit
Sun Tan's testimony.
Her Royal Highness did not respond.
But Lai Luozhi deliberately flattered you
with hidden intentions.
Today, Her Royal Highness
has specially invited you here
to give you a chance to speak.
You should understand
that Her Royal Highness
in this male-dominated world
must consider the voices of the subjects
while ensuring the loyalty of her officials.
I once believed that all matters
in this world are black and white.
But after all I've been through,
I've come to understand a bit more.
Her Majesty intends to show you favor
because she genuinely values you, for one,
and secondly,
it is also for Shen Du's sake.
You were married into the Shen Family
through the efforts of Lord Zhang.
Now,
Lai Luozhi also speaks highly of you,
which makes it hard not to suspect
whether you are maneuvering
between different factions.
Chief Clerk Yan Xing of the Ministry of Justice
offers my greetings to Lord Lai.
Having spent a long time with Shen Du,
your boldness
has certainly increased, Lady Yan.
I didn't get your point, Lord Lai.
Even the head of the Imperial Court
avoids this case,
yet Lady Yan dares to step forward
to take the lead.
It must be because you have
the support of the Imperial Guard, right?
And even those outlaws from the
Delinquents are also willing to help you.
Your clownish behavior does nothing
to alter the fact that the
Sun Tan' case
is irrelevant to me.
You should really grasp the situation.
Thank you for the reminder, Lord Lai.
I possess no extraordinary talents,
so apparently, my actions
are not always well-considered.
By the way,
your sister's actions are commendable.
She excels in literature and martial arts,
truly unparalleled.
That said,
the other day, my husband and I
were strolling through the streets of Yingzhou
and he mentioned
that he thought he saw your sister.
What are you talking about?
Recently, it has been quite chilly,
and my sister has been staying indoors.
A few days ago,
she was enjoying an outing
with the families of several officials.
How could she have been to Yingzhou?
My lady's accusations should
at least be backed by evidence, right?
If Shen Du is not guiding you properly,
you might as well come to my office.
I will certainly guide you
how to navigate these matters effectively.
Is that so?
Then I wish Lord Lai's sister
good health.
I'll humbly excuse myself now.
It just came to my mind that
Prince Xian is hosting a banquet
for officials during the Winter Solstice.
I assume the Shen residence
has received an invitation as well?
Lady Yan, we will
meet again at Prince Xian's residence
Shen Du!
I received words from the palace that
Lai Luozhi intercepted you on your way out.
I rushed over immediately.
He didn't harm you, did he?
Your ears are all red from the cold.
You often complain that the carriage
is slow, so why are you with one today?
It's cold out here,
and riding a horse would be chilling.
I never realized before
that you could be so thoughtful.
How did the meeting in the palace go?
Her Majesty' personal token?
Lady Xu reminded me of something:
"The depth of the royal grace, which is as"
"profound as the sea, but also as heavy as a mountain."
If I'm not mistaken, Her Majesty
has instructed my Imperial Guard to
keep an eye on the Imperial Inspectorate
and Lai Luozhi, while at the same time,
Lai Luozhi has also received orders
to monitor the Imperial Guard.
No wonder today
Lai Luozhi specifically
waited for me at the palace gate
and even praised me
in front of Her Majesty.
He probably figured it out too.
By the way,
at Prince Xian's feast,
do you think Lai Luozhi might
try to pull any underhanded tricks?
Ease your mind.
I'll definitely keep you safe.
Let's go.