Hello Debate Opponent 2 EP15
On New Year's Eve
from the opposite sex
if you receive an apple
then be careful.
He is not wishing you healthy
but courting you.
Why not friend WeChat account directly?
Don't these apples taste good?
You don't understand.
Look at you, a hick
who think that giving apples on New Year's Eve
means wishing someone peace.
Here's one for you.
Do I have to tell you whom you should give it to?
I'm waiting for apples from the opposite sex.
Hum
that's it.
Boss, are there more apples?
It's the last one over there
because apples sell well these days.
It's not good, so you can get it cheaper
two yuan.
Eat it, it's been washed.
Nan Bei
do you know
what it means
to give apples today?
I know
wish someone peace.
How are you going to celebrate the holidays?
Let's go to the People's Square.
It's a large place with few buildings surrounding it
and we can also set off fireworks.
So
let's go buy them later.
Nan Bei
Oh
sorry, I have something to do this afternoon.
You guys just go ahead.
Since it's not night yet
let us
use our time wisely
to prepare.
Ah.
Hello
do you see it under the table?
Hold on a minute.
I'll be right here.
Fructose, fructose, fructose.
Low sugar, low sugar, low sugar.
Fibre, fibre, fibre.
Your sacrifice is worth it.
Put the apple on the top.
What are you doing there?
Auntie, did you find
a stereo?
Auntie, auntie, auntie.
Ah
I'm sorry.
Hello, Hei
I need an apple
not an iPhone worth over 10,000 yuan
but an edible apple.
Forget it.
I'll get it myself.
Hello
what are you doing now?
I'm busy right now.
I'll call you later.
Nan Bei
Pay first, don't crowd
and don't snatch.
Boss
do you know
where I can get apples?
There's an apple orchard over there.
Try your luck there.
That's my bike.
I only borrowed it for a minute
and I'll buy you five kilos of apples tomorrow.
Don't forget to give it back to me.
Uncle
where's an apple orchard around here?
Do you say the earth is round?
No
I mean where is the apple orchard?
My last name is not Li.
Have a rest.
OK.
Boss
here comes the customer
boss.
What are you doing?
Boss
Stealing apples?
Go, my dog.
Boss
the money is in the basket.
Sorry, sorry
sorry, sorry
sorry, sorry.
Sir
People's Square.
Where's my phone?
Sir
how much is it to go to People's Square
If there's no traffic jam
it's about 30 or 40 yuan.
Relax, young man.
The bureau of public security is a few hundred meters ahead.
How about taking you there first?
Please don't do that.
Sir
I lost my phone
and ran out of money.
I'm not looking for a free ride.
I only have 8.9 yuan.
So, can we just
drive for 8.9 yuan?
You look like a student.
The apples
must have just been picked from the orchard.
How about
two yuan for an apple
and count how many apples you have.
All right
one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
eight.
Sir
there are eight apples in total.
Two yuan for an apple
16 yuan in total
plus this 9.8 yuan
where do you think we can go?
So
I can give you a rock-bottom price.
Later
I'll take you to the street.
For me
I can drive you for 30 yuan at most.
For the remaining 10 kilometers
you have to rely on yourself.
Thanks.
Hao
You come here so early, Xiaoyu
You too.
Where are Nan Bei
and Dango?
Dango went out to buy fireworks
and she will be back soon.
Nan Bei
Do you know where he has gone?
Did you quarrel again?
It's not a big deal.
Dandan picked up his phone
and asked me to give it back to him.
He said he saw Nan Bei
being chased by a group of uncles and aunts.
I guess he went to the square dance.
He will be back in a minute.
Don't worry.
I'll buy us something to drink.
OK.
Hey.
Yeah.
Let me ask you something.
Yes.
Do you boys
at the critical moment
fail to do important things?
Do you know
why boys
don't take the initiative now?
Afraid of taking responsibility.
Although gender equality has been promoted
but in a relationship
girls are getting more demanding.
Boys are required to take emotional care
to be attentive
and to act faster than command.
Boys
must be getting stressed out.
Isn't the game fun?
Isn't Internet café attractive?
Isn't the movie enjoyable?
So until a boy meets the girl
he is willing to give up his time
his freedom
and give all his heart
he usually does not choose to take the initiative.
So?
So if you realize first
the other person
who makes you willing to give up your time
your freedom
and give all your heart
then try to take the initiative.
Give me a cup of Chilled Mango Sago Cream with Pomelo, too.
Xiaoyu
Have you brought all the fireworks ?
It's all here, look.
So many kinds.
Did Nan Bei give you apples?
Maybe
he is not a romantic person.
Dango is here, hello.
You've come.
I bought you something to drink.
Hao
Dango bought many kinds of fireworks
almost everything.
Nan Bei
wow
did you go to the construction site?
What have you been doing all day?
Aren't we going to set off fireworks?
Hurry up
then I'm going back to sleep
come on.
Use a lighter.
OK.
What are you doing?
Keep warm.
Officer
we've checked that
in the city
fireworks are not allowed.
But in the north of that building
fireworks are allowed.
In the north of that building
fireworks are exactly allowed.
But where are you now?
Where?
This is the south side of the building.
It's not our mistake.
Dealing with cleaning up the mess
just like fireworks
why is it always us?
This is the worst New Year's Eve
I've ever had.
After being criticized
I have to write a review.
The worst New Year's Eve?
It's better than mine.
What have you been doing all day?
That's all
and it doesn't make sense.
Well
in the god-forsaken place
isn't there a music fountain?
Where is it?
Now it's
the worst New Year's Eve.
In this case
we can't even set off fireworks.
I want to buy you a gift.
Let me see
if there is anything else I haven't bought.
Is everything ready?
I told you
rise after restrain.
It must be from Nan Bei.
Dango, yours.
Oh.
Do you know
the meaning of giving apples?
I know.
Is that what I think it means?
Yes.
So, we are
in a relationship, right?
There they are.
What are you doing?
The annoying Nan Bei
dragged me here to hide from the officer.
We are trapped by the water.
The water is coming again
wait a minute
we'll go out when the water stops.
Why do we
need to wait for water to stop to go there?
What?
It's New Year's Eve
come on.
How's it going with you two?
What?
On New Year's Eve
nothing happened?
Yes.
Really?
Stop it.
Everybody please sit down
to listen to the notice.
In the second half of sophomore year
about professional directions
go back
and discuss it with your family.
After the winter vacation,
give the forms to the monitor.
Professional directions
must be considered comprehensively
for your future work
and career planning
which will play a very important role
okay?
Yes.
Well, keep learning.
How did you two choose?
I
have made up my mind on the first day of college.
I was born
to learn animation design.
So after graduation
I'm going to be
an independent cartoonist
who, with my works
goes to Japan.
When I come back, I'll be a
famous
and pretty cartoonist.
Well, that's kind of a comic idea.
And you?
Law major.
What's up?
Ha.
Look down on me?
No.
How about you, Xiaoyu?
Do you still want to choose international trade?
Yes.
Between me and my goal
there is always a gap.
Your mom?
Yes.
I'm still a little hesitant.
We like this major
so we choose it.
But now
the threshold of cartoonists is quite low.
Frankly speaking,
most cartoonists
earn a living by their talent
and luck.
I'm just worried
that I don't have much talent.
I also asked
some graduated students.
Most of them
have changed careers
while others
are now working as painters
and it is difficult to support themselves.
If you like it,
you should firm your will.
After all, the longest day has an end.
Well
Zishi
You stay alone after class.
Alright.
So
in general
I think
you are more suitable
for comic editing.
Of course
the final decision
is up to you.
Go back
and discuss it with your parents.
Yes
I know.
OK.
Your aunt is angry with me.
Is she too narrow-minded?
Your cousin is in his thirties
but until now
he has neither bought a dress himself
nor held a formal work
all by his family.
I said it was time for him to be independent.
Am I wrong?
No
you are right.
He dated his girlfriend for a month
and asked your aunt
for 500,000 yuan to get married.
I said that he lived off his parents.
Am I wrong?
No.
Doesn't he know the economic situation of his family?
Precisely
That's all.
Anyway, you'll be back tomorrow.
Send the train number to your father
and he'll pick you up.
Alright.
My son
why don't you hang up?
There's something I want to tell you.
Now we
have several professional directions
so
I want to talk to you.
Let's talk about it when you come back.
We may not make it clear on the phone.
So
we'll talk about it when I get back tomorrow.
Ah.
Well.
Did you
hear what Bei said?
Yes.
He studies law
then
what direction would he choose?
No need to guess.
Intellectual property law
which he loved since high school.
Yes, that's it.
Is this a good major?
Not bad, I think
but it is said
that the intellectual property law is imperfect.
Then
will it be hard to win the cases
and earn money?
He loves it.
To such an important matter
can you pay more attention?
Sure.
What should I do?
Does your colleague Chen's husband
work
in a law office?
Yes, I'll ask.
Nan Bei, where are we going?
Just
go for a walk.
So is it a date?
Yes.
On New Year's Eve
you said you liked me
Is it true?
Yes.
Then we are
a couple
right?
Yes
but
it's still up to you.
I have to think about it.
Why
why do you have to think about it?
Well
like
what do you like about me.
I like
anyway
it's fun to be with you.
Isn't it because I'm pretty
and lovely, etc.?
Part of it.
Only a part?
No, a lot.
In your heart,
I'm
beautiful and lovely.
And?
And
you have a good personality
love to laugh
for any worries
you do not really cares.
Whatever you do.
Stop it
I know
but hearing
someone I like say so
is kind of embarrassing.
Is that a yes?
Maybe.
You agree, right?
Let's
make it public.
If they know about it
they will be happy.
Um
keep it a secret for a while.
Why?
Surely they will be happy.
But in case we...
There is no in case.
I won't
let it happen.
It's okay for people to laugh at us.
But what if they are affected
and can't compete?
How could that happen?
Why not?
If you love another
and hit by me
or I love another
you feel dejected
and left alone.
How do we compete?
Your example
is
very awkward.
So
after adapting period
we'll tell them then.
When's that
going to happen?
After the provincial competition
we'll make it public.
Okay
at most
during this time
I
I will be gentle with you.
Fine.
Shall we
have a nickname
in private?
Why?
Because other couples
have nicknames.
So think about it.
There are several nicknames
wooden head
Xiwang's mom.
What are these?
Other couple's nicknames
are
baby
honey
something like that.
It's too common.
Really.
You can try it.
I
Try it
try it.
Baby
Stop it.
Did you talk to your parents
about professional directions?
Yes.
Didn't they agree?
They agreed.
How about your mom?
Don't mention her
just talking about her makes my head ache.
So I said that
without perfect preparation
I will absolutely
not start this war.
Pretty good.
When your parents
want to talk to you
just say what you think.
If they agree
then you don't have to talk
which is thoughtful.
If they disagree
you don't have to talk, too
just discuss it again.
You're an old hand
who has years of
combat experience.
So
is there a reward?
What reward do you want?
There's nothing.
What are you doing?
So
drink milk tea together tomorrow.
What flavor would you like?
Strawberry flavor.
What the hell.
Do you know you're wrong?
I'm not wrong.
You are not wrong?
Now
get out of here.
Don't regret it.
I'll eat your duck tomorrow.
I'll set your turtle free.
You got it.
What's going on here?
You best actor
good acting
there will be a reward tomorrow.
Hello, mom.
Xiaoyu
I got your message
What do you think?
I've thought about it
but
I'd like to hear your opinions first.
I consulted with
your uncle in the bank
and your cousin
in the securities company.
And your dad
on Weibo
also consulted several experts.
We all agree that
you are suitable for finance.
I have considered finance
but I think
international trade might be more suitable for me.
Don't be confused.
In these three hours
mom has prepared a lot of data for you
and analyzed
the big data of financial employment in recent years.
I'll send it to you now.
I'm not confused
and I have consulted the teacher
Why don't you listen to me?
Fine
we'll discuss it when you come back.
What kind of reward, wooden head?
No reward
because of your bad idea.
This is yours
and yours.
I heard that you two
have won the National Award for three years in a row.
Oh, I almost forgot.
This year
The Four Universities give our school
two places for excellent students.
In principle
I should
recommend senior graduates.
But after I showed them your resume
and grades
they were
very interested in you.
So they decided
to give you a try after the New Year.
Really?
This opportunity
is quite rare.
If you want to graduate early
and become a full member
I can apply for it for you.
I see. Thank you, director Li.
Here's the internship form.
Have a look.
Director Li
It is very important
so I think let Yin Nan
discuss it with her parents
before making a decision.
Of course, she should discuss it with her parents
and think about it and then tell me
OK?
Alright, bye, director Li.
Bye.
Bye, director Li.
Why hesitate about
such a good chance?
Even I want it, too.
You study law
and I study economics
are you going to take my place?
I can be a legal personnel
and we'll still be good partners then.
In fact, one of my seniors started
an Internet startup company
and he wanted me to go there next semester
to help start a business together.
I was quite interested in it before.
Although the starting point of the Four Universities is high
startups have more potential.
The two are both good.
If you can't decide
discuss it with your family.
After all
we don't have much experience in work.
Yes
discuss it with my family
but.
It is rare to see her dejected
what happened?
My daughter
it's up to you.
No matter what you choose
mom and dad will support you.
Ah.
Are you being tyrannized by your mom again?
Stop talking about me
and you?
How about you?
My dad opposed
my study of comic design
and asked me to study comic editing.
Your father spoils you so much
but now he opposes you
I guess it's hopeless.
I think
it's hard to deal with this time
it must be a tough battle.
Did you buy a ticket
for the same train with me?
Yes.
I can do anything
as long as I'm not with her.
Don't worry
there can't be such a coincidence
let's eat.
That's the task
ah.
In this holiday
don't relax training.
Find the game tapes
analyze
and take a closer look at them.
Sum up the experience
and draw lessons.
Ah
there are also some books I recommend
you can go to the library
to borrow and read them.
Don't worry, coach.
Every day
we spend two or three minutes
no, two or three hours
analyzing.
That's right
don't worry
We will train for sure.
But
later
I'm going to pack up
because I'm leaving tomorrow.
Yes, so don't worry
the information
that you said
we will read them carefully.
I bet ten yuan.
So do I.
Coach
don't worry.
I'll keep an eye on them.
Take good care of yourself
and watch our game when you get back.
I saw the game tapes last time.
Nan Bei, still the same question.
When you're so excited
you start making personal attacks.
You have to correct it.
Do you know that?
I wonder if the coach has recovered.
Why does he talk so much
right?
Why does it smell like the pig's feet braised in soy sauce?
No.
This one.
There are also bones in this basket.
Give me a chance to explain.
What's going on?
The doctor said
for this disease
I should take more collagen.
So I got a pig hoof.
Well
I think you need to eat
more pig brains.
Pretty good too.
I just don't keep an eye on you these days
You dare do anything
don't you?
You're so busy reading.
This is
our last day together this year.
Why don't you look at me?
The books that the coach recommended
this one is not lent out of the library
so I have to write down the key points.
Fortunately, it's not very thick.
But, it must
take a long time.
please stay with me.
Well,
help me.
Let's write together
so it's faster
I'll be with you when we're done.
Xiaoyu
I think I'm so thoughtless.
How can I disturb your reading?
I'd better serve you.
Come on, Xiaoyu.
Quick, write it down.
Hurry up.
I'll read it to you
social unity.
Is the book that the coach wants us to read
here?
Of course.
It should be
here.
Right?
Yes.
Let's go over there
and sit down to read.
OK.
Isn't it normal for us
to read in the library together?
Why are we hiding?
I don't know.
It's like a guerrilla warfare.
Ma Nan is so strange.
Did he find us?
No.
He went to the library so late
which is not his style at all.
It's normal.
There is a bonus for winning the provincial competition.
Each month
he pays off his mortgage several thousand yuan.
Send me
your train number.
I'll buy the ticket
for the next train to get you home.
Fine.
We can't see each other
for a long time.
A Chinese tongue twister to learn pronunciation.
What is he doing?
Idiot.
You.
Ah.
What are you going?