[English subtitles are available]
[Bright Time]
[EP09]
The inequality states that
√2/4 AB
≤ √2/4
(2+ √2 R^2 )
= √2/2 +
R^2
the maximum area is obtained
when A=B.
You got it?
Yeah.
Crystal clear.
Alright, it's getting late.
Let's call it a day.
Lan Jinghui,
aren't you going home?
I...
Will study a bit more.
I must be hearing things.
What's the matter?
Worried that I'll improve secretly?
It would be best if you did.
Did you hear him? It'd be best if you did.
Both of you just look down on me.
You all look down on me so much?
Young man, you should watch
where you're going when riding a bike.
Sorry, sorry.
Do you still want these?
It's fine. Don't worry about it. Go on.
So sorry.
Just go to school.
Alright.
Be careful on the road.
Sorry, sorry.
Thank you.
Go on.
I won't just let him off the hook!
Academic success isn't a pass to violence!
That's not possible.
My son would never hit anyone.
There's definitely a misunderstanding.
You're his mother.
For sure, you'd defend your son.
You owe us an explanation!
Here, here, honey.
Now your son is back.
Dong...
Come here and explain everything to me.
What's going on?
Let me get this straight.
I pay you to tutor my son,
not to hit him.
Come on, hon.
Alright.
If he's confused, can't you guide him?
Why did you have to resort to hitting?
Auntie,
please calm down, OK?
Shh, shh, hon.
Xiong,
please tell me,
was it like
what your mother said?
Xiong,
listen to me.
I need to do
a very important thing later,
so let's finish
our homework first, OK?
Come on, Xiong, stop eating.
Finish it and then you can eat.
Let's work on this one.
Xiong, look.
This matching problem is very simple.
Let's finish it and end the session, OK?
Come on, Xiong, finish the problem.
Come on.
No, I don't want to study!
Xiong, it's OK.
Don't cry, Xiong.
Xiong, what happened?
Xiong?
Why did you hit him?
Xiong, where does it hurt?
No, auntie,
please listen to me.
Can't you teach him gently?
Why did you hit him?
No, auntie, I didn't hit him.
If you didn't hit him,
Why is he crying so hard?
There, there, sweetie,
Shh, shh, shh.
Sorry auntie,
how about this...
Explain to me before you leave.
Auntie, here's the thing...
The thing is...
I have a
very pressing matter.
I need to take care of it. Now, it's...
You owe me an explanation.
Why did you hit him?
I'm really running late...
I can't explain it in just a few words.
Don't you leave before you explain this!
Sorry, auntie.
I really have to go now.
I'll explain to you another day.
Xiong,
Alright, alright.
here, here,
hon.
Boy, are you OK?
You were riding too fast.
It wasn't my fault.
If you're fine, then I'll be leaving now.
That day, were you crying
because you were scared of
being scolded?
How could that be?
He's just a little kid.
If you didn't hit him,
how could he possibly have scratched you?
Xiong, don't be scared.
My son couldn't possibly hit anyone.
You're still defending your son!
Auntie,
actually, you can check
if Xiong has any bruises.
What? You intended to hurt him?
If you hadn't hit him,
he wouldn't have cried so hard.
Come on, Xiong.
Xiong's mom,
isn't there some misunderstanding?
Dong is known
as a well-behaved student.
That's why I recommended him
to tutor your son.
Ma,
I just felt sorry for them,
a widow and her son on their own,
so I kindly let Ling Dong
tutor my kid.
I offered generous tutoring fee, didn't I?
Here's your money.
Take it!
Mom.
For your information,
my son couldn't possibly lie,
and even less likely to hit anyone!
How could she accuse you like that?
Mom, it's OK.
I don't care what she says about me.
This was all my fault, my fault.
Let's head inside.
Let's go.
Yeah, mom.
- Let's go inside.
- Let's go.
I'm going, mom.
Morning, see ya!
Catch up, you!
Good morning, Mr. president.
Lan Jinghui,
you've got to be kidding me.
You're taking
so many parking spots all for yourself,
how are others supposed to park?
Move me then.
I am discussing this issue
with you very seriously.
Move me aside.
I'm doing this for your own good, got it?
Just move me.
Unreasonable!
Slow rider, you finally made it.
You're a 17-year-old kid, but you lack the
energy typical of someone of your age.
I saved some parking spots for you.
Pick one.
Every year, many people
die in traffic accidents,
and among them, non-motor vehicles
make up 80 percent.
It means I value life more than you do.
You know,
you're quite a weirdo.
I saved a parking spot for you.
Instead of showing gratitude,
you cursed me!
What did you do after school yesterday?
I...
Nothing, really.
I was playing basketball with Ma Yiming.
Enough.
It's rare that I come early.
If I don't hurry to the classroom,
the teacher won't commend me.
Oh, by the way,
I bought too much breakfast.
Have some.
Later!
Yo, I haven't finished yet!
Oops,
sorry.
Go ahead, wipe them out.
This is incorrect.
How could an atom with the electron
configuration of 1s22s1 produce a spectrum?
Wha... what?
What's wrong?
Here.
1s22s1 is in its ground state.
1s22s22p1
and 1s22s22p3 are in their ground states.
They won't undergo electron transitions,
so the correct answer should be 1s22s22p1.
The ground state doesn't transition.
What is the ground state?
Why do atoms
need to be excited,
and why do they undergo transitions?
K-shell 1s,
L-shell 2s 2p,
just remember this sequence,
what other than these are not the ground state,
and are the excited state.
Excited state will transition.
Got it?
Write it down.
Alright.
1s
L shell,
2s 2p
K shell.
It's getting late.
Take this chemistry notebook,
and review it at home.
I've marked some key points.
Read through them.
I'm heading home.
Wait up, let's leave together!
What is it?
It's a phone.
What? I don't need it.
Why don't you want it?
Didn't your phone break?
I've got an extra at home.
Just take it.
I told you, I don't want it.
I've got an extra.
Just use it for now, OK?
Lan Jinghui,
did you see everything
that day at my apartment?
I...
I just happened to be passing by.
Right, passing by...
You are really presumptuous,
you know?
It's not about
me being presumptuous.
I just happen
to have an extra phone.
Just take it,
put it in. It's fine.
I told you. I don't want it.
It's OK.
Lan Jinghui.
I've got plenty of phones.
Take this for now.
Your phone doesn't work, right?
Don't make me repeat myself,
Lan Jinghui.
Just use this for now.
I don't want to repeat either.
Just put it...
Lan Jinghui!
Did I ever say I need a phone?
And before, at the bike parking,
in the cafeteria!
For your information,
I don't need your charity!
You don't want it?
Fine.
You don't deserve it.
Ling Dong.
Could you loan me
your chemistry notes?
I'll return them to you soon.
Ling Dong, you dork!
Good intentions taken for granted!
You idiot!
Do you have a grudge against the hoop?
Are you a ghost?
Did you have another argument
with Ling Dong?
Jinghui, I'm not criticizing you,
but as a man,
you should be more magnanimous.
Don't always be at odds with him.
Just beat it.
What do you know?
I see you bullying him all the time.
He didn't hold any grudges against you,
and came over to help you form a band.
We've been at peace for just a few days.
Here we go again!
So I'm the only one
to blame
in this whole mess?
Chalk and cheese.
What's it all about?
I came over to talk with good intentions.
Why did he get so angry?
Coming!
I got it. Just focus on your study.
Who is it?
What for?
Come in, please.
Ling Dong is also home.
Xiong, apologize to Mr. Ling.
Mr. Ling, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
scratch your face that day.
You didn't hit me either.
I was just so scared,
so I cried.
He was crying all day,
and I didn't know what was happening.
It seems I misunderstood Ling Dong.
I'm sorry.
He's your son.
It's your duty to educate him.
You shouldn't have showed up and accused
my son without knowing the full story,
right?
You are right.
He's just a kid.
I sincerely apologize for the trouble.
Please keep the money,
and regarding the extra,
consider that a small gesture.
That won't be necessary, thanks.
I accept your apology,
but I will only take what I've earned.
Just keep the rest.
Er...
OK.
We won't bother you any longer.
Wait, auntie.
May I ask why
you suddenly
changed your attitude?
About that...
Xiong,
maybe you should tell Mr. Ling.
Mr. John Doe told me to apologize.
He said if I didn't come,
I would...
I would be infamous forever.
We'll be leaving now.
Sorry for everything.
Let me walk you out.
Goodbye.
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
Then I'll get back to my assignment.
Go ahead.
[The great me is truly a genius.]
[I've got all figured out.]
[Can you believe it?]
[Was it you who went to talk to Xiong?]
[I have something to tell you.]
[Meet me at the racetrack.]
Mom, I'm going out for a while.
Where are you going?
Just some stuff. I'll be right back.
How was it?
Awesome!
You were good out there!
Of course.
[Dressing in red makes you go faster.]
[Absolutely.]
Lan Jinghui!
I've always felt
I'm the best.
Then what does that make us?
You are awesome!
We're pretty awesome too.
Lan Jinghui!
What?
About Xiong...
Come again?
I said, about Xiong...
What about it?
Thanks a lot!
Actually, the thing is,
no matter what,
I completely understand.
Right?
And...
What's up?
I was indeed being impulsive that day.
Pardon?
I said, the other day,
I was indeed being impulsive!
I can't hear you, what?
I said, the other day,
I was indeed being impulsive!
You were impulsive, OK.
And...
And what?
What I said was indeed
quite harsh.
So...
Yeah.
So what?
We're cool now.
I'm done.
See you.
Just a few bland words and he left.
There's no sincerity.
[Who wrote that?]
[Who was it?]
[Who wrote this on the blackboard?]
[Who is it?]
[I don't know.]
[It was already there when I came in.]
Sure, you wouldn't know.
Because this
is clearly someone admitting a big mistake
and apologizing shamelessly
in front of the whole class.
What kind of huge mistake would that be?
Which influential figure did he mess with?
He had to write such huge words.
You're exaggerating.
I think it was just written casually.
That's not true.
Let me tell you.
I know better than anyone
the feeling of writing a self-critique
after making a mistake.
That feeling of
regret after realizing
you've done wrong,
the annoyance after good intentions
are taken for granted.
That torment in the heart,
the complex feeling of being
too ashamed to admit the mistake.
Thinking about it,
I really feel
sorry for that guy.
What was he doing earlier?
Now he brought this out.
Lan Jinghui,
you sounded like it was written for you.
Do you know who wrote it?
Nope.
He didn't dare to sign his name.
How would I know who it is?
It was such good handwriting.
it's a pity to erase it.
The writing was so good.
Who do you think wrote it?
Help me figure it out.
Come on.
Midterms are coming up.
These are some key and difficult areas.
Finish up and give them to me tomorrow.
I don't want to.
I'm in such a bad mood
that I can't even grip a pen.
What about your previous homework?
I'm not like some people,
so petty.
Lan Jinghui,
I will always be your uncle.
Who cares?
Give me a pen.
Low-energy atoms
are called atoms in ground state.
When the electrons of a ground state atom
absorb energy,
they'll transition to higher energy levels,
becoming an excited state atom.
Geometry.
Sequence!
Geometry!
It's definitely geometry!
It's definitely sequence.
The last question is definitely geometry.
The big question is definitely sequence!
Got to be geometry.
Typically for midterms,
geometry is the final question.
Ms. Fang has been
focusing on sequences lately.
I think it's going to be sequence.
I'm certain it's sequence.
I'm betting on sequence.
I feel it's geometry.
It's definitely geometry.
Geometry.
Mengyu, what's your take on this?
Geometry and sequence
are both my strengths.
Whatever comes up doesn't bother me.
If only I could be in the
same exam room as Mengyu.
What are you dreaming about?
How could we possibly
get assigned in the same exam room?
The class rep is betting on sequence.
I'm changing my bet.
Me too.
Sequence.
What do you think? What's your bet?
What's your bet?
You want to know?
Yep.
Geometry.
Geometry!
Geometry, it is!
Ling Dong is betting on geometry.
You're still on sequence?
Forget about sequence.
It's absolutely geometry!
Geometry.
It's got to be sequence!
It will be geometry for sure!
Xiaohua,
this is specially ordered for you.
A huge pork knuckle.
I heard that eating this before an exam
can help you score high.
It's gigantic.
Let me have a bite.
No way.
This is for Xiaohua only.
But it's so big.
I can't finish it by myself.
You must finish it.
And you have to finish these too.
Eating eggs can get you full score.
They usually
eat eggs with dough sticks.
Eating only eggs will get you zero.
Too bad they don't offer koi fish in here.
I heard eating koi can improve your luck,
and it's particularly effective.
Isn't koi a decorative fish?
Can you eat it?
Eat carp fish instead, silly.
My cousin got in Jing University last year
because he
ate carp fish all year long.
Really?
That theory
has no scientific basis.
Of course, it's false.
Superstitions are not trustworthy.
Otherwise, why do we go to school?
Right?
Mom,
why is it all fish today?
I crave fish.
Exactly,
my sweetheart wants it.
Look how skinny he is.
Bon appetit.
I'm going to
finish them all!
Guys, get ready.
We're about to start the exam soon.
What's the matter, Lan Jinghui?
Ma'am, my stomach hurts.
I need to use the restroom.
We're about to start.
I can't hold it anymore.
OK, make it fast.
I'll be right back.
Hurry up, OK?
Alright.
Guys, prepare yourselves.
Just relax.
Do your best.
Alright, everyone,
put your phones on mute,
and bring them to the front.
Return to your seat.
You've returned.
Yes, I'm back.
Get to it.
Alright.
Bi Peng.
Stand up.
Ma'am...
Now!
This is unacceptable.
You.
And you.
Come on, hand them over.
Do you have anything else to say?
Ma'am,
Lan Jinghui didn't hand in his either.
Stop right there.
What...
What do you want?
I'll give you all my money.
I don't want that.
I have plenty of money.
Come here.
I've only got
a question for you.
I heard my brother bullied you.
That Ling dude,
the one who usually tutors you.
Did he really hit you?
It's no use.
That doesn't work on me at all.
Speak up.
Tell me the truth.
Last chance.
Did he really hit you or not?
Not really.
Then what about
the scratch on his face?
I scratched him with a ruler.
Is it that hard to
tell the truth to people?
After you get back,
tell your mother the same things
you've told me.
Did you get that?
If you didn't say it,
I would know, you know.
And you have to know...
Go.
By the way,
if someone asks you
who I am,
just tell them
my name is
John Doe!