English subtitles are available
Fall in Love with a Fox EP29
Why don't you fight back?
Because it is you.
I won't regret it.
Zijing
I'm sorry.
Qingyun
Zheng
Thank you
for sparing Qingyun's life just now.
He was just like you.
Being deceived.
So he's done too many bad things.
What's more,
he is blind now.
He gets what he deserves.
And most importantly,
I can't bear to see you
feel sorry
for another man.
He used to
be a good man.
Hope he'll repent and start anew.
Wait.
Zheng
You're still being poisoned.
We can't be so close.
But the forest is dangerous.
I can't let you go alone.
Ok, how about this?
You walk ahead,
and I follow you slowly.
Su Zhuozhuo said
that she had found
a new treatment for poisonous insects.
Maybe we should go back
to her.
Ok.
When you're cured,
I'll take you to Jin's Escort Agency.
Up to you.
Zheng, why do you stop?
Baiwan
Please feel free to cry.
I'm willing
to accompany you.
Zheng
I'm so upset.
Qingyun
is my only family
in Nonuple Palace.
We've lived together since childhood.
He's my brother.
He looked for me for five years.
After we met each other again,
I've never
talked to him patiently,
nor smiled at him.
Zheng
Since he went back,
he's been in a coma.
Is it because of the poison?
I felt the pulse for Lord Qu.
According to his pulse,
the poisonous insect has disappeared.
Disappeared?
The poison
is controlled by the blood of the person who poisoned.
The poisonous insect has disappeared,
which means
Qingyun, the person who poisoned him,
was dead too.
Dead?
So,
the poison has been neutralized?
But why is Zheng
still in a coma?
Let's talk inside.
Baiwan
Zhuozhuo
Please check Zheng.
Why is he still in a coma?
The poisonous insect in Lord Qu's body
was dead.
Your poison has disappeared.
Disappeared?
The poison has been neutralized,
but the residual poison
has hurt
his heart badly.
The injury is inside his body.
So, we have nothing to do but wait for him
to wake up.
But what if he can't?
No.
He'll be fine.
Since the poison has been neutralized,
he'll definitely wake up.
We will go outside.
Let's go.
Zheng, did you hear that?
Your poison has been neutralized.
Could you please wake up?
You're a man.
Stop crying.
Is it true
that Zheng can't wake up?
Maybe
he'll wake up soon.
he'll wake up long after now.
Ok,
I'll stay before he wakes up.
Fine.
I'll be here with you
and wait for him to wake up.
Please straighten your back.
Straighten your back.
Higher.
Cunning fox
You've slept clock around.
When will you
wake up?
When you wake up,
I'll make your favorite pastry.
We'll go to watch the shadow play.
Go for an outing to Mount Jiufeng.
Go
where we've never been
together...
Or
we can just stay in Tingqin Garden.
You're the lord,
and I'm your dear wife
to the end of our life.
Forever and ever.
Zheng
When will you wake up?
Ok,
no matter where do you want to go,
I'll be with you.
Cunning fox, you're awake.
My wife wants me to wake up,
so I have to.
Do you still feel bad?
Do you still have any pain?
I'll find Zhuozhuo to check you.
If you leave now,
I'll feel bad.
Baiwan
I'm sorry.
I made you worried.
If you do this again,
I'll never talk to you again.
I won't.
I'll be with you
from now on.
OK?
OK.
From now on,
No troubles will
happen to us.
We'll
live a peaceful life
till the last breath of our life.
Forever in faith.
Dependent life and death.
Be together,
and grow old together.
Ok.
Good morning, Mr and Mrs. lord.
Since then,
I really did what I said.
I stayed in Tingqin Garden
and became the hostess here.
And Zheng and me
was all good.
We are happy.
The division of labor was also very clear.
At the beginning of every month
was the routine meeting.
If you have something to report,
just do it.
Dear Mr. and Mrs. Lord,
the end of the month is the day
to report the spending.
This is the account book.
From now on,
all of the dealings in Tingqin Garden
will be handled by Mrs. Qu.
Yes.
Dear Mr. and Mrs. Lord,
The farmers who rents our lands down the hill
haven't paid the rent
for two months.
From now on,
all property leases
in Tingqin Garden
will also be handled by Mrs. Qu.
Yes.
There's a flood down the hill last month.
They don't
mean to fall into arrears.
I'll check the situation tomorrow.
The rent doesn't matter.
It's important to know
how they are now.
Yes.
Mrs. Qu is kind,
doing things in an orderly manner.
I'm totally convinced.
In other places,
people are correcting their conduct
and trying to live a good life.
Rock Paper Scissors!
Envoy Xueyue is back.
Hurry up.
Envoy Xueyue
I've told you
don't call her like that.
Nonuple Palace
is gone now.
You shouldn't call her Envoy Xueyue.
We should call her Sister Zijing.
Sister Zijing.
Good.
You're so smart.
From now on,
there's no Envoy Xueyue,
and you're not
the disciples of Nonuple Palace anymore.
You can
live a happy life and receive good education here.
Sister Zijing
We've performed well today.
The teacher said
we were getting better.
So,
what did the teacher teach you today?
We learnt
no one's perfect and all is good
if on can correct the mistakes.
The meaning is
we all make mistakes,
but if we can correct the mistakes,
we'll be good.
But
why don't we
practice martial skills anymore
and need to study?
Education is to help you
to figure out
what you want to do,
and what kind of person you want to be
in the future.
Don't be like me,
wasting half a lifetime
to figure these out.
Ok,
you must be hungry.
Let's have dinner first.
After dinner,
you can eat the Baiyu pastry I bought.
Great!
Here.
I want it, too.
Me too.
I can't reach it.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Try this.
It's good.
Yummy!
Oh, it fell on my clothes.
This is your favorite.
I still remember.
I took the kids
here.
Every day is noisy.
You must be upset.
I had a dream last night that you scolded me.
You were always so strict.
You never smiled when you saw me.
So I couldn't
recall your smile
in my dream every night.
But I'm satisfied
to see you
in my dream every day.
My drumstick fell off.
It's ok, you can eat mine.
Let's split it.
Ok.
What are you doing?
Nothing!
If we didn't
grow up in Nonuple Palace
but lived a life like them,
would the end
will be different?
But at least, after they grow up,
they won't
repeat our destiny.
It's great.
Sister Zijing
Why don't you have dinner?
I'm not hungry.
Sister Zijing
Why do you
always talk to this tombstone?
Who's under the tombstone?
He is someone
who likes eating Baiyu pastry
and
someone I like so much.
You like him so much.
Sister Zijing
Let's go to have dinner.
Ok.
Stop, stop running.
Dinner time.
Hurry up.
It's dinner time.
Let's start the dinner.
Wow.
Here, try this.
Is it good?
Yes.
Why are you looking at me?
Because you're pretty.
I know that.
Since you knew it,
stop writing.
What?
I feel so happy
to just look at you like this.
Mom
Fenger, leave us.
I want to talk to Qiuer.
Mom
But...
Are you writing the novel?
No, I'm not.
I'm practicing calligraphy with Shu.
You...
Why don't you write?
The book "I'm in Charge of the Garden for My Husband"
hasn't been updated for so long.
You said
we should get to know each other better,
and asked me
to read your novels.
You don't pay attention to your novels.
Why do you want me to read?
Mom, I'm sorry.
If you want to read it,
I'll write it soon.
But,
don't you think novels
are coarse now?
Well,
things can't be generalized.
Although the language is straightforward,
the story is new
and genuine.
But don't tell your father
that I read the novels.
Mom
Relax. It's a secret
between you and me.
I didn't even tell
Shu about it.
It's our little secret.
Qiuer
Since you need to write novels,
you can skip
the daily courtesies.
But,
you have to promise
the speed and quality of your update.
After I read your novel,
I found something that you can
improve.
Well, do you want my advice?
Of course, I want.
Look at this paragraph.
It's said
that the hostess scolded the servants.
How could she wear a
feather skirt with flowers on it?
How can such a costume
convince servants?
Am I right?
Yes, you're right!
Well,
and this one.
Zheng, try this.
I made it myself.
How's it? Delicious?
Of course, it's tasty.
Next month Zhuozhuo and Jianshan will
come back from their rounds of visits.
And I invited Mr Yu and Miss over
to celebrate the Mid-autumn Festival.
Muqiu's pregnant.
But the gender of the baby
is not clear.
Well... If it's you,
do you want a boy or a girl?
I have no idea.
We're so busy.
There's no time.
Yes,
we're so busy lately.
But,
we're free now.
What are you talking about?
No rush.
Mr Yu and Mrs. Yu
are about to have a baby.
We can't fall behind.
Stop talking nonsense.
Focus on eating.
It's all over your mouth.
Baiwan
I want a little girl
who is charming and cute
as you're.
Can you
make my wish come true?
What if it's a boy?
No,
I don't want a boy.
So if it's a boy,
will you abandon him?
What are you doing?
Take it as bribery.
What kind of bribery is it?
Enough?
The gender of the baby
isn't under my control.
I'll give it back to you.
Wait for me.
Things are quite good
in Yan School.
Why do we rush back to Tingqin Garden?
I'm sending you back to Tingqin Garden.
If you stay any longer in Yan School,
my parents will be yours.
Yes, I'm so charming.
How dare you.
You're a man.
Why did you
cry in front of my parents
for such a small thing?
Do you feel shameless?
That's because
you always bully me.
At least your parents
could fight for me in Yan School.
By the way,
they told me
to get married to you soon.
Shut up!
And,
you took so many things.
They're
the love of your parents.
They told me
to take it on my way.
You take nothing with you to Yan School.
But now you took
so much stuff back.
You're the most shameless person
in the world.
Yes, I'm shameless.
But you like me.
Zhuozhuo, wait.
Go away.
When will
we go back to Yan School again?
Don't ask me.
Your parents really like me.
Shut up.
I really like your parents.
I mean it.
Qiuqiu
Qiuer, Qiuer
Miss
Be careful.
Oh, oh,
slow down, slow down.
Miss
Baiwan
You're
Mrs. Qu, the hostess of Tingqin Garden now.
Why do you still call me like this?
No matter who I'm,
you're still my boss.
Zhuozhuo
I heard that you've brought the Song Jianshan back
to Yan School and see your parents.
How's it?
Did they
agree with your marriage?
My parents were so happy
to meet him.
Certainly.
Mr Yu
Long time no see.
I heard Mrs. Yu is pregnant.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Let's go.
Let's find a place to talk.
Ok.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Today is Mid-Autumn Festival.
You've gone.
What should we do?
Make moon cakes of course.
You should know it.
That's right.
Yes.
Shu
I don't eat moon cakes with assorted nuts.
Please rest assured.
I'll make
many moon cakes with sweet bean paste.
I'll go.
Go.
I heard it.
He's talking to me.
Stop exaggerating.
He's so young.
Age doesn't matter.
Quantities do.
Quantities?
You mean
there're
twins?
No need to surprise.
Look at how Lord Qu
treats you.
Maybe you will have to become pregnant soon.
I'm not in a hurry yet.
I feel that
it's good to be the hostess.
I could not only guide the disciples to
punish the evil,
but also protect the place and
expand Tingqin Garden.
They're more interesting than having a baby.
Yes,
it's called
career.
Yes.
Listen.
I'm getting better in
writing novels.
Even my mother-in-law
starts to read
my novels now.
Really?
Actually,
when she was young,
she also dreamed of receiving a good education,
so she now
support me to write novels privately.
So,
we women should
work hard on our careers.
Right.
Let me tell you.
When Song Jianshan was with me
during the rounds of visits,
after people knew that he's my husband,
they were impressed by him.
He's so proud of that.
Yes,
men should not be the only one to work outside.
Women should take the turn now.
I think it's good
to let them make moon cakes.
Well...
How about we take a look
how they are going?
Is there anything
we could help?
Miss
You're the least promising.
Coward.
You should say
"Let's go
and see
how's their cooking."
and "Is it to our taste?"
Right.
Let's go.
Slow down.
Let's see
if the moon cakes they made
are to our taste.
Slow down. Slow down.
Let's go.
Watch the steps.
Listen,
we're
all men.
You're
the famous lord of Tingqin Garden,
and you're
the venerable Lord of Valley Junior.
How could we
make moon cakes?
Don't you want to fight back?
How?
To fight against
the unfair treatment.
As for this,
I really want to talk to
our lord.
Me?
Zheng
Your reputation as the husband who spoils wife
has spread all over the society now.
When it comes to Tingqin Garden,
people would either talk about
the capable hostess,
or say
that the great Lord Qu Zheng
has now become a henpecked husband.
It's nothing
if it's only your business.
But do you know
how much pressure does it bring to us?
Right, Lord Qu.
And you should talk to your wife
to write fewer letters
to my Qiuer.
Every time your wife
wrote
to Qiuer,
she talked about
how happy you were.
So every time Qiuer finished reading,
she scolded me for not being romantic enough.
Yes,
you've improved
the standard on your own.
So in your opinion,
how should we
treat our wives?
Well...
Apparently,
we should be the decision-maker
on everything.
The women
should be obedient,
listen to us,
and do what we told them to do.
I...
Who should be obedient?
I, I...
Of course,
we should listen to our wives' orders.
Zhuozhuo, look.
How's the mooncake skin
I made?
That's not
what you said just now, Song Jianshan.
Zhuozhuo
There're so many people.
I'm sorry.
If I don't convince you,
you'll rebel someday.
Take this.
Zhuozhuo, Zhuozhuo, Zhuozhuo.
I'm sorry.
Stop.
Song Jianshan
Zhuozhuo
Stop!
I'm sorry.
Stop running!
Song Jianshan, are you looking for trouble?
What?
Do you think I'm not good enough?
Do you want to rebel with him?
Zhuozhuo
No, no, no,
no.
My dear Qiuer
Please.
Are you in charge of
all the affairs in Taoyuan Valley?
Or
who could write the novel
for all people in Taoyuan Valley,
right?
Ok, you're right.
Do you have anything
to say?
I'm really sorry.
Now people all said
that the Lord of Tingqin Garden is afraid of his wife.
They may call me a tigress.
Of course you're not.
But,
the thing that
the Lord of Tingqin Garden is afraid of his wife
wins a good reputation for me.
Am I right?
See if you can catch me.
Stop, you!
-Come on. -Stop.
I'm exhausted.
Listen to me.
So sweet.
Could you please stop?
You can't catch me.
This is what I always want.
To live a peaceful life
with you forever.
Baiwan
This is also
what I want.
To live a happy life with you till the end of time.
Cunning fox
Then we'll
live a peaceful and happy life forever.
Nothing can separate us.
Ok.
Live a peaceful and happy life forever.
Nothing can separate us.
Under the witness of the sky,
I'm marrying
Miss Baiwan
today.
I swear
that Baiwan is
my only love for my entire life.
From now on,
I won't
meet Miss Jin again.
Shu
Song Jianshan
Zhuozhuo
Stop!
-Stop! -Zhuozhuo
Watch out!
What?
You just don't want to be pricked.