English subtitles are available.
Just in Time EP03
Come on, come on.
Let me get you some honey water.
I don't want any.
You…
Why not tell me
you went to Beijing?
I did tell you. I said I was going.
You said you were still thinking about it.
Well, I made up my mind and went.
Why not me before you left?
I was in a rush.
How do I know you were really in Beijing
for a meeting?
Li Lin...
What's this?
Tell me.
You found it?
You already found it?
Got a little carried away
last night.
You...
At your age,
you're still doing this?
Aren't you ashamed?
I was just trying
to prove my innocence.
Don't you have concealer?
You could
use some to cover it up.
You know about concealer?
Anyway,
what's up with you?
Why'd you get so drunk last night?
Work stressing you out?
You even cried.
I hardly ever see you like this.
Feel bad?
My heart aches for you.
Fine.
I forgive you.
I'm skipping the meal later.
Got a date.
With whom?
A guy.
A guy?
Maybe don't use that concealer after all.
The response from the lower-tier markets
has been really positive.
So we've got that going.
Alright, let's go with that.
Head back to the office and wait for me.
Got it.
Okay.
Hey, old monitor,
you actually called me first.
I'm honored.
Come on.
Have a bite.
I saw Wanzhen last night.
And I found out
you've been too busy
to get back home.
She complained to you?
I've got my own grievances too.
Seriously.
I was in a business negotiation
when she suddenly called
saying she couldn't pick up the kids
and asked me to do it.
But hey,
nothing's more important
than the kids,
so I went
and picked my kids up.
But then what happened?
By the time I got back,
the deal was off,
and someone else swooped in.
All those months
of hard work were wasted.
If you were me,
wouldn't you be mad?
You just said it yourself,
nothing's more important than the kids.
So why get upset?
But we agreed back then,
she handles the home, and I focus on work.
The reason I work so hard
is all for her
and the kid.
Enough.
Stop complaining here.
She's raising two kids by herself
with no help.
You can try it
and see how long you'd endure it?
Okay, okay, fine!
I was wrong, alright?
You're always right,
my dear monitor.
Happy now?
Back to business.
What do you need from me?
It's more than just this, right?
I've got a meeting
upstairs soon.
Do me a favor.
What is it?
Xinmiao's situation
isn't looking good.
They're planning layoffs.
It's not just Xinmiao that's struggling.
Everyone's having a hard time.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
But my team,
I've led them for a long time.
They're all excellent.
So, I wanted to recommend them to you.
What's that got to do with me?
Not much to do with you,
but it matters to me. Please?
Just as a favor.
Alright, alright, fine! I'll help.
I'll send you their resumes later.
Okay.
Send them over,
I'll have HR review them.
I'll keep the useful ones,
but no promises.
I can't guarantee
everyone will be kept.
Just take as many as you can.
Thanks a lot.
No need.
Grab a bite with me?
No, thanks.
That's all about the favor.
Gotta head out now.
Alright, bye.
Where's your ring?
I don't like wearing it.
It feels uncomfortable.
I suggest you wear it.
Don't forget who you are.
And who am I?
A married man.
Alright, quit messing around. I know.
Send me those resumes.
So, who do you think
will be on the next layoff list
from Director Xu?
Even Qian Qian got cut.
He,
you're definitely next.
Mu,
you're good at buttering people up.
Got any insider info?
Sun, come with me.
Anyone else?
It's okay.
Let's go together.
Director Xu,
thank you.
I already got
an interview notice from Blue Ocean.
I have a recommendation letter here.
Take it with you.
This is as much as
I can help you with.
The rest
is up to you.
Thank you, Director Xu.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you for everything you've done for Xinmiao.
I don't agree with the negotiation.
Hiring and firing whenever you want?
My contract isn't even up yet.
How can you fire me?
I'm telling you,
I'm not leaving.
Can't we discuss this calmly?
Xu Meng'an,
Stop pretending
to be innocent here.
Tell me,
was the layoff list
decided by you?
Why did you choose to fire us?
The reasons for your layoff
are clearly stated in the notice.
If you don't mind,
you can share them
and let everyone judge.
I'm telling you, Xu Meng'an,
we're not satisfied
with your decision.
We're not leaving.
Everyone!
I bet you all know
how we've worked
day in and day out.
Working diligently and without complaint,
overtime and all.
And this is how it ends?
Think about it, everyone.
Could this be your fate too?
Did you really work diligently?
Did you really work without complaint?
The company's compensation
wasn't lacking, was it?
Not lacking.
If this outcome
is still unacceptable to you,
you can go through judicial process.
I'll be there every step of the way.
But if you want to spread rumors
and stir up trouble here,
I will call the police.
He,
still batting those innocent eyes?
Don't you know?
You're next in line for the layoff.
Right?
Director Xu.
Director Xu,
is that true?
Xu Meng'an,
you say we were late and left early,
fine.
We missed our targets.
But He, early in, late out,
working overtime, and even sleeping here!
Did she make any mistake?
Why should she be fired?
Director Xu,
please don't fire me.
Don't make a scene.
Are you trying to morally blackmail me?
Are you still the He
that I used to know?
Director Xu,
can you give me another chance?
Do you think chances
are something you can get
whenever you want?
I have a few words
to say today.
Regarding the layoffs,
I know everyone
is feeling uneasy.
I don't really have the standing
to console everyone.
But today,
whether you're leaving
or staying,
I hope you'll all think about this,
really think about it:
Who is responsible
for today's outcome?
We're all adults,
and we should be accountable
for our actions, right?
Rachel,
come with me for a moment.
Alright, enough.
The layoffs were a company decision.
What could Director Xu do about it?
She's not happy about it either.
Do you know how
we got our salary this month?
The whole company took pay cuts,
except our department.
Do you really think
you did well?
It was Director Xu
who didn't take two months of pay
to make up for us.
If you don't believe it,
you can ask finance.
Li, Sun,
stop making a fuss.
It's good enough that we got compensation.
Shameful.
Director Xu got you
the best compensation package.
If there's no issue,
just sign here.
Here.
And
this recommendation letter
is from Director Xu.
Originally, Director Xu
wanted to give it to you personally,
but your behavior just now
was really hurtful.
If I were her,
I wouldn't give this to you.
You should really think about
how many chances she's given you.
She's done enough to help you.
If it were up to me,
you would've been laid off long ago.
Hey, Jun.
Long time no see.
Are you having trouble finding Li Lin?
Meng'an,
do you and Li Lin still need money?
What money?
Li borrowed money from me.
I was short on cash,
so I couldn't lend it to him.
I felt a bit embarrassed.
Recently, I managed to gather some money.
If you  need it, you can use it.
Li borrowed money from you?
You didn't know about this?
Well...
forget I said anything.
Hello?
Hello, leaders.
Director, take a look.
These pieces of equipment...
...aren't they nice?
What do you think?
These models are all the latest.
This one is really good.
Hey, Li Lin!
Hey, senior!
What are you doing here?
I'm adjusting the equipment.
Mr. Ma,
you know him?
Li is my junior with the same mentor.
It's been ages since we last met.
Yeah.
You never drop by the campus to see me.
How've you been lately?
Pretty good.
Good.
Glad to hear it.
Mr. Ma,
The leader is already here.
We should head over.
Alright.
Li, don't forget
to come by the school sometime.
Let's catch up.
For sure, for sure.
Don't forget.
Absolutely.
That's good.
You got it.
Mr. Li,
So you're Mr. Ma's junior?
Great!
Mr. Li's been gone from the company
for a while.
The company's transitioning now.
The department Mr. Li was in charge of...
They laid off everyone there.
Such a shame.
I heard he's been freelancing
with one of the companies
we used to outsource to.
Doing odd jobs,
fixing equipment and stuff.
He didn't tell you any of this?
What's up with that?
Off to see a client?
You're doing sales now?
Boss wants me to tag along.
I couldn't really say no.
Competition's fierce these days.
R&D's important,
but the market's crucial too.
Just leave it there.
I'll be back soon.
You'll be back soon?
Just to see a client.
It won't take me long time.
I'll come back, chill for a bit,
then head to the office in the afternoon.
Where am I dropping you today?
Me?
I'm heading down with Yunjie.
Just drop me with her.
Hey, Meng'an?
Are you at the office?
Nope,
I just left, actually.
Well,
I'm on a call at Tianheng Tower.
What's up? Need something?
Nope. Catch up later.
Come on, time to eat.
Alright.
Okay.
Thanks.
Mr. Zhao,
Here,
I...
It's yours.
Thanks for putting up with this.
No problem at all.
See,
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you
It's no problem.
If you need anything
with the equipment,
just let me know anytime.
That's great!
Thanks, thanks, thanks a lot!
It's nothing, really.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll leave you to it.
Okay.
You all, hurry up to eat.
After you're done, tidy up.
Take your time.
Why are you here?
On an assignment?
It's full.
How long are you planning to keep this up?
How long has it been?
It's been a while.
I was planning to
tell you
after I find a job.
After you find a job?
I didn't expect
it's really not easy to
find a job these days.
So what have you been up to?
Just doing odd jobs.
It's like...
my previous company,
and some other collaborations...
They needed our equipment,
so I helped them set it up.
They called me in
to lend a hand.
and gave me some
payment.
How are you managing the mortgage?
I had
some savings from before.
But lately...
Things have been a bit tight
these last couple of months.
So, I was thinking
borrowing some money
Borrow money?
And you still planning to go to Beijing?
For what?
Thinking of moving back to Beijing?
Me?
Why would I move to Beijing?
You and Yunjie are here.
Why would I go to Beijing?
I'm just going for
an industry conference.
It's a good chance
to meet people,
and maybe find some job opportunities.
Actually, this time,
I ran into some old classmates.
They're all big bosses now.
We had a good talk,
and we will meet again
in a few days.
Maybe something will come up.
Feeling confident?
Yes.
Absolutely.
So, you need to
have faith in me too.
I have an interview
next week.
Maybe it'll lead to a job.
It's ready.
We can eat.
You can have it.
I've got work to do.
I have to go.
Haowen.
Are you free tonight?
Come over to my place.
I need to talk to you about something.
Waiter,
can I get this to-go?
Something happened.
What happened?
Someone took photos and screenshots
and reported the matter to Mr. Zhang.
They said you plan
to take Qianqian to Blue Ocean.
And before the layoffs,
you already met with Mr. Yu
and discussed the terms.
Don't mind it.
Just some rumors.
It's not even true.
But Mr. Zhang believed it!
Do you know what Mr. Zhang
did this morning?
He went to play golf with Mr. Yu.
He hasn't played in a long time.
His golf bag was gathering dust.
What does that tell you?
He's probing.
What do you mean by that?
I mean,
doesn't he trust me at all?
Not even a little?
The problem is, right now,
the company is full of rumors.
I think you really need to go talk to him
and make your position clear.
Mr. Zhang.
I'm here to clarify something.
Clarify what?
You mentored me from the start.
As long as you don't want me to leave,
I won't leave.
Are you
hearing rumors?
Who's been saying what?
Rachel.
I knew it was this chick.
Meng'an,
you need to understand me, too.
You know the current state of the company.
If you really leave,
the company would collapse.
Are you relieved now?
Yes, I am.
I won't hit the balls tomorrow.
I'll get back to work now.
Rachel.
Come here for a moment.
So, how is it?
Beautiful.
I think it'll definitely work
if you go like this tomorrow.
I think so.
I gotta
present myself well anyway.
I never expected
that you're so close
with the HR Director
and could do this for me.
Rachel and I are allies.
I can give you some advice.
If the situation permits,
in the company,
you may also find an ally.
Sometimes,
it's good to relieve work pressure,
and analyze the company's situation.
But in the early stages
of such a relationship,
you shouldn't consider her as your bestie.
Got it?
Yeah.
She's here.
Which one?
The one in the mini skirt.
Are you sure
she's the HR Director?
Don't be fooled
by her appearance.
Although she dresses like that,
she's ruthless.
In our industry,
many high-profile people
have been taken down by her.
She could definitely
give you some pointers.
Woah!
Here she comes.
Rachel!
Let me introduce.
This is my best friend, Chen Wanzhen.
And this is also my bestie, Rachel.
Rachel, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Please, have a seat.
Here you go.
Very well-dressed.
And you look great.
Thank you.
Take off your jewelry.
If you're applying for
an entry-level position,
don't wear anything too expensive.
It should fit the role.
So maybe tomorrow,
you may wear something
cheaper.
Got it.
Here's her resume.
Could you take a look?
This resume isn't good enough.
Why?
I already checked it.
Writing a resume
isn't just about
listing where you were and when.
The key is
where were you
and what you accomplished there.
Is it ok to write it
in an exaggerate way?
On the condition that it's truthful,
a little embellishment is fine.
Introduce yourself.
My name is Chen Wanzhen.
I graduated from Jiangnan University,
majoring in Economics and Management.
I've worked at…
Stop.
Don't repeat what's on your resume.
When I ask you this question,
I want to know your strengths
and how well you match the position.
Think about it,
and answer
the interviewer tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll ask you two more questions.
Why do you want to join our company?
I've researched your company,
and the position I'm applying for.
I believe I have the skills
to excel in this role.
Not bad.
Looks like you've had a deep understanding of
the company
and the position.
Tell me about the projects you worked on.
I assume this question is asking about
my approach to the projects
and the contributions I made, not just
describing the projects themselves.
Isn't it?
Meng'an, your friend has potential.
Though she has a few years of work gap,
her ability to grasp things is sharp.
I just asked her three questions,
and for two of them,
she understood exactly what I needed.
I think for the administrative role,
her educational background
is enough.
It shouldn't be a problem.
Thank you.
Any other questions?
When it comes to the interview,
is it okay to discuss salary?
Of course.
Within the limits
of what HR can decide,
you should confidently bring it up.
If you don't,
they might think
you lack the confidence
to handle the position.
Meng'an mentioned that you were
a stay-at-home mom for a few years.
You can be humble with us,
but
in front of them,
never show weakness.
If they even catch
a hint of weakness,
they'll definitely try
to lowball you.
So, do you think the reason
I haven't been promoted or had a raise
these past few years
is because I showed weakness?
Next time,
I'll give you more pointers.
Lastly, let me remind you again.
Do you know what you should
and shouldn't say?
What should I say?
What shouldn't I say?
Say less of what should say.
Say nothing
of what you shouldn't say.
Come in, please.
Take it easy.
Here.
Are you Director Sun?
You're here for the interview, right?
I'm Chen Wanzhen,
recommended by Director Xu of Xinmiao.
You're Meng'an's referral.
Here's my resume.
Hello, Ms. Chen.
Director Xu
has already
told me about your resume.
Your education
and work experience
are very impressive.
But the job we have here,
you might find it
a bit mismatched for your skills.
I just need someone for admin work,
basically
someone to handle miscellaneous tasks.
You might find it beneath your talents.
That's fine.
Director Sun, to be honest,
I haven't worked for a long time.
And going back to my previous field
is really tough.
But this,
daily office work,
I can handle that.
How old is your child?
Eight years old.
Eight.
Actually,
our internal work
is pretty good too.
Well,
it just involves
supporting the sales department.
And if you can,
bring in clients
to buy properties,
you'll get a commission.
Great.
Sure. See,
we've just moved to the sales office.
It's a bit messy.
I won't be able to make reception right now.
Come by some other day
to complete your onboarding.
I can start anytime.
Let me help you now.
No need.
No, no.
I'm good at this.
You needn't to do this work right away.
No need.
It's alright. It's alright.
These minor tasks
are part of my job anyway.
Then thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Sun,
has the copier been installed?
The after-sales servicer we scheduled hasn't arrived.
We can't use it yet.
We'll have to wait.
Well...
Let me give it a try.
This model of copier
is the same as the one at my home.
That would be great.
We're bad with the electric appliances,
We are old.
Let me introduce.
This is our new internal staff member,
Ms. Chen Wanzhen.
Hello, Ms. Chen.
Hello.
Here.
Sure.
Done.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Impressive!
Now, about this
network issue, it seems to be a bit off.
Can you check it?
No problem.
I always thought that
girls aren't good
with these things.
You're quite skilled, though.
Over the years, at home,
I had to do everything myself.
That's how I got good at it.
Alright.
The account and password are set.
Done?
Good!
From now on,
all the tasks at the sales office
will be your responsibility.
Thank you, Sun.
Director Xu,
here are the materials you requested.
Great.
You can head home now.
It's almost time to clock out.
I haven't finished the project proposal...
I'll handle it.
We're short on staff lately.
You've been working overtime for days.
Go home early.
Let me take on some of your workload.
No need.
I can handle it myself.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you, Director Xu.
Hello, Ms. Xue.
Hello, Mrs. Li.
Yunjie's monthly exam results
come out today.
Did you know?
I don't know yet.
I'll ask Yunjie and her dad
when I get back.
...the results this time
aren't very good.
I still want to discuss it with you.
There are some things that are
difficult to talk about with her dad.
Is it because Yunjie was affected
by that boy pursuing her?
No, no, Mrs. Li.
Let's not jump to conclusions
about the child.
I'm calling you
not because of
this exam's results...
...but because I hope you
pay more attention to
and understand your child.
Teenage girls
need their mothers
to be more concerned.
Yes, yes.
Yunjie's matters
have always been handled by her dad...
...and you know that.
Father's heart
is usually bigger.
This is a critical moment
that determines the child's future.
I believe,
for a family,
the child is the most important.
Don't you think so?
Yes.
I'll find out when I get back.
Thank you.
Stop.
What's the use of cleaning it?
Where's Yunjie?
She went...
...to play with He Lu.
Still daring to go out and have fun?
Did Ms. Xue call you?
She called me.
Do you know why she didn't call you?
It means you're not looking after
the child well enough.
Ms. Xue said
that Yunjie's exam results
weren't good
because of early relationships.
How are you usually looking after her?
Yunjie told me
that she didn't do well in this exam.
but it has nothing to do
with the relationships.
Ms. Xue called you
mainly because
of the girl's issues.
It's better talk to you.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Then why didn't you discuss
your unemployment with me?
If I hadn't gone
to your company today,
I wouldn't have known
what you've been up to recently.
Let's keep things separate.
Now let's focus on your issue.
Don't think you can hide your secrets.
I know why you went to Beijing.
I know who you met.
Mei Yiduo, right?
For what reason you met with her?
To help you find a job?
Did she help?
Someone knocks the door.
You don't need to hide.
This day was bound to come.
Hey!
Hello, Uncle.
Hi, Brother-in-law.
Where's Haowen?
He is coming.
Sis.
Come in.
What brings you here?
Sis.
We brought some seafood.
Mom and Dad said it's really delicious.
We brought some for you
Great, great!
Come on in.
Sure thing.
I didn't change my shoes.
Let your brother-in-law to bother anyway.
He's taken to cleaning lately.
Really?
Look at this place.
It's cluttered everywhere.
Isn't it cramped with you all living here?
You've only just been in a big house.
Complaining about everything...
Why don't you move to Mom's place for now?
At least it's more spacious there.
When will you move into the new house?
Maybe in a year.
There's still renovation to be done.
How much did you loan?
I heard from Mom that
you have to pay back a lot each month.
Who buys a house without a mortgage?
But with all your overtime,
it's all going to the bank's interest.
That's not ideal.
You should borrow some from Haowen for now.
Haowen.
Haowen, come here.
Come.
What's up?
Nothing.
My sis...
Nothing?
Sis.
I...
I'll make you some seafood.
I'll show you my skills.
It's really good.
Didn't you just eat?
Still hungry?
I just didn't want to eat too much
at Mom and Dad's home.
Right.
You are hungry.
Have some more.
Go wash the seafood.
I don't know how.
You don't know how to wash seafood?
No, I don't.
Come on.
What?
I'll show you.
I'm doing this for your own good.
Why aren't you appreciative?
I'll cover the renovation costs.
No need.
Even though we're not
as wealthy as you,
we're not short on money.
Not lacking...
With two executives in the house,
you're not short on money.
Right, Brother-in-law?
Yes!
Sis.
You seem stressed lately.
Your complexion doesn't look good.
You seem a bit down.
A little bit upset.
Are you going through menopause?
You've mastered the art of conversation.
I just...
I went to the gynecology department
at the provincial hospital yesterday.
I saw a woman
who was only thirty-four
and she's already gone through menopause.
Did she tell you that?
Just keep an eye on it.
We women need to take care of ourselves.
Here's a beauty salon card for you.
No need.
I don't have time to use it.
Just take it.
I'm pregnant now.
I won't be using it.
Okay, okay.
Anything else you can't use?
You can all give them to me.
Sis.
Is there anything wrong?
You are weird today.
You found out?
Brother-in-law.
I'll add more of this ginger paste.
Garlic paste, okay?
Later, I'll pour hot oil over it.
This seafood, fresh seafood,
shouldn't have any chili.
Or peppercorns.
It should be authentic.
Just like this.
Brother-in-law.
Why did you
invite us today?
Just to get together.
Meng'an said she missed you.
Me? No way.
She missed her sister.
I missed you, okay?
Okay.
I'll make sure this seafood
turns out perfectly.
It'll be delicious.
Did you bring the wine?
Sure.
Good.