Students
Prepare for the exam later
Sitting today
Our examination room
They are all from our school
Top students
Although you guys are already excellent
But the teacher still wants you
Getting your best
Correct one's attitude towards the examination
The teacher believes everyone will be fine
Four papers today
An answer sheet
Teacher now start handing it out
Oh my God, Ling Dong actually fell to
Consolidated the class
Did he take the exam with his eyes closed
Is he this time
I only write the answer but not the process
Lan Jinghui also passed the consolidation class
Clear day
We have to work hard
What about the agreed goal
Well
Next time it will definitely be better
Refuel
Yeah, come on, come on
I really don't understand
English and Science Comprehensive
Multiple-choice questions for these two subjects
You only picked half
You have to tell me why
Director, I misread the serial number
By the time I find out
It's too late to change
Wrong serial number
Both doors are misread, right
Yes
I was really careless this time
Will definitely pay attention next time
Go back to class
Goodbye, Director
Why did Dongdong fall into the consolidation class?
Dagang
Sister-in-law
You
All these years
You said you wouldn't change it either
Your habit of not being late
I'm fifteen minutes early
Still too late
Please take a seat
sit
That coffee
Which one would you like
Black coffee
Good
Sister-in-law, what would you like to drink
Coffee and all that stuff
I'm not used to drinking
I'll just drink plain water
Okay
Dagang
It's hard to be a teacher
You see, your hair is white
Worry about it
Now this kid
More thoughtful and more thoughtful
I can't control it
Yes
Hello, your coffee
Thank you
Okay, let's put it here
You suddenly contacted me
Is it because of Ling Dong
Yes
Dongdong, the child
Recent academic performance
has been slipping
This kid is so thoughtful
I'm afraid to ask
I'm afraid of putting pressure on him
Then I was thinking
Could it be at school
What's the matter
This doesn't
I've been thinking and thinking about it
All I want is from you
Take a look and understand some of the situation
Da Gang has caused you trouble
No sister-in-law
We've been friends for so many years
You want to tell me about trouble
That's laughing at me
Shang Jin and I
I've mentioned you a lot over the years
We just don't know
You guys lived
Da Gang, we're doing pretty well
Dongdong is a sensible child
Don't let me worry about anything
Let's go
You know I have a good face
And you're Dongdong's teacher
I'm afraid my children will know
The relationship between our two families
You're not easy to manage
Sister-in-law or you are thoughtful
What about Ling Dong? Don't worry about it
The child is kind and of good character
And it's very satisfying
What about the decline in grades this time
Blame me
Here's the reason
What about Shang Jin's son
The academic performance is slightly worse
Just right
The two children are in the same class
I've been thinking about it
Just built one for them
Study group
Can Ling Dong
Put his son's academic achievements
Pull it up slightly
It's going back and forth
These two boys are having fun
They're all like brothers
So I guess
Ling Dong this time
Maybe it was deliberately a little wrong in the exam
Want to talk to Shang Jin's son
Be assigned to a class
Keep helping him
If it's because of this
Let Dongdong's performance decline
I'm not worried
By the way, Dagang
Me
Brought you a gift
This is Ling Kun and you
When we started the band
That score
I'll bring it over
Let's leave a souvenir for you
Sister-in-law has a heart
Then what
It's getting late
I have to go back
Dongdong may be finishing school soon
Sister-in-law
We haven't seen each other in so many years
I wanted to see you one day
When convenient
My name is Shangjin
Let's three families get together
OK
Then when there is a chance
Okay
When you say this, you will wait until you have the opportunity
That's no chance
Let's do it like this
Let's set a time today
You think it's the weekend
Let's go down
Dagang
I know what you guys mean
But don't worry
We're having a really good time
Nothing is lacking at home
Ling Kun can have you
Such a good friend
It's his blessing
I thank you on his behalf
It's getting late at that time
I really have to go back
Sister-in-law
Goodbye
Hello
How about it? It's a lot of progress, right?
Really
But you still have to work hard
Get the sprint class
I got into the consolidation class
Still a little stressful
What about you going to the consolidation class
Does Auntie know
Aunt is in poor health
She
You won't be in a hurry
Don't worry
My mom knows
I told my mom, too
We're going to be admitted to Beijing University together
You can't make me break my word
Don't worry
Look at the second question of your question
This is a typical
conic curve
I know
Join a straight line with a curve
Then find two more simplifications
Then why don't you finish it
Such a big question
If you really can't get through it
There is no need to fight to death
A waste of time
You just have to write the formula
Finally, just take the step points
Small painting
Your score is so much higher than mine
Is it okay
You're making progress too quickly
This Wheel Practice Test
We'll definitely do it
Consolidate class meetings
Clear day
Your cloze error rate
Still very high
In fact, cloze fills in the blanks
It's all skilled
is essentially a
The process of logical reasoning
The key is that you know
What exactly is it looking at you
reasoning
Come on, you try
See if you can put this
Find out all the keywords
Good
You are already
The simplest sequence problem
I told you everything
I'm not suitable for studying
I shouldn't be here
The place I should go is the basketball court
What am I doing here
Why go to Ma Yiming
Brother Grey, this is really not the right place for me
I'm going to play ball
Bye
Bye bye bye bye
Bye bye bye bye bye
Smelly brat
The bench didn't sit hot and slipped away
Words
I have to take a mock exam again recently
Take the exam every week
Get used to it as soon as possible
Come on, I'm worried about you
I'm afraid you will have another problem in the exam
Then you'd better take care of it first
Take care of yourself
I'm telling you seriously
I've been like
Everything you do is like a god's help
It's very smooth
There's nothing I can't accomplish
When did you
So thick-skinned
Apprentice
apprentice
I, I, I, I'm endorsing
The gene mutation is essentially
Substitution addition of base pairs
and deletion
Has she been in a daze lately
You also learn from others
Record more endorsements when you go back
Okay, there will be times when the wind and waves break
Hang the clouds and sail straight across the sea
Keep reciting it
I won't
Known
square part of cosB
cosA squared plus
square parts of sinB
sinA squared is equal to 1
seek verification
Borrowed, borrowed, borrowed, borrowed
Thank you Thank you
Little painting, I'm actually here
I'm in the consolidation class
Let me see
Chen Luyang is actually still a sprint class
Lan Jinghui
I actually rushed into the sprint class
Ling Dong joined him again
How is this done
Small painting
You this time
Maybe I just didn't play well
You are usually very good
Is it okay
After passing the exam, I turned over the chapter
Please take a good exam next time
I can definitely enter the consolidation class
The college entrance examination is coming soon
I have a few more next time
Ling Dong knew you would come back
The spot is reserved for you
Thanks
Grey Brother
Classmate, you seem to
Take my seat
Who are you
Ruosi
You don't even know him
The scum of our school
Before it was because
Someone's at the bathroom door
Gave him a glance
On a dark and windy night
It's raining lightly
He put the ten people opposite him
Wrong
Fifty people
Blocked at the door
Fixed it all over the place
How is it possible
Are you making up a story
Really, if you don't believe me, ask Chen Luyang
This is indeed the case
So you just
Did you look at him
No No No
I'm gonna go to the bathroom
fifty
Sunny day, what's wrong with you
I'm worried about the little painting
She clearly tried so hard
Why do you always fail in the exam
The exam doesn't just look at strength
Mindset is also important
I see your learning mentality
It's fine
I'm probably all I'm left with
Is this an advantage?
Where is there
You have many other advantages
What other advantages do I have
Optimistic and cheerful
That's not all the same
I'm leaving first
Thank you for taking me home today
Sorry for troubling you again
No trouble, just drop by anyway
Bye
What about the bus card
Good time is up
Okay, apprentice
You only made two mistakes in multiple-choice questions
This accuracy rate is already very high
Nice
You
Just putting too much pressure on yourself
Calm down
no problem
Next exam
You're sure to get into the consolidation class
It's not
There is obviously a problem
What's wrong with her
She probably does have some problems
Why do I cry every time
You saw it all
Why don't you ask me
When you want to say
Naturally, you will say it
As long as you don't want to say
No matter how much others advise you, it's useless
I usually have no problem doing questions
But I'm nervous when it comes to the exam
I made mistakes in the questions that I can obviously do
At that time, the college entrance examination will only be worse
I'm really scared in my heart
What are you afraid of
I'm particularly afraid
I can't get into Beijing University
This is the first time I've violated
My mother's will
Chose to paint
In case you don't pass the exam
I'm afraid she'll be disappointed
You couldn't possibly
Always satisfy them
You wouldn't even be able to
Always satisfy yourself
You think maybe the worst outcome
That is, you didn't get into Beijing University
But even so
You can still choose
Other schools
You can still continue to paint
But this is already
Worst Outcome
So
What are you afraid of
You seem to make sense
You know what
There used to be a
Olympic champion in long-distance running
He was interviewed by a reporter
Ask him
What kind of perseverance do you use
To finish the 10,000 meters
Do you know how he answered
Don't know
He said
I don't know
I'm not thinking about anything
I just wanted to run this step
Then run the next step
That's it
Step by step
I've finished running before I know it
Step by Step
Xiao Xiaohua, you are the best
It's the best for me
Xiao Xiaohua
You will definitely be admitted to Beijing University
I Xiao Xiaohua
I will definitely be admitted to Beijing University
You're a campus champion
I'm a campus champion
Rooftop Squad
Go ahead
I hear you're Ma Mao's girlfriend
Ma Mao gambled with us some time ago
lost money
Do you have to pay it back for him
I don't know him
Don't know
I heard Ma Mao say it myself
Are you Xu Mengyu
Yeah, that's her
Last time at the basketball hall
It's you who I see
What are you pretending to be
I don't know him
You don't recognize it
Don't go, I'm telling you
Don't go
Let me go
Don't go anywhere without money
Did you hear me
What's the sound
Like Ma Yiming
Is that Ma Yiming
Ma Yiming
What's wrong
Grey Brother Grey Brother
They're looking for trouble with Mengyu
Are you okay
What's wrong in such a hurry
Lan Jinghui
Go away if you don't want to get into trouble
I'm looking for her alone
I'm welcome to you
You kicked your nose on your face, didn't you
You know my name is Lan Jinghui
Still talking to me like that
You don't know
Am I just looking for trouble
Bullying girls
Who are you
Looking for me
What's the matter what's the matter
You're not convinced when you have a helper, are you
refuse to accept refuse to accept
Unacceptable unacceptable unacceptable unacceptable unacceptable unacceptable
OK
There are a lot of you, aren't you
You guys just wait for me
Come
I thought
What's so great about bad guys
Lan Jinghui, where's your bag
And here
My mother bought me a bag
What about the new one
Scared me to death
We're amazing
Actually, you didn't have to send me back
I can myself
I'm afraid those people will come to you again
You asked me before
Which volunteer do you want to apply for
I didn't think about it
But I have a goal now
I want to be admitted to Chengdu University
Rongda
I've been thinking about it for a long time
I think
I still enjoy writing
I want to be admitted to the drama and literature department of Chengdu University
This major
It is the ace major of Chengdu University
However, the requirements for scores
Also very high
I don't know if I can do it
You must be fine
If you fail the exam
Then who can pass the exam
Is it not
My house is not far ahead
Thank you for sending me back
It's okay
See you tomorrow
Ma Yiming
Thank you for today
It's okay
How many scores do you need to get in the Chengdu University exam?
Look at this question
Don't tell you
You weren't there during the exam
Do I have to rely on myself
You can't help me forever
Is there anyone here
Here are the notes I have compiled
If you don't understand
You can ask me
Ma Yiming
The world is undecided
You and I are both dark horses
Real or false
Really
Jia Letian
Can you stop spreading rumors
I obviously lost weight, okay
Pity
This is not us anymore
The original arrangement of Class 5, Grade 2, High School
We're never gonna go back, are we
Who said that
You see
Our position is still there
Everyone is still there
We can still play together, right
Attend class
Stand up
Hello teacher
All right, classmates, please sit down
Long time no see everyone
Long time no see
The college entrance examination is coming soon
There are some points I still want
Let me explain to everyone
ID card and admission ticket
Everyone, don't forget
Especially those
A classmate who likes to lose everything
Jia Letian
Don't look, I'm talking about you
Of course there are some
Easily nervous at ordinary times
Students prone to emotional anxiety
It doesn't matter
It's no big deal
You've all been there
Thousands of exams in Qian Qian
Is that right
Right
Good
According to the usual practice
The teacher still gives it to you
Brought a gift
Make papers again
Easy harvest
Good
Students who heard their names
Come up and get the test paper
Lu Yao
Yu Chen
Fu Luwen
Li Ruosi
Lin Keke
Xu Chao
Zhu Ming
Yang Xuan
Liu Chenyu
Jiang Jing
Lan Jinghui
Thank you Teacher Fang
Ling Dong
The paper looks a little familiar
Done
Everyone has got it
Have you got the test paper
Got it
This is your sophomore year in high school
The bottom test paper at the time of admission
Think about it
How do you do it yourself
These topics
I was really stupid at that time
Such a simple question can be done wrong
What about this paper
Confirmed you
Changes in two years
Remember
You've all been there
Thousands of exams in Qian Qian
So next
You have to be in your best shape
Fight the most beautiful battle
The college entrance examination is coming soon
The teacher nagged a few last words
Students are leaving soon
This classroom
You know, in mathematics
There is a very gentle word
Call there and only
So in the past few years in Chen County
That is, you have
And the only time of youth
In the past few years
You sweat
Overflowing with youth
It's also us
Years of Together Growth
Maybe the last few years we've been getting along
Not so smooth
Because I keep criticizing you
But
I want to say
I'm reluctant to leave you
You guys are like my friends
Like my teacher
I grew up with you guys
Youth is a column
A train that won't turn back
I'm honored to be a part of
Your best flower season
Accompany you through
Just the years of classmates and teenagers
What about the future
I never got another chance
I took you to the tour
And no one will be outside the classroom
Watch you secretly
Did you sleep
And I wouldn't suddenly
Suddenly walk into the classroom
Take away your cell phones
But I wish you all
Every day after that
You can be healthy and happy
Harvesting
I hope your youth
Don't have regrets
Come on for the college entrance examination
Good
Next I announce
Class 5, Senior Three
The last lesson
After the class
Stand up
Goodbye teacher
Goodbye students
Let's find a classmate
Take an interview
Hello classmate
Can I interview you
Yes, yes, yes
Excuse me, what do you have to say
I want to say to my high school self
I want to say
It's against this lens
Then face
Does this microphone say
Yes, yes, right
Good
Let me think about it
Hello
Lan Jinghui
Are you really really really
Very excellent
For the first time in my life, I became
Role models for others
Do you feel particularly proud
Particularly proud
I allow you to be proud
Remember
Ling Dong
Ling Dong comes over
What's wrong
Come on, come on, come on
Interview
Say a few words Say a few words
Say what
Just say
Do you want to do something about your high school self
Say what
That is
There's still a lot to gain, right
What did you gain
harvested
A very good group of friends
And a big nephew
Interview
I also want to say
Mai, this is Mai
Ma Yiming
Play basketball well
Don't be proud
And what you want to do
Never give up
Like that
Save money for sneakers
Okay, okay, you're done
Chen Luyang, tell me
I didn't finish
Are you done
Be careful
Let me say
I think my high school
The biggest change
That is
My life is full of sunny days
Give
Summer sunny day
You're amazing
Finally under the leadership of the monitor
Your math score
Over your weight
That's all you got in math
What are you talking about
Sister Lai Meng, tell me
Xu Mengyu
Be down-to-earth occasionally
There's nothing wrong with it
After all
It's someone who will have fans in the future
Come, come, come, come
Know well know know know
Come and say a few words
I
Been standing on the edge for half a day
Say a few words
There's so much I want to say
Don't know what to say
Then you say what you want to say most
Xiao Xiaohua in high school
You are the one in this world
A unique existence
Draw firmly
Your own color