[I won't work overtime today]
[Episode 11]
Nice photos
It's still good-looking in real life
It's nice here
So you look up
You can see
Actually, I think you can
Directly set as computer desktop
Just a little suggestion
What are you doing
Practice how to tie a tie
Tie a tie
Then what do you use these gloves for
Boxing gloves
Sincere gift from the merchant
You can buy it directly
Mannequin
You are clearly trying to do this
Mr. Li
Sometimes curiosity is too good
Not a good thing
He Jiaojiao
If you were to me
If you have any comments
You can just come at me
I will never resist
For example
You hit me
I know
You still feel sorry for me
You guys are here
Mr. Li's dinner tonight
I have something else on the horizon
Maybe I won't be able to go with you
Okay, I got it
Then I'll go by myself
Mr. Li of the organizing game this time
He is a fastidious person
Make it clear that you want to bring a female companion
You have to dress formally
You can't go alone
It's better to let Special Assistant He
Come with you
Do you think it's suitable
I'd rather
I don't know He Jiaojiao
Would you like to
Special Assistant He
Sister Mingyue is here today
But what else do you want to say
This palace outfit
Is the concubine the empress
Made overnight
My concubine was born in an embroidery workshop
Not good at piano, chess, calligraphy and painting
Just this little craftsmanship
I can catch your eyes
Stop by today
Send this to you
Thank you for your advice yesterday
Thank you, sister, for your heart
What do you mean by that
I used to be too naive
Trying to meet the imperial concubine
Become a sister
Now it seems that I was wrong
I will keep my eyes open from now on
Remember what the imperial concubine said
As an assistant to the boss
It's my duty to help my boss
I'll get ready
Then thank you for your hard work, Special Assistant He
I'm going to get busy first
Do you really like Li Su
What are you talking about
I like it but I don't dare to admit it
Not like your character
You think you know me well
Or do you like it yourself
Want to test me
All I have in mind is work
For this kind of affection between children and daughters
No interest
Since there is only work in my heart
That's in the company
Ask such a question on this occasion
Does it seem appropriate to you
Sorry, Mr. Wei
I'm talking too much
It's okay
Fuck it well, I'm watching you
Mr. Wei
Mr. Li's female companion for so many years
It's always been you
How did you take this opportunity today
I gave it to her
Let
Let her be able to eat it too
In just a few hours
The dress thing
It's enough to give her a headache
Let's go
She was attending for the first time
Such a formal occasion
This so-called unwritten rule
Handling of interpersonal relationships
She's completely inexperienced
I'm afraid there will be many mistakes and omissions by then
What if she
It's all handled perfectly
That's her skill, too
Just this one
Good
Mr. Li
Is there anything you want with me
That tonight
That is, with various partners
Connect with emotions
If there's anything you're lacking
You can tell me whenever you want
It's okay, I can do it myself
Are you sure
But I do
Need to prepare
Mr. Li
Can I have half a day off
Okay, I'll pick you up later
I was going to give you a dress
It looks pretty good now
That's Mr. Zhao
Have dealings with the company's business
You can say hello more later
I'm sorry I'm late
Mr. Li, I sent you a message
You didn't see
It's okay
Just in time to come, so let's join us
Mr. Zhao
This is what you have seen, Mr. Wei
This is my new assistant
He Jiaojiao
Jiaojiao
Mrs. Zhang
Mr. Li often mentions you to me
Say that you are Mr. Zhang's good wife
And keep your hobbies
I really envy you
Where Where
Your dress is really unique
Which store did you buy it
This
I designed it myself
If you like it
I'll design a set for you, too
Thank you so much
You're welcome
Mr. Li, you're here
Don't introduce your female companion
So beautiful
It's been hidden all the time
This is Mr. Li's assistant He Jiaokjiao
The first time she saw Mr. Zhao
Must be very happy too
Jiaojiao
Come and let's have a drink
Of course
Mr. Zhao, we
The company's important cooperative customers
Of course I need a drink
Mr. Zhao
The cooperation behind our company
I'll excuse you for a moment
How are you thinking about it
Let you down
Didn't let you see a joke
What are you talking about
Why are you still so hypocritical
Same as before
You laugh at me
All I laughed at was
21st century
You who are still targeting men
You are beautiful and have a good family background
And the ability
Why do you say you
Have to be for a man
Jealous
He deserves it
He doesn't deserve it
Only you are worth it
Is it
What about you
What are you trying to do with him
He's handsome, he's rich
Wei Yahan
Today's society
What is a woman
By one's own efforts
Unavailable
You have to rely on a man
Even if I like him
Me too. He likes me too
Then you're so sure
He must like you
I'm not sure
Compared to him
I know better
What do I want for myself
He Jiaojiao, please stop drinking
You're drunk
Wei Yahan, you are the one
Are you okay
Do you want me to take you home
No, no, no
Stop drinking
If you can't drink it, don't drink it blindly
Nothing, nothing
I told you to stop drinking, do you hear me
Miss Ho
Would you please have another drink with me
You can't drink this wine like this
Why don't we have a drink
Mr. Zhao
I didn't let one of my own
The habit of blocking my wine
Why don't I have a drink with you
How to
Where Where
I did
Mr. Li, you feel free to do anything
I'll be here today
I'm leaving first
Why are you standing there? Don't you leave
Why do you say you
Have to be for a man
Jealous
Compared to him
I know myself better
What do you want
Mr. Wei, why are you here
You're the one
He Jiaojiao's little follower
What's your name again
Du
Du Xiaosong
To Du Xiaosong
Come
Du Xiaosong
You also like He Jiaojiao
He Jiaojiao asked me
What do you like about Li Su
I can't answer
Why do I like him
Because my mom told me since I was a kid
Don't miss the opportunity
Only Li Su
Such an excellent boy
To be worthy of me
And it's just me
To be qualified to stand shoulder to shoulder with him
Mr. Wei, let me take you home
Don't call me Mr. Wei
Call me by name
Ya Yahan
Don't you say I'm not beautiful
Am I not excellent
Don't I deserve to be liked
You're beautiful
So do you like me
I
Do you dare to kiss me
Is this not so good
So do you want to kiss me
Can you slow down
What are you doing
You're crazy
I'm mad
Let me ask you what are you doing
I
You're not invulnerable
Don't you eat hard and soft
At the critical moment
I don't know how to protect myself
Aren't you very good at it
You beat him, you scold him
Why don't you break his salty pig's hands
Do you think I want to drink with him
I'm not because
He's us
An important customer of the company
Yes, he's a client of our company
But from tomorrow
I will terminate
Work with all of them
You're crazy
I'm sensible
Because I know deeply
In this world
Everything Adds Up
Not as precious as you