English subtitles are available
Fall in Love with a Fox EP05
Waiting for you for a long time.
That's right.
She is Jin Baiwan.
Don't worry.
I'm Qu Zheng from Tingqin Garden.
I wonder
why you are coming to the house
of Qing Songke today?
Qu Zheng
The Lord of Tingqin Garden is also here?
Whoever he is,
we are here for demanding fairness today.
Fairness?
What is that?
We heard that
Jin Baiwan, the escort of the Jin's Escort Agency,
did an inside job.
In order to embezzle the Puyuan Canon,
she had killed the hero Qing Songke.
That's why we are here.
I...
The people in the village said that
Qing Songke has been dead for many years.
You have to find out the truth before you frame us.
How did you know?
In my view, it is you
to kill Qing Songke
for the Puyuan Canon.
Why are you
so unreasonable?
There's no need to
reason with them.
They are clearly here
for the Canon.
She has the Canon.
Give it to me!
That's mine.
Mine.
What?
How...
How could this be?
Blank paper?
No.
Two pages are worded.
Is this Canon originally fake?
That must be Jin Baiwan
who changed the real one.
I...
Qing Songke doesn't exist.
And the Canon has only two pages left.
Instead,
you guys who were snatching for the Canon
fought with the gloves off.
Isn't it that clear?
Is it possible that
we were fallen into the trap?
If it wasn't for your greed and desire
to grab the Canon,
how would you fall into the trap?
This Canon thing is really strange,
for I am the Lord of Tingqin Garden,
it's my work to find out the truth.
But during this period,
if any of you
stand up to
against it in the name of justice.
Don't blame me for being ruthless.
Clear?
Get away from here!
Get off!
Leave!
Go away!
Get away!
How could it be?
It seems that
not just Qing Songke,
even the Puyuan Canon
you were escorting,
they are all fictitious.
What the hell is going on?
You don't understand?
This is clearly a scam.
Only you can't figure it out.
How?
This is
the secret box of our Jin's Escort Agency.
Do you still think
that someone wants to exchange
your precious Canon?
This is clearly two pieces of waste paper.
Stupid.
My task
is to escort the Canon.
Whether it's real or fake,
I need to take it to the owner.
Only in this way can the mission be fulfilled.
Mr Qu
So now,
what should we do?
The situation has changed.
Miss Su, you must go back
to Yan School immediately,
and tell all the Grandmasters
about the current situation.
Would you
go with me?
I have something important to do.
I'm afraid you have to go alone.
No way.
I can't let you two
stay alone.
Miss Su
Do you think I'm here
for an outing this time?
Of course not!
Okay.
I'll go back to Yan School.
That would be good.
You...
Are you driving me away?
I'll leave if that's what you want.
She...
I'm leaving.
Why did she go?
Mr Qu
So,
where are we going then?
Given the current situation,
I am afraid there is no reason
that I go with you.
Why?
The Canon have been delivered,
so our mission is over.
Time to say goodbye.
But...
No one has signed
the receipt of my escort.
How could it be finished?
Qing Songke is dead,
who else could you find
to sign the receipt?
Mr Qu
How boring would you be if you go alone?
You should find someone to accompany you.
It's definitely easier for me
to go alone
than being with you.
But didn't you hear
those guys said
they suspected that I replaced the Canon?
If someone observes me secretly,
what should I do?
But didn't you say
that when the Canon is delivered,
we will have nothing to do with each other.
I know
that you won't leave me in the lurch.
The situation has changed.
It might be more dangerous
for you to go with me.
Miss Jin
Take care of yourself.
Fine.
Do you really think
I can't get out of this wood
without you?
I have my own way.
Fake?
There are only two broken pages in the Canon.
So those guys
all left.
Did you see what has happened?
Yes, I did.
There are indeed only two pages.
That's it.
Finally, it's the time.
The Canon is genuine?
I will fetch it immediately.
Wait...
Such confidentiality,
of course,
the fewer people know it, the better.
The man wore a mask,
so I couldn't see his face.
He should be the leader of the group
at the lantern festival.
But,
he did not bring more people
this time.
He must be the one
we are waiting for.
Dad
What's wrong with you, Dad?
Puyuan Canon.
Who are you?
He really doesn't go with me.
The hell of Lord of Tingqin Garden.
The hell hero.
He even doesn't care about me.
What a man!
Will he come?
He will.
Oh no.
Someone really followed me.
Hello lady, that Puyuan Canon,
I really don't have it.
By the way, the Canon is fake.
If you don't believe me,
you can go ask Qu Zheng.
I'm looking for you.
Are you here to watch the show?
Move.
How come
I leave you here alone.
We just meet by chance.
Save those formalities.
I know you will come.
You have been practicing
kung fu from all genres,
why don't you dare to show your true face?
Okay.
Since you want to die,
I will show you
what I've got.
This is...
We have no issues,
why do you want to kill us?
In the past five years,
I have been longing to
kill you in person.
You can restrain my palm power?
It's him.
I know
he won't leave me alone.
Who are you?
This is
the question
I want to ask you.
Miss Jin, are you OK?
Yeah.
Where's the hero?
Hero?
The one who saved me just now.
Why did he leave without saying a word?
The hero who saved you
is in front of you,
you are still looking for another hero?
I did not mean that.
But...
You just gave your life to save me,
did you get hurt?
Thank you for your asking,
I'm fine.
I know
you are chivalrous-heart,
and will never be as cold
as you say.
You will come.
I just happened
to pass by here.
Since you and I are all safe,
then I will...
Mr Qu
This forest
is so dangerous.
It will be more dangerous
if we keep staying here.
How about
going to the inn before?
Okay.
Mr Qu, after you.
I didn't expect to
be in the same room with you tonight.
Hope you don't mind.
Living in a room is just convenient for me
to seize the last chance.
I must convince him.
Mr Qu
I have heard of your reputation
when I was in the Escort Agency.
What did you hear
about me?
This is what my family young lady said.
Qu Zheng, hero Qu.
Took the lead in the Wuhu Meeting
three years ago,
and founded Tingqin Garden.
That is invincible,
and unparalleled.
He is a genius at Wuhu Meeting.
You know a lot.
Mr Qu
It's late,
please go to bed early.
Mr Qu
You didn't ask me
to send you back to the Jin's Escort Agency.
It's because the Canon thing
has not been ascertained yet.
If you go back now,
you will only drag down the Escort Agency.
The Jin's Escort Agency,
I'm afraid you can't go back.
Mr Qu
Will you send me to Taoyuan Valley?
I can't.
Really can't.
Why?
Because of my family affairs.
Family affairs?
What's that like?
I fought off the gangsters for you
this morning,
now I'm really sleepy.
If you still have questions,
we might as well talk about it tomorrow.
Mr Qu, you haven't told me
why you can't go.
I'm too sleepy.
Mr Qu
How could you fall asleep in a second?
Are you deliberately annoying me?
Based on the injuries,
even I can't tell
which genre of Kung Fu it came.
It even hurt your meridians.
The Majesty's supernatural power is so superb,
is there really anyone
who can hurt the Majesty?
However,
most of the meridians of the Majesty
are backed up by his own palm power.
It can be seen that this person
is quite familiar with the Puyuan Canon.
Madam
With these Kung Fu Cheats,
how could our Nonuple Palace
be restrained
by Alliance of Martial Arts.
I...
I will be the martial arts chief in the future.
How could two pages be missing?
I was eager to dominate the martial arts world then,
even though two pieces were missing,
I still
practiced Puyuan Canon.
But I didn't expect this
has left me with so many troubles.
Although you have achieved those skills,
you cannot dissolve
the backlash of the Puyuan Canon
to your body.
So when the moon is surging or waning,
you will lose your mind on a regular basis.
Although I have made Vitality Pills
for the Majesty,
it can only relieve for a while.
I am afraid that
it will be more frequent in the future.
Of course, I know
that the last two pages of the Canon
are the key.
If not,
how could I
be calculated
by his little tricks.
My Majesty
When will our Majesty
be recovered?
This skin wound is not difficult to heal,
but the meridians are the most difficult.
Doctor Demon
Is there really
no other way?
Yes, there is.
Saussurea involucrata can heal this injury.
Now, Taoyuan Valley
has the last Saussurea involucrata in the world.
Taoyuan Valley
How is the investigation?
The spies in Tingqin Garden said
they have gone around for news.
Not only those
who fought you in Yinxue Village,
but the female assassin
who chased Miss Jin
is gone.
I'm not surprised at all.
Over the years,
they have been doing things cautiously.
It's that the female assassin
stroke deadly movements when chasing Miss Jin.
I felt like she did not come
for the Canon,
but more like a private vengeance.
Is it
related to that incident five years ago?
It's a pity that
we didn't catch them
in Yinxue Village.
Otherwise, we can figure out everything.
Don't worry.
You don't need to worry about this.
So you have your ways?
He took a palm of me,
so I'm sure,
he will
go to a place in a few days.
Which place?
Taoyuan Valley
Then why didn't you promise Miss Jin
and take her to Taoyuan Valley?
I will go of course.
But,
not with my current identity.
I see.
The woman you like
is so miserable.
Are you really
not going to Taoyuan Valley with me?
If I
go with you,
whether we meet people like Yu Chen,
or the killer yesterday,
I have to be distracted
to protect you all the time.
Not cost-effective.
Not exactly.
I was in front of you when Yu Chen was trying to stab you,
that is to say,
I am your savior.
You got the point.
As you protected me from being stabbed,
I do feel guilty.
So,
I almost died
because of you.
Shouldn't you pay me back
for such a great affection?
Life-saving debt
must be paid back.
However,
I told you yesterday,
it's really because of
my family affairs.
What kind of family affairs?
I can help.
Miss Jin, I'm afraid you won't be able to help
with this problem.
You are the hero yesterday.
Forgot to introduce him to you.
He's my dark guard,
Song Jianshan.
Dark guard?
So yesterday?
That was my Lord
who asked me to save you.
If you want to thank,
you can thank him.
It turned out
that he didn't leave me alone
in the woods yesterday.
Miss Jin, it's great that you are here.
Help me find out a way
to let my Lord go home
for a blind date.
A blind date?
Go back home for a blind date?
When my parents were alive,
they asked me to get married
before I was 25.
But until now,
I am still single.
It's really ashamed to say it.
So, my Lord.
You must go back to Tingqin Garden with me
for a blind date.
Is this your family affair?
Yes.
But...
You are the Lord of Tingqin Garden,
why are you forced to go on a blind date?
Parents' orders cannot be violated.
Besides, my parents are no longer alive.
I can't bear
to see them still restless
for worrying about me.
But escorting the Canon
is also a top-notch event
in the martial arts world.
Nothing could be important
than that
of my Lord's marriage.
Isn't it, my Lord?
Marriage
cannot be hasty.
My 25th birthday
will be in next month.
This can only be done like this
as things are urgently followed.
But...
It's great if you can figure it out.
Tomorrow I will ask our disciples
to send the portraits of the girls
as the suitable age from noble families
for you to choose.
You should marry
someone you like.
Yeah.
Then you can
pick a girl you like.
Do you like heart-shaped face
or round face?
Big eyes
or small eyes?
But...
But what?
When it comes to my Lord's marriage,
why are you trying to stop?
You like him?
I, I'm not.
That's a pity.
Otherwise,
I can finish the task earlier.
However,
I should thank you for helping me.
If it weren't for your help, Miss Jin,
I wouldn't be able to
persuade my Lord so quickly.
Me?
Now that you have agreed,
we can't wait.
Let's set off now
to go back to Tingqin Garden.
My Lord
Everything is ready,
and we can set off right away.
Mr Qu
Are you really leaving now?
Miss Jin, you have seen it too,
I have no choice.
I know,
you actually don't want to go.
How about I take you to escape?
Thank you, Miss Jin.
But this matter
is about my parents' death wish,
and there is no way to hide.
Unless,
this marriage thing can be done,
I don't want to give a hard time on Jianshan.
But, you don't have to rush
to leave, right?
Sooner or later, we still say goodbye.
Maybe just as you said,
no matter where,
we will never see each other again
W... What do you mean?
We won't meet each other any more?
Yes.
But you're right,
for you saving my life,
I feel guilty of you.
If you have any needs
in the future,
you can come to me in Tingqin Garden any time.
You don't need to see me off.
Take care.
Miss Jin
I'll see you again.
No matter where,
we will never see each other.
Is that mean I will never see him again?
Wait!
Mr Qu
What else do you want to say?
Is it that as long as you get married,
you don't have to go?
Yes.
Then marry me.
If you don't want,
just pretend that I didn't say it.
I do.
What did you say?
I said I do.