English subtitles are available
Fall in Love with a Fox EP21
It's Qu Zheng who killed the lord's son.
You'll pay with your life, Qu Zheng!
Do you have any evidence
that said I've killed Mr. Yu?
You were the only person at the Battle of martial arts by the lake
that my lord's son has a grudge against.
Who else could it be if it isn't you?
What are you talking about?
He could never be the murderer.
Baiwan, please stay out of this.
I will handle this on my own.
Qu Zheng and Yu Chen have grudges.
Yu Chen was the one being punished.
Why would he seek revenge?
Moreover,
If he really killed someone
he wouldn't have been sloppy
and cause rumors.
Why do you say that?
Based on my knowledge of him.
You and your husband are sneaky.
How can I believe you?
I'm just being reasonable.
Since you said that he killed someone,
Where's the evidence?
I...
What Baiwan said is right.
Where's the evidence?
Could it be
Your lord is like Mr Yu?
He accuses without evidence.
Don't listen to his nonsense.
Let's revenge for our lord's son.
Let's go.
Stop
WuHu Token is here.
Even if you have WuHu Token's warrant
So what!
My lord's son died innocently.
Are you trying to cover up for the murderer?
I came
to take Lord Qu
for investigation.
Yu Chen's corpse shows no sign of poison
but he's definitely murdered.
According to Miss Su's examination
What Martial Arts is this?
Look at the time
How are you still so calm?
Didn't Baiwan say
this whole thing
could not have been done by me?
Since I have a clear conscience,
why should I worry?
You...
Yu Chen was killed with a kind of
Martial Arts that I have never seen before.
But Lord Qu's speciality is guqin.
Therefore the murderer couldn't be him.
Who do you think it is, Miss?
The murderer's internal force was specialized.
Only a few in this arena
have this force.
If this person confronts you,
I'm afraid it's no match.
Miss Su, what else have you found?
The bones in Yu Chen's body was broken.
I'm afraid all of his internal forces
have been sucked up before death.
As seen from this,
the person who practices this Martial art
was extremely cruel.
I agree with you.
At the Battle of martial arts by the lake,
who do you think
meets this criteria?
I'm here for the autopsy
and to report all the information
to you.
But as for who the murderer is?
I'm gonna need you
to investigate.
Yes
It is what you say.
Have you given any thought on
how to explain this later?
I don't need to explain myself to anyone.
What if they frame you?
What will you do then?
It'll clear itself because I'm innocent.
You...
She's coming out.
After the Host and I
conducted the examination together,
Yu Chen died from an
extremely insidious and mysterious Martial Arts.
This Martial Arts is not only cruel.
It may suck all of one's internal forces
and completely absorbed.
Sucking one's internal forces?
Isn't that Dark Magic?
Please calm down everyone.
With the palm mark
on top of Yu Chen's head,
the murderer's height should be around seven feet.
Therefore, the murderer
could not be Lord Qu.
Thank you for clearing my name.
You are welcome, Lord Qu
Host
Host Host
At last, I finally meet you.
I've trapped by your disciple
for the whole day
and never had the chance
to meet you.
But I'm truly innocent.
Host
I truly know my mistakes.
These are some of my house deeds.
If you could help me
to fix this matter,
our Yu Family
will give you whatever you want.
Host, have a look
what would you like?
Host
The Majesty
I am...
I am Zijing.
It's me.
The Majesty
You said that you do not like explanations.
But I really
have so much confusion.
I want you to explain to me clearly.
Alright
As long as you want to know,
I will tell you everything I know.
Did you set the trap
for the Canon?
Yes
Why?
To investigate for the truth
and to bring forth
the murderer of the Xu Family
and the person who stole the Puyuan Canon five years ago.
Although I did not personally see
Yu Chen's corpse,
but I speculate
that he might've died in
the hand of the Puyuan Canon.
The person who have done this
was never far from us.
All these years
he has been using the Puyuan Canon
to kill the innocent.
So I was wrong about you.
But then why
didn't you explain it to me?
There's no need for explanation.
Today
Baiwan should understand by now.
Also at the Battle of martial arts by the lake,
you helped me to get the Lingyao Herb.
But before you have never want me
to regain my memory.
I have thought of that before.
Maybe
If you didn't know any of these things
You would've been much happier.
But after I saw you
struggling to regain your memories,
I started to think
whether your memory
is good or bad
or whether I am your husband or not
I have no right to stop you
from finding yourself.
Then if I have regained my memories,
aren't you afraid that
I might return to the Nonuple Palace?
or leave you?
Or even fall in love with someone else?
No matter when
You're still you.
You would never do anything
your heart will regret.
And I
never had to worry
that you would leave me
or fall in love with someone else.
Such confidence
Because you promised
to be with me until we're old.
Because I believe you will not disappoint me.
Also because
In this world
No one understands you better than I do
and no one loves you more than I do.
Why is Baiwan not back yet?
Could it be something went wrong?
Baiwan
Qiuer
What are you doing here?
I came here to apologize.
You...
What do you want to say?
I've reflected on myself.
Qiuer, the reason you are so angry
was because of what I said
about your novels
right?
Qiuer, you're right.
These novels are not a joke
and I shouldn't
simply
just let you give up
your many years of hard work.
In this case
It's all my fault.
You...
finally understand
why I'm so angry.
Also
Mother was born in a scholarly family.
She knows
that the act of that day
was really inappropriate.
She is the elder,
some things are hard to say.
But she wants me to bring you home.
As long as you are back in Taoyuan Valley,
she will get along with you.
Your mother
really said that?
Of course
Then she agreed that I write novels?
Qiuer, how about this?
Let's go back to Taoyuan Valley
and we will discuss this afterwards.
Qiuer, let's go home.
I have written letters and ran away.
Aren't you mad at me?
I am responsible for this matter too.
It is not your fault.
Then from now on,
could I really
do things that I like
and not need to pretend?
As long as you're back at Taoyuan Valley,
everything will be easier to say.
Jueming
Why did Mother come all of a sudden?
All because of who?
It's definitely because of Young Mrs.
I heard that this time
You guys have caused trouble at the Battle of martial arts by the lake
I'm finished.
Mrs must be angry about it.
Qiuer, this matter
we could never let your Mother know.
It must be resolved properly.
What matters that I couldn't know about?
-Mrs -Mother
Don't even try to hide from me.
I know everything.
How dare a woman
attend the Battle of martial arts by the lake
without considering
the decent of my Taoyuan Valley.
Mother, I think you misunderstood.
Misunderstood?
It just so happened that Jin Head Escort
has come to the Battle of martial arts by the lake.
I will plan to meet up with him tomorrow.
As long as it is officially signed with the "leave book"
From then on, Yu Family and Jin Family
will have nothing to do with each other.
Mother
actually...
Qiuer has acknowledged her mistakes.
She has said earlier
that she will plead with you.
It's just that we didn't think that
you would have done it first.
The situation is like this.
Qiuer participating in the Battle of martial arts by the lake
was to gain glory
for us in Taoyuan Valley.
If Mother
really dislike it,
I will let her be expelled
from the Battle of martial arts by the lake
and immediately return to Taoyuan Valley.
With her looks
and her lawless attitude,
how can our Taoyuan Valley
allow resting with the Big Buddha.
Mother
Qiuer, she actually knows that
she has made you angry many times before.
But she promised that
from now on
she will change her character
and listen to Mother's teaching.
So please Mother
give Qiuer one more chance.
She really said that?
Definitely, mother is
not a mean person at all.
Fenger knows
Mother has always been magnanimous
and can forgive
Qiuer's youthful ignorance.
Hope that she would become what you have said.
Goodbye, Mother
Goodbye, Mrs
Lord of Valley Junior
Are you still
the person I know?
You're even
starting to lie.
I can't bother so much for now.
Mother always do what she says.
Now I can only get rid
the idea of separating
me and Qiuer.
The most important thing now
is to let Qiuer change her mind.
Miss
This hairpin is broken.
It really can't be fixed.
Unacceptable
This hairpin must be fixed.
Do you have any other ways to
fill in the lost part
and fix it?
Miss
Haven't you heard that what's done cannot be undone?
The hairpin has already broken
and it has lost a part of it
it can never be fixed.
I would rather you get a new one.
But I have also heard a wise saying.
Broken mirrors can be fixed.
Since Miss
wants to fix the hairpin so badly
this must be
very important.
I would like to ask Mr. to be more cautious
and fulfill her wish.
How is this? Can it be fixed?
Yes, yes, yes
Come you two
The hairpin has been fixed.
How is it possible that
you have the lost part?
You were the one who knocked out the thief?
Mrs left me to travel alone.
Husband would naturally pay more attention.
Our marriage contract has ended.
I'm not your Mrs.
It that right?
I always listen to Baiwan's words.
If Baiwan says it this way,
then I'll better deliver this to another person.
Stop right there.
This Blossom Hairpin
was given by you.
Don't even think of taking it away.
Even if it is left with one piece
that will also be mine.
No matter this hairpin
or the one who gave you this hairpin,
my entire life is yours.
Since Baiwan
has collected this hairpin again,
shouldn't you give me
something in return?
What...
Of course, it's to become
my wife who'll stay with me forever.
Should've done this earlier.
Dangle this
for such a long time.
How did these two?
Do you want to know?
Let's talk.
Come
These are all the
deserts that I have collected.
No one has even had a chance to eat it yet.
Try it.
You have to tell me honestly
what just happened?
How did they get together?
Isn't it normal for young couples to
have fights every once in a while?
But before that, they were...
That's not important now.
What's important is that
they are together again.
But Qu Zheng is...
Everything you know
about Zheng
are also from the words of Jin Baiwan.
Right?
How would you know if it's true?
So what you mean is
We have misunderstood Zheng from your household
Of course
Think about it.
if Zheng is really
who you thought as
the big bad guy.
At Tingqin Garden,
he could've already
kill everyone.
Why would he let you alive till now.
Then tell me
what really happened?
I can't say, I can't say.
Tell me...
I'm not telling.
Just tell me...
Not going to tell me?
I, Su Zhuozhuo is a highly skilled doctor
and a doctor who is specialized in poison.
Those are just three feet away from me
You still dare to eat?
Su Zhuozhuo
You poisoned me again.
I have my ways to let you tell me.
It's good.
Lord of Valley Junior
bad news, bad news
What happened?
I heard that earlier this morning
Mrs has called for
Young Mrs.
What!
It's over.
Now both sides will know.
You Taoyuan Valley
have gone too far.
Saying the three obediences and the four virtues.
And you even require that once entering Taoyuan Valley,
our girl will never leave the house but stay at home all-day.
Screw that.
Who do you Taoyuan Valley people
think you are?
Back then
it was Yu Linfeng
who begged our Qiuer.
Then she promised
to meet up.
If you want to marry into Taoyuan Valley,
then my Taoyuan Valley's rules
must be followed.
Didn't Miss Jin say
that she will be a good lady
and learn
to be a housewife?
Your words and actions do not match up.
You're lying.
You said you would apologize
for burning my novels.
Apologize?
There is no such rule!
Why do I need to apologize
when I'm an elder.
You...
Qiuer
Elders
You have come at the right moment.
Very well, Yu LinFeng
What you did is being a matchmaker.
Lying at both ends, right?
Are you trying to fool us?
Jin Brother
Obviously
there are some misunderstandings in this matter.
Since you and I are in-laws
this is house matter.
We still have to
think of the reputation of both families.
Shut up
You bullied my Quier
in this way.
I... I... I...
What dignity do I have left?
If your Qiuer
still wants to marry into Taoyuan Valley,
she can't be so unorderly.
Who would want to marry into Taoyuan Valley?
I have already said
he and I have broken up.
Qiuer
Marriage is not child's play.
You can't break up just like that.
Yu Lord of Valley
This matter has been settled.
Jin Brother
Qiuer
Let go, Mr Yu
I shouldn't lie to you
and mother too.
If we did not meet today,
how long are you
going to keep lying to me?
I was thinking when we
go back to Taoyuan Valley.
How could we settle anything going back there?
Continue with the lies?
You and I are
in different worlds.
We shouldn't be together.
If you want to go back
go on your own.
From now on
we are strangers.
What do you mean by two worlds?
You are my wife.
I am your husband.
No matter what obstacles there may be,
I will always have you by my side.
Your are my world.
No matter what you said,
I will never let you go.
Even if I can't persuade you,
I have ways to make you go back.
What do you mean?
You and I are Martial Arts Family.
Since what I have said does not count,
I will have the entire arena
to persuade you.
Tomorrow, we'll meet at the Ring for Battle of martial arts by the lake.
Qiuer
This Ring for Battle of martial arts by the lake is not child's play.
Don't be too hasty.
I'm not being hasty.
Remember this Yu Linfeng,
you forced me.
Please leave, Mr Yu.
Everyone, the Ring Competition for Battle of martial arts by the lake
The first match
Taoyuan Valley's Young Master Yu Linfeng
against Jin's Escort Agency Miss
Jin Muqiu
Isn't she the wife of Yu Linfeng?
What!
Miss...
Qiuqiu already told me
she doesn't want anyone to advise her.
so I didn't inform you earlier.
Some time ago
I heard that they broke up.
Who would've thought
things would've gotten this bad.
It's so unfortunate
that this family is so troubled.
Mrs
Mrs please wait.
Qiuer, what are you doing?
Come down this instant.
Dad, please don't stop me.
Qiuer, even if its a breakup
I can still help you.
How could you fight
with Linfeng in the Ring?
Dad
Ever since I was a kid
everything was solved
by you.
But this time
I must deal with this on my own.
Don't interfere.
I will interfere.
Jin Headescort, Please forgive me.
But no one is allowed to interfere
with the match in Battle of martial arts by the lake.
This is the rule.
Are you really
going to do it this way?
Both sides have asked to set up a martial arts plan in public.
If I win
you are going back to
Taoyuan Valley with me.
The breakup will be cancelled.
Seems like Mr. Yu's heart
still has a place for Miss.
But last night
Qiuqiu's attitude was very firm.
I couldn't persuade her.
I will not go back with you.
If I win,
then act as if
I have never married into Taoyuan Valley.
From now on
I, Jin Muqiu and you, Yu Linfeng
never saw each other.
Do you really
hate me that much?
Both parties have said their terms.
Start the match.
Qiuer, just give up.
You can't beat me.
The match hasn't been decided yet.
Qiuer, are you okay?
None of your business.
I already said
After you've lose the competition
go back to Taoyuan Valley
we'll never see each other again.
Jin's Escort Agency Miss
Jin Muqiu Wins.
Lord of Valley Junior, are you okay?
Qiuer, are you okay?
Miss
Qiuqiu
Give me that.
Are you okay?
Mr Yu, please stay.
What are you doing?
Miss Jin has promised the Martial Arts plan.
If you win
Yu Linfeng shall
no longer see you ever again.
The match is over.
Of course, the conditions will be followed.
Yu Linfeng understands perfectly.
From now on
I and Miss Jin
will never see each other again.
Baiwan
He lost the competition
just to save me.
Miss, please stop crying.
Am I really
never going to see
Brother Shu ever again?
They said
setting up a Martial Arts plan
has to be like this.
He was hurt because of me.
I don't even know the extent of his injuries.
Baiwan
I don't even have the right to see him.
This is all my fault.
It's not your fault.
It's okay.
Don't cry.
Okay
Miss, please don't cry.
I will find a way for you.
Anybody here?
No one?
Is anybody here?
Why is there no one here?
Why are you yelling?
Are you also
the referee of Nonuple Palace?
I have something I'd like to discuss.
Are you sure you want to discuss
with me in the Ring?
Aren't you the referee?
How do you cancel the Martial Arts plan?
Martial arts plan is the irrevocable law of martial arts.
What exactly is Mrs. Qu thinking?
Rules are set by humans.
Who knows what stupid old fool
was the one
who set the rules at the time.
Am I right?
Back then the heroes gathered here
to set the rules of martial arts plan.
There was Lord of Taoyuan Valley Yufei
and the head of Jin's Escort Agency
Jin Gunan.
Do you still think they are
some stupid old fool?
No, how could it be.
Jin Head Escort
will never be some stupid old fool.
I'll go back and discuss with him.
See if there's any
room for change.
Stop
Since you are already in the Ring
and banged the drum of war,
and invited my court disciple
Feilian to the Ring,
then you should know
Your opponent in the Ring
is now Feilian.
What drum of war?
I didn't know anything
about this rule.
The drums have been hit.
Two days later in the arena,
we will have Jin's Escort Agency Jin Baiwan
going against Nonuple Palace Brother Feilian.
Both of you prepare yourself.
I didn't expect
Jin Baiwan to be so stupid
and fall into my hands.
Since she has amnesia,
her previous martial arts have also been lost.
I gave you one chance,
a good opportunity to challenge
her ex Xueyue.
I get it.
This time, I
will make her suffer.
Young Host
I warned you
to not hurt Chu.
Young Host
It was Jin Baiwan who
hit the drum for war.
Do you feel like
you have lived long enough?
Young host, don't need to be mad.
The act of Jin Baiwan
matches the rules of Battle of martial arts by the lake.
We were merely following the rules,
dealing with her
righteously with a competition.
If you dare to hurt Chu
in the Ring again,
I will never forgive you.
It's not the fist time
Young Host has threatened me.
But only this time
even if I let her go
she will be against
the entire Battle of martial arts by the lake.
What can Young Host do?
Baiwan is going in the Ring in a few days.
I'm afraid that it's useless
for training so hard today.
Even if my improvement is little
I'll practice one more minute
to increase my hope of winning.
To be honest,
with Baiwan's Martial Arts currently,
the aim to
beat Nonuple Palace's Feilian
is nearly impossible.
I know.
But with the Lingyao Herb,
even if my chances are small,
I'll still fight for it.
What I can do now is just to train harder.
There is no other way.
Who said there's no other way.
You have a solution?
If possible,
I would hope Baiwan abstain.
But if you really abstain
you will not be Baiwan.
Therefore, I'm here to
help Mrs.
You want to help me practice?
If you want to win Feilian,
I have three skills to teach you.
First move
Lure the enemy
Seemingly weak,
but you are paralysing the opponent
both offensive and defensive
to find opportunities to overcome.
The second move
Hold fast
after mastering each other's
rhythm pattern of their moves,
you can prolong the fight time
strengthen the defence
irritating the opponent by preventing
them from breaking through.