[English subtitles are available]
[Bright Time]
[EP01]
[Students,]
[silent please.]
[The voting is now closed.]
[Director Zhang, if you would,]
[please proceed with the counting.]
One vote for Chen Luyang.
Another vote for Chen Luyang.
One vote for Xu Mengyu.
One vote for Li Hongyu.
And another for Xu Mengyu.
[My name is Xiao Xiaohua.]
[In just a few minutes,]
[my love letter]
[is about to surface among the ballots,]
[exposing my secret]
[to the entire school.]
[Then, I'll become]
[the butt of the joke.]
[Another vote for Chen Luyang.]
[One more for Li Hongyu.]
[And one for Xu Mengyu.]
[Farewell, Chenjun High School.]
[Farewell, my high school days.]
[Farewell, my dear friends.]
[Farewell...]
[Please wait!]
Wait just a moment!
Lan Jinghui, what on earth are you up to?
Why are you taking the ballots?
[Lan Jinghui!]
Everyone, don't just watch,
[stop him!]
Have you found him yet?
Where's Lan Jinghui?
Has anyone found Lan Jinghui?
[No, not yet.]
[No, not at all.]
What do you want?
That's my letter!
Keep searching!
This is my letter!
My letter!
Mine!
Lan Jinghui!
Lan Jinghui, you've lost your mind!
I swear to expel you!
[Ballots flying in the air.]
[A hero descending from the heavens.]
[If only all of this were real,]
[It wouldn't be so bad.]
[Alas, it's all just my imagination.]
[Years later,]
[every time I hold a paintbrush,]
[I'm taken back to that morning.]
[The first day of my Grade 11.]
[That was the day]
[I met them.]
Slow down.
Greasy stuff isn't good for health.
Hey, Xiaohua.
Come on.
Have some fried dough stick.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Goodbye.
Drink this up, drink this up!
At least have a sip, sweetie.
Sweetie, you've been studying so hard.
Goodbye.
Alright, alright.
Study hard and come home early.
Morning, Xiaohua!
Good morning, Aunt Zhang, Aunt Wang!
Morning, Aunt Zhang!
Hey, Xiaohua.
Break's over, right?
Yep.
The usual for you?
Boss.
Three egg rolls and two dough sticks
for order No.3, are they ready?
Yours is still missing one item.
There's someone's order ahead of yours.
Aunt Zhang.
How about giving my order
to this gentleman?
Thank you, miss.
I'm really pressed for time.
Sure, here, it's all good.
Hey, what the hack?
Look, you need to compensate for my car.
It was clearly you who sped up suddenly
and crashed into me.
Who saw me hit you?
Who witnessed it? Anyone?
I did. I saw it.
I witnessed it.
Think before you speak.
I'll give you one more chance.
Did you see it?
You saw it, huh?!
I saw it too!
You?
Are you trying to scam him?
You saw it?
I witnessed it with my own eyes.
Who the hack are you?
[Say that again!]
[You witnessed it with your own eyes?]
[Trying to scam after hitting someone?]
What's this supposed to mean?
Are you trying to hit me?
Did I hit you?
Everyone's watching. Did I hit you?
What's this for?
[What are you doing?]
[Did I hit you?]
[Don't get physical. Let's be civilized.]
[Watch it!]
Stop recording, you!
[Hey, stop!]
[I said stop! You!]
[Don't get worked up, calm down.]
Ling Dong?
Who are you calling worked up?
You're in this together, aren't you?
Give me your phone.
[You're all trying to scam me for money.]
[That's not happening! I'm telling you.]
Hello, 110?
There's been a traffic accident.
Could you please come over?
Thanks, please be quick.
[They're definitely in this together!]
Don't you brats go anywhere.
- Here.
- The police are on their way.
You hit someone
and then accuse them of staging it?
Hey, thanks a lot!
Turns out we're all
From the same school.
Could you stick around
to be a witness?
Once the police get here,
we can...
How can he be so cold?
You're from Chenjun too?
You did great. I'll give you a thumbs up.
He was driving on the wrong side.
Be reasonable, people!
Alright,
I understand the situation.
Let's head back to the precinct,
and wait for the resolution.
No, please, just take a look.
Let's head back to the precinct.
Just look at it.
Go to the precinct.
Alright, guys.
Thank you for your help today.
No problem.
As Chenjun High School students,
this is something we are supposed to do.
Chenjun High School?
Don't you have classes today?
Oh no.
We're going to be late!
People, you can all leave now.
Why did you stop running?
I can't run any further.
Here, take my bike!
I don't know how to ride.
Don't worry.
Piece of cake.
I'll show you, come here.
Here, give me your hand.
Come on, one foot here, the other there.
There you go.
Come on, pedal it!
My soy milk is going to spill!
Help!
See, I told you I can't ride a bike.
Are you alright?
You?
I'm fine.
If you can't ride, that's OK.
I'll run with you.
Let's go.
Go!
Which class are you from?
Class 5 of Grade 11.
Class 5 of Grade 11?
Yeah.
I think I'm also from that one.
I've just got transferred here.
You seemed to know the other guy.
Yeah,
right.
His name is Ling Dong.
He's our school's top student.
That explains it.
He looks quite unpleasant.
What's your name?
I...
My name is Xiao Xiaohua.
I'm Lan Jinghui.
No, just wait a little longer.
Hey, miss.
Where's your uniform?
It's a matching set.
I was worried about being late,
so I didn't manage to put it on.
You two are late too, right?
I helped her over the wall to get in.
Isn't that cool?
Impressive!
Could you tell me
where Class 5 of Grade 11 is?
Class 5 of Grade 11?
Yeah.
I'm also from Class 5 of Grade 11.
You too?
We both are.
Let me take that for you.
Thanks.
No problem.
Be careful.
It's fine, it's fine.
Let's go.
Turn left. It's the second classroom.
Alright.
I'll leave it here.
Yo! Jinghui!
Ma Yiming!
Thanks.
[I've missed you.]
Me too.
Here, take a seat.
Why didn't you walk me in?
Morning, guys.
Morning, teacher.
Everyone, stand up.
Good morning, teacher.
Please, have a seat.
Xiao Xiaohua, you...
sit
over there.
OK, thank you, ma'am.
Go on.
Lan Jinghui.
Yes, teacher...
Isn't it too cramped over there?
Indeed.
You sit over there,
next to Ling Dong.
For being late and climbing the wall,
you owe me a 2000-word report.
Make sure to submit it on time.
[Aye, aye, teacher!]
Alright.
Now, I'd like to
properly introduce myself.
My name is Fang Hai.
I'm your new class advisor
for this term.
In the next
two years,
I have only one goal.
To help you all perform your best
in the college entrance exams.
I've also placed
a suggestion box in our class,
right over there.
If you have
any feedback for me
or about the class,
feel free to drop it in.
But I won't be reading them.
Furthermore, I hope everyone
will bring a potted plant
that you like
to school tomorrow.
OK.
This term's class rep
will be Xu Mengyu.
No objections, right?
Ma'am.
Xu Mengyu is on leave.
Right.
So...
Ma'am, I'll take over.
My name is Chen Luyang.
As last term's deputy class rep and
the vice-chairman of the Student Union,
I'm confident I can fulfill
the duties of class rep.
Fine, it's yours then.
Great, where's the applause?
That's enough.
A new term, a new start.
I've
also brought
a little surprise for everyone.
Are you excited?
Yes!
A pop quiz.
Brilliant!
[Only Ling Dong]
[was my rival before.]
[Now, another one?]
I want to have a word with you.
I'm speaking to you.
Did you hear me?
Hey, I'm talking!
I've noticed that
you're not only inconsiderate
but also incredibly selfish, you know?
We're all classmates.
Why couldn't you stay this morning
to give a statement together?
Allow me to get three things straight.
Firstly,
I didn't even know
we are classmates this morning.
Secondly,
there are cameras across the sidewalk
that recorded everything,
which can serve as evidence.
Thirdly,
I really don't need to bother with you.
Alright,
even if...
even if what you said is correct,
it's still a classic case of
being a Monday morning quarterback.
Isn't that right?
It's just hindsight.
Am I right?
I'm speaking to you.
What?
Want to join me in there?
Shut up!
Xiaohua, Xiaohua,
where's our breakfast?
Right here.
Qi, here's your rice ball,
and Na, here are your three egg rolls.
It's all gone cold.
Why are there only egg rolls?
Where's my fried dough stick?
Sorry,
I ran into some trouble
on my way here.
Tomorrow,
I promise I'll bring everything,
nice and hot.
Alright then.
Xiaohua, just remember,
don't forget about us just because
we're in different classes now.
Yeah.
Is this Li Mingjiang's soy milk?
I'll take it to him.
What's all the excitement about?
Talking about breakfast?
Both of you, listen carefully.
From now on,
in this school,
as of 9:15:45 am,
she won't be
bringing breakfast for anyone else,
except for me,
Lan Jinghui.
Do you know why?
Because I'm her master,
and she's my apprentice.
Lan Jinghui,
what are you doing?
They're all
my former classmates.
Plus,
since when did I become your apprentice?
Didn't I just teach you
how to ride a bike this morning?
Classmates, good friends,
should help each other, right?
Besides,
isn't it natural for an apprentice
to help her master?
You're going to write that report for me.
But,
you ended up eating the breakfast...
Got a perfect score? Out of my face.
Wholesale?
Why don't you set up a stall?
Nice taste!
I love reading this, you know?
Don't touch my stuff.
I'll touch it, so what?
I'll...
I didn't mean to...
I'll make it up to you.
It was an accident. I swear.
Ms. Fang,
I won't sit next to
Lan Jinghui anymore.
He's seriously disrupting
my life and my studies.
I won't
repeat myself.
Just sit down. We're about to start.
Just sit down.
I'll definitely compensate you.
It was an accident.
Alright, class is starting.
Stand up!
Good morning, teacher.
Good morning, everyone, please be seated.
[We're going to learn about probability.]
[What is probability?]
Firstly,
the probability of random events
can be divided into two types:
random events and certain events.
Certain events mean
under condition S,
[events that will definitely happen]
are called...
Are you awake now?
Stay focus, alright?
[That is, events that will definitely]
[happen under condition S]
[are called certain events]
[relative to condition S.]
[So, events that will definitely not]
[happen are...]
Why didn't you alert me, huh?
[...Impossible events.]
[Thirdly, events that may]
[or may not happen]
[are called random events]
[relative to condition S.]
So now, we are about
to run 800 meters.
What, you want more?
No, sir, it's enough.
The last three students to finish the run
will each run 1500 meters
next time.
Boys and girls, split up and warm up.
Girls, over here.
Let's switch, come here.
You're such a
small-minded person.
I tore your book,
but it wasn't intentional.
I didn't say I wouldn't compensate you.
Besides, we're all classmates.
Is the friendship between classmates
really that fragile?
There's no friendship between us.
But we're still desk mates.
You can't deny that.
Are you good at running?
I'm OK.
Good enough to handle you.
Let's make a bet then.
About the 800 meters run,
if you outrun me,
we'll continue to be desk mates,
and I'll forget about
the book you tore.
But if you lose,
we'll change seats.
Deal!
No problem.
Get ready!
Come on, guys!
Wow, you've really tried your best, huh?
Nice job, sport!
Four meters, five meters.
I'll leave you behind, seriously.
I haven't even started yet.
I'm faster than you even by walking.
Have you noticed?
Huh?
I'm gone, seriously.
I'm going for real.
Keep it up!
Class rep, what's the matter?
Can't run anymore, huh?
Let me give you a boost.
Don't you think my dance moves
are quite...
What did you...
Are you alright?
Sir, I finished first!
Are you OK?
I finished first.
Where are you off to, Jinghui?
Sir,
sir, I need to talk to you.
I have something to discuss with you too.
In a bit,
your sponsor will arrive.
We need to meet with him.
OK, sir.
But I have another issue.
I don't want to
sit next to Lan Jinghui.
Why not?
Because...
No rush, take your time.
Because he...
Not only is he poor in his studies,
he's rude, doesn't follow rules,
and his behavior at school
is extremely bad.
Being deskmates with someone like him
will negatively affect my studies
and might even
impact my future participation in
various activities and competitions.
So, sir, I strongly suggest
you find me a new deskmate.
I really can't stand him anymore.
Ling Dong,
you're quite the character.
Complaining about me behind my back.
If you have an issue,
why can't you discuss it with me directly?
I have nothing to discuss with you.
Well, that's too bad
because I have things to discuss with you.
Sir,
I've heard that
Ling Dong is the
top student in our entire school, right?
I can't do without
such an excellent deskmate.
I need to progress together with him,
right?
I don't accept, sir.
Ling Dong,
you're really selfish.
Let me tell you, today...
Lan Jinghui!
Dad?
How can you
speak to him like that?
No, I...
Why can't I speak to him
like that?
Do you know who he is?
Who is he?
He is...
He's your uncle!
My uncle?
Wait...
When did I get
another uncle?
I also don't know when
I got such a nephew.
Don't you call me that!
I warn you, don't just...
Lan Jinghui,
behave yourself, will you?
It doesn't matter if you are
uncle and nephew.
Now that everyone's here,
let's just talk this through.
Alright.
Talk about what?
Ling Dong,
you're the benchmark
for academic excellence at our school.
I'd like to ask you a favor,
to help him with his studies.
Sir, what?
No way, sir.
Absolutely impossible!
Even if you paid me millions of dollar,
I would never
study with this bookworm.
How can you speak to
your uncle like that?
No, Dad, I...
Just be quiet.
Get out.
Dad, I...
Out, now!
- Mom.
- Hi, honey.
Here, I'll take your backpack.
Dinner's ready; I've served it for you.
Just dig in.
I need to
go help Auntie Ma.
Mom, you really don't need to
work so hard.
Don't worry about these.
Your only task is to ace your studies,
and get into a good university.
It's all worth it for me, no matter what.
Your father would be
at peace too.
Oh, mom,
today at school
I met someone
who said he knew Dad.
Oh, finish your dinner,
and start doing your homework.
High school is very demanding.
Mom's in a hurry,
I have to go now.
Just eat.
Be careful, mom.
Ling Dong!
stop right there, Ling Dong!
What did my dad want with you yesterday?
It doesn't concern you.
Doesn't concern me?
That's my dad.
And I'm your uncle.
Stop right there.
I'm warning you,
we're just
classmates.
If you keep claiming to be my...
My...
Uncle.
Shut up.
We are not related.
If you mention it again,
I'll...
What a punk?
Ling Dong,
er...
I, I, I want to...
What?
You...
You didn't bring a plant?
I failed again.
Such a great opportunity,
and you missed it.
What should I do?
I get nervous as soon as I see him.
This is that letter?
It's nice..
Be careful with it,
don't ruin the flower on it.
I think
you should go ahead
and hand it over to him.
But I'm not
mentally prepared yet.
Maybe tomorrow.
No, that won't do.
You've been waiting from last semester
all the way to this one.
I'll take care of this.
Qingtian,
you...
Don't do anything rash.
Thanks.
Do you believe in me?
Yes I do.
Go for it. I'll definitely vote for you.
Qingtian.
What?
Regarding the election,
you will vote for me, right?
Sure thing...
Yo, Jinghui, let's shoot some hoops!
Let's go!
One minute.
What's this?
A friendship letter.
You? Get these?
Is it that shocking?
For me to receive this kind of letter,
isn't it expected?
Back at my previous school,
I used to get these letters
by the bagful.
Look at this!
I got here for only two days.
What, it's from you two?
No.
No way!
What does it have to do with us?
Hey, take a look for me.
What plant is this?
What's the meaning
behind this flower?
Help me. Take a look.
If I roll a dice,
what's the probability of
getting a number less than three?
I'd like to ask you guys.
Who can tell me
what are the numbers
less than three from one to six?
Chen Luyang.
One and two.
Correct.
So, what's the probability
of getting a one?
One-third,
no, one-sixth.
Right.
We can tell me the probability
of getting a two?
Anyone?
Also one-sixth.
You're going to write that report for me.
Xiaohua,
how do you know someone like him?
Someone like him?
What's wrong with him?
You don't know
about his past, do you?
At his previous school,
he was known as the Demon.
What?
Just because some guys
glanced at him in the restroom.
Just a glance,
Lan Jinghui trapped them
in an alley.
Was it a rainy day
or a foggy day?
Details don't matter.
Just make sure you never
make direct eye contact with him.