English subtitles are available
Bright Time EP19
Chen Luyang, hand these out.
Okay.
I've only got
17 copies.
So, two students share one,
okay?
Alright, now,
let's start with this question.
I don't know
when or
why they're at odds.
Guys can be really weird sometimes.
But I know
they'll patch things up eventually.
The question is,
when and how
will it happen?
So light on salt.
Ling Dong?
Ling Dong.
Attention!
We're gonna do
the 800-meter run for girls,
1,000-meter run for boys,
long jump, and sit-ups.
What?
Stop the whining.
I have to remind you that
the school is really strict
about this fitness test.
Lan Jinghui.
Yes.
You lead
the training.
Got it.
You guys can help each other
if you can.
Ling Dong, team up with Lan Jinghui.
Go do your warm-ups.
Go for it!
Come on.
Good.
Chen Luyang, speed up.
Come on, Xiaohua!
Time's up.
You're free to go.
I attended a meeting
days ago,
and a major issue was raised.
A lot of seniors aren't
passing their fitness tests.
If they don't improve,
their sports grades in the college exam
will be bad.
So our principal
requires
all students of Grade 11
to undergo field training
this weekend.
It's mandatory.
Take a look at this chart,
very few have excelled,
and 30% have failed.
Okay, I got it.
Hey guys.
Listen up.
We're all going on
a training trip.
No one's skipping.
Alright, stop.
This trip
is primarily
a training exercise
to improve our physical fitness.
It's scheduled for this weekend.
Anyone not down for it?
Hands up?
No one?
Nope.
Cool, everyone's in then.
Class begins.
Okay, guys.
When you get on the bus,
find a seat and chill out,
no messing around,
got it?
Okay.
Take care.
Attention!
For this training trip,
the school has assigned
a drillmaster to each class
to lead your training.
This means
the entire activity
will be conducted strictly
under semi-military management.
This is Mr Wu,
who will be in charge of Class 5.
Let's give him a warm welcome.
Good morning!
Good morning, sir.
Welcome to our training camp.
I know
at home, you might have
some prince or princess syndrome,
but here,
you gotta
put all those
bad habits away.
During the training,
no mobile phones,
tablets, snacks,
or any other entertainment devices
are allowed.
Give them up now.
Goodbye, my chicken feet,
beef jerky, instant noodles,
and potato chips. I'll miss you all.
Now.
Students who are ready,
follow Mr Wu
to the dorms.
We'll have night watches,
so stay put
and listen to orders.
Do not
leave the camp without permission,
okay?
Yes, sir!
Let's go.
Follow me.
I'll take this bed.
I want the upper bunk.
Mind if I sit?
This bed's pretty hard.
Listen up.
Let's start with
the three-legged race.
Now,
quick and easy.
First row,
you, 1, 3, 5, 7,
step up two.
Back row guys, move up
and mix it up
by height,
let's see some variety.
Now.
Relax, Mengyu.
I got muscles,
if you lag behind,
I'll just piggyback you.
Alright, teams are set.
Just don't hold me back.
Lend a hand and tie up the
girls' legs to boys' with those strips.
Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Shall we get the leg-tying done?
The race
is all about
teamwork.
Stay safe.
And keep an eye
on your members'
speed and rhythm.
Understood?
Yes.
Louder!
Yes!
Practice on your own.
Take it easy,
follow the rhythm.
One, two. One, two.
Here.
Left, right.
Left.
Watch out.
You alright?
I'm fine.
You okay?
Yeah.
One, two, three, go.
One, two.
Wait, wait, wait.
Slow down.
Why are you
syncing with him?
I asked you
to stick to my beat.
Xiaohua.
Tell Lan Jinghui,
he's going too fast.
Ling Dong says you're going too fast.
Tell Ling Dong,
he's the one
going too slow.
Lan Jinghui says
you're going too slow.
Tell him.
It's a group thing.
He needs to
think about the team.
Ling Dong says
it's a group thing.
You gotta think about the team.
Tell him...
Enough!
What's going on with you two?
Ask him.
What the heck is he up to?
Has he been treating me right?
What? Ask him.
What does he mean?
What nerve,
asking me to explain?
Ask him
to clarify his mess!
Xiaohua.
This is really pointless.
Tell him to cut
to the chase.
I won't say it,
let him confess himself.
I'm no
criminal to Lan Jinghui,
what confess?
What...
Stop it!
How about a quick breather
before we get back to it?
I'll beat Ling Dong this time.
Keep going.
Left, right.
Chen Luyang, you're too fast.
We can't keep up.
Moving this slow,
we won't win first place.
Try again.
Go.
Left, right.
Left, right, left...
Qingtian, you alright?
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
My bad.
I rushed it, my mistake.
You really gunning for that top spot?
Always being runner-up
makes me wanna be No. 1, badly.
Alright.
I'll try again.
I'm no study buddy,
but maybe this time I can
get you that top spot.
Hold out your hand.
Why?
Why are you giving me lollipop?
Gotta put some ointment on,
it'll sting a sec.
Just open it.
Sorry.
I...
I'll do it gently.
Am I doing right?
Left, right, left.
You alright?
Yeah.
Let's take a break.
Left, right.
Ms Fang.
Hi, Mr Wu.
Feeling under the weather?
Not really.
My shoulders ache from sitting too long.
Shoulders?
Let me give you a massage,
got some good kneading skills.
Nah, thanks.
I'll do it myself. It's okay.
It's fine.
Well, thank you.
Come on, it's a pleasure.
Feeling better?
Yeah, it's working.
You bet.
We've got a whole session
on rehab
in the Special Ops.
Oh, really?
You take classes for rehab?
Yeah.
Also gotta strike a balance
between work and rest.
Here, here.
Here?
Right.
You made it.
Your muscles are really tight.
Um...
too many lessons, you know.
Excuse me.
Mr Wu.
The students
have practiced enough,
let's give 'em a breather?
It's time.
Gather up!
Training's done.
Well done, everyone!
Dismissed.
Ms Fang, you worked hard too.
Nah, you did.
Mr Wu.
You must be starving,
grab
some dinner?
Wanna join me?
- Nah. - Sure.
Mr Zhao, you ain't going?
Well, Mr Wu.
Let's go then.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Bye, Mr Zhao.
Can you teach me
some kneading skills later?
No problem.
You're all up?
Here you are.
Here.
Take one.
Candle?
Get down here.
What's up?
All right,
you guys just skip the candles.
Hey, listen up.
Something crazy
happened at
my aunt's village.
It's true.
A guy cheated on his wife,
dumped her.
And she
jumped to her death.
Then
weird stuff started happening.
The guy kept seeing
his ex-wife's ghost
flitting
around
his bedroom
wall.
He's freaked,
so he goes to a guru.
The guru told him
that hiding...
under the bed
can protect him.
Just as predicted,
it happened again.
One night,
the man was asleep
when he heard
thumping noises on the roof.
He believed that
this must be his ex-wife.
He quickly blew out the candle
and hid under the bed.
Thump, thump, thump...
Suddenly, an upside-down face
appeared
before him,
whispering softly
in his ear,
"I finally found you!"
It scared him out of his wits.
Jinghui, are you okay?
I'm off to the night shift.
You're so timid, Jinghui.
So annoying.
You really scared me.
Really scared me.
Are you okay?
Why did you come out too?
What?
You have to watch me outside school?
I'm your uncle,
of course I need to care for you.
What if you weren't?
What do you mean?
I mean, if we
had no relation at all,
would you still force me to study,
care about me,
and be nice to me?
I wouldn't want to, honestly.
Who would want such a big nephew?
That's not what I'm asking.
Then what?
Don't you know what I'm saying?
I...
Lan Jinghui,
do you know?
I've been waiting for you
to say that for days!
I really don't know
what you're talking about.
Come on, make it clear.
What's gotten into you these days?
What's
wrong with you?
What did I do wrong?
I'm just trying to
help you improve your grades,
so you can stay
and prove yourself
to your dad. How is that wrong?
Yeah, right.
You just want to prove it to my dad.
What?
Tell me,
did my dad
give you the scholarship?
So, you think
I'm only caring for you
'cause I got the scholarship?
No.
Then you...
Well,
you...
tell me,
did you take it
or not?
I did.
You did?
Then why are you so arrogant?
Why are you
so confident?
Why can't I?
I earned it with my own abilities.
I earned it with my own
grades.
Why can't I be confident?
But you did take it,
and that makes
your intentions impure.
What do you think my intentions are?
I thought...
you genuinely
considered me a friend,
so I...
treated you with
my heart.
But now it sounds like
my dad
gave you a task.
What you're doing is like writing
a named composition
instead of original writing.
Do you know
why did I participate in the talent show?
Why?
Because
you gave me a quiz question
and I answered it.
At most...
it was a fair exchange.
Okay, what about the locker room?
Why was I
on time to the room
and even testified for you?
Fine,
that only proved you're
a kind guy.
That's true.
Even so,
why would I
join the basketball game?
Maybe...
you wanted to show off.
Yes,
I wanted to show off.
You're right.
I have nothing else to say.
No, no.
It's not like that.
No, I...
Just give me a moment.
Calm down for now.
Just listen to me.
I just...
wanted to discuss it
with you today.
I'm not
looking for any answers.
Besides,
aren't you
too temperamental?
Getting angry so soddenly.
I just wanted to
talk this through with you.
I...
You...
Don't come over.
Ma Yiming, go stand guard.
What, jumping into the lake?
Just exercising.
Jinghui, to be honest,
Ling Dong really treats you well.
Why don't you just apologize?
You think I'm wrong too?
Of course.
No,
you don't even know
the whole story,
but you think I'm wrong?
Look at you, all guilty
and sheepish.
I don't even need to know it
to know you're wrong.
I'm telling you, Jinghui,
Ling Dong is really nice.
Look,
he helped you in the talent show,
and the basketball game too.
Just think about it with your heart.
That's your stomach.
Your heart is here.
Eyes may not
be able to see the truth clearly,
but the heart can.
C'mon.
You're here just for a training.
Why suddenly
philosophical standing by a lake?
I am the son of the lake.
Ma Yiming.
I'm passive.
Come on,
move over a bit,
give me some space.
Ling Dong,
does this height work?
Is it okay?
Is there any gap?
What's going on?
Just put in a good word for me.
Shall we start?
Sure, let's start.
Not yet, wait a moment.
Okay.
Let's go.
You call the shots.
Me?
One for this side,
and two for that side.
No problem.
Come on.
One.
Two.
Slow down.
Let me adjust it.
My bad.
I'm sorry.
How about this?
Ling Dong,
how about you call the shots?
We'll follow your rhythm.
What do you think?
Xiaohua,
I'm calling it.
Okay.
Ready?
One, two.
Slow down.
Lan Jinghui, what's wrong with you?
Can you do it or not?
I...
I was really...
It's okay.
I quit.
Oh, no!
Don't!
Don't.
Please.
I'm begging you.
How about this?
Let's stop for now.
We all stop.
When you want to practice,
we'll continue.
We need to rest, right?
And it's so hot now.
Xiaohua,
I think the two of us
can practice it first.
No, no.
Listen to me,
we're practicing
the three-legged race,
so,
about this...
- Move. - Let me help you.
Alright,
I'll move.
No problem.
Ready?
We can go.
No, I...
Wait a second.
I just got here.
I'm not ready yet.
Just give me five seconds.
Are you ready now?
Wait, wait,
wait a sec.
It's okay.
Okay.
Ready?
One.
Two.
Good.
Yes, one, two.
One, two.
People really can't make mistakes.
Those who do are so pitiful,
humble and miserable.
Suffering and feeling
so unsettled.
Who can feel my pain?
What do you want?
I...
I just want
drumsticks.
Just that?
Yeah.
Is it enough?
Yes.
What a coincidence!
You're hungry too?
Hungry at the same time, huh?
What are you eating?
No drumsticks?
I happen to have some extra.
Here's one for you.
No, thanks.
Come on, you have to eat.
You're the backbone
of our team, right?
You need to replenish
with some quality protein.
Lan Jinghui,
are you bothering me all day
just to find out the answer?
Alright, I'll tell you now.
Don't.
I'll tell you now.
No need!
I'm serious, you don't have to.
I'm sure that
you have your own
reasons.
Given our relationship,
a few clumsy words can't
stir trouble between us.
Impossible!
Do you think I got close to you
just for the scholarship?
No, definitely not.
Listen to me,
I think you...
You must be...
What kind of person do you think I am?
What kind of person do you think you are?
Then what kind of person are you?
What kind of person do you think I am?
A bit dull.
Yes, exactly!
My grandma always says
the same thing.
Not dull,
more like silly.
Yes, silly.
Pretty much.
Silly boy.
Ask them, they always say that.
Silly isn't quite right.
I think it should be
heartless.
Well,
I...
I'm heartless, dull
and silly.
Whatever you say.
Is that okay?
Speaking so quietly?
No.
This is your sincerity?
I am sincere.
Then, say it louder!
I...
Repeat what
you just said.
C'mon,
you know...
Back down?
No.
You dare not say it?
Well, help yourself.
Bye.
Gosh.
It's too hard.
Ling Dong is too hard
to deal with.