I won't work overtime today
Episode 3
He Jiaojiao
Why is this coffee so strong
Sister Jing
I'm following
Made it to your own taste
If you're not used to it
Then I'll make you another cup
All right, all right
You go back
Capable, right
Sister Jing didn't make any trouble for you today
I'm holding it back
Coming soon
Du Xiaosong
What are you doing in a daze
I didn't ask you to move that far
You come back here
I asked you to move to
He Jiaojiao's position
You move back to me
My mother called me to dinner at home
Sister Jing
Do you have any arrangements
You did a good job yesterday
I'll give you one today
More valuable learning opportunities
This is our company
Customer information for the past two years
You sort it out
By the way, get familiar with the company's business
OK
By the way
Time is still the same
Give it to me tomorrow
No problem
This is too bullying, isn't it
Director Wu didn't give it to her
A month's worth of work
She actually let someone else
It will be done tonight
See others are interns
Easy to bully
In traditional drama episodes
Or she can live to forty episodes
But we only have twelve episodes
Time is tight and tasks are heavy
She can't make waves again
When will the moon come?
Studying overnight last night
Actually fell asleep
However, according to
My observations from the previous two days
This point
Should be coming soon
Emperor
You
A man singing here
Working overtime here alone
What's wrong
Be wronged
No
Not wronged
It's Sister Jing, the senior of our department
Let me sort out the client profile
I think this is a
Particularly good learning opportunities
So I stayed and worked overtime
Customer Information
Yeah, yeah
These customer information
It is our company in the past few years
All customer information
I heard that the average person
Can't even see it
I feel like it's a big deal for me
That's a great help
Customer Information
Is a company
The most core and confidential resources
They actually
Assign you an intern
To sort out
I can't watch it, can I
I'm sorry, Mr. Li
I'm my fault
Don't blame Sister Jing
It's okay
Don't blame you
It's getting late
Pack up your things and get off work
Here is the command
Good
Let's go
I'll go down with you
Where do you live
Let me ask the driver to drop you back on the way
No need, Mr. Li
My family lives in the front building
I'm leaving first bye bye
By the way, Mr. Li
See you tomorrow
By the way
What's your name
I'm just an unknown
Little intern
The servant is just an unknown
Little palace maid
It's getting late
Not as good as
Follow me back to the bedroom
The slave did not dare
I'll take my leave first
Emperor
Do you need a slave to help you
Look it up
Which palace is she a maid-in-waiting
Notify
Anyone in the future
Then put your own work
Push it to an intern
Direct dismissal
Although this is not as good as the ones in the palace
But it's okay
You're quite leisurely
Something you're asked to do
Are you done
Sister Jing
It's not that I don't do it
Just
They're all here
Let me say something
And yesterday
Special Assistant Xu specifically conveyed to me
Mr. Li's meaning
Regular employees of our company
It is not allowed to
Own work
Push it to interns
Especially from our company
Collation of confidential documents
Once discovered
All will be dismissed
You guys are so smart
Be responsible for yourself
There are some pots I can't carry
Brother Kai
Please take a look
That
Sister Jing
This is last night's announcement
It's your fault
How is it possible
I'm a little intern
Also
Measure you little shrimp
Can't make any splash either
By the way, there's another thing
Liu Jing
You get ready
Hand it over
What about that company
Assigned to you an important task
Go to Dachuan City to open up the market
What
Isn't that a third-tier city
To Okawa City
Isn't it equivalent to exile
Send it again and refuse to let me
Notice to push jobs to interns
It should have something to do with this
Inseparable
Blame herself for being too arrogant
Bullying interns is a small matter
Leaking secrets is
What he cares about most
Why did you leave?
Don't even know
Still that stupid
Hello everyone
I'm Zhao Ting
We'll be colleagues from now on
I give everyone
Bought some afternoon tea
Too polite, too polite
After everyone is a family
Take it yourself
Hello
Hello you guys
It's you
That
I will later
Will take good care of you
Come
Thank you
Brother Kai
Tingting ah
Why did you come here
Isn't this busy
I kept this just for you
Thank you
After that
I have to rely on you to take care of me
No problem
Thank you
Work hard
Okay
Sister Jing
Think then
I'm still an intern with you
How long has it been
I'm here to hand over the work with you
I really didn't think of it
I'll be back
That
You come on
Don't be too proud of yourself
Be careful of the waves behind the Yangtze River pushing forward waves
The front wave died on the beach
I won't bother you
I
Be prepared
What to do
Sister Jing just left
Sister Zhao is here
And she just
And glared at me
It's okay
Have me
I won't offend others unless they offend me
If someone offends me
This is my first time
Have a meeting with Mr. Li
Take a good look at him
You arrange interns
Take minutes of the meeting
That
He Jiaojiao
Then you do it
Sister Jiaojiao is a little unfamiliar
Let me do it
It's okay
Brother Kai
Look, now the interns
Even originally belonged to
Their own work
I don't want to do it anymore
I'm already doing
We can
Record it with your mobile phone
It's okay to type slowly
Mr. Li's meeting
But it's all confidential
You said recording
Then when the time comes
These recordings went out
What can I do
Brother Kai
Do you think it is
I said you interns
Why are there so many problems
Do it if you can
Can't resign yourself
It's okay
Everyone get ready
There's going to be a meeting
Mr. Li
Mr. Li, everyone is here
It's ready to start
After last year's hard work
The company's business has covered the whole country
One thousand forty-two cities
And successfully expanded
Overseas operations
The overall output value has increased
One hundred and ninety-three and seventy-two percent
Keep up the good work, everyone
Pretty handsome
Director Wu
You put the last project
Continue to report
Our entire center last month
Relatively good
What about my three projects
Already entered
Very good results in January this year
Very depressed
So ask the boss to give us
That's all for today's meeting
Adjourned the meeting
Brother Kai
Mr. Li said so much
She only remembered two lines
Is there any intention
Before going to work tomorrow
I can't keep it
Words from the minutes of the meeting
Regular application
Never try to pass
Be careful
No recording
How to hand in the minutes of the meeting
Do you treat people as stenographers
That sister Zhao Ting is really
Looks smiling on the surface
Actually deliberately embarrassing people
Is much smarter than before
But that's
Just being clever
Sister Jiaojiao
You must become a full-time and show it to them
I've also remembered some
Let me do it for you
After last year's hard work
Our Company's Business
Has expanded across the country
One thousand forty-two cities
And expanded overseas business
The overall output value has increased
One hundred and ninety-three point seventy-two
You remember it all
Don't miss a word
Bold bitch
How dare to deduct
Our Empress's monthly salary
You must have stolen it
I
Still want to quibble
Give me a call
Let me see which one of you dares to touch me
Dare to touch me
No one has good fruit to eat
Last month at three quarters afternoon on the second day of the lunar month
You and the other palace maid Xiao Yun
Come together to receive the service
Last month at twelve at twenty quarter afternoon
Here you go again
What you were wearing that day
Green clothes
Wearing a red head flower
Your exact words are
There's an emergency in your mother's house
So I want to make an advance
Next month's service
Every account I have here
Remember all clearly
And there are account books to prove it
Don't you dare to say that I deducted it
Your lady's service
I
I see the deduction
Someone your lady serves
Is it you
You spit your mouth
You still don't do anything
Let go
The imperial edict arrives
Which one of you is He Mingyue
You're the one who's
Kunqu Opera sung in the Imperial Garden
Yes
He Mingyue received the decree
Fengtian carries the emperor's imperial edict saying
Ho's Mingyue
Beautiful temperament
Gentle and obedient
Make him a noble person
I admire this
Thank you, Your Majesty
If you don't remember this
How do you get around in the harem
Sister Jiaojiao
You're talking nonsense again
Done
You leave me alone
You should go back to work