[English subtitles are available]
[Fall in Love with a Fox]
[EP09]
What?
You were pretending!
Keep your voice down!
What are you afraid of? There's no one.
Brother Shu prefers fair
and grace ladies.
If I didn't pretend,
how could he like me?
So,
the dozens of music scores and chess manuals,
the Woman Commandments,
and all those poems,
you've recited them all?
Oh, my god.
But you may pretend that
you are good at Unique romance.
What if he knows
you're the author of the novel
that he hates most.
How could you do?
None of that matters now.
The important thing is that
the tune that Mrs. Yu ask me to play
on the womenfolk gathering,
I don't know how to play at all!
What can I do, Baiwan?
What can I do, what can I do...
Stop.
I'm sure I can find a way.
I got a way, too.
Lord Qu
is so good at playing zither.
Or...
Let's ask him for help.
If you wanna go, go on your own.
I'm not going.
Why do I have to come?
It's enough that he practices with you.
This is my big obstacle,
aren't you gonna help me with that?
Besides, I always think that
there's a misunderstanding between you two.
Take advantage of this opportunity
to explain clearly.
No. But I...
Come on!
Go.
Lord Qu
I am honored
to hear from Miss Jin
to learn the zither from me.
Lord Qu is indeed good at playing.
It is an eye-opening for me to know
what is
the splendid melody and the true sentiments.
Love hurts make love sincere.
The sound is moving,
may because the player feels hurt.
It's about you.
It's not.
Lord Qu
Now that madam is here,
you can just start teaching.
Since Miss Jin asked,
I'll do.
Miss Jin
Are you familiar with the music score?
I memorized it,
but I always feel like something is wrong.
Strings move with your emotion.
The wrong feeling
may because you
haven't known the sense
of heart-broken.
The sense of heart-broken?
How to feel that?
Well...
Miss Baiwan
Could you smile to me?
Why would I?
Just as what I expected.
This is the sense of heart-broken.
You broke his heart!
What the hell...
Why do you teach
something about heart-broken?
Can you teach her
something good?
What is good?
How can I know?
All I know is a tune called
My Mind Not Brought.
My Mind Not Brought?
I'll never think of you,
You'd never think of me.
You put your heart on me in the past,
but now you can put it on others.
I see.
You're telling me to abandon,
don't pester.
I didn't say that!
You mentioned this tune,
don't you want me
to shrink back from difficulties?
I said I wouldn't come,
but you let me do.
I'll go!
-Baiwan  -Miss
Lord Qu
Don't be sad.
In my opinion,
Baiwan still likes you.
Miss Jin
do you think so?
It's just she
didn't realize that yet.
Then I should
make her realize it soon.
Excuse me, please.
Where's Miss Jin?
She's waiting in the wing.
Invite her to come here.
It's impolite
to have so many people waiting for her.
Yes, Madam.
Jin Baiwan
I'll teach you a lesson today.
Heroine Zijing
Mrs. Yu
Excuse me for not going out to meet you.
This way, please.
Why is she here?
Miss Jin
Madam said it's time for dinner.
Okay,
got it.
What do I do, Baiwan?
It's okay.
You can do it!
Can I?
Yes!
Definitely!
Okay!
I can!
Go for it!
I can't...
I definitely can't do it if Mrs. Yu is there.
Madam, it's just a womenfolk gathering.
Take it easy.
Relax, relax.
Yeah.
Relax.
As usual.
What are you doing?
I'm drinking to make myself courageous.
This is not good.
It's okay.
All right.
Why hasn't Miss Jin come yet?
Go and ask again.
Yes, Madam.
Madam, here they come.
Are you okay?
Mrs. Yu
I'm here.
Let's get started.
Come on!
The womenfolk gathering is
a tradition of Taoyuan Valley.
Muqiu is going to marry into Taoyuan Valley.
And I hope,
hope that...
Interconnected.
I hope to take this opportunity
to know ladies of all families,
and heroines.
We can be closer in the future,
and inter...
inter...
What's next?
Interconnect!
For me, being docile comes to the first.
Put others before ourselves.
Serve the husband and bring up the children.
Then we can have a harmonious relationship
and make a satisfactory family.
Let us encourage each other.
It's our great honor to
serve you.
Please help yourselves.
Madam
Before that, I will play a tune first.
Come on!
Get the liquor!
The liquor!
Before madam plays,
let's toast to her.
Good idea!
Welcome to
Taoyuan Valley today.
Cheers!
Thank you, Mrs. Yu.
Here comes the Tingqin Lord.
Sorry for keep you waiting.
-Lord Qu  -Lord Qu
Lord Qu
I've gathered you here today.
First is
celebrating the marriage for my son.
The second is
to discuss the matter
of Puyuan Canon.
Lord Qu
please tell us the detail of it.
A month ago,
the matter that Jin's Escort Agency
transported Puyuan Canon,
you must have heard of it.
Right.
When we received the mission,
we didn't know it was
Puyuan Canon.
Otherwise, I wouldn't accept it!
Mr Yu
Someone must have
set Jin's Escort Agency up on purpose.
The sacred book reappeared,
and disputes can hardly be avoided.
So the master of Yan School and I
talked about it.
Su Zhuozhuo, Miss Su of Yan School
will investigate the case with me.
That's right.
Mr Su told me about it, too.
It's true.
But,
what if
you were coveting the sacred book,
and you make use of the investigation,
steal it and replace it with something else?
Nonsense.
You covet the sacred book so much,
so don't you really know
what kind of book it is?
Good, good!
Well done, madam!
Madam
It's time to make poems!
Make poems?
Making poems is one of the traditions
of the womenfolk gathering
in Taoyuan Valley.
Muqiu
Let's start with you.
Okay.
I think
no one wants to make poems,
nor comes to the gathering either.
Gosh, gosh, gosh.
She's drunk. What do I do?
What do I do?
Let's get drunk together.
Let's toast to
the host of this gathering,
Mrs. Yu.
Here it is.
Well,
please help me fill the glasses.
-Thanks.  -Wait!
-I'm not done yet!
Obviously,
no one wants to be here.
But we have to do things that are prescribed
because of the traditional customs.
It's unreasonable!
As a woman,
being docile comes to the first.
How could you be so rude!
Why should women
be docile?
Why should women follow
so many rules and regulations
after getting married?
Even can't do
the things they love.
You!
Do you wanna be a heroine?
If you want, just do it!
Do you want to be a tailor?
Just do it!
If one wanna write novels,
she should do it too.
Jin Muqiu
Mrs. Yu
I'm scared to see you.
Why are you always mad?
Come on.
Have a drink!
Madam
How dare you!
Here's another toast to Mrs. Yu.
One more.
Fill it.
Here it is, Mrs. Yu.
Come on!
How dare you!
Don't be so serious.
To everyone!
You need to smile more, you know?
Smile.
As we all know,
Puyuan Canon is a book on martial-arts
of the Xu's for generations.
What do you mean, Lord Qu?
Five years ago,
The Xu family were murdered,
and the sacred book disappeared.
But if the sacred book
is really that good,
why didn't the Xu's practice it?
-Well...  -Well...
It makes sense.
I've heard something about it.
Although the Puyuan Canon
is very powerful,
one who practices this martial arts
is easy to be possessed by the Devil.
So the Xu family
was only guarding the book.
That's right.
The ancestors of the Xu's
who practiced the martial arts
all died because of
being possessed by the Devil.
Since it is so,
why do I cut my own throat
to steal such a book?
This book is so dreadful,
then why do we find it?
Idiot!
Besides,
if I really
wanted that book,
I would definitely steal it secretly.
Why would I investigate it
with the escort,
and made myself a target for all?
Good point.
Leave the book is true or not alone.
However,
the man who let Jin's Escort Agency
sent off the Canon
must knew the facts.
Lord Qu
Can we find this man?
He disappeared.
Disappeared?
The sender is
Xing Laoliu.
When I went to his home,
there's no one.
Why!
You're right!
Why men can
decide anything?
After we marry them,
we can't be ourselves.
Poor the two heroines!
Why should we obey the rules?
Why!
Why women should
follow her husband?
Exactly!
I've tried to obey him.
It's
too tired!
I'm telling you,
In the past days,
I was the famous Flying Leopard!
Come on.
Yes!
How did she get that mark?
The madam and the guests
are so drunk,
shall we ask Lord of Valley to come here?
Hurry up!
I see.
This man
must be
the manipulator.
His purpose was simple,
that is, to mess up the whole world.
As long as we catch him,
we can...
Something's wrong, Lord of Valley!
Lord of Valley
Something happened in the womenfolk gathering.
Be a woman of indomitable spirit!
We can't be bullied by these men.
We can't!
Come on, Baiwan.
How, how, how,
how much did they drink!
Yeah.
A nasty cunning fox!
Qiuer
Darling
I was Fooled.
Qiuer
You...
Dad
The smell!
Ladies and gentlemen,
we didn't take good care of everyone.
Please take your wives to
the side hall to have a rest.
Hangover soup will be there in a minute.
Excuse me, excuse me.
It's okay.
It's really him.
So he came to Taoyuan Valley too.
Come on, come on.
What?
You're all gone,
nobody takes care of me.
Okay, Okay.
Don't go, please.
Darling, be careful.
Come on.
Fox?
Why are you here too?
I'm here to pick you up.
Come on.
Water still flows,
though we cut it with our swords.
We may drown the countless sorrow with wine.
-The countless sorrow.  -Miss Jin
Please stop!
Jueming, close the door.
Yeah, yeah.
The countless sorrow.
Qiuer
Come on.
Give this to me.
Brother Shu
-Be careful.  -Stay there!
Unique romance is
a piece of cake for me.
Lord, the windows and door are closed.
Stay there!
Lord
Stop.
Stop that now.
Go to find uncle Jin.
He went to find Miss Su
to get the hangover prescription
when he saw Miss Jin was drunk.
Then urge him.
Okay, okay, okay.
Why do you go?
Qiuer
It's not appropriate
for a single man and a woman
to stay in the same room.
Well,
I'll let a maid look after you.
Stop!
Come back!
What?
Let me ask you,
whether you love me
or not?
Of course, I do.
There's
no doubt.
I swear to God.
No!
Who you love is not me!
Qiuer
You're drunk.
Well,
let's talk
when you're awake tomorrow.
Let me help you to rest.
I'm not drunk!
I don't wanna lie to you anymore.
What?
I lied.
I don't like
unique romance,
flower arrangement and the tea culture at all.
I'm not a grace lady either.
To make you like me,
I read books,
play the zither and paint every night.
I'm so tired.
I don't wanna be a grace lady.
I don't wanna be others.
Qiuer
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't break the rules
of Taoyuan Valley.
Rules, rules!
Why are there
so many rules in Taoyuan Valley!
I hate rules!
Why do you like
everything
I hate?
If I tell you,
I'm not
a grace lady at all.
Will you love me?
I don't care
if you are or not.
But
this thing
angered father and mother.
I need to end it up for you.
Put me down!
I'm gonna get even with them!
Baiwan
You're drunk.
I'm not.
I'm Jin Baiwan,
the heroine of Jin's Escort Agency!
So,
before you went to Jin's Escort Agency,
what did you do?
How do I remember what I did?
I don't know!
Put me down,
I'm going back.
Be good.
Impossible.
Dad said
she is dead.
Yes!
But why would Zijing want to kill her?
And the mark,
it won't be wrong.
Put me down, put me down.
I'm gonna get even with him!
Who?
Qu Zheng
Why?
You're a liar!
You tell me you don't know kung fu, huh?
And you tricked me into being your bodyguard?
And you tricked me into an engagement?
You're a big liar!
But the engagement
was proposed
by you.
Me?
How could that be possible?
He even wanted to break off the engagement.
This was
proposed by you too.
Me, again?
Forget it.
Well,
he told madam
that
he likes me.
This I can
assure you,
it's not a lie.
How can you assure that?
I'm telling you,
Qu zheng
He is a liar,
a cunning fox!
Don't believe
what he told you.
I hate him!
If
you really hate him,
why were you so angry
when Su Zhuozhuo
said she loved him?
And why
did you go into
the trap
he set up?
If you really hate him,
why were you thinking of him
when you were drunk?
Yeah,
all I thought about was him.
No, no,
get out, get out,
get out, get out, get out.
All these signs show that
you love him.
I love him.
When you can't see him,
you'll miss him.
A little bit.
You're watching him
every minute.
How do you know that?
Because so do I.
Qu Zheng
Yeah.
You beat me?
Did you try to burn me?
Did you? Did you?
I never said
I didn't mean it.
I did it on purpose.
I made you angry
on purpose
in front of Su Zhuozhuo.
I did it on purpose
to make you
speak your thoughts out
in front of Miss Jin.
I wanna hear you saying
you love me.
Do you admit it now?
I'm sleepy.
Why is it so hard
to make you say you love me?
Come on.
You big liar.
You've promised me,
you wouldn't lose this pendant.
You forgot.
Well,
even it is
from me,
you forgot too.
Make the little fox
as our
love token.
I hope you can keep it
and don't lose it.
Aren't you willing to?
I just thought
we've only known each other for a month,
and we don't know each other well.
That's because
since we came here,
you never told me
where you came from.
It's my master's order.
But I assure you,
I'm definitely not a bad person.
What my master let us do
were all good things that
maintained justice and punished evil.
Well, in that case,
I won't force you if you don't say.
Anyway, we still have
a lifetime
to be together.
Chu
Don't turn me down,
okay?
Do you accept?
The moonlight is so beautiful tonight,
let's make a vow under it.
Okay.
Moonlight in the sky,
witnessing my faith.
I will love Chu
for my lifetime.
From now on,
our commitment will never change,
we'll be together no matter life or death.
I swear to the moon,
I'll keep my words.
We'll won't be apart,
never and ever.
I, Chu, will do that so.
Cunning fox
Isn't it
any trap, is it?
You said so,
do you go back on your word so soon?
No.
What if you do
as soon as we leave the valley?
What can you do then?
Well,
no matter up to the sky
or down to the sea,
even to the ends of the earth,
I'll find you.
When leaving the valley,
we made an appointment
to meet each other in three days.
But later,
you disappeared.
I've been looking for you for five years.
All is ready.
The last escort
will be right out.
It's her.
What's wrong?
The world, I'm on my way!
Chu
What?
She is Chu?
The plan has changed,
We also go to Furong Town.
What have you experienced
in the past five years?
She's asleep?
It was so treacherous on the way.
She may haven't slept
so peacefully
for a long time.
What do you wanna ask?
You've been looking for her for five years.
Finally, you made it,
why don't you tell her
all the things before?
I'm the one
who got her involved in this for no reason.
Now there is still a big problem.
The less she knows,
the better.
When it is the right time,
I'll tell her
the whole thing.
That's your business,
I don't care.
However,
two days later,
it'll be the day to open the warehouse.
Are you sure he will come this time?
Since Puyuan Canon
can lead him to Yinxue Village,
this time,
he'll come for sure.