English subtitles are available
Fall in Love with a Fox EP13
Now, all sects
have changed their attitude to Tingqin Garden
since the wedding night in Taoyuan Valley.
Some people even said that
what you did is to provoke
Alliance of Martial Arts.
It was urgent that night.
As long as I can prevent
those people of Nonuple Palace from taking Baiwan away,
I wouldn't regret.
But...
What?
I have surveyed the
Young Host of Palace.
As you expected,
Qingyun
and Chu
grew up together.
Qingyun was blind since he was young.
It was Chu who has been taken care of him.
Therefore,
he is fond of Chu
deeply.
Five years ago,
Nonuple Palace declared that
Chu was disappeared.
Young Host was in pain.
It's a pity that
although Young Host of Palace was in deep love
and met Chu
five years later,
this time our Lord
seizes the initiative.
What do you mean?
I just think that
we took
Miss Jin to Tingqin Garden,
Qingyun
won't forgive us.
So what?
Whoever he is,
I won't
allow people of Nonuple Palace
to approach Baiwan.
Mrs.
Zheng, are you there?
Just leave them to me.
I can take care of him.
Okay.
Baiwan is coming.
Zheng, are you there?
Zheng, what are you going to do?
Go away.
Zheng
I took some breakfast for you.
It's so early.
Come in.
Zheng
Does it hurt?
No.
You haven't changed your clothes.
I'll call the maid in.
No.
She's a girl.
She can't change clothes for you.
Then, I'll ask Jianshan.
No, he can't either.
Why?
I'm your wife.
I can help you.
Don't bother others.
If you need any help,
I can do it for you.
Then,
how can you help me?
Let me see...
Young Mrs.
Head Escort Jin
left this morning.
He asked me to deliver the letter to you.
Left?
Qiuer, you finally got married.
So I come back to the Escort Agency.
I don't want to
see you cry.
So I didn't tell you.
From now on,
you and Linfeng
should support and love each other.
Then, I'll feel relieved.
Baiwan left.
Dad left, too.
How can you leave me here
alone!
Young Mrs., by the way,
I just heard...
Stop.
I'm sad now.
You asked me to inquire about
Miss Jin Baiwan, didn't you?
Baiwan?
Just tell me.
I just heard Lord of Valley and Mrs.
were talking about
Miss Jin Baiwan.
They said
Qu Zheng of Tingqin Garden is a renegade.
What?
Lord Qu
told me
he was attacked in the valley
the night before the wedding.
I was afraid of affecting your marriage,
so we just
hid it.
I thought
Taoyuan Valley
was their objective.
But at the wedding night,
Lord Qu stunned everyone
to take Jin Baiwan away.
Then I just understood that
all the issues
are linked with
the Lord
of Tingqin Garden.
His behaviors
not only pissed off the crowd,
but also affected our Taoyuan Valley.
Now all sects
think that Tingqin Garden and Jin's Escort Agency
are related with
Puyuan Canon case.
Your father-in-law
is afraid of embroiling our Taoyuan Valley,
so he left in advance.
If Jin Baiwan
was taken by
those of Nonuple Palace at that day,
then everything is okay.
Lord Qu
looks calm.
How can he be so stupid
in dealing with this thing?
Jin Baiwan and Jin's Escort Agency
have a close connection.
Feng
Take care of Miss Jin these days.
Don't allow her to
communicate with Jin Baiwan.
Otherwise, we may be in trouble.
No problem.
I will tell Qiuer.
They slander
Baiwan and Mr Qu.
I don't know the condition of Baiwan.
I have to figure out an idea.
That's it.
I'm Qiu Qiuer.
As long as I write the story
of Baiwan into my novels,
then all people will know
Baiwan and Mr Qu are innocent.
Young Master of Valley
Lord of Valley asks us to...
Qiuer and Miss Baiwan
have a good relationship.
It's not easy to cut their connection.
The words I just said
were to relieve
my parents.
After all, she
went here alone.
She must be lonely and helpless.
Jueming
You
send some
dishes she likes to her room tonight.
Okay.
I bought the food,
medicine,
and sugar.
Is there anything I need to buy
for Zheng?
That's it.
Zheng is boring
since he's sick.
I can buy him novels.
You even have
novels written by Qiu Qiuer?
We have
all Qiu Qiuer's novels.
There are only a few.
The others are in the store.
I can take them
for you to have a look.
Okay.
Wait a moment.
Spoony Royal Highness.
It was out of print.
How can you have it?
The No.1 Husband.
It's my favorite novel.
Miss
Is the novel in your hand
that interesting?
Yes.
You can have a look.
Then,
why is it interesting?
I admire the No.1 husband
shield his wife from the glare of the sun,
and they chat under the tree.
Zheng, it's you!
I didn't recognize
that it was you
just now.
I didn't see you
since the morning.
I'm worried about you.
So you are here to...
No.
I'm afraid you're boring.
So I want to buy a novel for you.
But I don't know
which one you like.
I think
the one in your hand
is good.
This one?
No.
Why not?
Since you like it,
it must be a good novel.
I need to know
my wife's preference.
They use lotus leaves together to keep the rain off.
Do you like it?
Gently kissed her mouth with his mouth
and swallowed the cake.
It's interesting.
I learned a lot
from The No.1 Husband.
Is this your favorite
plot in the novel?
It's indeed good
with a good title.
Since you like
the novel,
I need to work hard
to be the No.1 husband
in your mind.
Let's go home.
It's a good idea.
You...
I bought you much food.
I'll make you some soup.
Let's go.
Alright, this is the last dish
ginseng chicken soup.
Zheng, let's enjoy the meal.
You worked hard, daring.
No.
Let's have a taste.
Taste it when it's still hot.
Here.
What's wrong?
Let me help you.
Take care.
You can hit me,
but can't eat a meal?
How about it?
One more taste.
What do you want to eat?
I'll feed you.
This one or that one?
Purple yam?
This one?
That's enough.
I can't bear it.
I don't want to eat.
Don't bother us.
You are so
suitable.
Zheng, what do you want?
I can feed you.
This one.
This one?
Here.
You have drunk the medicine.
Just have a rest early.
I gotta go.
What's wrong?
Does it hurt?
No.
You shall go.
What if
you hurt again?
Or
you can tell me a story.
Maybe
I'll be sleepy when listening to it.
Okay.
I'll tell you a story
in Bamboo Annals
you always read.
That's so boring.
Which one do you like?
This one.
Why is it here?
You like it.
Of course, I'll buy it
and learn from it
to win your favor.
No.
I want to listen to this novel.
Alright.
I'll tell you the story.
Mr Xu said,
"As long as you're alright,
I am willing to do anything."
You worked hard all day long for me.
It's my fault
to ask you to tell me a story.
that you were hurt.
No.
Because of you,
I didn't descent into hell.
I have punished the rogues
that offended you.
I'm Xu Yifei.
Can I know
your name?
Baiwan
Don't remember
your past.
Although you didn't
remember me five years ago,
I just hope
you can
live a happy life
like this.
Young Mrs.
It's time for meal.
Are you
writing novels again?
No.
I'm writing a letter to my dad.
Okay.
Young Mrs.
Just listen to me.
Don't
write novels again
in the future.
That's all.
I shall go.
No.
It's too dangerous to write novels here.
Qiuer
Yes?
Nothing.
Jueming
Ask the cook
to prepare two dishes of cakes
for young Mrs.
Don't let her be hungry again.
Okay.
I heard that Miss Jin
is obedient these days.
Thanks to your discipline,
Muqiu is obedient.
In these days,
she was learning needlework
in her room.
As for her behaviors,
she's more dignified than before.
Since she's in our Taoyuan Valley,
it's a must to be dignified.
It's not appropriate to be crazy.
Mother
It's windy outside.
What about having a rest in the room?
Why are you hiding me?
What's it?
Mrs.
These are the novels of Miss Jin.
What do you want to do?
Such stuff
can't occur in our Taoyuan Valley.
Fenger, fire them.
You want to fire my novels?
No way.
Mother
It's indeed her fault to write novels.
But such punishment
is too serious.
We Taoyuan Valley
won't bear them.
Mother
As Young Master of Valley,
do you want to shield her?
Take her away.
Young Mrs.
Don't touch me.
That's my stuff.
Don't fire it.
I spent a lot of time on it.
Fenger, you fire it.
What are you waiting for?
No.
If I don't fire them,
mother won't forgive
Qiuer.
Qiuer
If you're angry,
just be angry at me.
It's my fault.
Please don't fire them.
No.
Young Mrs.
No, it's my fault.
I can do anything
as long as you don't fire them.
Don't fire them.
No.
No. No.
Rules in Taoyuan Valley
are right?
Why do I feel so sad
when I obey them?
You indulge her too much
so that she can do such things.
If you don't teach your wife,
I'll do it for you.
Come with me.
Release me.
Are you okay?
Young Mrs.
Just listen to me.
Don't mind it.
After all,
you will live a whole life
in the Taoyuan Valley.
A whole life?
You're the wife of Young Master of Valley.
That's for sure.
No.
I can't live a whole life here.
Young Mrs.
Young Master of Valley
It was her fault.
Why are you
punished for her?
You got the caning
and are copying women's commandments for her.
That's too much.
Jueming
Young Master of Valley
There's bad news.
Young Mrs. wrote a letter for you and left.
I'm gone.
You Taoyuan Valley people have pushed me too far.
You can regard it as we have divorced peacefully.
From now on, we're strangers.
This...
I'm supporting you.
You should have energy now,
But
you're painstaking.
No.
You should have recovered.
How could it become serious?
No.
You were hurt in the chest,
not the lags.
And last night,
you picked me up and sent me to my room.
You finally discovered.
You cheat me again.
It's you who asked to
support me
to go for a walk outside.
I have no fault.
I know.
If you hurt,
you'll say nothing.
You look sick
and ask me to do a lot of things,
so you must have recovered.
You know me a lot.
You're a cunning fox.
So,
since you're alright,
I want to go back to Jin's Escort Agency.
Last time,
when we left Taoyuan Valley,
I didn't
even tell Head Escort Jin.
You wanna leave?
Okay.
I won't leave.
You want to go back to Jin's Escort Agency
for a long time.
It seems that
our Tingqin Garden is not good enough.
Of course, Tingqin Garden is good.
But I can cook everyday
in the Jin's Escort Agency.
I don't know what to do
here.
You're a cook in Jin's Escort Agency.
In Tingqin Garden,
you're my wife.
It doesn't matter what you should do.
You should think about
what you can do with me.
According to Miss Jin's novels,
we are
couples
now.
So have you figured out
what you want to do
with your love?
I can do whatever
I want to do?
Sure.
I have
a husband now.
But what should
couples do?
That's it.
I have read
a lot of novels.
I can learn from them.
This plot is good.
I'll copy it.
Are these what you want to do?
But actually, I don't know.
I just read Miss Jin's novels,
and I want to
try them.
Okay, I can do
these things with you.
Really?
Then, let's begin with the first one.
In the novels,
couples would
mold clay figurine
of each other in their minds
and form them by firing.
That's the love token.
I want to try it.
Shall we start?
Okay.
I will mold a figure
more handsome than you.
You can be relieved.
Don't steal a glance at mine.
You can't steal a glance at mine, either.
I didn't steal a glance at yours.
I just looked at it.
Yours is ugly.
But it's you,
Baiwan.
Are you saying that
you're ugly?
I'm not ugly.
You...
Mine is ugly.
I'm done.
Me, too.
Let's disclose them.
One, two, three.
Disclose.
You mold a rabbit.
You mold
a cunning fox.
But your rabbit
is better than my cunning fox.
So,
in the future,
the cunning fox will listen to
the rabbit, okay?
Okay.
The cunning fox
will only listen to Baiwan.
I don't expect that Lord
really molds figures.
Our Tingqin Garden has established for three years.
It's the first time that
I see Lord is such happy.
No.
I'm going to cook the dinner.
He's seduced by Baiwan.
So
love is harmful.
Otherwise,
even Lord
would fail.
Miss Jin said that there is a wishing tree
outside the Furong Town.
Since we can't go there
to have a look at it,
we can make a wish to the sky lantern.
Miss Jin's novels also
have such a plot.
What wishes do you want to make?
I have a lot of wishes.
I wish you
to recover as soon as possible.
don't get hurt anymore.
I wish Miss Jin
and all people in Jin's Escort Agency
can live a peaceful
and happy life.
I wish all people of Tingqin Garden
to be healthy and happy, too.
I also wish Puyuan Canon case
can be investigated clearly
so that people will know that Jin's Escort Agency is innocent.
It's your turn.
I have no wish.
Why?
Everyone has their wishes.
I used to have one.
But I have achieved it.
So I think
I can work hard
to achieve other wishes.
I'm afraid God may punish me
because of my greed.
Is your wish related to me?
Sure.
So you don't make a wish?
Let's release the sky lanterns.
Okay.
I have another wish.
I forgot it.
I wish
I can remember my past,
so that I
have all my memories.
But you said,
you don't want to
remember the one who hurts you.
I don't want to remember him.
But
maybe he's not my family.
I just
want to know my family
and find them as soon as possible.
Then, I can see them with you.
Okay.
Aren't you cold?
I won't be cold.
This time,
what do you want to try?
Rainy days.
Many couples in novels
are met and fall in love with each other
in romantic rainy days.
So I want to try it.
Okay.
We'll wait for a rainy day.
Everything is just alike five years ago.
Baiwan
I hope you can be happy
forever.
Although it doesn't rain,
it snows.
I only focused on the battles
in novels
of Miss Jin.
I didn't expect...
Being with the one you love,
it's also happy
to do the stupid things.
There is a guy
who is willing to do the stupid things with me.
It's so good.
I also think so.
Which part do you think is good?
It's good to meet you.
Then, one of my wishes
is achieved.
Is that easy?
Although it's not a rainy day,
it's a snowy day
which is more romantic.
What a coincidence!
Last night,
I read the novel you like.
On such days,
couples should
do this...