[English subtitles are available]
[Fall in Love with a Fox]
[EP04]
I think
Yu Linfeng is a good boy.
Trust me.
This young man, Linfeng,
will be a good husband
who takes good care of his wife.
What are you talking about?
He...
He doesn't fancy me at all.
What?
He...
Did he say it himself?
We shouldn't go to Taoyuan Valley.
Let's go back home,
and break off the engagement.
I don't think this engagement is necessary.
-Find him.  -Dad
He...
Although he doesn't like me,
I... I...
It's enough.
I can't
let my baby daughter
marry a
foolish brat who doesn't cherish you.
I will kick his ass.
Dad
Then let him like me.
Is it okay?
What do you mean?
I'm the most famous
writer of love novels, Qiu qiuer.
As long as
I follow the designed plan,
he will fall in love with me for sure.
Miss Muqiu
Mr Yu
I didn't expect that
you would invite me to
such a romantic place.
Compared with the scene here,
the scenes in the stories
are so mediocre.
I'm glad you like it.
What's wrong?
Is it too cold?
How about this?
It's still a little cold.
I will get closer to you then,
and help you keep warm.
I...
I should go back to the carriage first.
Perfect place.
Perfect pace.
And a little unexpected surprise.
It will work.
Miss Muqiu
Since you invite me here,
what can I do for you?
What's wrong?
Mr Yu, did you catch a cold?
I'm allergic to tea trees
since I was a child.
Allergic to tea trees?
So, you can't drink tea?
I do drink tea.
But the tea tress...
Then use my handkerchief to block it.
What's wrong again?
I...
I'm also allergic to perfume.
Then what should I do?
How about
we go to another place?
Are you sure here is a good place?
It's not romantic.
I...
I feel chilly.
Chilly?
Miss Muqiu
You won't feel chilly now.
It's warm indeed.
Coming through!
I will go back to my carriage.
Let me send you there.
Okay.
After you.
Lord of Valley Junior
What's the matter?
Which is better? Fry it with chili,
or plain-frying?
I've told you that
it's up to you.
Okay.
Fry it with chili then.
Where is my wallet?
Lord of Valley Junior
What's wrong again?
Should we set off now?
I'm watching the time.
Do you understand?
Miss Muqiu
I'm fine.
Lord of Valley Junior
You lack a sense of romance.
Why?
Look, Miss Jin
She just wants to create an opportunity
to be with you alone.
Look at you.
You have
embarrassed her.
Nonsense.
Do your job.
Yes.
Help!
Somebody help!
Someone is stealing the sacred book.
Shut up!
Since you dare to do this,
you should take responsibility.
You shut up!
Let it go. Let it go.
What's going on?
Stop!
You're the young lady of the Yan School.
You can't just leave
after stealing things.
What do you want?
If you don't want to make a sincere apology to me,
I will make it public
in the meeting of martial arts.
You...
bring great reputation
to your Yan School.
In fact,
Miss Jin is more reasonable on this matter.
Just an apology.
Sorry. Are we done?
Wait.
Are you still not satisfied?
Since Miss Su already made an apology,
Miss Jin, please be generous
and forgive her.
That's right.
I also want to be generous.
But
I'm afraid that
some shameless people
will steal it again while I am sleeping.
So...
So Miss Jin,
what do you want?
So from now on, when I'm sleeping,
you, Mr Qu,
the righteous gentleman,
need to stay in my room to protect my sacred book.
Just in case that someone shameless
tries to steal it again.
You're the shameless one!
It was you
who tried to steal my book.
So, you have no right to judge me.
-You...  -Okay.
I accept it.
Mr Qu
How can you...
Guess the number is big or small.
Big.
Why did you choose big again?
You've lost so many times.
Be serious, please!
I'm a greedy man,
so I want everything.
Certainly, the big one is better than the small one.
Besides,
it may not be a bad thing
to temporarily lose several times.
Fine, I appreciate your confidence.
Open.
Two, two, and three.
I win again.
I have won enough money
to buy a gift for the young lady.
Mr Qu, why are you still smiling?
You almost lost all your bride price.
Bride price
is for the bride.
No.
This guy is so smart.
But why did he lose so many times?
I'd better stop playing.
Bride?
It's late.
I have to go to bed.
Mr Qu
You should also go back to sleep early.
You... what are you doing here?
In the morning,
I have promised you that
this evening
I will sleep in this room
to help you protect the book.
But we made the deal that
it was just a plan to trick Su Zhuozhuo.
I never break my promise.
It's the same this time.
Don't worry.
Since you trust me,
and think I'm righteous.
I will also trust you.
I know you won't
do anything impolite.
What do you want?
Take a quilt to sleep on the floor.
Take what?
Go, go, go.
Never think about it.
Go out. Go out.
What are you looking at?
I'm shutting the door.
Why does my heart is beating so fast?
It's reasonable.
He scared me like that,
it's normal that my heart will beat fast.
What a cunning fox!
It's time to sleep.
Did Miss Jin kick you out?
Enough.
Let's talk business.
Anything new?
The news about the sacred book
has been spread over the country.
Now, everyone
is looking for Jin Baiwan.
The real murderer
we're finding
must be one of them.
It seems that it's time to set off.
Now, Miss Jin's wound
has almost healed.
What's your decision?
Shall we take her with us?
No.
She has lost her memory and strength.
We can't take her with us.
She will be in danger.
Don't worry.
Since you trust me,
and think I'm righteous.
I will also trust you.
I know you won't
do anything impolite.
That guy is really a cunning fox.
I should stay away from him in the future.
Who do you want
to keep a distance from?
Why are you here?
Miss Su said that
if you take this medicine,
your wound
will recover well.
She won't dare
to do to this medicine, right?
What's your plan
after your recovery?
I haven't sent the sacred book yet.
I still need to go to Yinxue Village.
You will also go with me,
won't you?
Do you want me to go with you?
Since you want to investigate the sacred book,
that's for sure that
you have to go with me.
What if what I need is not the same
as you think?
Then what do you need?
It's too dangerous on the way ahead.
I just want you
to be safe.
Miss
Your lunch is ready.
Lunch is ready.
Shouldn't I be in the yard?
-Miss  -How did I come here?
Come in.
Miss, it's your lunch.
Put it there.
Why is it only for one person?
Where is the lunch for Mr Qu and Miss Su?
The gentleman and lady with you
have left in the early morning.
Left?
Yes.
This is the letter that the gentleman
asked me to give you.
You can go.
I've left with the sacred book.
Take care.
Qu Zheng
The sacred book.
That cunning fox.
Get it done. Hurry up.
Yes, sir.
Lord of Valley Junior
Did you sleep well last night?
We can get ready soon,
and set off as soon as possible.
Why are you pouting again?
What happened?
Did that brat make you angry?
I will get this even.
Dad
He is over there.
It's not because of him.
Then...
what's going on?
It's all my fault.
It turns out that my methods
are all impractical.
None of them is useful.
I'm not qualified to write love stories.
Uncle Jin
It's Linfeng.
I'm leaving. You can talk.
Please wait, uncle Jin.
I'm just here to give something
to Miss Muqiu.
Miss Muqiu
I think
this must be your lost draft.
Did you read it?
No, no, no.
Without your permission,
I won't read it.
I just subconsciously
saw some words.
I didn't expect your handwriting
so excellent.
It's impressive.
I learned it when I was a child.
I have nothing else to ask.
I got to go.
Dad
Maybe he has read it.
Didn't you see
my hint before?
I told you to stay calm.
If he saw it,
could he be so calm?
Then why he doesn't have any reactions
to my methods?
My silly girl,
it's not because he doesn't react.
It's because you used
wrong methods.
Wrong methods?
Why?
You...
Why can't
my beautiful daughter
succeed
my smart brain?
Completely wrong.
My thought was that
if that brat is not sensible,
we should go back directly.
I... I won't go back with you.
I know you like him.
So I decide
to help you
to deal with this matter.
Take it.
Yu Linfeng's hobbies.
Where did you get this?
The older, the wiser.
Speaking of this matter,
it's a long story.
Jueming
You are the one
who has stayed with the Lord of Valley Junior for the longest time.
Then do you know what is
his favorite color?
You ask the right person.
Blue is the Lord of Valley Junior's favorite color.
Yeah.
Blue.
Blue is great.
Great color. Great color.
Then what's his
favorite book?
He likes many books,
such as
the Book of Songs. Yeah.
The Book of Songs.
He likes reading the Book of Songs.
The Book of Songs is nice.
Yeah.
This is just the method
I used before
to chase your mother.
To know his hobbies,
and like what he likes.
No matter where he runs,
he can't run out of
your control.
We should have got rid of
that burden earlier.
That girl definitely didn't know
that we would go this way.
Why can't I know this?
Even you know this way.
How did you come here?
Do you think you can cast me off
with drugs?
You can take the shortcuts,
so can I.
It seems that
I have underrated you, Miss Jin.
Cunning fox.
I trusted you so much.
Give me the sacred book.
I treated you
so gently.
Why do you call me
the cunning fox?
Hypocritical.
Let go of me.
Miss Jin, just think about it.
If I
were really a bad guy,
why would I
help you all the way?
I even requested Miss Su
to heal your wound.
Then why did you
steal my book?
In the letter,
I have made myself clear.
The way to Yinxue Village
is too dangerous.
I don't want you
to be in danger again.
So I decided to take the risk
and help you to send it.
Nonsense.
I don't need your help.
Since you
can't accept it,
I won't say more.
What are you doing?
Sir
Well done!
You should have treated her like this earlier.
Put me down.
Don't worry, Miss Jin.
Since I've promised you,
I must send the sacred book there.
Wait. Don't go.
Goodbye.
Put me down.
Sir
Here you are.
Put me down.
Help!
Is someone here?
We should have done this earlier.
It has spent our so much time to
treat her wound.
It's my fault,
because I took her sacred book.
However, we took her book
just because we don't want her to be in danger.
It's good enough.
Hope she can go back
to Jin's Escort Agency as soon as possible.
I can do this.
Oh my God.
Who is it?
Jing Yuan?
Why is it you?
Why did you
catch us?
Why?
A dead man
has no need to know so much.
What do you mean?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
you can't
always be like this.
So I must get
Puyuan Canon.
How is your investigation going?
According to my investigation,
the Puyuan Canon
escorted by Jin's Escort Agency
may be real.
I have got the news that
the book is going to be sent to
a man named Qing Songke.
Moreover, this man
also has an extremely
mysterious identity.
It is said that he is
the only descendant of the Xu family.
That is to say.
Someone wants to send it back to its owner.
I will try my best
to get the sacred book for you.
Hope you can finish your training as soon as possible.
That won't be necessary.
If it's true,
this time,
I will do it myself.
Are you flying with your legs?
How did you catch up with us?
You will never trap me
with your little tricks.
I...
You're so capable.
But after the long journey,
I am really exhausted.
I'm gonna go upstairs to have a rest first.
Wait.
What do you want?
I just want to have a good sleep.
Please forgive me.
I will never
give up.
I...
I'm here to take the sacred book back.
Then I can't let you
take it.
Qu Zheng, you cunning fox.
Let's see
if you will come out tomorrow.
What's this?
Tingqin Lord Qu Zheng
is shameless and ruthless.
He pretends to be kind to steal Puyuan Canon.
It's Jin Baiwan who made this.
Attention, everyone.
let me tell you
why the Tingqin Lord Qu Zheng
is a shameless villain.
He is
a thief
and a liar.
He has stolen
Puyuan Canon from me.
Mr Qu
She is slandering you. Won't you stop her?
I will.
Yeah.
It's too rude.
Qu Zheng
Speaking of him,
look at his ugly face.
It's so ugly.
Is he just Qu Zheng?
Qu Zheng
Go, go, go.
How about this?
Is it shameful to be exposed
in public?
I'm here to warn you.
Warn me?
For what?
To warn you
not to make up stories.
When did I make up stories?
Why is there
a black nevus on my face?
Is that what you want to say?
Yes, it is.
You...
Qu Zheng
You're not only a cunning fox,
but also a rotter.
Sir
Are you hungry?
I'm going to buy some baked pancakes.
Come on and have a look.
The hot baked pancakes!
Take a look.
Excuse me, can I have two pancakes, please?
I won't sell it to you.
I won't sell.
No.
Fresh plums!
Take a look!
Excuse me,
I want some plums.
Take a--
I'm just doing a small business.
Please, my lord,
don't hurt me.
Lord?
Mr Qu
This might be also
because of Miss Jin.
Yeah.
One of them is in white
with an instrument on his back.
While the other one looks
murderous,
like a demon.
They rob and kill.
They commit all sorts of crimes.
If they come to buy your goods,
don't sell anything to them.
If they are full,
there will be a disaster in your village.
Jin Baiwan
Here they come.
Run.
Go, go, go.
I can accept that you slandered
Mr Qu and me.
But, you even
persuaded them
not to sell foods to us.
Do you want to starve us to death?
You bad behaviors deserve it.
It's all because you have stolen my sacred book.
I have tolerated you for a long time.
Jin Baiwan
Do you really think
I won't beat you?
Beat me then.
Do you think I'm afraid of that?
I...
Miss Jin, do you think
Miss Su and I
treated your wound,
so we won't
beat you?
Do you really want to hurt me
because of the sacred book?
I have told you that
this world is not
as naive as you think.
What if I say
you can only choose one
between your life and the sacred book?
Jin's Escort Agency
has never failed any mission.
It's my mission to send it to the destination.
I will never give up.
Ever!
So you want to choose
the latter one.
Sir
I will never give up,
even if the price is my life.
In that case,
I have to...
I can't do anything to you.
I can only allow you
to go with us.
There is a tea house ahead.
Let's go there and have a talk.
Please forgive me.
I behaved like that
just in order to force you
to give up.
However, it seems that you will never
give up.
What tricks do you want to play again?
The sacred book.
The way to Yinxue Village
is so dangerous.
I
don't want you to take these risks.
So I have to do that.
Sending the sacred book
is the mission of Jin's Escort Agency.
It should be me to do it.
Indeed.
I should have got your permission.
Mr Qu
Do you really want to
take her with us
to Yinxue Village
just because of her stubbornness?
It's me who must go to the Yinxue Village.
And it was you
who are so stubborn.
Indeed, it's our fault before.
Since you must
go to the Yinxue Village,
I will escort you to your destination.
Escort?
She was so stupid that
posted the notice everywhere.
Now everyone in this world
knows that sacred book
is in your hand.
What if we
meet bandit on the way?
How about we
disguise ourselves?
It will help us hide it from them.
It's so deserted.
Did the man already die?
It's impossible.
I have to finish this.
Mr Qing Songke
This yard seems to have been abandoned for a long time.
But, how could there be
such new footprints?