English subtitles are available
Bright Time EP16
People often wonder,
why bother trying our hardest
if the result
might not be perfect?
Some say that
it's so that when it's all over,
we can say with a clear conscience
that I really gave it
my all.
No matter how much you love it,
how badly you want it,
and how much you
sweat and toil for it,
your dream may not
necessarily come true.
Youth's not always picture-perfect.
Tomorrow might not bring sunshine, and
you might still fall short in the end,
but you gotta keep
pushing forward,
That's just
how it is when you're young.
Good morning, Ling Dong.
Morning, Xiaohua.
Well...
yesterday's game
was awesome.
But it's a pity that we just needed
one more goal.
Can't believe
he scored
in the last few seconds.
We let our guard down.
So...
I know you're
probably bummed out today,
but as the cheerleader,
I gotta stay positive.
I specially made
the hearty breakfast
to give you a boost.
That's way too much for just me.
This one's for Lan Jinghui.
Thank you.
I think he probably
needs it more than I do.
Thank you, Xiaohua.
Um,
off to class.
Is Jinghui okay?
I don't know.
He's not answering
my calls or texts.
C'mon,
it's just a game, isn't it?
You don't know how important
this is to him.
It was his shot
at the youth team.
Yeah.
To lose it like this,
won't he just be crushed
and never come back from it?
Just make sure when you see him later,
don't say anything
that'll upset him.
What's the secret plan, guys?
Ash Lan!
You did all these?
What happened to you?
Why are you guys so late?
You know what they say,
make the most
of your mornings.
It's time to up our game,
to improve
the quality
of our lives,
and not waste
our youth lounging around.
You don't have a fever, do you?
Listen.
Most of the things
we encounter in life
are not going to be perfect,
but we should move on.
Good boy.
He's right.
Here. I specifically made
this breakfast for you.
It will
fill you up.
Just remember,
we got your back,
no matter
what.
Jinghui.
You alright?
Are you okay?
Jinghui.
Can we go to your place tonight
and game it up?
I'm stuck on a bunch of levels!
Nah, forget it!
Finals are coming up!
I gotta hit the books.
After all, I am
Captain Chenjun!
Are you flexing on me
with your perfect score?
Check this out.
I made a mistake,
and it was
a really silly one.
So what?
Even a
straight A student like me
would make mistakes.
It's the same
for everyone.
You...
What?
Homework.
From yesterday.
After everything that went down,
I didn't feel like doing anything.
Yesterday...
C'mon... alright...
I'm gonna catch up
on them.
Class begins.
Stand up.
Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning. Sit down please.
We all saw
the basketball game results.
It's unfortunate
that we lost to Class 8.
But
we are
not done.
Finals are around the corner.
Gonna let them
win again?
No!
Good.
I've got three stacks
of test papers for you.
I'll pass them
around.
Listen up!
Lan Jinghui made
significant progress
during the last midterm,
proof that study groups work.
So I suggest you
make your own
groups,
help each other out,
and improve together.
Okay?
Yes.
Can we
pick our own crew?
Yeah.
You can decide
for yourselves.
Qingtian.
How about you,
me, and Xiao Xiaohua
form a study group?
I can help you.
Impossible.
Xiaohua is gonna join Ling Dong's crew.
Ma Yiming.
Wanna be in
our study group?
Nah,
I'm joining Mengyu's team.
Qingtian.
Honestly,
a study duo
is the best way to go,
it's really efficient.
Really?
Let's eat.
Okay.
You done?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Okay.
- Xiao Xiaohua. - Xiaohua.
- Take this drumstick. - This is for you.
Why are you...
We want you to join
our study group.
Yeah. Join us.
Daily drumstick on us.
Nah, I'm good.
Here, take some pork too.
Take it.
Take this.
And mine.
It's all yours.
Here, take this too.
Thanks.
Xiaohua said that
she's joining our crew.
Lan Jinghui.
It's for Xiaohua!
What are you doing?
She won't be able to finish all these.
But why did you make
a decision for her?
She hasn't given her word yet.
Right!
Xiaohua, tell me...
Xiaohua, here.
Who's your pick for the group?
Ling Dong
and Lan Jinghui.
You hear that?
She chose it
herself.
You better bounce, quick.
I want it back.
Eat by yourself.
Meet me at
the study room after school, on the dot.
Got it, I'll be there sharp.
Well...
Congrats on our
three-people group!
Congrats!
Brilliant!
Qingtian.
I've never seen you this serious
about your homework before.
It's all because of Chen Luyang.
He's promised to buy me
lots of snacks
if I do my homework well.
You know me,
how can I
resist snacks?
Hi, Doudou.
I think he has
a thing for you.
Nah,
he's just keen on face-saving.
He can't tolerate
Ling Dong having a greater
impact on you
than he has on me.
Do I need to play dumb
to make him
feel better?
Who do you think you are, huh?
I've been doing
really well lately,
I'm in the zone.
Anyway, Xiaohua.
You've been acting
differently these days.
In what way?
Like with
this study group thing,
you declined Lu Yao's offer.
You never would've
done that before,
you're not the "yes" girl
anymore, huh?
Do you think
I'm gonna getting better?
Of course you are.
You're in
Ling Dong's group.
Even Lan Jinghui
is making such rapid progress.
I'm sure you can do it too.
I may not be as brilliant
as Ling Dong,
but I can
keep up and get closer,
little by little.
I trust you.
Back to work.
Coffee time.
There's plenty for all.
Last mini-test
before the final.
Got any toughies?
Feel free to ask me after class.
Tomorrow's the big day,
so keep your confidence up
and bring your A-game.
Time to unleash
my inner beast.
Results are in!
The grades are out!
How did we do?
Did you check for us?
Of course.
Ling Dong is the champ.
Cut the crap,
give me the real deal.
Xiaohua did really well this time.
Significant progress!
Really?
Awesome!
Oh no,
Jinghui's been
trailing behind Xiaohua,
Is he screwed?
You jumped 198 places.
No way.
Ling Dong. How do you know?
Ash Lan really shot up
by 198!
For real?
Seriously?
198?
What? Why?
Give me...
a reason!
What? Why?
He is honest with you.
Ling Dong did the rankings.
C'mon!
How calm you are!
More fun when it's a secret.
Almost had a heart attack there.
Guys,
don't get
too carried away.
This time...
we beat Class 8
and became No. 1
in our grade for the finals!
Okay. Stop.
Class begins.
Stand up.
Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning.
Sit down please.
Thank you.
Ling... Dong?
It's nothing.
I admit,
I was wrong.
We all have unlimited potential,
Do not judge anyone
based on stereotypes.
But
what I said
still stands.
He did make
significant progress this time,
but can you guarantee
that he'll never affect your grades?
I can't.
But why do you
care so much?
You know...
it's good for me actually.
Like you said.
We all have unlimited potential.
I'm gonna keep pushing,
and one day,
I'll be the one on top.
Just wait and see.
Okay.
I will.
Winter break
starts tomorrow.
But all of you
must
complete
your homework well!
No slacking off.
Lastly,
let's go over
the holiday dos and don'ts.
Alright, stop.
Let's call it a day!
See you next semester.
Bye. See you.
Gotta wash this mop.
Qingtian.
You did quite well on your
final exam.
Thanks to your help.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't have done so well.
How can I thank you for this?
Easy,
just treat me to a meal.
Sure.
What do you want to eat?
I've been
studying so hard lately,
I need a good meal.
Great!
Let's go to
the new BBQ restaurant.
I'm so much looking forward to it.
Good idea!
Twenty.
Uncle Wang has more.
They are so cute.
Look at this polar bear
and the penguin...
I like that deer.
I like the polar bear.
This one looks like you, Ma Yiming.
That one looks like you,
see?
Skiing, huh?
What's wrong? You don't know how?
No such thing!
I'm a jack of all trades,
of course I can ski.
Come on, let's get our gear.
I'll show you how good I am.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Aren't you taking photos?
We only have ten pieces of film.
I don't even want her to waste them on me.
Then do it now.
Come on!
I only have 9 pieces now.
Don't worry,
seize the moment.
Aim at Ling Dong and snap a photo.
Let's go.
Xiaohua,
your shoelace is loose.
Let me help you.
Be careful.
Ling Dong,
you haven't even tied yours properly.
Why are you helping her?
She's my apprentice.
Leave it to me.
Do you know how to do it?
Come on, take a break.
I can do it myself.
Sit down.
No need.
My shoelaces...
are loose.
Get away.
- Go away. - Go away.
Why aren't you going away?
Why should I go away?
- Go away! - Why don't you go away?
Look at your big teeth.
Jinghui, I'll go first.
Ma Yiming.
I'm leaving.
Wait for me.
Can you two
make it?
Of course, I can.
Lower your body.
Squat a little more.
Hey,
why are you so clumsy?
That's more like it.
Do you know how to ski?
Mind your own business.
Anyway, I'm better than you.
You two wait here.
Please hold this for me.
I'll be back soon.
Here.
This doesn't suit
my style at all.
Take it.
It looks just like you.
Thanks.
I just saw that everyone else has one.
You should have one too.
Put it on.
Let's go.
Lan Jinghui, get dressed now!
Are you ready, big potato?
Not yet.
Ready!
Remember
to lower
your center of gravity.
Got it.
I'll go first.
Are you really going down?
Xiaohua,
are you scared?
I... Yes, I am.
Master, how about you?
I'm scared too.
Ling Dong! Lan Jinghui is frightened!
No way!
I'm a jack of all trades!
Is it fun?
So much!
Xiaohua.
I wanna go one more round.
Let's go.
Ma Yiming, you...
Why is it Ma Yiming again?
Watch the center of gravity.
Lower the center of gravity.
Get out of the way.
Lan Jinghui.
Are you okay?
My back...
What's wrong?
What happened?
Does it hurt?
Speak slowly.
Take it easy.
It hurts here.
It hurts right here.
What's wrong?
Does it hurt here?
It's like...
Look...
What's...
Lan Jinghui!
Ma Yiming!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Ms. Fang?
Qingtian?
Why are you here?
Hi, Ms. Fang.
Hello.
You guys came skiing too?
Yes, we two
and Lan Jinghui,
Ling Dong, and Xiao Xiaohua,
came together.
Where are
the other three?
They are playing over there.
How's your skiing?
Good.
Not bad.
Ms. Fang,
is this your boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
No, this is...
A friend.
We won't bother you then.
Alright.
We'll go have fun now.
- Okay. - Okay.
We're leaving. Bye.
Bye.
Take care and have fun.
Let's go, my friend.
Goodbye.
Bye.
What happened?
Take off your glasses.
It's inconvenient.
Why do you say so?
Ma Yiming!
Chen Luyang? What a coincidence!
I come to ski.
You just got here?
It's so nice to meet you here.
Can you ski?
Not really.
Come on, I'll teach you!
Thank you for what you've done in school.
Sounds cool.
Let's go.
Go.
Ling Dong,
Lan Jinghui,
let's take a picture together.
Sure.
Jinghui,
I just saw Ms. Fang
and her boyfriend.
Wait a bit,
they might come over soon.
Why are you so nosy?
Leave them alone.
I just happened to run into them,
alright?
I didn't mean to...
Hi, Ms. Fang.
How many times are you guys
going to pull this prank?
Don't act like three idiots,
okay?
Hello, idiot.
Hi.
Hello, Ms. Fang.
Where's your boyfriend?
What boyfriend?
It's not easy to get a break.
Then, I still run into you guys.
He's...
just a friend.
Just a friend!
Alright, stop!
Are you
gonna take a picture?
Yeah.
I'll do it for you.
Thank you.
Alright, I'll give you
a countdown.
Okay.
Here we go.
3, 2, 1!
Cheese.
Perfect.
Thank you, Ms. Fang.
Thank you so much.
Crispy outside,
and juicy inside.
It's the grilled sausage I like.
Glad you like it.
Xiaohua!
Chen Luyang?
- Why are you here? - Why are you here?
The ski resort
isn't owned by your family.
Why can't I be here?
It's really great to have so many here!
We can have a meal together later.
Sure.
I'm starving.
Let's
go to Mr. Lan's place.
Wait.
Mr. Lan?
Well...
Ma Yiming is saying that...
Actually, the thing is...
Does that man look like
your dad?
C'mon,
he is!
It's pretty cold here.
Yeah.
My boy, do you feel cold?
Have fun?
You must be tired.
I reserved a table
at the restaurant nearby.
Let's go eat!
That's cool!
We're starving!
Let's eat together.
Come on, dinner time.
Let's go.
Let's change clothes first.
Time to eat.
Don't just sit there.
Just do it.
The food will get cold soon.
Make yourself at home.
Do it!
Thank you, Mr. Lan.
You're welcome.
If you want anything else,
just
let me know.
Just tell him what you want, okay?
You are
Jinghui's best friends.
I'm sure
he's troubled you often.
I appreciate
your kindness.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Ling Dong,
I especially wanna thank you
for helping Jinghui
achieve good grades.
I'm flattered.
He worked hard himself.
I didn't do much.
Alright, stop chatting.
It's dinner time.
Right, do it.
By the way,
I have a question for you.
Since you're gonna in Grade 12,
what are your plans
for the future?
Play professional basketball.
Amazing.
I want to be a food blogger
and try all kinds of food.
That's great.
To be admitted by the Department
of Computer Science at Jing University.
That's tough, and you might go bald.
Really?
Should I change a major then?
You'll have to wear a wig in the future.
Ling Dong,
is your goal
also Jing University?
But I'm fond of physics.
Physics?
I heard it demands a pretty high score.
Go for it!
Thank you.
I envy you guys with good grades.
You can choose whatever you want.
What about you, Xiaohua?
I...
haven't decided yet.
I don't think Jinghui has decided.
But no worries,
I've arranged everything
for you to study abroad.
That's a really good university.
Besides,
an IELTS tutor
is also prepared.
You could use the winter break
to improve your English
and prepare for
studying abroad next semester.
Dad,
you've got it all set up?
Why didn't you
ask for my opinion?
Well...
haven't I ever
listened to your opinion?
See,
I transferred you to Chenjun
as you wish,
but you didn't make a name for yourself
in basketball.
Now,
studying abroad
is the best choice for you.
But I don't want it.
Then,
what do you want to do?
I...
I'm aiming at Jing University, too!
When Lan Jinghui said
he wanna go to Jing University,
we're all surprised.
We didn't know if he just said it on a whim
or had long planned it.
Perhaps it was a dream
he buried deep in his heart
but never had the courage
to say out loud.
Hello.
I'm here already.
Yeah.
I don't see any of you.
Hello?
Where am I going to be taken?
Shut up,
you'll know it later.
This is kidnapping!
Skiing, huh?