English subtitles are available
Bright Time EP25
Everyone, what you have in front of you is
the college application preference form.
As per our school's custom,
you can all choose the university
that you aspire to attend.
And then,
you should focus on this goal
and redouble your efforts.
Ms. Fang,
when do we need to submit it?
There's no hurry.
However,
I do hope that all of you
will think it over carefully at home,
fill it out based on your capabilities,
and then submit it
to the class rep.
They will be posted by next Monday.
That'll be all.
I'm aiming for Jing University!
That's wishful thinking!
Mom.
Hey,
Dong, welcome back.
Yeah, I'm back.
Mom, come on,
I'll take care of it.
It's OK.
Why don't you
watch some TV for now?
Dinner will be
ready shortly.
Dong, wash your hands and eat.
What are you...
Er...
Mom,
what's happening?
Are you not feeling well again?
Look at you,
so young
yet always so inquisitive.
It's nothing serious.
It might just be a slight cold
from changing season.
It's truly nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Then why didn't you tell me?
If I had told you,
you would have asked more questions.
It's really nothing.
Really?
Honestly, it's nothing.
I know my own health
better than anyone.
Don't fret.
Alright, Mom,
I'll be home early for the next few days.
I'll take care of whatever
needs to be done at home.
You just take a break.
Got it, alright.
Look at you,
you're so young
yet you worry so much.
Come on,
let's eat.
Look,
what delicious dishes Mom has made?
Your favorite,
tomato and scrambled eggs.
Come on, sit down,
let's eat.
I...I'm scared...
What's there to be scared of?
Go ahead and check.
You check it.
No, you check it.
Fine, I'll do it.
What's the matter?
I didn't pass, did I?
Why is it this score?
I knew it, I definitely...
You passed.
I passed...
I passed?
You've scored
over 30 points above the cut-off score.
I've always said,
you could do it.
Does this mean
I am able to apply to Jing University?
Yes!
Halt!
Alright.
To celebrate Xiao Xiaohua's
success in the exam
and the first step on her great journey,
let's go out and
celebrate after school tonight.
Absolutely!
Let's hit up a spicy pot place!
Spicy hot pot!
Spicy pot!
Hot pot!
We'll have both.
You guys go have fun tonight.
I've got other plans.
Why is it that at times like this,
you always have to act
like a top student?
Are you planning to
sneak off home to hit the books?
Are you
trying to get ahead of us?
I'm telling you, it's not happening!
No,
I do need to take care of something.
Come on,
how long
can dinner take?
It's OK, it's OK.
I need to head home early today too.
To share the good news with my parents.
Let's do it next time.
Alright then.
Let's hooray for it one more time!
Look at this kid, so cute.
Look, look, impressive, right?
Reminds me of you when you were younger.
Look at her, how adorable.
When I was young,
I was just as adorable.
You were way cuter than her.
Look, so adorable.
Indeed.
It takes me back to my childhood.
Mr. Xiao Datu,
Mrs. Guo Ying,
your daughter
has an important announcement to make.
Move aside, move aside.
We're just getting to the good part.
Come on, move.
Hey!
Is the show more important,
or is your daughter more important?
Your daughter passed her exam.
I scored 30 points above the pass mark.
Oh.
Is that it?
That's it?
Just that?
That's your reaction?
What else?
Alright, go back to your room and rest.
Don't you think that passing the art tests
means you can skip the academic exams.
Don't interrupt our TV time.
Seriously.
Where were we?
So funny!
Yeah!
Oh dear.
Our daughter,
she might be so touched that she's crying.
It's very likely.
We artists do
have deep emotions.
When did you prepare all this?
This afternoon.
Your mom checked your results,
and she took me to buy all these.
Look!
She's never bought me
such expensive paints before,
nor brushes!
Can you compare with our daughter?
Our daughter is so talented.
Unlike you, neglecting your duties.
Mom,
I'm so happy you support me
in chasing my dream.
Sweetie,
I've been doing a lot of thinking lately.
You have a long journey ahead,
and there's so much you can do.
So,
your dad and I just want you to be happy.
Doing what you love
is the most blissful thing.
We have our limitations.
The rest is up to you.
Dad, mom,
I promise I'll work hard
and not disappoint you.
I love rainy days.
The umbrellas of different colors
are like little dancing figures.
Rain and hoops, a perfect match.
How do you play basketball on a rainy day?
There's indoor basketball.
Basketball gym?
Mom,
I've prepared breakfast.
I'm heading to school now.
Mom.
Mom?
Mom, what's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
Stay still, I'll grab your meds.
I'm fine now.
I'm fine.
I just got up
too fast earlier
and felt a bit dizzy.
It might be low blood pressure.
I feel much better now.
No, Mom,
please listen to me.
I'm going to take the day off today,
and I'll take you to the hospital.
I've already told you, I'm fine.
Look, I am
feeling quite good now, right?
You should go to school today.
We'll go for a check-up this weekend.
Don't be late today.
Go to school, come on.
I'm fine.
I'll be all right soon.
Then...
Don't go to work today.
Just take a day off.
Call me if you need anything.
OK, I promise you.
Go on, don't be late for school.
Make sure to call me
if anything happens.
OK, just go.
Well, I'm off then.
Go on, go on.
Go.
Rest up, OK?
Don't worry.
Off you go.
Gosh, so many!
What schools are these?
These are all prestigious.
Rousi, which school are you applying?
Me?
I don't want to go too far from home.
How about Rong University?
Rong University?
That one is pretty good too.
Many majors demand high entry.
Let's give our best shot!
Yes!
Xiaohua, you're so impressive!
Aiming for Jing University's art program.
God!
Maybe she was just filling it out for fun.
Did you see Lan Jinghui
also chose Jing University?
You think I can't make it, Liu Shu?
Jing University isn't
just any university.
If it were that easy,
would it still be Jing University?
You're really concerned about me, huh?
How odd.
Odd about what?
Ling Dong, he...
Ling Dong.
That geek didn't fill it out.
Where is he?
Why didn't he fill it out?
He didn't put any school in there.
He hasn't filled it out yet.
It makes no difference if he fills it out.
Hello?
Auntie Ma,
is my mom with you?
No.
Your mom isn't with me.
Is there a problem?
No, no, it's nothing.
Got it.
Next class is about to start.
Where are you off to?
I've got to take care of something.
Could you let the teacher know about it?
What's so urgent?
Mom.
Mom!
Mom, what's wrong?
Mom. Mom!
Mom! Mom!
How long has she been unconscious?
I'm not exactly sure.
We need to conduct
further tests.
Take it easy.
Please wait outside.
Mom.
Why hasn't Dad come out yet?
Why did you come?
You left in such a rush.
I was worried.
Don't worry,
she will be fine.
Thank you.
Doctor, how is she doing?
Thankfully, you got her here in time.
She's out of danger now.
But,
we do suggest
she stays in for observation for a while.
Her condition is mainly
due to excessive fatigue.
She needs to rest more regularly,
OK?
OK.
You're her son, right?
Please go complete the admission process.
Alright, that's it.
OK, OK.
Thank you, doctor.
Thanks, doctor.
No problem.
So typically,
I just need to
pay and
pick up the meds, and that's it,
right?
Yes.
Thank you.
No problem.
You're alright?
I'm fine.
You should go back to school.
No way.
Just leave you here by yourself?
I've already had Xiao Xiaohua
request leave for me.
If I go back now,
wouldn't that be wasting the leave?
Zhang Li's family member,
come here, sign this.
You sign it.
It's the prescription pick-up slip, right?
I'll get the medicine.
Where's the pharmacy?
Hello, I need to pick up some medicine.
This is window number three, right?
It's not your turn yet, wait for yours.
Hello.
You're missing these two.
Go to the Chinese medicine section.
Hello, could you please tell me
where to pick up these two items?
Go straight
down the hall,
then make a left,
and you'll see a white door.
Inside is the place.
Got it, thank you.
Where is it, exactly?
Is this where I pick up this item?
Let me see.
Hold on.
Young man,
you're all over the place.
Haven't you picked up meds before?
Who comes to the hospital every day?
Here, your medicine.
Thank you, doctor.
Your mother,
due to long-term overexertion
and not resting properly,
has suffered heart muscle damage.
If you had been any delayed,
it could have been life-threatening.
Hey,
why are you still here?
Ah.
You said you were going to stay the night.
I'll stay with you.
If you're tired,
you can take a break.
We can take turns.
It's cool.
I can manage on my own.
Come on,
have a seat.
Here are the meds.
What about these?
How come I didn't see this one?
It must have been overlooked.
I'll get it now.
Hold on.
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
Are you sure?
I remember it being on the other side.
We're already here.
Well done.
I looked everywhere
to find this place.
It's surprisingly close.
My mom's health
has always been fragile,
so besides home and school,
the hospital is the place
I frequent the most.
How's she?
You should rest a bit. I'll keep watch.
Lan Jinghui!
Apprentice,
what brings you here?
Ling Dong's mom fell sick.
I'm here to pay her a visit.
My mom made this chicken soup with love,
especially for her.
Your mom doesn't think
you're dating us anymore, does she?
What are you talking about?
Our relationship, of course.
That's old news.
It's been put to rest a long time ago.
It ended that soon?
What, what, what
are you doing here?
Come on, let's go.
Here, Mom.
I feel a lot better now.
Do you?
I feel particularly lively today.
That's great.
This is the freshest batch.
Who's here?
- Hello, auntie. - Hello, auntie.
Your classmates have come.
This is the chicken soup my mom made.
Really good.
Thank you so much.
Thanks for coming
to visit me.
You've brought so much stuff.
You should focus on your studies.
No worries,
it's the weekend today.
Have you finished your homework?
All done, finished it a while ago.
Doctor.
- Doctor. - Doctor.
Doctor Zhang.
You guys go on.
I'll go wash some fruit.
You are recovering nicely.
We'll observe for a couple more days.
If there's no issue,
and once the report is out,
you can go home.
Thank you.
Doctor,
is it possible to leave a few days early?
My son's birthday is coming up,
and I'd like to be at home with him.
OK,
but remember,
you still need to recuperate at home.
OK.
Thank you, doctor.
Told you so, I could get discharged.
Auntie,
go ahead and
try this soup while it's warm.
Thank you.
Ling Dong, are you holding up OK?
Get plenty of rest these days.
I might as well
stay and keep you company.
It's fine.
I'm fine on my own.
You should head back soon.
Don't worry,
I'll keep you up to date with
homework and notes
while you're away from school.
He's going to be here
taking care of her mom.
He won't have time for notes and homework.
That's right.
Don't listen to him.
Just give them to me.
Then...
Alright then, go ahead.
I need to go upstairs.
Alright, call us if you need anything.
Goodbye.
Xiaohua,
you've done so many paintings.
I had a late start compared to others,
so of course, I have to spend more time
practicing.
What's with the kettle here?
This is a relic from my grandma's time.
Where did you find this?
Just throw it away.
No, no, no!
This is my kettle of fortune.
An old-fashioned kettle like this.
This is quite obscure, isn't it?
In this day and age,
who still uses such a thing?
This is...
A kettle.
Will the exam include something like this?
It's all about predicting, right?
Just practice with everything you've got.
You can't overlook
any possibility.
Please be quiet now.
The exam duration is three hours.
Guys, please manage your time wisely.
Students,
our sketching topic this time
is "Rainy Day."
Depict the dynamics of three characters.
Jing University,
we're coming for you!
What?
He actually guessed the topic right?
He must have stumbled upon it by luck.
Even if it was luck,
he still got it right.
I'm actually thankful to him this time.
Who would have thought that Duncie
could be of use at a crucial moment?
Do you think he can
guess the final exams too?
Are you kidding?
For final exam predictions,
obviously, we turn to Ling Dong.
Ling Dong may be talented,
but Dingdang's knack for predictions
is also remarkable.
Dingdang?
Who's Dingdang?
I'm not telling you!
What's with you,
always leaving things half-said?
I'm not telling you!
I'm not telling you.
Come on, spill it!