[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP08]
The more fiercely you fight,
the more peaceful I feel.
[Where are you going?]
[Jia is sick]
[and wants his father there with him.]
Let go!
You always use
Jia as an excuse.
Do you think I can't tell?
I won't allow you
to go to your mistress!
You shrew!
Jealous shrew!
[You live off me and]
[still have the nerve to be rude to me?]
[Stop!]
[Get lost.]
What are you doing?
[That's Lady Shen.]
You shrew,
this isn't over.
Move!
Go away now.
Go back to your business.
Yijiao.
What are you doing here?
Are you here only to laugh at me?
I...
How could I?
You married well
so you came here to flaunt it in my face?
I don't need your pity!
Go away.
[Yan Xing, clerk of Ministry of Justice.]
[Your Majesty,]
Lady Shen is here.
Greetings to Your Majesty.
Get up.
[Lady Shen, you've made great
contributions to the Buddha case.]
I really want to give you a reward.
But I couldn't
[come up with anything.]
So tell me yourself,
what reward do you want?
Your Majesty,
I don't want a reward.
[However, I humbly]
request a favor from Your Majesty.
Sure.
Let me hear it.
I wish for Your Majesty
to address me as Clerk Yan
instead of Lady Shen.
You are very young and
already have such insight and ambition.
That's a good thing.
My court values talent and ability,
regardless of gender.
This way, women, naturally,
can forge their own path
through their own skills,
without relying on their husbands.
I'll allow it.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
If I might speak frankly,
although there are female clerks in
all the six ministries, most of them
are confined to cleaning and organizing.
For instance, at the Ministry of Justice,
the female clerks aren't allowed to conduct
investigations with the male clerks.
Look,
I am a woman as well.
[I am well aware of]
[the hardships]
[a woman must endure]
to be seen as equal to a man.
If I can
sit in this position,
then a female official
can surely conduct investigations.
[Lady Xu,]
write up a decree for me:
From now on,
female officials in all six ministries
will have the same rights
as male officials.
Her Highness is truly wise.
Clerk Yan,
from now on,
you'll
have the freedom to investigate cases
just like your male peers.
Thank you, your majesty.
[Xing.]
Xiangren.
Is the Chief Clerk here?
The Chief Clerk isn't well these days,
he's on leave at home.
Is there anything urgent?
It's nothing urgent,
just very shocking.
What do you mean?
Regarding the
chronic poisoning of Liang Chenzhong,
Didn't you ask me to investigate the source
of the Guanyin poison from those near him?
I followed up on it.
Guess who did I chase it to?
It led me to Rong Zhui,
the owner of Tongming Pavilion.
Stop!
Stop resisting.
Toxic plant Guanyin?
Take her away.
Move.
[I brought some supplements for your mom,]
there's some for you as well.
Looks like you've had a rough time in jail
and lost quite a bit of weight.
Your support is much appreciated, Shen Du.
I didn't
have a tough time with the prison guards.
[And it was quiet in the prison,]
giving me time to come up with
many ideas for improving siege equipment.
I know
it was foolish of me to turn myself in.
But my mother has been through so much,
[I could not allow her]
[to endure any more suffering.]
I really need to thank you
for finding out the truth
and clearing my family's name.
The Buddha's case may be closed,
but we still haven't found who was behind
the toxic plant Guanyin poisoning.
Your family's name
is not cleared yet.
So...
So you'll still arrest my mother?
[Why are you arresting me?]
[Take him away.]
[Chief Shen,]
Xu Xiangren and Lady Shen
arrested Liang Jiren.
They went to Tongming Pavilion?
Yes.
Before that,
they already arrested the owner of
Tongming Pavilion, Rong Zhui.
They are fast.
Should I bring some men
and stop them?
Why?
She's just been granted authority to
investigate, let her show off for a bit.
Yes, Sir.
Lord Liang,
[recently,]
I have frequently visited your family.
Besides Her Highness's task on me,
I also had my own agendas.
But now,
everything has been clarified.
And the culprits
have been captured by someone else.
Like the saying goes, the Emperor's 9 sons
are each different.
The toxic plant Guanyin poisoning has
nothing to do with you and your mother.
The second branch of the Liang family has
nothing to do with what the first branch did.
Focus on your own business.
Don't let
Her Highness's expectations down.
It was you who poisoned Liang Chenzhong
with the toxic plant Guanyin?
That's right.
It was me.
His eldest son
is nothing but a scoundrel.
If he died,
sooner or later,
he would have killed his father.
Besides, I am already
carrying his father's child.
Of course I had to think about the future.
[My lord,]
this way please.
There are some new dancers.
Would you like me to call them over
for you to pick?
Great.
Bravo!
Lord Liang,
I have a new beauty
for you.
Lan,
come over.
[Beautiful!]
-Come here.
-My lord.
Lord Liang,
please have some tea.
[I had no other choice.]
That scoundrel
either gambled
or wasted money in pleasure houses.
[When he's out of money,]
[he would come to me to threat]
for more.
He almost took everything we had.
[Otherwise,]
[I wouldn't have been forced to do this.]
Moreover,
I have
a child on the way.
Shouldn't I have to
think about him as well?
So,
because Rong Zhui was carrying his child,
he decided
to abandon his eldest son
heartlessly.
Yeah.
I have been a Delinquent for a long time
and have seen all kinds of cases.
But a father
deliberately poisoning his own son
is truly unheard of.
Who would have thought it.
A father would hurt his own son.
The human
is truly the most mysterious thing.
Chief Shen.
why are you here?
Lord Liang, did you forget?
The Buddha case
was entrusted entirely to me
by Her Highness.
[You, on the other hand, have truly]
shocked me with your ruthless method.
If I had any other choice,
I wouldn't have resorted to this.
I really had no choice.
They say even beasts look after their young.
How come with you,
you simply brushed it off with
'I had no choice'.
Chief Shen,
there's no need to mock me.
I did try to murder my son.
But you,
have turned in your father.
[We are essentially the same, aren't we?]
Back then, among the various crimes
my father was charged with,
one was the theft
of a weapon schematic
and leaking it to an enemy nation.
That schematic was drawn
by none other than your brother.
I was wondering
why you were always
hanging out with my foolish nephew.
I thought it was out of mutual respect,
that you were truly
close friends.
Turns out,
it was because you suspected our family.
My lady,
why did you come?
What are you doing here at this hour?
I'm here to see you.
[Did anyone see you?]
[I don't know.]
We'll get into big trouble if anyone sees us.
[That's the least of our concerns now.]
Your son
must have known something.
That's why you wanted to kill him,
to silence him.
Chief Shen,
if you had discovered anything,
you probably
wouldn't be here asking me.
If this matter
reaches Her Highness,
I
will claim to know nothing.
So that means,
your concern
for your unborn child
must be fake.
If,
you promise me
to look after my unborn son in the future,
I am willing to recall what happened.
Perhaps,
I can remember something.
You are in no position
to negotiate with me.
Have you ever heard of the 'Cui Zhe'
used by the Imperial Guard(IG)?
Each cut
draws exactly
36 drops of blood.
Over three days,
the convict is cut 360 times
without dying.
Shen Du,
I'm a court official.
I was involved in an attempted filicide.
But,
but I was an accomplice.
I don't merit a death sentence.
You.
Don't... Don't be reckless.
Reckless?
Lord Liang,
why do you think
they call me the White Death then?
Once you are in the IG,
don't expect to walk out of here alive.
You...
How, how dare you?
This is the first cut.
I have no other plans these days.
I'll just keep you company for three days.
I'll tell you.
I was drunk, and accidentally
leaked my brother's weapon schematic.
[Afterward,]
[I was too afraid to admit it.]
Your father and my brother
were very close at that time.
[Moreover,]
[he was already convicted of treason.]
So I just went with the flow
and placed the blame on him.
Chenzhong learned about this
by chance and
[has since been extorting me for money.]
I couldn't take it anymore.
I couldn't take it anymore!
[Chief Shen,]
[your father]
was already found guilty of treason.
[With concrete evidence,]
[even without this charge,]
his conviction would still stand.
It was really you.
[Then I'll overturn the convictions]
[one by one.]
[I do not seek fame in history but]
only wish to be true to my conscience
and to the people.
I won't align myself with your corrupt ways.
Absolutely not.
[Don't blame me for not warning you.]
Upright trees are cut down first,
Clean wells are drained first.
Should you refuse to ally with me,
you would meet your end.
You wouldn't stand a chance.
[As a servant of the emperor, it's my]
duty to address His Majesty's concerns.
I am prepared to face death in doing so.
[With the divine will of Heaven and time,]
[I command you:]
court official Shen Bingzhu had
[colluded with the enemy,]
[burnt our military supplies,]
[leaked weapon schematic,]
[colluded with foreign forces]
[and aided the enemy.]
[These crimes are punishable by death.]
[The male family members will be executed,]
[the women and children will be imprisoned.]
[This will be made known to all.]
Father,
all these years,
I've never given up on seeking justice for
the many lives lost in the Shen family.
But who was that woman?
I have never had a clue.
Was she friend or foe?
No matter what,
today,
I can at least prove that
you were framed for the weapon schematic,
Father, rest assured.
I will find that woman
someday.
I will find
the remaining evidence
piece by piece.
[Chief Shen.]
Chief Shen.
The celebration banquet of the Delinquents
and the Ministry of Justice is tonight.
What's it to do with me?
My lord,
you are right!
[Here, here, here.]
[Here. Good work!]
[Finish this one.]
[I'll pour you another one.]
[Let's get hammered!]
Can you drink or not?
Let's go over there.
Let's go.
Here, Meng,
I'll drink to you.
Let's eat.
Good work!
Here, drink.
I almost forgot.
Your letter.
It was sent to the Ministry of Justice.
What made you so happy?
Chichi is coming to Xiang'an.
She wants to see me.
That's great!
I've heard you talking about
this Chichi
so many times.
Back then the Ministry of Justice received
so many self-recommendation letters.
Only you were foolish enough
to read each one carefully.
I even made fun of you.
Who would've thought that
you'd actually find such a reliable friend.
I envy you so much!
I still remember
the first letter
she sent from Jiangnan,
with golden floral decorations,
a delightful fragrance
and even flower petals inside the envelope.
I'm so envious!
I'd really like to meet
such a talented
young woman.
She must be very beautiful.
I'm sorry.
She only asked to see me.
I'm so angry.
They can really drink.
Let's eat then. Let's have some grapes.
Here.
Xing,
here.
I really admire
your investigative skills.
[This drink]
is to you.
Xiangren,
I don't really drink.
[That's no problem.]
[You'll learn.]
You'll slowly understand
the mysteries of wine.
Here.
I advise you to behave yourself.
Do you want to be caught again?
Chief Shen.
Shen Du,
why are you here?
Chief Shen,
have a seat.
Did I say I wouldn't come?
Chief Shen.
Chief Shen,
what an honor
having you here.
Here's to you.
Here, here.
[Here, Chief Shen,]
[I'll drink to you.]
Who would've thought,
Chief Shen can really drink.
Chief Shen,
I'll drink to you.
Here.
What kind of 'can really drink' is this?
I'm not drunk.
I'm very fine.
Sure, sure, sure.
You're very fine. You're very fine.
If you don't believe me,
get someone to fight me.
Well,
I do have someone in mind
who could use a good beating.
Let's go.
Farewell to Chief Shen.
Be careful.
Jinglin,
the light.
What light?
Who would carry a lantern
to beat someone up?
Let's go.
Beat someone up?
Yes.
But we can't do without the light.
Of course we can.
Look at me.
I'll be your light.
Let's go, let's go.
Jinglin, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
C'mon.
Be careful.
Xing, take care!
Farewell to Chief Shen.
Be careful.
-Be careful.
-Chuichui,
let's go. Let's go drink some more.
[Who wants to drink with you?]
[I want to eat.]
Be careful.
Jinglin,
come hold
Chief Shen.
He's too heavy.
Let's go.
Chief Shen, watch the stairs.
Slow down.
Another stair.
And up, and up, and up.
Stand still.
Be careful.
[Who's there?]
[Come out!]
Who's there?
Wait for me here.
I'm going to beat him up.
I'll go.
Fine, fine, fine.
You go, you go.
[Who's there? Who are you?]
[Come out!]
He's really drunk.
[Who's there?]
[Who?]
What do you want?
[Only those who were unfaithful]
[were killed in the Buddha’s case.]
That many disloyal men and women
were buried at Ximing Temple.
[Yet you still dare to lust after mistress]
and neglect your wife and children?
[This]
is only a warning.
If there's a next time,
I'll take out your heart
and bury it in the ground!
[I' won't do it again.]
I' will never do it again.
[There won't be a next time.]
So this is what the White death
is like drunk.
Take your 'sober' Chief
back to the residence.
Let's go.
Be careful. Let's go.
Be careful.
Who was it?
Who was this ruthless?
Who knew the mighty White Death
can't hold his liquor.
What happened to all your usual prowess?
It would be easier
to carry a body than you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[It's nothing to]
bring back home my drunk roommate.
No need to thank me.
The Detention Center.
So you knew.
I thought you didn't remember anymore.
Are you okay?
This is from
a newly opened candied fruits store.
[Who's there?]
I should go now.
[I'll bring back a comb tomorrow.]
[This is really good.]
[Try some.]
Let her go.
-Let go!
-Let her go!
[-Let her go!]
[-Du!]
Let her go!
I will find a way
to get you out!
Wait for me!
[Lady Xu,]
thank you.
Shen Du!
Shen Du,
you annoying little devil!
[Morning, my lady.]
[My lady, breakfast is served.]
You...
Morning.
[I misbehaved last night after drinking.]
No problem.
Last night...
It's okay.
[Xing!]
Xing!
Qi Yeyun?
Xing,
what happened to your forehead?
Who hurt you?
Was it you?
Did you hit my sister?
No, he didn't.
I had a bit too much to drink last night
and bumped my head.
By the way,
what are you here for?
I'm here to bring something to you
for my lady.
Your lady?
Yeah, Lu Chuichui.
This is the Hundred Flowers Essence
she has treasured for many years.
Brew it in water.
It can help with the hangover headache.
She specifically asked me to bring it.
Chuichui is so thoughtful.
But when did you join the Lu family?
The last clerk at the Lu's Pawnshop
was fired for talking too much.
So now I'm their new clerk.
I thought,
since you don't want to take me
as your apprentice yet,
and I'm too young to apply
for a position in the Ministry of Justice,
working as a clerk at your friend's
family shop
allows me to be closer to you.
If you keep talking so much,
I think you are about to
follow the last clerk's suit.
How could that be?
I only talk this much
in front of my sister.
Zhong,
so you just let anyone in now.
Who let this
boy in?
[First of June.]
[The Hu cake was too hard at breakfast,]
[Du was furious.]
[Second of June.]
[Dinner was pagoda tree leaf cold salad,]
[Du had three serves.]
[Third of June.]
[The douhua was too salty at breakfast,]
[Du was furious.]
[Fourth of June.]
[There was no more candied fruits,]
[Du was furious.]
Xing,
do you
take me as a three year old?
My lord.
Is everything at Yingzhou taken care of?
Yes, my lord.
They also sent their accounts.
[This year's revenue is nearly 30.000.]
Keep this a secret.
Be sure not to mention this
even to Prince Xian.
My lord, rest assured.
This matter
will remain completely confidential.
[Moreover,]
[I've also]
[taken care of the families]
[who support the Emperor.]
Now that they've been compensated,
they will surely
keep their mouths shut.
Nothing will go wrong.
Liang Jiren
tends to talk too much.
Her Highness
might secretly exile him this time.
Find a chance
to shut him up for good.
He knows too much.
[Cheng Cai.]
[Here.]
[Zhang Xinliang.]
[Song...]
Isn't this Lady Shen?
[What happened?]
Lady Shen
has come personally to report.
Yan Xing.
Here.
How did you
get all these injuries?
I accidentally fell.