[I won't work overtime today]
[Episode 12]
Are you okay
I'm fine
How
You want me to press the elevator again
No need
I want to press
Wait a minute
I, I didn't see anything
Ya Yahan
What are you doing here
Don't you go in
I'll go in
Mr. Li
Here's your snack coffee
And newspapers
I brought you all at once
So that we
Improvement of work efficiency
If there's nothing else
I'm leaving first
Jiaojiao
Why are you doing it to me again
This attitude
Last night
You're obviously not like this
Mr. Li
Let me report it to you
Today's schedule
Today at 10:15
He Jiaojiao
Look me in the eye
What exactly do you want
Mr. Li
I can't drink
I get drunk when I drink
When you get drunk, you can't remember anything
If I offend you
Please forgive me
What do you mean is
You forgot again
Yes
I
I'll leave you the schedule here
I have work to go first
She just doesn't want to be responsible for me
This scumbag
I didn't let one of my own
The habit of blocking my wine
[He Mingyue He Mingyue]
[How can you do such a thing]
[But it must have scared him out]
[He's nothing more than that]
Sister Jiaojiao
What are you doing? Sneaking around
I
What's wrong
If you have nothing to do, you want to act coquettish with me
That's the one
I
I have a girl I like
Whenever I'm near her
My face will be red
My ears will get hot
My breathing will get short
My heart will speed up, too
I'm gonna become a
Big uncontrolled idiot
Is it Wei Yahan
Why did you just say it like that
Not
How do you know
Normal
You liked her in your previous life
It's pretty good
Come on, work hard
You can do it
That
Then do you think I
Is it whimsical
Like someone
Be brave enough to tell her
Yahan
Yahanme
Don't rush and talk slowly
Wei Yahan, I like you
I want to be responsible for you
Responsible for what
Take responsibility for your first kiss
How do you know
That was my first kiss
Then the second one
Third
M-th 1
I want to be responsible for you anyway
Although I don't have any money
And no career
He looks pretty good, too
It's not ugly, is it
No car, no house
There is no bright future
But
But I have this
What are you laughing at
I I have more here I
You got that button off of your clothes
I like you Wei Yahan
I like you
I I
This is my second kiss
You're also responsible
Answer the phone
Mr. Li
[I'm already on the plane]
[Take off in five minutes.]
You don't have to worry about me
Don't worry
[Stop acting]
I'm not asking you to come back as an assistant
Then I'm relieved
[Don't have time to talk to you]
Let me ask you
I have a friend
[etc. etc.]
You you have no friends
Your friend is yourself
You close
You shut up
[Hey hey hey]
I have A friend A
He was kissed by B
But what about this B
She didn't admit to kissing A
And the attitude towards A
And very cold
You say my friend
What should I do
Mr. Li
I didn't expect you to be such a scumbag
I told you it wasn't me
Promise
Do you want to fly straight to Africa
[No, no, no, it's not Mr. Li]
Then that's you being scum
Which female hero is it
Tell me about it
Say the solution
If you dare to say more nonsense
I promise
Once you go, don't think about coming back
[Don't, don't, don't]
That solution
Let me think about the solution
Usually playing with feelings like this
Irresponsible circumstances
[Often can]
[By forcing the palace to be superior]
[For example, you said you were pregnant]
Fuck the company pulling banners
[Speaking on a loudspeaker]
[etc. etc.]
[How about it]
He Jiaojiao
He Jiaojiao, come out
You have the ability to play with my feelings
Why don't you come out
He Jiaojiao He Jiaojiao
He Jiaojiao, come out He Jiaojiao
He Jiaojiao, come out
Come out
Promise
[Fly to Africa]
[Don't come back]
I fly to Africa
I'm out and I'm still talking to you
Li Su
What is Assistant He doing here
I have something to do with you
What is it
What happened last night
I remember
Remembered
Isn't it just a kiss
Then Assistant He is really
A man of unrestrained character
He Jiaojiao
Do you like me
I really like you
Sorry to interrupt
It's so disgusting
I couldn't hold back
When did you come
I came at the beginning
But you
Compare investment
So what do you have to do
I'm here to quit my job
What
Congratulations
Finally decided to find myself
Because I lost
Continue to stay in this company
Reasons and goals
What do you mean
Li Su, you will always be high above you
Get used to others circling you
You won't understand
Just never understand
Mr. Li, please speak your mouth first
I'm going to talk to Mr. Wei alone
Bye-bye go
Go!
Let's give his company first
I'm sorry, Mr. Li
The resignation application just now
I was impulsive
I have to think about it in the future
Continue to work for this company
So
You two
What the hell did you just say
-this is our girl's secret
This company also counts
Have you worked hard
I heard you started college
I followed Li Su to start a business
Before I mistakenly thought
I like him myself
But now I understand
That was just forced on me
It's just a habit
Without this reason
I really can't find anything
Continue to strive for the goal
Have you ever thought about it
Let's take over the company
We
To us
Are you gonna
What's wrong with it
All along
I really appreciate it
Your talents and abilities
Soon I'll show you, too
My sincerity and strength
So don't you think it's interesting
This is indeed
Something worth challenging
You decided to help me
Can
But I have another problem
Since we decided to cooperate
Then between the two of us
Be honest
Your feelings for Li Su
Is it true
What do you think
Okay, then I'll go first
Mr. Li, I'm leaving first too
I like you
I like you too
If time
Can really stay
It would be fine at that moment
Maybe I'm really doing something wrong
But you succeeded
Although you leave
But it took his heart away
Bright moon
Wake up quickly
I was wrong
I really know I'm wrong
From beginning to end
You are the only one I love
The emperor invites me to dinner
Take it down, I can't eat it
Your Majesty, please eat some
I'm afraid of you if I don't eat my slave
Hurt the dragon's body
Taiyuan Hospital researched it
Did you find out how to treat the queen
Reply to the emperor
The imperial doctors in the Imperial Hospital said
Said it would take a while
A bunch of waste
Pass the order down
If there is no way within three days
Chop them all off
Your Majesty, calm down, Your Majesty, calm down
Lord President, let's go home
Let's go home
You want to eat flies
I don't want to eat flies
What do you want to eat
You can eat anything
Who are you
Emperor