English subtitles are available
Fall in Love with a Fox EP02
Now, if there is
a dashing man
who is brave and resourceful
wants you to stay,
will you say yes to him, Miss?
Well, no.
Why?
Mr Qu
We've been fought together,
so we're friends, right?
It's my honor
to be Miss Jin's friend.
I mean
we'd better
avoid any confusion as friends.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to deliver a message to you, Miss.
The young master wants to meet both of you.
Right.
Look.
Why did she leave?
We should go, too.
Let's go.
There's something wrong in this house.
Actually, it's...
No.
There's something wrong with Yu Chen.
We just wanted to escape from the Mole Gang
as fast as we can,
and we had no time to think about
the time that Mr. Yu showed up
was so coincident.
You're right.
He knew
I work for Jin's Escort Agency.
Maybe he's...
coming for the sacred book.
So...
We can't stay here.
I'm afraid it's not easy to leave here.
Don't worry, Miss.
Since you consider me as your friend,
I will protect you
no matter what happens.
You hired me as your escort
before, right?
But why do you want to
protect me now?
And you know nothing about kong fu.
How can you...
Although I don't know kong fu,
I'll find a way
to protect you.
Okay.
Leave here?
Yeah.
Thanks for your help this time.
Mr. Yu
It's just that...
Miss Jin and I
have something to deal with right now,
so we must leave.
No.
How can Miss Jin
want to leave?
I just found something.
What did you find?
I helped you
in a such cool way.
I'm afraid it already
made a lasting impression
on you.
Don't be shy, Miss.
If you
stay here,
I will keep you safe.
As the young master of Yu's family,
how can you force the people
from Jin's Escort Agency to stay here?
You misunderstood me, Miss.
If you can stay in my house,
I will keep you safe.
As for him...
He can leave now.
Mr. Qu
Just help yourself.
You misunderstood, Mr. Yu.
Since you
have a crush on Miss Jin,
wanting her to stay here for a few days more,
then I
will comply your request.
What?
No, no, no.
You guys
held a wedding ceremony in Mole Gang.
How can you let her
stay here like that?
How did you know that?
I...
I heard of it.
Don't worry, Mr. Yu.
What Miss Jin and I did
was to fool
the leader of Mole Gang.
Besides,
Miss Jin once said that
we had no other option at that time.
Just let it go.
What're you talking about?
I thought you were my friend.
Good.
I believe Mr. Yu is a magnanimous person,
so you
will let that pass, right?
Me?
Of course, I will let it go.
That's great.
Tomorrow morning,
I will say a proper farewell
to you two.
Young master
Don't you remember
what you said just now?
What did I say?
We had a deal that...
What's the deal?
There is no sacred book in the bag.
Well, tomorrow morning
we will send Mr. Qu off,
so I will leave you to talk.
I have something important to deal with.
Wait! I...
You can't go.
Come here.
You tell me exactly
what you mean?
If Miss Jin keeps
badgering me like this here,
it will be inappropriate.
Badgering you?
I would not have thought that
you were an ingrate and traitor.
At stake,
I have to
keep myself safe first.
You should only blame yourself
for being so trusting.
You...
After all,
it seems that
you lack life experience.
Don't worry, Miss.
Everything's for a reason.
The young master told me
Miss Jin has been bustled about for one day,
so you'd better bathe and dress.
Bathe?
Lord Xueyue, I have news to report.
The escorts took the sacred book
to Yu's house.
It doesn't matter if she dies.
What matters is
to figure out
if the sacred book is authentic.
Got it.
You must do it quietly and carefully.
If there is anyone that
knows Nonuple Palace
get involved in it,
we're all gonna die.
Got it, my lord.
Miss Jin
We have been tracking
along the escorting route,
so I believe we will
find something about Miss Baiwan soon.
Really?
Thank you, Mr. Yu.
Miss Jin
What're you writing?
Nothing.
I just copy
some books by sages.
That's cool.
Thank you.
Each time I finish my needlework,
I copy some words from books
to self-reflect.
That's great.
As an ancient saying goes,
"Every day I examine myself on three counts."
I admire Miss Jin
for keep doing that every day.
You're the one that I should learn from.
So...
Mr. Yu
You can go on.
I will go to meet my father.
Bye.
Watch out!
Are you alright?
Yeah.
Stop!
What happened?
I can do it myself.
It's okay. Let me help you.
I said no!
Are you okay, Mr. Yu?
I didn't mean it.
Let me bind it up.
I'm okay, Miss Jin.
Well,
I'm going to ask someone else
to pick it up for you.
It doesn't matter.
Your scratch is more important.
Well...
Qiuer
What're you looking for?
I'm looking for some medicine for Mr. Yu.
Is he sick?
No.
It's my fault.
I hurt him.
Did you guys get into a fight?
Are you badly hurt?
-No  -Let me have a check.
His hands got hurt.
There are bruises on them.
Oh, my daughter,
stop searching it.
That's a precious gift
for your future father-in-law.
Besides,
it won't work for
the bruises on hands.
How about that?
That's the Medication for Wound Infection
passing down from our family.
That is more precious than
Taoyuan Valley's Yulu Pill.
Whatever.
Just let him pick himself.
Qiuer
She hasn't got married with him,
but she has been so nice to him.
Kids all get to grow up one day.
Miss Jin
Is it serious?
Don't worry, Miss Jin.
The wound is so long.
It must be pretty bad.
Thank you.
Trust me.
These are superior medications.
I got that from my dad
for you.
What...
Young master
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Miss Jin
Don't trouble yourself.
Well, I'm going to take a new one for you.
Miss...
Young master
Didn't you say that
you don't love her?
Why you're so nice to her?
We can't see our engagement as a child's play.
Somehow,
I have to marry her
for Taoyuan Valley's sake.
You will marry her though you don't love her.
What will you do with it later?
I believe
we can be a good couple
if we treat each other with love and respect.
Miss Jin is coming.
I'm back with the medication.
Miss, please.
Leave me alone.
Why did they follow my instruction?
No.
There must be someone else here.
The reason why Yu Chen asked me to get a bath
is to get
the sacred book.
Don't worry, Miss.
Everything's for a reason.
So does that mean...
he has other ideas.
Why do I think of him now?
The sacred book will be mine.
You're so smart, young master.
Miss Jin
The sacred book has been
thrown out of the wall
as you ordered me.
We can get it back
after escaping
from here tomorrow.
Good job.
No one knows that
we had thrown the book
out of there.
Don't freeze!
Go find it!
They've gone.
Have you found it?
There's nothing, young master.
Master
Jin Baiwan has escaped!
What?
We're fooled! Move it!
Okay, okay.
Go!
It's beautiful.
Look at those staffs.
Have a look, sir.
Come in, sir.
This way, this way.
Come on. Come on.
On my god.
This...
There!
Go!
What're you doing?
It's crowded here.
If you rush everywhere,
you'll be easy to spot.
What can we do now?
They're over there.
We can watch the lantern shows
with others.
Watching the lantern shows?
What're you doing?
To cover up.
Sorry for my offence.
What is she doing here?
It's impossible.
Goodbye, sir.
Come again.
A mask?
Taking that,
it will be more difficult for them to find us.
Have we met
somewhere before?
They're over there!
Move!
I don't want to be a burden to you anymore!
Leave!
I have punished the rascals
that offended you, Miss.
I'm Xu Yifei.
It's nice to meet you.
My I know your name, Miss?
Stop!
Freeze!
You wanna run away?
No way!
Yu Chen, the young master of Yu's family,
wants to kidnap a girl here.
Help me!
Shut up!
You, you little girl
damaged
my reputation.
Why don't you self-reflect?
Why did Qu
abandon you?
Mr. Yu
Although your family is so rich,
but you have venereal disease,
the worst one.
How can I marry you?
I don't have any venereal disease.
I'm so healthy!
You! Move!
Go!
Get her back!
Rise!
Go!
Stop!
Here she is! Here she is!
You want the sacred book, right?
Yeah. The sacred book.
I won't give it to you
even though I rip it into pieces.
Pick it up!
Screw you!
You two
get her down!
Go!
Okay.
Freeze!
You! Get down!
You want that, right?
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Where're you going?
I see. You collude with each other.
Little girl
You know it until now?
He's so weak?
Go, go, go.
Come on.
Go.
Stop!
Freeze!
Okay.
Get all the pieces back!
Am I clear?
Yes, sir.
Go have a check there!
How's it going?
These are the pieces of the sacred book.
Okay. Let me have a look.
The Romance of Flower Rain and Swordsman.
A Collector's Edition with Qiu qiuer's Signal.
It may be a fake one.
I know!
You must get her back
for me today!
I must cut her body into pieces!
Let's go!
How can she go out with such an ugly face?
Is she ugly?
Yeah.
Move!
Lord
The escort ran away anyway.
The Guqin player with her
is not a normal person.
He doesn't matter.
What matters is that you must
find the escort.
But the Majesty told us
to make it clear
whether the sacred book is authentic, right?
Are you questioning my orders?
No. I'm sorry.
Here's what you should know.
You must
find the escort for me
at any cost.
Yes, my lord.
Don't worry, Miss.
We're out of the town for miles.
Finally.
Thank you so much, Mr. Qu.
You saved me one more time.
It's so flattering, Miss.
It's my honor
to go through something with you.
But you don't know kong fu.
Weren't you afraid that you would be in danger
when you came for me?
I can't be a traitor
or an ingrate
whether I know kong fu or not, right?
And I promised you that
I would keep you safe,
so I must keep it.
Come on.
Here we are.
You saved me again this time,
so you're a friend of
Jin's Escort Agency.
I'll protect you in the future.
What're you doing?
She is...
She's my cousin, Su Zhuozhuo.
Thanks to her,
we can escape from there.
Oh, she's your cousin. I see.
I'll treat your cousin
as my cousin.
Who's your cousin?
Although Qu...
my cousin saved you,
don't expect that you can get along with him
in a causal way.
Get off.
You can get off now, my cousin.
Be careful.
She is so wild.
So,
except for Yu Chen,
those crowds of gang members
headed for
the goods escorted by you.
If you insist on
escorting the goods,
the way you go
will be more dangerous.
Jin's Escort Agency never lose the goods.
I must deliver the sacred book to my client
though it is difficult.
So...
Will you deliver it by yourself?
Well...
So where will you go,
Mr. Qu and cousin?
In fact, I'm meant to
find a people this time.
Find a people?
I had received the news that
the person would head to Tongzhou.
Tongzhou?
So we're on the same path!
Really?
Well, then,
how about going there together?
And we can help each other.
Okay.
Cousin
Are you sure we have to go there together?
It's inconvenient for Miss Jin
to take us together.
You're right.
We're not in the same world.
If you go there with us,
we'll be a burden to you.
No, no.
The more, the merrier.
It's settled, then.
You've been bustled about for the whole night,
so you must be hungry, right?
Let me cook you a meal.
Wow, you can cook.
I'm the best chief of
Jin's Escort Agency.
Have a taste.
It looks not bad.
Of course.
You don't know what the delicious food is.
Well, try it.
Nice.
I knew it.
Mr. Qu must be the one
that can enjoy my meal.
What the meal?
It's too spicy and salty.
Why do you take
so many peppers with you when going out?
How to have a meal
without peppers?
It's said Jinbian Town's people like peppers.
So that's true.
By the way,
I've been meaning to ask,
did you grow up
in Jin's Escort Agency?
Yeah.
I grew up in the agency,
so I began to eat spicy food when I was young.
Haven't you ever left
Jin's Escort Agency?
Of course no.
Since you like
my soup so much,
let me take another bowl for you.
No. Stop.
If my cousin get sick because of
your soup,
you can't take the responsibility for that.
Cousin
Don't take the soup, please.
Go to sleep early.
We'll have a long way to go tomorrow.
What will you do
if I disappear some day?
I will
find you
wherever you're,
either in the heaven or hell.
Why didn't you show up
after three days?
Who is he?
Why did he keep asking about my background?
Does he really know nothing about kong fu?
The spicy dried meat from Fuyun Restaurant.
Don't you have a try?
You know
I never eat spicy food.
But you took the meal
cooked by Miss Jin,
and you enjoyed it.
How's going on?
Is she the one?
She didn't like peppers before,
so I can't make sure about it now.
How about you?
How's the investigation going?
There were two people with masks
on the lanterns show.
I can't figure out which school they're from.
The leader of them is so powerful.
I nearly got caught
when I stalked them.
So I had to give up.
It doesn't matter.
Since they
headed for the sacred book,
they will show up again.
So...
You have to make up your mind quickly.
I'll try to figure it out
whether she is the one
I want to find.
You've glanced at me for many times
in one hour.
What happened, Miss?
If he knows something about kong fu,
I will know it by his hands.
I just feel
it's boring.
I want to play a game with you.
You can just speak it out.
I want to read your palms.
Read palms?
But I wonder
if you can trust me.
I believe all the words
you speak.
Excuse me.
There are so many calluses on his hands.
How can I know
if he practices kong fu?
Have you got something, Miss?
Of course.
But I wonder
what you want to know.
It must be something about my love.
Your love?
There are so many sets in finding your love.
Why?
It's not precise
only by reading your palms.
Do you know something about reading bones?
So you also master that skill, Miss?
I only know a little.
But I can know
all the secrets
that the one has.
Go ahead, Miss.
The bones of the one who practices kongfu is special.
Will I know it
at such degree?
What're you doing, Jin Baiwan?
I knew it.
I knew why you
asked things about him.
You have a crush on my cousin.
No.
Yes.
We can't see our engagement as a child's play.
Somehow,
I have to marry her
for Taoyuan Valley's sake.
It's not about the engagement.
He doesn't love me actually.
Miss...
Miss Jin
May I call your
given name in the future?
Miss Muqiu
What happened?
The fruit is for you
to quench your thirst.
You got it by yourself?
Yeah.
Young master
What you ordered
are all prepared.
You can have a check.
Okay.
Miss Muqiu
I will leave first.
He picked some fruit for me,
so it means
he kind of loves me.
The fruits picked by young master are sweet.
He's so nice.
I...
It's not sweet.
You haven't found her?
Jin Baiwan...
She disappeared
after the lanterns show.
There must be someone
helping her to hide the track.
But I've found something else.
I found
the sacred book
is for a person
named Qing Songke.
Qing Songke...
Do you know
the school he belongs to?
I'm on it, my lord.
I will go back to the palace
and report it to the Lord.
You must find the escort
as soon as possible.
Don't let anyone else get
the sacred book.
Got it, my lord.
On the lanterns show, you said that
you might meet me before.
May I know
where did we meet?
I got it!
You got it?
You played the Guqin in Jin's Escort Agency
on the Huazhao Conference three years ago.
You were
the Guqin Player in blue dress, right?
Did I say something wrong?
Miss Jin
Did you really grow up
in the escort agency?
Miss Qu
Are you alright?
-What happened?  -What to do now?
Step aside.
Does it hurt?
No.
Fortunately, that's not a venomous snake.
I just
left to get some fruits.
Then she put you in such a position.
It's because of my carelessness.
It's not her fault.
Why are you on her side now?
You've been nice to her along the journey,
but you didn't treat me like that.
Miss Jin is pure and simple.
Miss Su
Don't be hostile to her.
Did I?
I'm going to find
some herbs for you.
Does that hurt?
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It happened suddenly.
It's not your fault.
Mr Qu
You've been helping me along the journey,
however, I not only put you in such a position
but also lied to you.
What does that mean?
I didn't tell you the truth
when you asked me about my experience.
In facts, I was took to Jin's Escort Agency
five years ago.
Five years ago?
I lost all the memories
before that.
But my young female master told me that
I couldn't tell my experience
to anyone.
So I lied
to you.
I have nothing to
pay your debt of gratitude.
But I have a pendant.
Although it's valueless,
I've been wearing it all the time.
I can give it to you
if you don't mind.