Hello Debate Opponent 2 EP12
How about we start now?
So many people haven't come yet.
How can we start?
How about you ask Dango,
where she is?
Nobody answered.
She must've gone somewhere
to eat delicious food.
Senior
You asked me to meet you in the classroom in the evening.
What do you want to do?
What's this?
Open it and you'll know.
Low gluten flour 100g,
Tender tofu 50g,
and eggs.
This...
According to my taste last time
and recipe for butter cookies
from the Internet,
I wrote this.
But,
I can't make
what you made before.
Senior
Do you really think
that making desserts
is so simple?
There're many cooking recipes
in the world.
Following the cooking recipes,
everyone can make food.
But,
the perfect proportion and purity
can only be made
by me.
First of all,
you should be familiar with the "temper" of your oven.
Does an oven have a "temper"?
Yes.
You should know
whether its temperature is high
or low.
So first,
you should prepare a thermometer.
Learning is endless.
Can you please teach me?
Yes.
Look.
Look here.
You should sift the flour before you use it.
You should sift it
twice.
Hao
I have to hand in my paper
tomorrow
Or I'll fail.
You're good at writing and meticulous.
Please help me.
Don't worry.
It's going to be fine.
OK.
Then I'll get you a glass of water.
Thank you.
Senior Ma Nan
Someone asked me for help again.
So can I
go training later?
Why
did you ask me? What's wrong with you?
You've been helping me seriously.
But it's an emergency.
I can't refuse her.
So,
at least I can let you know it.
What's more,
on my birthday,
you didn't give me a gift.
Can this request be
my gift?
Okay.
So I'll go first.
I'll go there as long as I finish this.
Please
tell Xiaoyu and others.
Thank you, senior Ma.
Hello.
The subscriber you dialed is busy now.
What's wrong with them?
Why didn't they answer the phone?
No one answered the phone.
Let me ask Ma Nan.
Hello, what are you doing?
Why aren't you here now?
We were here long ago.
I'm playing computer game.
I'll go back after this game.
Don't worry.
OK.
Hello?
Help!
You're the only one who can help me.
Ma Nan is playing computer game again.
You can't rely on Ma Nan.
The students are late.
Why is Sa
also late?
I'll ask him.
Hello, Nan Bei,
I've got an emergency.
So I have to be there a bit late.
OK.
Bye.
Pull your arm harder.
It hurts.
I came here to help you.
But my arm is stuck in it now.
What a disgrace!
Let's be more tacit.
About this,
let's make it a secret, okay?
Why are you so stupid?
You came here to help me.
But your arm is stuck now.
My great name!
Oh my god!
Wait a moment.
What?
Why are you holding my hand?
I'm not holding your hand.
It's you who are holding my hand.
And when you breathe,
please stay away from me.
Your breath,
I can feel it now.
Do you think I want to do that?
Two...four stars are shining in the sky.
Three stars are shining in the sky
Four...
She is gone.
I'm on my knees.
Can you be politer?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
We're just here for training.
Why so many troubles?
It's all team one's fault.
Do you regret coming to team two?
Regret?
Yes.
I mean, do you regret coming to team two?
We didn't expect before we came to team two
that we would be terribly bullied
by team one.
We don't even have a place for training.
Heaven invests a person with great responsibilities.
It's just beginning.
And I told you before
that I would follow you.
I mean,
I will
accompany you to the championship.
You still remember that.
Of course.
Don't worry.
It will come soon.
Nan Bei, Xiaoyu, I'm sorry.
Why are you so late?
Xiaoyu, let me tell you.
There is
something that makes me happy today.
Wait a moment.
Sir, I'll pay the bill.
How much is it?
It's paid.
What?
OK.
Where have you been in the morning?
I haven't seen you.
Good news!
I borrowed a car from the school.
The car will pick you up later.
So you don't have to take the subway anymore.
Good, Mr. Sa.
Not bad.
Yeah.
But we do need
to find another place.
Changing places every day
is not a good choice.
Yes.
Boys and girls
have to crowd in one room.
It's inappropriate.
Yes.
The point is
that the bathtub is so hard.
Here you are.
It's done.
Thank you.
-You're welcome.  -Thanks.
Let's go.
You choose "old friends are better than new ones".
I can understand.
Because you're afraid
that your old friends'
choices would be different from those of yours.
But we can see
that under the cover of
the pitiful appearance,
there is our selfishness to old friends
and our fear to make new friends.
So, on the pretext of morality
and love,
we kidnap the friendships.
Thank you.
The winner is
debate team two three five of positive side.
Congratulations!
What time is it now?
Ma Nan
It's 8:30.
I remember that
we have class at nine o'clock.
How long will it take us to get back?
More than 40 minutes.
I think that skipping class once in a while is okay.
Look at you.
It's Mr. Li's class.
Mr. Li isn't here.
Are you looking for me?
What's wrong?
I see the ceiling twirling.
Are you OK?
Let's go to the hospital.
Or the school clinic, let's go.
No, I want to keep on learning.
OK.
You're pretending.
Keep on pretending?
Come to my office after class.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Sit down.
OK, everyone.
Today, we'll talk about
"Situation and Policy".
Please turn to
page 131
and see low-carbon economy.
Where are we going to train tonight?
What?
Train you?
I didn't mean that.
I say, where are we going to train?
We go to train.
We can go anywhere.
Coal,
oil, etc.
High carbon energy consumption.
Reduce greenhouse gas emissions
to...
Let's change our seats.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
Economic development situation.
Sir
What?
How do you sell the milk?
Today we have a special offer.
You can enjoy a discount after you apply for a card.
You only need to spend ten yuan a day.
If you order milk for more than seven days,
you could enjoy 10% discount.
And we will send it to your dorm.
This milk is very nutritious.
It's airlifted
from Ordos.
OK.
I'll order it for a month.
A month.
OK.
Let me calculate the price for you.
Do you need calculation?
I need to pay ten yuan every day.
There are seven days a week,
and four weeks a month.
And I also have 10% discount.
So I need to pay 250 yuan.
You don't need calculation anymore.
Do you pay with WeChat or Alipay?
WeChat.
OK.
Senior Ma Nan
Are you ordering the milk?
No, I'll sell it to Mengyuan.
So,
are you going to work for Mr. Li again?
I'm going to borrow a classroom from him.
You're confident.
I was not confident at all.
But I'm confident as soon as I see you.
Why do I have
an unlucky premonition?
I was planning to meet him myself.
And I had no confidence.
But if you go with me,
the chances of success would be much bigger.
I don't want to go.
I'm busy.
Sir
How about we calculate
the price of milk he just ordered again?
Let's go to find Mr. Li.
Goodbye.
Come again.
I don't have a classroom to lend you.
What's more,
is there anything
that stumps you?
I agree.
Do you need the teacher's help
with this kind of trifles?
To compete with team one,
you directly withdrew from the school team.
Where are your
spirits now?
Mr. Li
After all,
this classroom was the school's arrangement.
We have done
whatever we can do.
But we have no other solutions.
But now you belong to
the society team.
You can't
occupy the school resources.
Yes.
Isn't it cool under the overpass?
Isn't the steam room clean?
Isn't the sports field wide?
Who has given you the courage
to start an uprising here?
Am I right, Mr. Li?
Shut up.
Mr. Li
We signed up
for dozens of competitions.
We're facing with intensive schedules and heavy tasks.
We do need
a classroom for training.
We don't have blood ties with Mr. Li.
So we have to
obey the rules set by the school.
Why can't you understand?
In addition,
perhaps we would
be cut off from the famous competitions
and have to attend those
obscure ones.
So don't haggle over.
These are all our experiences.
Am I right, Mr. Li?
I said this for you.
I'm on your side.
Come to sit here quickly.
What are you doing?
All the details of the club classrooms
are here.
You two,
help yourself.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
Actuarial Science Club, Chess Club and Singing Club
are clubs
that have won awards in the city.
So they will not
give us their classrooms.
Basketball Club and Tai Chi Club
are outdoor activities.
So they don't have classrooms.
Look.
Foodie Union.
Why does Foodie Union
need a classroom?
Don't they just eat out?
Chinese Traditional
Dominoes Skill Game Research Association.
Don't they play mahjong together?
Why do they need a classroom to play mahjong?
Those kinds of obscure clubs
even don't have enough members.
So it's possible for them
to share classrooms with us.
That sounds right.
Let's split up.
OK.
Let's go.
Is that true?
Can we
share a classroom together?
Welcome.
We have
a big classroom.
So help yourself.
Thank you.
We are pretty experienced.
So don't worry.
See you.
Welcome to Biology Club.
Wow!
Oh my!
What's wrong with them?
Girls haven't come to our dorm for a long time.
So they need to clear up.
Oh, they don't have to do that.
We just came
to find a place for training.
Welcome to boys' dorm 213.
Why don't you enter the dorm?
They're better to go in to feel it first.
The boys' dormitory
stinks.
Now, I think
that leave the boys' dorm,
I can feel Maldives everywhere.
I'm used to it.
How can it be so exaggerated?
I've sprayed half a bottle
of air freshener.
Or,
how about we go to the girls' dorm?
OK.
If you can come in our dorm, that would be okay.
Aunt, what did you have
for lunch today?
Did the food in the canteen taste good?
Aunt, this is the dance I just learned today.
Is it good?
It smells great.
Go in.
You go in.
You go first.
What are you doing here?
Come in.
Have a seat please.
Please grab a seat.
My feet are not well.
My waist is ached.
Oh my neck!
What are you going to do?
You're leaving as soon as you came in.
And,
My dormitory is a little shabby.
Please don't mind.
You allowed
to let us train here.
We appreciated it a lot.
Come in please.
Please come in.
Help yourself.
So,
everybody find a place to sit.
Where can we sit?
Hey.
You.
Which muscle are you working on?
Wow!
It's a famous brand.
Jingwen gave it to me.
Did you hook up with her?
Why did she
give you such expensive clothes?
I wanted to confess to her.
Jingwen
Yes.
What?
The season is going to change soon.
I want to buy a coat.
So do you have a favorite one?
Let me see if it suits you.
No.
I like this.
It's nice.
Jingwen
Can you lend me
1500 yuan?
What's wrong with you?
You wanted to confess to her.
But you borrowed money from her
to buy a coat.
Why didn't you borrow money from me?
I borrowed money from her
because I wanted to confess to her.
What?
You know,
I borrowed 1500 yuan
from her to buy a coat.
I could pay it back over 15 years.
I could pay back 100 yuan a year,
8.3 yuan a month
and 27 cent a day.
So I could
give her a red envelope every day.
I could give her 13 cents in the morning
and 14 cents in the afternoon.
So I could confess to her by the implied meaning of numbers every day.
Are you a student of science?
How do you know
that I studied science in high school.
What happened to this coat?
Coat...
I don't know what happened.
When we
were eating,
she went out for a while.
When she came back,
she gave me this coat.
She is a good girl.
Look at her, she looked out for you.
She didn't want you to be embarrassed when you pay the bill.
But borrowing money from her
was not my original intention.
Let's forget it.
Let me ask you,
well,
when did you find out
that you like Jingwen?
When I first
saw her,
I could hear
hear our exclusive BGM
in my head.
Each couple
has their exclusive
BGM.
Is that true?
Yes.
Don't you and Xiaoyu have one?
No.
How could you know that?
Bro
Things between you and Xiaoyu
seem remain unknown
only to you and her.
Is it so obvious?
Anyway, anyone with eyes
can see it.
Here is your take-out.
Shui
We didn't order the bar takeout.
Xiaoyang's guitar is broken.
I want to buy a new one.
So I took a part-time job.
I'm leaving.
Please give me a five-star review.
No problem.
But,
do you know
where the training classrooms are in our school?
The classrooms have to be empty, not engaged
and accessible.
Backing one step to say,
a place where can keep out the wind and rain.
That's easy.
You can go to the attic of teaching building three.
Hey.
Make it clear.
That attic often stores
unclaimed express.
You can play cards,
have a rest
and even have a party there, no one will bother you.
Wait.
It stinks.
Be careful.
Look out!
Xiaoyu, be cautious.
My job is done.
Enjoy yourself.
I'll leave.
You are so ungrateful.
It's changed a lot here.
Oh.
As the saying goes, the desolating gale freezes Yi River.
Pooh!
Your words are ominous.
Do you have that feeling?
We are like
ancient celebrities and heroes
who were forced to be bandits on the mountains.
So do you want to be a bandit?
What kind of bandits do you want to be?
That is "have my wish succeeded".
and "free as a cloud".
I declare
this is
our future base.
From now on...
Let's clean the room first.
I always feel something missing.
Get it.
That's only an electronic lock.
It can't beat me.
I have many friends in the computer department.
Hey!
What are you...
What are you doing?
I'm feeling it.
Hey!
Is your bag big enough?
It's very big.
Western University of Science and Technology.
Why are there only their trophies?
What did I tell you before?
No.
I remember we have won many trophies.
Yeah!
Eureka!
I have no impression of it.
I have.
I won it five years ago.
Great.
Did they hide our trophies?
Hey.
I found your certificate of merit.
"The best debater of the chicken hot pot in Wutong road".
Yeah.
Great.
Why are you staring at me?
I did not.
Yes, you did.
You were laughing while you were looking at me.
That was weird.
I just think...
I just think
that the soybean milk should be delicious.
It's so hot.
Drink some water.
Nan Bei, be normal!
You're weird.
Review panel.
The evaluation of subsidies for poor students
was decided by each department at its own meeting
in previous years.
But this year, the school stipulates to
randomly select several departments
to cooperate to do it.
The school made this decision to prevent
the situation that evaluators
and the evaluated students are good friends.
So they don't have to feel awkward.
Do you have any objections?
How could we have no objections?
I have a question.
Why do we
have to do everything?
Are there no other students in our school?
It means that the members of our debate team
are excellent.
Yes.
I heard
that only students with high GPA
can attend the meeting.
Do you mean that my five-year GPA
is not as high as your two-year one?
OK.
Let me illustrate the standard.
The school has others poverty alleviation policies for
students who are in special poor.
So they are beyond
our discussion scope.
Now, the application forms
you can see now
are from ordinary students.
Evaluations should be made
according to applicants' academic performance,
average per capital household income
and family background.
And,
I would also like to emphasize one thing.
Although our school can't give them
a large amount of money,
but for the poor students,
the money
is far more important
than we can imagine.
So everyone,
please make the evaluation
with a responsible attitude.
Hey.
Take it easy.
Don't worry.
I'm good.
So,
let's get started.
There is a student
whose family is in debt of 50 million yuan.
And their house was also mortgaged.
His family is in straitened circumstances.
Do you agree?
No.
I don't agree either.
If we make evaluations according to the debt situation,
Lin Chao from art management department
should take the grant.
His parents are rich.
Yeah.
But Lin Chao's family
owes the bank hundreds of millions yuan.
We should make a concrete analysis of each specific question.
OK, next one.
Next is a monitor.
Gao Zhenzhou
He is in the top five of grade.
And he gets excellent results in each subject.
He applied for the grant last year.
And he made it.
As long as he succeeded last year,
he should be able to meet the standard.
What's your opinion?
No.
Yes.
I agree.
He used the money
to set up a Happiness Fund.
Its purpose
was to lead all the students to a happy life.
But actually he used the money
to flirt with girls.
So how about this one?
In his family,
his father is the only labor force.
His family's annual income is less than 30,000 yuan.
He also has a younger sister
who just went to the primary school.
Even his tuition fee was borrowed from his relatives.
Family's annual income is less than 30,000 yuan.
That means the family's monthly income
is less than 2,200 yuan.
I think he meets the standard.
What about you?
I agree.
I agree, too.
Hao, what's wrong with you recently?
Don't mention it.
The previous treatment was excessive.
It has caused some complications.
So now she instinctively opposes everything.
We don't know that.
Ma Nan, why do you know that?
I told you before.
Tao Hao is my research object
in psychology.
When something goes wrong, there must be a reason.
Hurry!
There are so many remained.
Let's move to the next one.
No.
So,
let's go on.
Go on.
What are you laughing at?
What are you looking at?
I'm watching love studies.
If you happen to act as six of them,
it means that you like him.
Let me have a look.
You look this kind of
pretentious forum.
It's a bluff.
It aims to fool people like you.
No, it's true.
Anyway,
it's true to me.
What is Nan Bei doing there?
Where is Nan Bei?
Where is he?
I don't see him.
He is the third one on the left.
I can see him at a glance.
Nan Bei
Yeah.
The first performance if you like a person is
that you can recognize him at a glance in the crowd.
And,
have you read the information
about poor students?
What's your opinion?
You don't want talk about it, right?
Let's go to eat something.
I know a delicious hot pot restaurant.
Let's go.
I don't want to go, I'm on a diet.
You go.
Why did you call me here?
What's the matter?
Can't I say hello to you
when I see you?
I'm leaving, goodbye.
Xiaoyu
Sister Tao Hao, can I sit next to you?
OK.
Everyone is here.
So let's go on the evaluation
according to the process of yesterday.
Ran Da's family
relies on subsistence allowances every day.
He meets all the standards.
Why did you kick him out?
Because his roommate reported
that he had just bought
a pair of roller skates worth 2,000 yuan.
So?
So he can't apply for
the grant for poor students.
Why?
A pair of roller skates worth 2,000 yuan
is a luxury.
He brought a luxury.
So he lost the right to apply for the allowance.
It's a convention.
Strictly speaking,
a pair of roller skates worth 2,000 yuan
is not a luxury.
It is at most
a medium and high-end entry-level product.
We should call it high consumption.
Then we can't approve it.
I don't agree.
What's wrong with you?
According to the convention,
we can't approve students with high consumption.
What convention?
Why are you always the special one with different thoughts?
We held this meeting
because we wanted to discuss
who could be given special care.
If we all follow the general trend,
we wouldn't have to hold this meeting.
Because most of the students
don't need the allowance.
That's a false deception.
I mean,
since our school has no clear provisions,
why should we obey that?
I think it's a hidden rule.
Now, the point is
whether there are clear provisions
that stipulate
to disqualify the students with high consumption.
We don't have such provisions.
But if you have high consumption,
it should prove that you're not so poor.
Is there any
direct relationship
between consumption and poverty?
No.
But a student who goes to the canteen
but is reluctant to buy some meat
and a student who buys a pair of roller skates,
who do you think need the money more?
A student
whose phone is worth 1,000 yuan,
and a student
who uses an iPhone,
who do you think need the money more?
I don't agree.
I don't agree, either.
Now on the market,
a relatively cheaper iPhone
costs 5,000 yuan.
If a student
takes a part-time job in a milk tea shop,
he would have to stand
for eight hours a day.
During the eight hours,
he would have to keep brushing the cups,
adding water
and making milk tea.
He could earn
about 80 yuan each day.
That means
he would have to eat and drink nothing
for two months.
For him,
5,000 yuan is the cost of going home twice a year,
together with
all kinds of books,
medical treatment and social expenses for a school year.
Then,
another student
would buy an iPhone
with the money.
Who do you think
is more qualified to take the money?
So a poor student is not qualified
to use an iPhone, right?
If I meet
all the conditions of poor students,
because of the money,
should I be deprived of
all the rights to enjoy my life?
No.
But according to
the example I just gave,
who do you think need the money more?
The student could also save money
for a meal every day.
After a year,
he would be able to buy
a 5,000-yuan iPhone.
Couldn't he?
The money you saved
belongs to you.
But the poverty grant is not.
You can't use the country's money
to satisfy your own desires.
So,
as long as you've brought a pair of roller skates,
why do you need
the country's grant?
First of all,
we need to reach an agreement.
Can high consumption
be a reason
to disqualify the grant application?
Yes.
It's true
that high consumption behavior can reflect
that he is not so poor.
As long as he is not so poor,
so this
is the reason
why he can't meet the standard of the poor students.
OK.
From your perspective, what kind of poor is real poor?
About this, there are provisions
in the subsidy rules.
But provisions don't ask him not to buy
a pair of roller skates.
His other conditions,
such as family background,
average per capital household income,
academic performance
and poverty situation,
can all meet the requirements.
Why can't we give him the grant?
You're right.
But the school asked
us to make the evaluations here.
Because they know that provisions are fixed.
They also need us to evaluate
whether a student is qualified
according to the reality.
I think that at least
one's high consumption can prove
that he is not so poor,
right?
Does a poor person
have the right to have high consumption?
Definitely yes.
So it is clear.
Imagine that
your "enough poverty"
can meet
the generally agreed poverty standard.
It doesn't need
any restrictions.
But the question is
how can we judge
that a person
who had high consumption behaviors
is not poor enough.
A high configuration computer
costs tens of thousands yuan.
For us,
it's certainly high consumption.
But for those students
who major in
animation,
it's an indispensable tool
for them
to do freelance jobs.
You can ask Dango about this.
So now,
how can we prove
that a so-called high consumption
must mean
that his family is not poor enough?
I can't prove that.
I just think there is something wrong.
Okay.
Now you two have almost expressed yourself.
Let's vote.
Those who agree to give the grant to Ran Da,
please raise your hand.
Those who disagree, please raise your hand.
Hao
You don't have to object
to show your character.
I do think
that what Xiaoyu said is right.
The report is needed three days later.
Then
we'll vote again.
That's all for today's discussion.
It's a little tense
due to the debate.
How about we go to drink a cup of milk tea?
My treat.
The second performance if you like a person is
facing with
the sudden physical contact,
you would feel shy
and overwhelmed.