Hello Debate Opponent 2 EP26
Spring awakens apricot branches.
A happy couple comes to us.
The happy bride
wearing a beautiful
white wedding dress
has come to
our wedding scene.
She comes to us happily
It's all right.
It doesn't matter.
with a smile on her face.
All right.
The bride is coming.
I don't dare to look.
All right.
Xiaoyu, Hao
It's all right.
Umm.
She's not Xiaoyu.
How do you know that?
Xiaoyu walks with her legs facing outward.
She walks
like a model.
Who are you talking about?
Oh.
I know you can't let me go.
The world is full of happiness
at this moment.
The earth...
What's going on?
The bride returns by herself.
She has a serious quarrel with her parents.
She says she must get married.
That's right.
Anyway,
you just love
and care about me.
I don't love you.
For the birth of this new family,
they bring...
Umm.
What do you like about me?
Symbolizes
sincerity.
Everything.
You're perfunctory.
Please.
Send their
token of love.
Thank you.
I'll eat this.
Ah.
Your body fat
is on the high side.
The doctor advises you to keep a bland diet.
Eating habits
are difficult to change
once they are formed.
So
let me prepare
your three meals every day.
You don't have to make breakfast.
Well.
Let's have lunch and dinner
together.
The boundless sky and endless earth may pass away,
but this vow unfulfilled will be regretted for aye.
A small
diamond ring
guards
their love
for each other.
Let's bless the newlywed.
It's mine.
Left.
This way.
Nan Bei, you are wonderful.
Cheers.
It's too hard.
It's too hard to get married.
There are so many people.
It's really hard.
You don't know.
No, thanks.
Give it to me.
Xiaoyu, please persuade him.
Why do you wear it again?
Don't think too much.
I tried on wedding dresses for them.
Then they gave me the wedding dress
after altering it
according to my size.
So I put it on.
Don't be angry.
All right, I promise to
let you go to
the Internet cafe all night once a month.
You can also buy game equipment at will.
You're not angry?
I'm not
petty at all.
It doesn't matter at all.
I don't care at all.
I'll treat it as charity.
But
let me do this kind of thing
in the future.
OK.
Umm.
Xiaoyu
You'd better
give them this dress back.
In the future,
I'll definitely buy you a big one.
Nan Bei
I'll change it.
You look especially good in this.
This is very strange.
No, we're a good match.
If we get married,
it will be a second marriage.
Its wedding ceremony has to be held at noon.
Stop it.
You should wear a pink wedding dress when you get remarried.
Ah.
It is held at different times
depending on the place,
with some being held in the morning
and others in the afternoon.
You know?
Implementation measures
of Kaili City for standardizing the behavior
of handling catering.
Ah.
Do you think
we can debate
about remarriage without catering?
Do you...
Right.
Do I...
Too young.
We haven't had noodles in a long time.
Hello, everyone.
The annual provincial debate league
is about to kick off.
After six months of fierce competition,
the university will have two debate teams
participating in this league.
It is worth noting
that the school debate team
led by Liu Yanze,
president of the student union,
has lived up to your expectations.
They have been undefeated
since the provincial points competition.
The other team
is originally the second school team.
They left the team for some reason in the points competition.
Then they successfully
entered the league
as an independent social team.
Hello.
Everyone,
good morning.
Good afternoon.
Good evening.
Welcome to the campus radio.
I'm Shan Dan.
First of all, let me announce a piece of good news.
The only two debate team in our university
have entered the second stage
of the provincial competition.
Their strengths are obvious to all.
Of course.
Among them, the most likely to win
is the high-profile
Team 235.
This team is not afraid of larger powers
and struggles hard amid difficulties.
They are simply the best
of the dark horses.
The leader of this team is Nan Bei.
He is not only the handsome Ares of DUFE,
but also Mu Xiaoyu's boyfriend.
Under his leadership,
this team is sure to beat team one.
Oh, no.
It will definitely go hand in hand
with team one
to create good results.
Although team two has also entered the league,
the strength of the teams entering the second stage
is generally higher than
that of the first stage.
Therefore, as a social team,
its competition prospect is still slim.
It's not like team one.
You're right.
Team one has been in the greenhouse for a long time,
so its strength and vision
are limited.
The second team has been fighting outside for so long,
so its strength and vision
have been improved rapidly.
Team one
was runner-up in last year's provincial competition.
Team two didn't even
enter the provincial competition.
To be honest,
if there is no team two to help team one
play the points competition,
team one may not be able to enter the provincial competition.
Team two has always
lost to team one.
Isn't it obvious
who is the winner?
Of course, team two is the best.
Why does team one...
Mao, why are you here?
Have you reviewed the press release?
You talk nonsense.
Mao
You are so naughty.
I haven't turned it off yet.
You piss me off.
Don't be angry.
The league is stationed
at the five-star Xinghua Hotel.
All the contestants will
stay here one after another.
Follow-up competitions
will be broadcast live on the network.
Coming soon.
Xiaoyu, look.
This hotel has the highest score.
Its breakfast is a buffet.
There are celebrities who have lived here.
That's great.
Who did it?
Who threw the material under the table
when he couldn't finish revising it?
Ah.
Please admit your mistake at once.
I'll put these
outside.
Do you pack so much
to quit the team?
What?
If we stay in the hotel,
we can't waste
our time here.
Be a man.
Please help me pack.
My legs hurt. I have a gout attack.
Three.
Two.
All right.
Xiaoyu
There is a popular
Chongqing old hot pot restaurant
next to this hotel.
I've long wanted to go.
We are there to compete,
not to play.
Never forget who you are.
Dango
There's something more appealing
than the five-star hotel.
What? Crawfish buffet?
Liu Yanze is also in that hotel.
We should concentrate on the competition and not be distracted.
Xiaoyu
Do you think we'll
live next door to them?
Go away, please concentrate on
reviewing.
If Hao knows, she'll be angry.
Did Hao see it?
No.
Please check it again.
How can there be no room for us?
Right.
I already said
that the competition committee
didn't book your rooms.
There can't be no room for us here.
We really
are the team for this competition.
I have the invitation to the event
from the organizing committee.
Please check it again.
You've seen it three times.
There's really no your team here.
Please check it again.
Did you get our name wrong?
Our name is Team 235.
Thank you, please.
Please check it again.
All the teams are here.
There's really no your team here.
Please wait a moment.
Well.
What's the matter?
They are the team for this competition.
But the hotel doesn't
reserve rooms for them.
Please.
He is
the logistics director of this competition.
If you have anything, you can ask him.
Hello.
Which university do you come from?
Dongzhou University of Finance and Economics
The team of DUFE has already checked in.
No, we
don't represent the university.
We are the social team,
Team 235.
Social team.
Right.
Please listen to me.
We have
limited rooms this time.
So the organizing committee stipulates
that it is not responsible for the accommodation of the social team.
So you're not
on this check-in list.
But,
among dozens of teams,
why is it only not responsible for
the accommodation of the two social teams?
Right.
This is formulated by the organizing committee.
Have you seen the competition statistics?
Our team is the first
in the number of competitions
among all the competition teams.
And we win
the only AI competition.
This is the rule.
So is there any other way?
I'm really sorry.
We really don't have
any other ways here.
I'm off to take a taxi.
Could you please see
if Nanjiang Drama Academy has checked in.
It hasn't yet.
Thank you.
Why?
We've entered the provincial competition.
They still look down on us.
Right. Everyone
wins by strength.
Why do they look down on us
and treat us differently?
Umm.
In fact,
it is inconvenient
for us to live together
in a hotel.
After all,
we can save
a lot of time
on the road.
I have
the car
to take you there and bring you back.
We are sure to be late.
He's also right to think so.
Social team sounds
richer than students.
It's okay for them to arrange it this way.
How rich the school team is.
Dango
Ask Liu Yanze
what else
we can take advantage of.
No.
Please ask him yourself.
I didn't handle this matter well.
I'm
sorry for you all.
Hao, please don't be angry with him.
He doesn't mean that.
Hao, this has nothing to do with you either.
I'm also angry.
Up to now,
we are no worse than any other team
in terms of strength and experience.
But as a leader,
I can't even win
the most basic fair treatment.
Hao
We don't blame you.
So blame it
on Sa.
Ah.
Right, blame it on Sa.
Right.
Hao, don't
take it so seriously.
We are all students.
It's normal that we can't handle it.
It's a shame that the teacher can't handle it.
Right, I'm ashamed.
I'm indeed ashamed.
I just feel sorry for you.
You don't need to apologize.
Now that it's done,
we should work harder
to get back
the fairness and respect we deserve.
What does our team
do best?
Be back in the saddle.
Right.
Hao, don't worry.
I'll definitely make them pay for
their foolishness.
Right.
Let's start
preparing for it.
Please believe us.
Why doesn't Sa
join us?
He says he'll go to
meet a friend at the hotel.
He waits for us at the hotel.
I heard that there are many
brain boxes of the debate circle in a while.
Really?
Yes.
What about Chen Ming?
I don't know.
They should all be here for the final.
Wait a minute.
Look, is that
Sa?
Sa
Do you work as a bodyguard
or an emcee?
For an interview?
For a blind date?
For love?
There is the opening ceremony today.
We can't lose
in the imposing manner.
Don't touch me.
Let's go.
Didn't you stay away from us
because of something this morning?
Why is he so strange today?
He doesn't compete.
Why does he do that?
He's been strange since yesterday.
If something goes wrong, there must be something strange.
But
he is quite right about one thing.
We can't lose in the imposing manner.
Let's go.
Coming.
Wow.
This is Qiu Heng,
the best debater in the last competition.
His strength is unfathomable.
Together,
you can only tie him.
What's wrong with you?
How can you boost other people's morale
and reduce our own courage?
I can do it alone.
If I become a champion in the future,
I'll walk as cool as him.
This is Shang Da,
the third place last year.
She's better.
She had just been on a debate show.
She's gaining popularity.
Netizens jokingly claim
that her logic is clearer than the crosswalk.
That's just a quarrelsome
variety show.
It's just so-so.
Hao, right?
Can I ask him for an autograph?
Me too.
What's the matter with you guys?
We are professional debaters.
Can you
be professional?
It's just us two who are knowledgeable.
Right.
These three are so attractive.
Who are they?
You don't know them?
The thinnest one
is Jiang Yanchang,
the best debater
in the 1993 International Chinese Debate Competition.
He became famous
in that competition.
The one wearing glasses
is Yu Yi,
the best debater
in the 2001 International Chinese Debate Competition.
He is known as a role model for debaters.
The fattest one
is Lin Fanjiang,
the best debater
in the 1995 International Chinese Debate Competition.
Hello.
I'll go, too.
Could you sign for me?
Thank you.
Just the two of us still have some concentration.
Really.
Right.
Too...
Why do you wear sunglasses?
For sun protection.
He's so handsome.
There's no sun here.
The moon and six debaters.
This bar is quite literary.
Where's Sa?
I don't know.
He is very strange these days.
He may have gone to do good deeds.
By the way,
I remind you
that there are many school teams
in this competition,
so we can't talk
like we are at school.
We must behave ourselves.
Right.
We should look like
the championship candidates.
Look, this is amazing.
Here.
Need, root, solution and gain/loss ratio.
It turns out that
this is a debate-oriented bar.
It's amazing.
Need, root,
solution and gain/loss ratio.
Everywhere is value.
Waiter
One cup for each, please.
Need, root, solution and gain/loss ratio.
Drinking in order
will taste better.
Shui, why are you here?
When you play the game,
I'm paid three times the usual rate.
So
I come to earn money.
If your band
doesn't win the championship, they should be sorry for you.
All right, let me get your wine.
Let me make a special one
without alcohol for Xiaoyu.
Shui, why?
Please show me some respect.
Are you going to
play a game or
a group fight
when you drink too much?
I'm sorry.
Yo.
There you are.
I have packed all kinds of food
in the dining area
and put them in.
We're drawn for
the opening competition.
We're going to get ready in a minute.
You just arrived at the hotel
last night.
How's the preparation going?
Can you?
We prepared all night.
Enough.
This is a provincial competition.
Don't underestimate the enemy.
If you guys have this in mind,
you might as well worry more
about yourselves.
I'm afraid that we
have a hard time making it to the finals,
but you guys are eliminated.
You can't be eliminated, right?
Of course not.
Attention, all teams.
The opening ceremony is about to begin.
Please move to the auditorium.
Let's go.
Liu Yanze
I'll cheer you up later.
Come on, Yin Nan.
You are an ingrate.
Let's go?
No.
The level of the first competition
is very low.
There is nothing worth seeing.
First of all,
on behalf of...
Sorry.
These seem to be our seats.
And
the support of all universities.
Let me express my heartfelt thanks.
Hello.
You're from Team 235, right?
You have your own seats.
But they're not here.
Please follow me.
Thank you.
We have privileges?
This organizer is good.
A total of 14 college debate teams
and two social debate teams
participate in the final.
I hope
you can
show your best
in the following competitions.
I will
double this revenge.
Demonstrate youthfulness.
Now let's have the two teams
of the opening competition.
The school team of DUFE
and the National University of Business and Economics.
Give it up
for them.
Come on, Liu Yanze.
Welcome to the first competition
of this year's league.
I am Wang Yi'ni,
the chairman of this competition.
Today's resolution is
about anxiety marketing
for the middle-income group...
What are you doing?
Videoing the competition.
The positive side DUFE
thinks it is immoral.
They play the competition.
Why do you video them?
Xiaoyu, please mind your boyfriend.
Don't bully my friend.
Sa
What are you going to do?
Going to the bathroom.
This is the roster.
Which debate team are you from?
Team 235.
We've changed players before.
I'll see
if it's up to date.
The so-called anxiety marketing
is just a marketing method.
My fellow debaters, it's not appropriate
for you to judge by morality, right?
So is pyramid selling
a marketing method?
Can't we say
it is immoral?
Anxiety marketing
takes advantage of specific emotions
of specific people.
But what kind of marketing
doesn't take advantage of people's emotions?
Discounts and promotions
take advantage of people's
emotions of taking advantage.
The use of spokespersons takes advantage of
fans' idolatry.
Even some health care products for the elderly
take advantage of their children's filial piety
and their worries about their parents.
Different from this,
the article about anxiety marketing
is about
what kind of life
we should have
and what kind of partner and path
we should choose.
These are all important events
concerning our lives.
One wrong step will ruin our lives.
This is totally different from
discounts and promotions.
If a few words can affect life,
a country can be destroyed
if a nail is lost.
My fellow debaters,
you think people
are too stupid.
Don't we all recognize
the content farms
for fear mongering?
My fellow debaters,
if so,
why is anxiety marketing
so popular?
How is it?
No problem.
Team one is going to lose?
He means there's no problem
for team one to win.
Well.
They play steadily.
Basically,
the other side's arguments are all refuted by them.
That's good.
This proves that this provincial competition
is not as terrible
as we think.
My fellow debaters, how do you define morality?
For example,
cheating is immoral.
Not necessarily.
White lies
are moral,
don't you think?
I agree with you.
So do you think
anxiety marketing is well-intentioned?
No.
But we don't think anxiety marketing
is malicious.
So good or bad,
you admit that anxiety marketing
is a kind of deception, right?
Please don't play with words.
It's just a marketing act.
It's neither deceptive nor malicious.
Anxiety marketing is full of
tactics
that use innuendo
and biased views
to induce anxiety in customers.
It knows it will have a bad influence,
but it still does so.
Isn't this malicious?
This cannot be judged.
And we don't think
it makes sense.
After all, even the law
doesn't make any provision for this.
You are wrong again.
The penalty for intentional injury
is different from that for unintentional injury.
Murder and manslaughter
are also completely different crimes.
It can be seen that
the law has explicit provisions on this.
My fellow debaters, I suggest you
can minor in
a major in law.
Thanks to the debaters of both sides
for bringing us
a wonderful
free debate.
Next is
the final summary of this competition.
Please.
Hello, everyone.
We are here today
to discuss whether anxiety marketing
is a moral issue.
What is morality?
Why should we abide by morality?
Sociologically speaking,
morality is our contract
to protect collective interests.
Psychologically speaking,
morality is a good way for us
to gain recognition.
Ethics tells us
that morality is the value and goal
we pursue personally.
It has too many definitions.
But if
we define it in a simple and straightforward way,
I think
it's morality that lets us know
right and wrong.
Some people may ask
why anxiety marketing
for middle-income people
is wrong.
Is it wrong
to remind them how dangerous
the world is?
It tells them that if they don't work hard,
their children may
not be as good as themselves.
What's wrong with this?
Others have houses, cars
and no loans.
This should be
your pursuit and goal.
There is nothing wrong with this.
In fact, the mistake is
that you tell the truth,
but you only tell
a small part of the truth.
You tell people
that danger is everywhere.
But you don't speak
kindness is even more everywhere.
You stimulate others' desires.
But you don't say
that actually these desires don't matter at all.
If there is someone
who keeps telling you
how dangerous the world is
until you get upset
and finally die by suicide,
then it is wrong.
Sorry.
It's wrong
to fill other people's lives
with false
bubble-like anxiety
and to deprive them of time, energy, traffic
and money
in ways that hurt them.
Thank you.
He's good.
You're jealous.
You can also win such a simple competition.
Not necessarily.
They are better at defending,
so they are restrained.
We are also good at
defending.
So we always lose.
Congratulations to Dongzhou University of Finance and Economics
for winning this competition.
You were really great just now.
Where were you sitting just now?
Why didn't I see you?
Umm.
The newly added seats in the last row.
It's okay.
If you sit too close to the front,
you will affect me.
You have a competition today too, right?
Yes.
The third division.
The time is almost up.
It's time for us
to get ready.
We'll be there later
to watch you play, too.
Okay. See you later.
Okay.
Bye.
Come on, video from the coach.
Hello.
When will you
come to see us?
Right.
Why don't you come for a few days?
Why does he cough so badly?
He's not really sick, right?
Of course, he is really ill.
Otherwise, why does he
stay in hospital for such a long time?
Don't worry.
Please take care of yourself.
We can hold out
until you come.
Coach
Let Sa
pick you up then.
You haven't been
in his car yet.
He drives like a roller coaster.
You can experience it once.
Let me say a few words briefly.
Don't be nervous.
Just like usual.
Although I have not
personally guided you
recently,
your progress
is obvious to all.
That's okay.
Do a good job.
Try your best.
We got it.
We'll do our best.
Don't worry.
We'll work on it.
Goodbye.
I feel like he's
in particularly poor health today.
He
is
really nervous.
Everyone.
We've had a tough journey.
Thank you all for not giving up.
Let's do our best.
Let's bring the trophy
back to the old coach.
Only we know
how much hardship we have experienced along the way.
Come on.
Let's give ourselves a boost.
Hello, everyone.
Today, our view is
that knowledge economy
is widening the gap between countries.
Knowledge economy
is not a strict economic concept.
It is mainly used to define
economic activities based on the production,
distribution and use of knowledge.
We all know
that human knowledge has developed
to a leading position
on a large scale
and systematization,
both in terms of science and technology
and humanities.
The ancient people just studied hard for ten years
before they could join the imperial examination.
But today we are
still in our first year of high school
after ten years of study.
We can't even complete
a basic education.
So the progress of knowledge
is increasingly dependent on
scale, teams, resources
and even the input and support of national strength.
Scale is
the biggest obstacle to future knowledge.
And it will
certainly promote the trend of monopoly
from the source
of the knowledge economy.
This may not be
what we expected.
The knowledge economy has no way
to bring us
more equal opportunities.
And it
will certainly widen
the gap among countries.
Thank you.
Will knowledge itself
be more widely disseminated
in the development of the knowledge economy?
The first debater
Yes.
But not all knowledge
has only economic value.
What kind of knowledge
has no economic value at all?
The fourth debater
Many.
Value does not mean
economic value.
If benefits are less than inputs,
it can be said that there is
little economic value,
such as the commercialization debate.
Don't avoid it.
The fourth debater, please answer me whether the knowledge
has been more widely disseminated.
On the whole, yes.
The third debater, does it make it easier
for countries with traditional educational advantages,
such as Japan,
to be caught up
by late-developing countries like China
and narrow the gap?
According to you,
the improvement of public knowledge level
has brought great advantages
to countries with large populations,
while countries with small populations
are difficult to catch up with.
Doesn't this widen the gap?
Yes, but now it is not to
widen the gap
but to narrow it.
After all, developing countries
like China and India
are populous.
The United States is also a populous country.
According to you,
it is difficult for the United States to catch up?
The fourth debater, your argument notes
that the development of knowledge economy
can help late-developing countries
surpass other countries quickly,
right?
Of course.
African Uganda's
booming film industry
and India's world-leading
IT industry
are good examples.
As far as I know,
the development of IT industry in India
has led to the weak industrial base,
insufficient comprehensiveness
and sluggish momentum of economic development in India.
The first debater, how can this be explained?
What I see is that India's economy
is booming.
Besides, even as you said,
at least the gap
in IT industry
has been indeed narrowed.
A poor student
narrows the score gap
between him and a good student
by memorizing English model essays.
But all his time and energy are
spent reciting model essays.
So he misses more classes.
Excuse me, is this gap narrowing
a real narrowing, the third debater?
Of course.
That's the problem.
Because the score of composition
is limited.
A brief narrowing is followed by
a rapid widening of the gap.
Because once the time and opportunity of poor students are lost,
they will not come back.
And the national competition,
just like the exam,
won't wait for you to start over.
Does the development of knowledge economy
promote
the progress of copyright industry?
The progress of copyright industry
protects knowledge producers,
which is equivalent to protecting
the development opportunities of late-developing countries.
Late-developing countries are poor.
The perfection of copyright industry
makes them
have no chance to
buy knowledge.
So the gap has been widened.
The core of knowledge economy lies in talent.
Talent has a better chance to
discourage late-developing countries
than hard power
such as rockets and aircraft carriers.
Qian Xuesen
broke through
the obstruction of the United States
to return to serve China.
Is it too easy
for you to sum up
with the word "easy"?
My fellow debaters, do you agree
that knowledge economy promotes
globalization
and breaks more barriers?
Nearly 90%
of the knowledge and information
on the Internet
are in English.
Unfortunately,
most people who use English
come from developed countries.
Does this break down the barrier
or build it up?
Different reactions to one thing
will lead to completely different results.
Today, we advocate narrowing the gap
is to make more Chinese people
realize that
seizing opportunities and strengthening the country with knowledge.
Different reactions to one thing
will lead to completely different results.
This is based on
having a correct understanding of events.
My fellow debaters, you misinterpret the debate
from a factual one
to a value one.
However, the discussion
is what it is,
not what it does.
We believe
that it is precisely because the knowledge economy
will widen the gap among countries
that we realize the crisis and urgency.
This is the real way to strengthen the country.
Thank you.
The result is now in.
The winner of this competition is
Team 235.
Let's congratulate them.
You're great.
I know.
Honestly,
I'm still nervous.
My palms are sweaty.
Let's have a slap-up meal.
OK.
Let's go, let me treat you.
The small restaurant nearby.
OK, let's go to the small restaurant today.
Let's go to the grand hotel in the future.
What a shame to go to the small restaurant.
You scared me.
Why are you here?
You especially wanna
go to the hotel buffet.
So I've got a voucher
for each of you.
Thank you, Shui.
Thank you.
It is useless and insufficient
to thank more.
What are you waiting for?
Go for it.
Thank you, Shui.
You're great.
Dear all.
Enjoy yourself.
There are also many delicious foods here.
Food in the five-star hotel
is delicious.
Shui, you are not afraid of being fired
for treating us like this?
Right.
It costs 399 yuan for one person.
The ancients said that swords should be given to heroes
and delicacies should be given to fellow debaters.
Look, Ma Nan.
There is another person
who can make up famous sayings better than you.
I don't think so.
He's not as cool as me.
Well, dear all.
No bullshit with you.
I gotta run.
If you have anything, call me.
Thank you, Shui. Bye.
You can't drink coke like that.
Why?
This is the biggest taboo of eating buffet.
Do you know
what its essence is?
You walk around
and eat all your
favorite foods.
This is a carbonated drink.
Carbonated drinks can cause satiety.
Satiety is the biggest taboo.
Look.
Take the first sip of coke, three yuan.
Take the second sip of coke, two yuan.
Take the third sip of coke, three yuan,
worthless just like this bottle.
One yuan.
Your major is economics.
You don't understand this.
It's none of your business.
What I drink is not coke
but happiness.
Happiness.
Well.
All right.
Let's eat.
We have to prepare for the competition.
We have to compete every day
before we're successfully qualified to the semi-finals.
Cheers.
You're a drama queen.
You're good.
It's water.
The first challenge we face is
heavy competition tasks
and little preparation time.
So we prepare according to
our most familiar division of labor.
Nan Bei and Xiaoyu are responsible for attack and defense.
Ma Nan is responsible for the closing argument.
There are many competitions.
So let me and Dango review the manuscript.
We take turns as the first debater.
Come on.
Let's begin.
This is
the common view
of our previous generation.
They think that if you don't suffer,
you don't grow up.
Young people are not trustworthy.
This is too outdated.
The generation after 2000s
who grow up happily in peace time
have already held up half the world.
As far as our generation is concerned,
we have experienced extremely difficult NCEE
and faced the huge pressure of buying a house and employment.
Moreover, it is not easy for people
who go to work in big cities,
so they can't be regarded as having never suffered.
So will they say
that every generation
has its own suffering?
It doesn't make sense. Remember
that the debate is aimed at discussing suffering itself,
and it does not require suffering to exist.
Can suffering
cultivate people
to a certain extent?
Right.
It cultivates us
and makes us grow.
Isn't it worth thanking?
The enemy who killed my father
can also develop
my strong character.
Do I have to say
thank you to him?
You should thank him for developing
your strong character.
You should also hate him for killing your father.
You should look at a matter dialectically.
According to you,
I can thank everything
in this world.
Thanks to the earthquake
for giving real estate developers opportunities.
Thanks to the fire for giving succors
a chance to show their bravery.
Thanks to the war
for making heroes and legends.
Thanks to those spoiled brats
who broke my mobile phone
for giving me a chance
to change my mobile phone.
Can you name
one thing
I can't thank?
My fellow debaters
This is not dialectical, but bitchy.
Thank you.
The winner this time is
Team 235.
Let's congratulate them.