English subtitles are available
Fall in Love with a Fox EP08
Please speak frankly.
Miss Su
Mr Qu
I've known that
your engagement with
Jin Baiwan is fake.
So?
I have been adoring you for a long time, Mr Qu.
It was also me who managed to
beg the Puyuan Canon case
from my dad.
Well, what do you think of me?
All along the way,
you must have
read my mind.
No wonder Song Jianshan told me not to come here.
But I never expected that
Jin Baiwan, who has ulterior motives,
popped up.
Who has ulterior motives!
Well, Miss Su,
how did you know
she has ulterior motives on me?
You knocked her out,
took her sacred book,
and hung her in a tree.
But she still badgers with you.
Isn't it obvious?
What else did you find, Miss Su?
More than that.
Think about it.
All along the way,
she cooked for you and kept
pestering me for your news.
So you mean that
she's into me.
She's only a kitchen maid
and isn't qualified to like you.
What...
What are you talking about?
Jin Baiwan
How dare you to eavesdrop us?
Well, you bad-mouthed
me first.
I was just telling the truth.
Last time in the carriage,
Mr Qu would have been
offended by you
but for me.
I'm not an anthomaniac
like you.
You want him, right?
He's yours.
Baiwan
Mr Qu
Leave her alone.
Isn't your engagement
fake?
So what?
Maybe I just wanna make it real.
One more thing, Miss Su,
don't ever keep doing such things
to Miss Jin, otherwise
I'll be unpleasant to you.
Baiwan
What do you come here?
Shouldn't you
coax your Su Zhuozhuo?
Since our engagement has not
been canceled officially,
you are still my fiancée.
So I owe you
an explanation.
I thought you forgot you are engaged
and started to develop
a romance with that Su Zhuozhuo.
Baiwan, you're jealous?
No, I'm not.
I'm just angry for her nonsense.
So you didn't cook for me
on the trip?
Well, someone
has to cook.
And I am a kitchen maid.
Then you didn't enquire
about me
from Miss Su, either?
Well, we just knew each other at that time.
Of course I wanna know more about you.
So you never
look at me with
that eager face
as Miss Su said,
right?
Well, I always look at you
like this.
What do you think of
this look, Baiwan?
It's surely natural and poised,
with nothing personal.
Nothing personal?
Why do you evade my eyes?
I didn't.
That's strange.
Why is my heart beating so fast?
You see yourself getting
alone with me
in your mind, right?
How...
How do you know?
Baiwan
You really feel nothing
romantic to me?
I...
Then I see.
It's all my
wishful thinking.
Well,
then...
Then what?
Then our engagement...
The young master takes
Miss Jin back.
They are back.
Miss Jin's back.
Qiuer, what's the matter?
Is that your father?
Looks not so fierce.
Don't worry.
He's a modest and gentle man.
What about your mother?
The servants say that she's good at
lyre-playing, chess, calligraphy and painting
and likes reading Commandments for Women.
She must be strict, isn't she?
Well, my mother comes from
a scholarly family,
observing the laws and rules.
Everyone in
this valley holds great
respect for her.
As for being strict,
she indeed is.
Regulations?
What kind of rules?
For example,
in this valley,
no private talk
between a man and a woman
around the corner is allowed.
Well, we come over here.
Anything else?
Well,
my mother doesn't like
to be talked behind her back.
Luckily she's not here.
This flowerpot
is her favorite.
You'd better leave it alone, Qiuer.
Then I'll put it back.
Never mind.
I'll just say it's me.
But...
Qiuer
Don't worry.
You are my dear future wife.
I will deal with all the things
in this valley.
All you need to do is waiting for the wedding.
Feng
Mother
What are you doing here, talking
with Miss Jin alone at this corner?
Miss Jin doesn't know
the rules of Taoyuan Valley.
What about you?
Mother, it's all my fault.
Miss Jin, see me in the main hall.
It's okay. Don't worry.
You must be tired after such a tough journey, Jin.
It's okay, never mind.
Mrs. Yu
Father
Qiuer
Greet to Mr Yu and Mrs. Yu.
Nice to meet you, Mr and Mrs. Yu.
Nice to meet you.
Jin
I've heard that you've been chased
by bandits along the road.
Are you hurt?
Thanks for your concern, Yu.
All along the way,
thanks Linfeng for protecting Qiuer,
Quier is safe and sound.
Yu
Fortunately
we had the foresight
to bring about
such a beautiful marriage.
That's right.
I feel quite pleased
to have Miss Jin
in our Taoyuan Valley.
Don't worry, Miss Jin.
I'll help you to get familiar with
the daily affairs and the various
regulations of the valley.
Regulations again?
What regulations
do I need to remember?
Bring it up.
Such two thick books.
You are mistaken in that, Miss Jin.
It's just a catalogue
of the rules and regulations.
The detailed rules
are kept in the bibliotheca.
It's available for you
to read yourself, Miss Jin.
You'll get to know it gradually.
It's in no hurry.
Please.
Sorry to let you stay in this
wing-room before the
wedding, Miss Jin.
Thank you.
Father
I don't wanna get married.
My daughter,
what are you talking about?
Here we are in the Taoyuan Valley.
Well,
the catalogue is
indeed a little thick,
but you'll get used
to it finally.
You'll get used to it.
No.
-I wanna go home.  -No, you don't.
-No, you don't.  -I miss Baiwan.
Miss Jin
Finally you're here.
I miss you so much.
Baiwan's here.
How do you do, Mr Jin.
Great.
Do you have a hard trip?
No, not at all.
Where have you been?
Who are you?
I've been worried to death.
It's okay. I'm fine.
I am Qu Zheng from Tingqin Garden.
It's great to see you're fine.
You are the
legendary Mr Qu.
So sorry that I didn't recognize you.
Mr Jin
May I have a word with you alone?
Sure.
Give them some minutes.
Please.
I said it long before that we
Taoyuan valley is an aristocratic family
of distinguished military commanders,
but we have strict family regulations.
However, you insisted on having Feng engaged
with that barbarous family.
Darling,
you have been talking about this
for over ten years.
Now Miss Jin
is already here.
What's the point to say
such words?
Mother,
Quier is a cheerful, lovely girl.
I'm sure you'll like her after
getting alone with her for some days.
I didn't expect so many things
to happen all along the way.
We Jin's Escort Agency
must be framed.
I'm trusted by Mr Su
to investigate this case.
I ran into Miss Jin
on the way.
She was deeply concerned about
Jin's Escort Agency.
Despite all the danger and difficulties,
she insisted on coming here
to inform you.
Thanks for your selfless help, Mr Qu,
otherwise Baiwan could
hardly keep herself alive.
No need to thank me, Mr Jin.
Although my trip was originally for
the Puyuan Canon
case,
I've gained a lot on the way.
Have you got anything?
I gained
myself a lady.
What?
You're engaged?
With Qu Zheng?
So
you are Mrs. Qu now,
first lady of Tingqin Garden.
No, not the first lady.
This engagement...
might...
probably...
be canceled soon.
Then there's no connection
between us anymore.
What are you talking about?
True love?
I fell in love with
Miss Baiwan at first sight.
Back in the Mole Gang,
we had a pledge of love
and said our marriage vows.
Then
Yu Chen kept standing in the way
to take the sacred book.
He even tried to
keep Baiwan in his resident.
But she chose me
over the wealth and rank
of Yu
and ran away with me.
I cannot
let her down.
He's such a liar!
Right.
He lied to
every man he met
on the way.
He tricked me well.
What?
He's so bad!
Well, not that bad.
Except for being a big liar,
he's a pretty nice guy.
What's more,
he's a righteous
big hero
and has saved my life for several times.
What happened?
So it
was Baiwan
who saved your life.
Yes.
After having the knife wound,
Baiwan couldn't sleep for the whole night.
Dare not to go beyond the discipline,
I stayed outside the room
to protect her as she fell asleep.
However, in the dream,
she kept calling
my name.
At that time,
I swore to myself
that I would protect her
for the rest of my life.
I shall never allow her
to get any hurt.
So
he has saved your life
for lots of times.
Well, I saved his life too.
Don't you think
it's romantic
when he took you to see the fireflies?
I think it's okay.
What a romantic story. I'm touched.
So what happened then?
After going through
all the hardships on the way,
our love is stronger than anything.
So we promised to each other
and signed the
marriage contract.
However...
What?
Recently Miss Jin
had some misunderstandings with me,
even planning to cancel our engagement.
It really makes me have no appetite
and no sleep at night.
Mr Qu, don't worry.
Baiwan is like
a daughter to me.
You can count on me
with this matter.
What a perfect match.
I'll try to convince her for you.
Thanks a lot, Mr Jin.
But for now,
due to the escort thing,
Baiwan has become the target for all.
Before the truth has been found out,
I think
it's better not to
present her in public.
Right,
you are right.
I can rest easily to trust
you with Baiwan.
But I think we should
inform
Mr Yu.
How about
discussing with him now?
Okay.
Wait.
In you words,
he's crafty but righteous.
He took care of you and lied to you at the same time.
Is he a good guy
or a bad guy?
Never mind.
It doesn't matter, anyway.
What matters is that
you like him since you first
brought up the idea of getting engaged.
Well,
I'm not sure.
Come on,
don't you know your own heart?
I suppose I don't.
You suppose you don't?
Well, maybe.
I might probably do.
What about him? Does he like you?
Well,
how could I know
if he's into me?
Let's go ask him if you don't know.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Miss Jin
It's not the right time.
I...
It's always the right time.
You said yourself
that Qu Zheng
is a liar who plays tricks.
He's indeed a liar...
Don't worry. I get your back.
She's the escort
Jin Baiwan, right?
Right,
it's her.
Who are you?
Jin Baiwan
We've been looking for you all along the way.
Don't worry, Miss Jin.
How dare you come to Taoyuan Valley?
What...what do you want?
Miss Jin
I am the
Miss Jin of the Jin's Escort Agency.
She must have received
the instructions from Jin's Escort Agency
to substitute the sacred book,
claiming that it's fake.
You are slinging mud at me.
You got no evidence.
Evidence?
We're here in the Taoyuan Valley
is to confront
Jin's Escort Agency.
You've come just at the right moment.
Having tied you up,
we can go confront Mr Yu then.
Right.
Who dares to touch a single hair of my love lady?
Love lady? Lady?
I got you.
My daughter
Father
They are slandering Baiwan.
Mr Qu, you said you would
track down the canon yourself.
But now you're
mixing with this
escort.
The custodian has turned the thief.
You two must have connived
to stole the book.
Right.
How dare you!
The fame of my Jin's Escort Agency is worldwide.
The rare treasures we escorted are countless.
Not a second did we
have the thought to
pocket the goods.
The book was escorted by me.
And I got framed on the way
for many times.
If I want it,
why didn't I take it
at the beginning?
Stop acting here
to clear
the suspicion.
Right.
Acting? I could act better
if I left the escort agency to
pretend that it got stolen.
Why did I even bother making a marathon
journey to the Yinxue Village?
How could it be possible?
Isn't she...
Many of you
have been to the home of Qing Songke
in Yingxue Village,
and you've seen the fake canon
with your own eyes.
I'm amazed that now you're playing dumb
and dare to
press my wife.
We are not here to get the canon,
but the great justice.
Right.
The great justice?
Where is the great justice
when you kept
pressing this weak young lady
and framed up
Jin's Escort Agency?
You...
Hold on, everybody.
Mr Yu
-Everyone. -Mr Yu.
What happened here?
Yu
This is the lord of
Tingqin Garden,
Qu Zheng.
Jin's Escort Agency has been framed
when we escorted the Puyuan Canon.
Thanks Mr Qu
for his selfish help.
Mr Qu
Well, you owe
us an explanation of the canon case.
Right.
Now that I am part
of the escort,
I would explain it clearly.
But I won't do it now,
when I am surrounded
and pressed by the wicked.
You...
Mr Qu is right.
I believe Mr Qu.
Everyone here,
it's a matter of great importance.
Given the fact that
grandmasters of all schools
have come to the Taoyuan Valley,
how about
Mr Qu announcing the truth?
Since Taoyuan Valley has been
well-known for justice,
I wholeheartedly agree with this plan.
Later,
I'll make it clear to the public.
Sounds okay.
Okay.
Now that we got
the resolution,
how about we put the bias aside?
All you heroes
come here originally for
my son's wedding.
I request all of you put the swords away.
Have a good rest
and enjoy yourselves
in the valley.
What do you think?
Of course we'll do it
for Mr Qu's favor.
Thanks a lot.
Please.
We'll take our leave.
For the details,
please come with me to the hall for discussion,
Mr Qu and Jin.
Okay.
I'd certainly be frank.
Please.
I'll be right back.
Baiwan
It turns out
that you've been living such
a hard life.
You must be exhausted.
No, not at all.
Look at me, I'm fine.
Mr Qu
called you his wife
in front of everyone just now.
He's so cool.
Well,
he was just
getting me out of trouble.
Just getting you out of trouble?
Why did he take the risk of offending
all the heroes?
In my view,
he must like you.
Like me?
How could you tell?
Even a fool can tell.
Answer me again.
Do you like him or not?
I'm not sure, for real.
You know me.
I have no experience
for liking others.
You idiot.
Alright, just leave it
to me,
the expert matchmaker.
What do you mean, Miss Jin?
You didn't ask him that question.
Is it okay to do that
for our girls?
Of course it's okay.
We're going to give this back to him.
The Puyuan Canon case is
no trivial matter.
Thanks for your efforts, Mr Qu.
They are out.
It's my responsibility.
Please.
Mr Qu, Mr Qu.
Miss Jin
Come on.
We're here to give you this,
and have a little chat maybe.
Mr Qu
Thanks for your heroic act today.
You not only saved the reputation
of Jin's Escort Agency
but also saved Baiwan.
No need to thank, Miss Jin.
It's a matter within my duty.
I wonder what the matter is
that Miss Jin came to me.
Baiwan is like a sister of me.
So
as her family,
I have some questions for Mr Qu.
Please speak frankly, Miss Jin.
I'll put it mildly.
When is the wedding day
of Mr Qu and Baiwan?
Are you going to stay in
Tingqin Garden after the wedding?
I heard that Tingqin Garden
is pretty close to
Jin's Escort Agency.
Is Baiwan free to
visit her family frequently?
I told you it's a fake engagement.
Fake engagement.
Real love!
Right, Mr Qu?
You are right, Miss Jin.
So
you like Baiwan, right?
I won't deny that.
You see?
I told you that he likes you.
Well,
Baiwan is my best friend.
Now that Mr Qu are deeply
in love with her,
I can only reluctantly
agree with your marriage.
It's not the right time.
Why?
All along the way,
I can't help falling in
love with Miss Baiwan.
Unfortunately,
I've asked Miss Baiwan
for several times yesterday.
She has no romantic
feelings for me at all.
You really said that?
Miss Baiwan only
regards me as a friend.
And I know the love
cannot be forced.
How could I
force Miss Baiwan to marry
a man she does not love
in the name of marriage?
You don't know if she loves you!
Baiwan
I...
Do you like him or not?
Never mind.
Miss Jin
Stop embarrassing
Miss Baiman
and
stop hurting me.
The fallen flowers would like to float away with the stream,
while the stream has no feeling for fallen flowers.
Excuse me.
Go.
Baiwan
This is mine,
could I have it back?
Baiwan
It seems that
you hurt
Mr Qu deeply.
What did you say exactly?
He's so upset.
He's upset?
He's a cunning fox.
He'd swear black is white if he wants.
Miss Jin
Finally got you.
Mrs. Yu wants to see
you in the courtyard after dinner.
Baiwan, come with me.
I'm not going.
Go by yourself.
Why are you mad at me?
Think about it yourself.
Feng
Is everything okay?
Don't worry, mother.
Quier
Mrs. Yu
Feng said that
Miss Jin got strict family disciplines,
having a good command of lyre-playing, chess, calligraphy, painting,
and Confucian classics, right?
Mother
Qiuer is a well-read and
brilliant girl.
She can surly hold the
the womenfolk gathering successfully.
What is the womenfolk gathering?
It's a tradition
of Taoyuan Valley.
Every bride
needs to hold a banquet
inviting the ladies of
all the big families and
the chivalrous ladies in the ganghood.
Hold the banquet
all by myself?
Now that Miss Jin is about
to marry into the Taoyuan Valley
and become the lady of the whole family,
this banquet is just
for practice.
Nothing difficult.
When is it then?
It has been turbulent
due to the Puyuan Canon
case recently.
Jin's Escort Agency is also involved.
Since the Shiming gathering is around
the corner, what about
holding the two at the same time?
It comes so soon.
Qiuer
Don't worry.
I've prepared it for you.
This is the process
of the gathering.
I've written it down for you.
Everything would be fine as long as
you follow the instructions there.
It's just a chance to
know the ladies.
Mother will be your side.
Because of such a short time,
I come to direct you.
I heard from Feng that
Miss Jin has read the Woman Commandments.
Yes, I...I've read about it.
Feng also said that
Miss Jin is skilled at lyre-playing.
How about
playing a piece of song
to begin the banquet, Miss Jin?
Is that really her?
I'm sure
she died five years ago.
Whoever she is,
I won't allow her
to appear in front of me
like haunting ghost.
Lord Xueyue
You mean...
Feilian is in the charge of Lord Xueyue.
I will do whatever I am asked
by Lord Xueyue
and keep the secret for good.
Good for you to know that.
But
there are lots of masters in the valley.
And we still have the task of stealing the
Saussurea involucrata.
Is it...
Of course I know the priority.
Tomorrow's womenfolk gathering
is a good chance
to take her life.
Qi
I was delayed by some things.
This is your medicine.
I'm not injured.
Your hand...
I heard that
you are from Jin's Escort Agency
and involved in the Puyuan Canon case.
Sorry
to keep it from you.
Look,
I bring you this.
It's from the lady of the valley.
A first-class tag of the retainer.
With this,
Steward Wang would never dare to bully you.
Here.
Why are being so nice to me?
It's nothing.
You are a younger brother
to me.
I like you.
Brother?
But I won't be
in the kitchen anymore.
Take care of yourself.
I gotta go.