English subtitles are available
Just in Time EP04
Did you bring the booze?
Yep, I got it.
Great.
Wait, you want to drink?
Just a little.
Did anything big happen to you?
You know, drinking alcohol can boost courage.
Two bottles...
Two bottles should be enough, right?
Two bottles? That's too much.
I will get drunk.
You drink with me.
No problem.
I'll prepare some great seafood for you.
Hit me one more time.
Son,
eat more shrimp.
Dad made some really good shrimp today.
Come on,
Brother-in-law.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I can still have a couple more sips.
Pour some more.
This wine is really good today.
Let's have another drink together.
Okay.
Enough, enough.
We have two bottles.
Let me finish this first, then we'll pour more.
Enough.
Jia Haowen.
You're quite willing to drink with others.
Well,
When eating seafood, drinking liquor
is for sterilization.
Sister,
why don't you have some too?
Are you sure?
Let's just drink together.
Okay, okay.
It smells so good! What are you eating?
Yunjie is back.
Come on, come on.
I made a lot of delicious dishes. Here, try some.
Aunt, Uncle!
You are back!
Have you eaten?
I've already eaten at He Lu's home.
You haven't tried this.
This seafood was just made by your uncle.
It's really good.
Have another bite.
Here, you sit here.
Okay.
I'll get you chopsticks and a bowl.
Come on.
Xiongxiong, you are here.
Did you mess with my stuff?
No.
Really?
Hurry up and eat shrimp.
Eat shrimp.
They've all left.
What's going on with you and Jia Haowen?
What do you really want to do?
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have kept this from you.
I'm not angry with you.
I'm angry with myself.
I didn't even notice
you were unemployed for so long.
No, no.
I just didn't want you to know.
I told a lie,
and then kept having to cover it up.
At work,
you're already so tired.
In life,
I don't want to add
any more pressure.
Then give me a hug.
I'm sorry.
I just had a dream about my dad.
I told him I regretted
not learning traditional Chinese medicine from him.
If I had learned it
and had a skill,
I wouldn't be so useless now.
Be more confident.
I know
my own level.
You are right.
I haven't made
much progress in these years.
It's not that.
It's because of this family.
It's me and Yunjie who have dragged you down.
Actually,
I've been thinking these past couple of days.
If you hadn't
left Beijing with me back then,
would things
be better now?
Maybe you could have even become a professor
or maybe even a scientist.
I'm unlikely to become a scientist,
I know myself
very well.
I'm
too passive.
If it weren't for you
leading the way these years,
I might be in an even worse situation
than now.
I am content
with you
and Yunjie.
Actually, I know it myself.
All these years,
I've been focused on myself.
And you've
been too indulgent with me.
You've taken care of everything,
big and small, around our home.
I'm really
not a great wife.
What are you talking about?
You're amazing.
Really?
Isn't it just that you're more career-focused?
But one of us
has to
take care of the home, right?
That's true.
You could call it sacrifice.
But honestly,
my parents passed away early,
so taking good care of the family
is what I really want to do.
How can you say that?
Haven't you ever wondered
what it would be like
if you weren't with me?
No.
Being with you
makes me feel so secure.
I don't have to think about anything else.
Did you also feel secure
when you were
with Mei Yiduo?
Who?
Dad!
Hurry up and change,
it's time to go.
I...
Your dad's not going to work today.
Yes.
Not going to work again?
No,
he's meeting a client.
Not going to the office.
Yes,
I'm going to meet a client.
Dad, your job
seems pretty easy
compared to my school.
You think your dad has it easy?
He makes you breakfast in the morning,
and picks you up from school in the afternoon.
Is that easy?
That's true.
Are you ready?
Okay, let's go.
I'll drop you off.
No need,
I'm catching a ride with He Lu.
Don't we have a car at home?
Or are you just planning to
stop riding with me altogether?
I just really don't want to listen
to your paid life lessons again.
I'm off.
Paid life lessons?
Are they really that bad?
Bye.
I think they're great!
I've learned a lot,
and sometimes
they even make me enlightened!
Right?!
Yes.
She is still a kid.
I'm thinking maybe
I should find a chance
to tell her about my situation.
There's no need.
It's not like you'll be unemployed forever.
That's true.
Since she's out
and we've got some time.
Let's settle the score.
Settle the score?
Settle the score again?
Didn't I just
clear my name recently?
I mean our budget.
We spend around
2,000 yuan a month on groceries
and cooking at home.
I spend about
50 yuan a day on lunch at work,
so that's around 1,500 yuan
a month for 30 days.
Coffee costs about 400 or 500 yuan.
400 or 500?
Let's write down 500 first.
Yunjie's English
and piano classes
cost 3,000 yuan a month,
which is 36,000 a year.
Is it really that hard
to find a job now?
You're even calculating expenses annually?
Let's be conservative
and calculate it annually.
The car!
And the car.
Gas costs
about 500 yuan a month.
And washing, maintenance,
and repairs...
That's easily another
1,000 yuan a month.
I think we could
cut back a bit in that area.
But some expenses we can't avoid.
Every month,
utilities like water, electricity, and gas
cost 500 yuan.
We need to charge 400 yuan per month for our two phones.
Visiting our parents once a week,
and we need to buy something.
That's another 400-500 yuan a month,
so over 1,000 yuan altogether.
Four weeks a month,
that's 2,000 yuan.
2000, 2000...
And that's not counting anything else.
We wouldn't be able to buy clothes,
shoes,
go shopping,
watch movies,
or even eat out.
If we do,
we'd run out of money
and will have a fiscal deficit.
How much savings do you have left?
Over 20,000 yuan.
I'll transfer some money to you later.
And you pay this month's mortgage first.
If we had known earlier,
we should have saved more.
Let's not dwell on the past.
So,
we can cut back on the money
we give to my parents,
and I'll stop drinking coffee.
And I'll stop eating lunch out.
You can't cut lunch!
You need to eat lunch.
I'll make your lunch from now on.
Cooking at home
is healthier anyway.
I've got some good news.
I've found some
great ways to cut costs.
Why go to the supermarket to buy things?
Because there are specials.
A fish
costs 15 yuan in the morning,
but after 4:30 PM,
it's only 10 yuan.
A carton of eggs is 27 yuan,
but there's a promotion
where they're free
at certain times.
If you time it right,
you can get
that carton of eggs
for free.
Do you know the livestream channel?
Do you know the giveaway items?
Do you know the lucky bags?
If you're patient enough,
you can get all sorts of things:
chickens, ducks,
fish, meat.
Flash sales?
Yes, flash sales.
These are all great methods,
but we can't just
focus on cutting costs.
We need to increase our income as well.
When are you planning
to contact
the CEO you met in Beijing.
I'll give him a call in a bit.
You've got to strike while the iron's hot.
Otherwise, in a few days,
he might not even remember who you are.
Okay.
This job was introduced
to you by Mei Yiduo.
There's no shame
in asking her for help with finding a job.
What are you doing?
Didn't you say you needed to restock?
Li Lin isn't doing well.
How did he switch to a domestic one?
I bought this, okay?
Guess there is no love between same genders.
Eat or not?
Sure!
Mr. Zhang is looking for you.
What's going on?
Mr. Lan was personally approached by the boss and has already left the company.
When did that happen?
Just now.
The two Content Departments are merging.
Seize the opportunity,
you're due for a promotion.
Will there be a raise?
Your level is not something I can decide.
The boss has to decide that.
Make sure you negotiate well.
Mr. Zhang.
Were you looking for me?
Yes, have a seat.
I wanted to discuss something with you.
Mr. Lan from the Content Department
suddenly submitted his resignation.
Mr. Lan is leaving?
The process is already underway.
I'm thinking
we merge Content Department One and Two,
and I'd like you to take charge.
What do you think?
If we can merge the Content Departments,
it should definitely boost efficiency.
Alright,
go ahead and coordinate the handover with him.
Then
draft a merger plan
and bring it to me for review.
Sure,
I'll get it done.
Well,
anything else?
once
the content center is established,
what should everyone call me?
Content Director,
CCO (Chief Culture Officer).
Chief Content Officer...
Then my salary would be on par with a VP's, right?
Pretty much.
I'll talk to Rachel about it then.
What do you mean, talk to Rachel?
About the salary, of course.
She can't handle this,
you need to discuss it with me.
So, what do you think?
I think...
I've sold my house already.
Don't you know what's going on
with the company right now?
Once I'm back on my feet,
I'll make up for it, I promise.
So, what am I now?
Here,
take this for now.
I'll definitely make it up to you later.
What's going on now?
The Content Director's raise.
Xu Meng'an, you're really something.
Negotiating a raise that's different from everyone else's.
In all my years,
I've never heard of
a Content Director getting a raise
in the form of a shopping card.
How did you manage that?
Teach me your ways!
Don't distract me.
Quickly find out
for me
how much
a Content Director earns per month?
There's no need to ask around.
How can I manage this role
without knowing the market rates?
So, how much should I ask for?
I can't tell you.
First, I don't want to hurt your feelings,
and second, I have to consider Mr. Zhang.
What if you
find out and get unhappy,
and quit?
What would we do then?
Am I being naive?
No,
you're just kind-hearted.
How much money do you think is in the card
One thousand?
Two thousand?
You're thinking too much.
Five hundred.
How could it be that low?
The year-end
bonus is usually several thousands
and several thousands.
Yes, that's what I gave to Mr. Zhang.
The cards with more money have already been given away.
There is only a card with a limit of 500 yuan left.
This card is one I gave to him.
How much did you give him?
What do you mean?
I just wondered...
if he could give me one of these cards
every month,
that would be great.
Mr. Liu,
this is Li Lin.
Did you review my resume?
Oh, yes, I'm Mei Yiduo's classmate.
Yes, yes.
You are on a business trip.
Beijing.
No, I'm not in Beijing.
I'm in Chunjiang.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay. I...
Next time I'm in Beijing,
I'll visit you. Is that okay?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Bye, bye.
Awkward.
What's going on?
Where did you get the discounted eggs?
Over there, over there.
Okay, okay.
Get me a box of the discounted eggs!
the discounted eggs!
One box per person.
Give me one first! Just give me one first!
Watch out, my basket.
Sorry, sorry.
Don't push, don't push.
You stepped on my foot.
Young man...
Give me one!
Young man,
could you please
grab a box for me?
You want one box?
Alright, alright.
I'll squeeze in first.
Hello?
Mr. Li,
Get me a box, please.
This is Zhao.
Your resume is impressive,
but we don't have
any current hiring plans
at our company.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about that.
Okay, okay, thank you thank you.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
Where are the discount eggs?
They're all gone.
They were gone at once.
What's left are the full-price eggs.
Next time, come earlier.
Just answering a phone call,
the eggs were gone.
Dad,
what dish are you planning to cook?
Isn't this loofah?
Isn't that pumpkin?
I'll fry them together.
What's gone?
Nothing, nothing,
just the eggs.
Eggs?
There are plenty of eggs.
How could they be gone?
Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.
There are still eggs at home,
so we won't buy more.
No need to buy more.
Let's go.
Can these two be fried together and taste good?
It's really delicious.
Dad, sit here.
Eat slowly.
Here, switch to this one.
This popsicle is good.
The other one has too much sugar.
Too much sugar,
made of chocolate.
This one has no sugar
and no fat.
This is good and healthy.
What's going on?
At home,
my wife manages me.
And now, out here,
my daughter's husband has to manage me too?
This has too much sugar-too sweet.
But life should be sweet, right?
It's fine, let me eat it. It's no big deal.
Alright,
just eat slowly, this one is too cold.
How come you have time to shop at the supermarket?
Well, today I
have a meeting
with a client later,
so I am not too busy.
Earlier, when I
was picking out loofahs,
I heard
the supermarket staff mention that
the discounted eggs had arrived.
I saw a bunch
of elderly people
rushing over,
so I thought I'd check it out.
When I looked up,
I saw someone ahead of me
who looked a lot like you
same height,
same build,
even the same face shape.
I called out,
"Li Lin, Li Lin,"
but no one responded.
Then I thought,
it can't be you.
You're
a high-level professional,
a white-collar worker.
How could you
be fighting with these elderly folks
for discounted eggs?
Don't you think?
Yes.
It definitely wasn't you.
It wasn't me.
I must have mistaken someone else.
I just
saw them making such a fuss,
so I went over to take a look.
When I came there, I saw they were
fighting for eggs.
When I turned around,
I saw you were standing behind me.
Yes, yes, that's right.
Didn't I almost hit you with that loofah?
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
So, how's work at your place? Busy?
Yes,
quite busy.
Still doing design work?
Yes.
Really busy.
But no matter how busy
you are,
it's just a pen,
a ruler, a compass,
and a piece of paper, right?
How busy can it be?
How long has it been
since you came over to play chess with me?
Look, you're
so busy, you've forgotten.
It's been two weeks.
Two weeks!
Indeed.
Dad,
I've indeed been quite busy lately.
Yes, you're right.
All those...
All those tasks are still there.
Those tasks are still there.
Now, my boss
wants me to
go out
and meet people,
expand business,
and explore the market.
Times have changed.
So...
Your boss has given you more responsibilities.
That's a good thing.
It means
you're not just doing product design anymore.
You might also get involved
in procurement and sales.
Yes,
getting familiar with everything.
Good.
Make sure to cherish this opportunity.
That's how it is.
More skills,
more options,
right?
Don't worry, Dad.
I've got a handle
on work.
Don't mind me being nagging.
I'm just reminding you a few things.
Also, we
won't play chess anymore.
I'm not playing chess anymore.
I am prepared to keep up with the times.
So what?
Keep up with the pace.
Stratego.
Stratego?
I'm telling you...
Who is playing stratego now?
That's something children play with.
What do you mean a kid's game?
Isn't it for kids,
currently?
It's something played by philosophers, thinkers,
writers,
and military strategists.
No, seriously,
are you really busy
or just pretending to be?
Or are you just lounging around at home?
I'm busy,
really busy.
Look at me, I'm out shopping,
and soon I have
to go to meet a client.
So you're really busy then.
That's good.
Okay.
It's good that you're really busy.
I hate lying the most.
I can forgive you for causing trouble,
but who taught you to lie?
Mengxin!
What's going on? Why are you so angry?
Alright, calm down.
Come on, Wanwan, Zhenzhen,
take your little brother
to play.
What's the matter?
Calm down.
It's not good for the baby.
I understand that
boys can be naughty
and mischievous.
I can even forgive them for causing trouble,
but he can't be playing tricks on the teacher.
After he played his prank,
he even lied to me!
Tell me, isn't that infuriating?
Don't get so upset just yet.
Let's figure out why this happened.
Xiongxiong just
transferred here, right?
He doesn't have many friends yet.
Maybe he's
playing tricks on the teacher
to get
some attention.
I think
we need to help him
adjust to this new environment quickly.
If he feels more at home,
he won't need to act out
to get noticed.
And since you're pregnant with your second child,
could it be that
you've unintentionally neglected Xiongxiong's feelings?
You guys just moved here,
so maybe everything feels new and exciting to you,
but Xiongxiong
lacks a sense of security.
Now that you're expecting a second child,
you should be even more
attentive to your firstborn.
There's precedent for this
in psychology.
Many sensitive children
start exhibiting unusual behaviors
when they find out their mom is having another baby.
I think you should
observe him closely.
Actually, since
we moved to this neighborhood,
it's not just Xiongxiong who feels insecure,
I haven't fully adjusted either.
Exactly!
When I first moved here,
I noticed how these moms
are really dedicated
to their kids.
They even
have their own little group
that's hard to break into.
So how do I
join these mom groups?
Easy.
Just trade your educational resources
with them.
I just moved here,
I don't have any educational resources.
If you want,
I can help you with that.
What do you have in mind?
I can transfer Wanwan and Zhenzhen's foreign tutor
to your Xiongxiong.
Then you share it
with Haoze's mom
and make a trade.
That's a great idea!
But if you transfer the tutor to me,
what will Wanwan and Zhenzhen do?
Before, I thought
giving the kids the best education
and the best life
was being responsible.
But now,
I realize that only
by figuring out my own life
and living it well
can I truly do right by them.
Here, here, here,
your
orange juice.
Why are you coming back so late?
Guess who I ran
into at the supermarket?
Who?
Guess.
Chen? Li? Wang?
Liu? Liu? Zhao?
Li.
Your elder son-in-law!
I saw him over there,
grabbing those
discounted eggs!
What? Isn't he supposed to be at work?
I asked him,
I said, "Why aren't you at work?"
He said
he's now out there running the market,
doing sales.
Look, look.
I saw on WeChat's moment
that he's selling insurance now.
Look!
Did he change jobs?
Honey!
You're back!
Where is your phone?
On the tea table.
I'm in the middle of a flash sale buying groceries.
Don't touch it, okay?
Flash sale!
Don't touch it!
Why did you delete it?
If you keep posting
those insurance ads,
the whole world's going to know you're unemployed.
You can't post that anymore, got it?
Weren't you the one who said
I should put my pride aside and ask for help?
I meant ask the people
who can actually get you a job!
Selling insurance isn't shameful.
My colleague
sells insurance
and does pretty well at it.
I don't know about others,
but you're definitely not doing well.
Are you someone
who makes money just by talking?
Did you contact the people
I told you to?
No response?
Look for yourself.
Your resume
isn't working.
What's wrong with it?
Look at the resume
I revised for you
and then compare it to your original one.
No wonder no one's replying to you.
If you can't even sell yourself,
how do you expect to sell insurance?
What were you thinking?
But this...
this...
is this still me?
Why wouldn't it be?
Yes, I might have exaggerated
a little when I wrote it.
But that's not the point.
The important thing is
to secure
an interview!
True...
that's what really matters,
right?
Exactly.
Got it.
Then I
go ahead and send out another round.
Send out another round.
Alright.
About our
household budget deficit,
I have an idea.
What is it?
I heard from a former colleague
that in my current situation,
I can go to my original company and get a certificate
saying that I was laid off.
That way, I can claim
unemployment benefits,
two thousand yuan a month,
for two years.
What do you think?
No way.
Why?
You've seen
my situation.
It's hard to find a job,
and two thousand yuan a month is not a small amount.
I'll stop as soon as
I find a job.
I said no, and that's final.
Why not?
I don't want
you to give up on yourself,
and I don't want
to see your name
on that list.
I'm back!
Oh, you're back.
Alright, I'll start cooking.
What are you drinking?
We're about to eat.
Milk tea.
He Lu gave it to me.
Let's go camping this weekend.
Mrs. Xu.
Do you have a lot of free time lately?
What's with that tone?
For the first time in my life,
I don't have to compete with your work for attention.
I'm starting to wonder if you're really unemployed.
Didn't we say we'd go camping
when we got the new car?
It's been six months,
and we still haven't gone.
All the camping gear we bought
hasn't even been used once.
Are you going or not?
If not, I'll go with your dad.
Fine, let's go.
Ha,
why don't you seem excited at all?
We'll go camping!
How excited should I be?
Should I be jumping for joy?
Yeah, yeah! So happy, so happy.
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
See you on Tuesday.
Yeah, see you.
And,
don't forget the homework!
I won't,
bye-bye.
Xiongxiong's mother!
Haoze's mother!
Was that the same tutor
from Mrs. Yu
just now?
Yes.
It was recommended to me by Wanzhen.
Mrs. Yu is really kind to you.
I've heard that tutor
is excellent.
I've been
struggling with this lately.
I want to find a tutor
for my son Haoze.
His spoken English
isn't that good,
and I want to help him improve.
You know,
distant relatives aren't as good as close neighbors.
Could you recommend the tutor to me?
I can,
but the thing is,
this tutor already teaches many children.
I'm afraid they might get spread too thin.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I came to see you about something else.
We're having a party
this weekend.
Since you've
just moved here
and haven't joined any gatherings yet.
Why don't you bring Xiongxiong along?
This party
could be like
a welcome party
for you.
What do you think?
Well,
okay then.
As for the tutor...
Distant relatives aren't as good as close neighbors, right?
I'll have a word with them.
Wonderful!
I knew it,
you're such a kind person,
Xiongxiong's mom.
You must come this weekend!
Okay.
We'll be expecting you at the party this weekend!
Thank you!
Bye!
Welcome, Mrs. Jia,
to the Happy Moms Group!
Where did I write it?
Yunjie says we're going camping this weekend,
right?
Right.
We've been talking about it for half a year,
but we haven't gone yet.
I don't want to disappoint her,
so we should go this time.
Why?
I want to sell the car.
Sell the car?
What about
commuting to work?
I can
take a taxi, subway,
or bus to work.
We used to
ride bikes, remember?
And
what about Yunjie?
We could
get a small electric bike.
You ride bike with her.
It's not far from school
and there's no traffic.
That's a good idea.
But we just bought this car
less than half a year.
If we sell it now,
we'll only get half the price.
I feel bad about it too,
but the current situation is different from the past,
and we can't keep living like this.
I checked a second-hand
car website today.
If we sell it well,
it could cover
five or six months of mortgage.
I give you ten months.
Can't you
find a job for ten months?
Look,
we calculated
the car costs, including fuel,
maintenance,
and washing.
It's over a thousand a month.
That's money we could save.
What do you think?
Let's think about it some more.
After all,
switching from an SUV
to a small electric bike
might be hard for Yunjie
to accept right away.
We can't worry about that too much.
Let's take her camping
and cheer her up.
Next week,
we should also explain the situation at home
to her
so she's mentally prepared.
We'll be going through
a tough period.
Where are we going?
Could you help me look at some apartments?
You want to buy an apartment?
I want to live closer to you.
What do you mean by living closer to me?
You have experience buying houses.
Could you help me as an advisor?
I can certainly help as an advisor.
I have a lot of experience
in buying houses.
The key
of the apartment is
location, location,
and location.
I can help you look at apartments,
but that's more of a company benefit,
not a personal favor.
Okay.
Which property are we looking at?
We're almost there.
Thanks a lot.
Mr. Zhang, Mrs. Zhang.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
Thank you.
Bye, bye.
Bye.
Wanzhen!
That materials
are for our sales department.
Please send them over as soon as possible!
Okay, okay!
The apartment of Huaxing?
I know their boss.
If you plan to buy this apartment,
I'll invite you for a meal
and give you
a discount.
You mentioned it was a company benefit.
Is it true?
You said it earlier.
I haven't had any drinks.
Welcome!
Wanzhen.
Why are you here?
Wanzhen,
why are you here?
Are there no sales here?
I'm working.
Working?
What job are you working for?
Can't you see I'm working?
Don't disturb me.
No, no,
let me explain.
Explain what?
This...
I'll help you with this.
Don't move.
Look.
This unit is rare
with its north-south orientation.
Let's go check other properties
another day.
Thank you.
You can take another look.
What are you looking at?
Let me help you.
Are you guys bored at work?
Go do your own thing.
Don't watch.
Director Sun,
the sales department's brochures
have been delivered.
Is there anything else you need me to do?
There's no more work.
You can leave once you're done.
Thank you.
Wanzhen.
Didn't you say you weren't feeling well recently?
Why are you out here instead of resting at home?
What about the kids
when you're outside.
This is where I work.
Don't disturb me, okay?
No, what kind of work is this?
You're just doing odd jobs here.
How much can you earn?
3,500 during the probation period,
5,000 after becoming permanent.
No, no, no.
Our family doesn't lack this little bit of money,
right?
We won't be a family
for long.
I need to get used to
this working life.
No.
Look at how you're talking.
Is it really necessary?
Yes.
I came to accompany a female colleague
to look at houses today,
but it doesn't mean
we're no longer a family.
Yu Hai,
actually, I've wanted to talk to you
about this for a long time.
But you haven't been coming home lately,
so I haven't had the chance.
Today,
I want to officially talk
about our divorce.