[English subtitles are available]
[Bright Time]
[EP11]
Xiaohua, I'm so hungry.
Why?
Didn't you just eat this morning?
But I'm still starving.
What do you want?
BBQ.
Grilled pork belly,
spicy beef,
fatty beef, grilled mushrooms,
potato slices,
and...
All right, stop.
I'll go
with you.
But...
I'll get fat.
Then...
just forget it.
Ma Yiming!
Why are you
putting my kumquat down?
It will die if it gets more sun.
Look at Mengyu's flowers.
I take such good care of them.
They need more sunlight.
Aren't you afraid they'll get sunburned?
What improper remarks
you've made!
I can't stand this anymore.
What are you gonna do?
Uh...
where's Xu Mengyu?
She hasn't been to class for a few days.
She's accompanying her mom
to prepare for a book signing.
How do you know
all this gossip
that I don't know about?
Right,
I'm a know-it-all!
What? Jealous?
Put my plant back!
No way!
Hmph!
Hello,
Ms. Xiao Yinqian.
I heard
your new novel
is set in a school.
Yes,
the idea came from my daughter.
She's in high school now,
and we talk about
a lot together.
Is your daughter's talent
in writing
inherited
or trained?
She's not specially trained.
I think her talent is even stronger
than mine.
At this signing ceremony,
I also wanna announce
that her first
collection of essays
will be out soon.
Liu Wen.
Xu Chao.
Jia Letian.
Mengyu, you're incredible.
But it's not published yet.
It's my first time
publishing a book,
so I brought some sample copies
for you guys to review.
You're so talented.
Honestly.
I'm a big fan
of you.
You flatter me.
Amazing!
Wow.
Xiaohua, this copy is for you.
I get one too?
Of course,
every type of reader
is important to me.
How come
anyone can publish a book?
Well, not everyone.
You can't.
Who cares?
Ling Dong,
looking forward for your feedback.
What is this? Let me see.
Lan Jinghui,
if you want one,
I can get you a copy,
but this is for Ling Dong.
No, thanks.
I don't deserve it.
No worries, Mengyu.
I'd like one too.
Ma Yiming,
this one is for Ling Dong.
Ma Yiming, take it.
Mengyu,
can I get another one?
Xiaohua, why do you want it?
To learn and improve.
I didn't print many.
I didn't expect it to be this popular.
If you really want,
I'll give you my personal copy.
Thanks, I'll read it carefully.
[What do you think?]
[It's really good.]
[So touching.]
Everyone,
I have
good news.
This week
is our school's activity week,
so media
will come to film.
I hope
you can stay
after school,
showcase your talents,
and help out.
I can.
What can you do?
Anything.
Fine, you can help
carry equipment.
Sure.
Xiaohua,
you'll be in charge of decorating
the bulletin board.
Okay.
Liu Shu, Lu Yao, Lin Keke,
do Xiaohua a favour.
All right.
Thank you all.
Over!
Stand up.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Bye.
I've printed everything.
We can start now.
Why are you so late?
We have a lot
of work to do.
C'mon, we'll die.
Look!
Let's take photos with Mengyu.
Good idea!
But, how about...
Xiaohua, can you start first?
We'll be back
soon.
Thank you.
Sure.
Help us out.
Thanks a lot.
You're the best.
Let's go.
Bye.
Mengyu.
Welcome. Here.
Okay.
Well,
you can do it together.
What do you need to put up?
These...
Let's get to work.
Oh, okay.
Four pretty girls together.
Four of you.
Perfect.
Hey, boy...
Sorry.
[Let's continue.]
[It's fine.]
[Good.]
Ma Yiming, let's go play basketball.
I'm not going, Jinghui.
I'm taking photos.
What do you have to do here?
I haven't finished the task
assigned to me.
You go ahead.
Can't believe you.
A full-body shot, okay.
You should
dodge to your left.
Too late now.
Xiaohua,
are you dumb?
They're taking pictures,
leaving you doing this alone,
huh?
Enough talk. Just do it.
You handle the tape.
Lucky you
ran into us today.
What if you hadn't?
First time realizing
she can't say no?
Today,
I'm teaching her to say no.
Got it.
Is someone talking?
I didn't hear anything.
I hear nothing.
Got it.
What's that noise?
All right, all right!
I'll say that more often,
like "no", "no way"...
Happy now?
Now that's more like it.
Apprentice,
remember my lessons.
I'm not your apprentice.
Quick learner.
Just tear the tape.
Let's get to work.
Great job, everyone.
I bought you drinks
with my own money.
Enjoy it.
You're so considerate.
It's the best time.
C'mon.
I want one too.
Qingtian,
come here.
What's up?
I bought you
your favorite milk tea.
Wow! It is!
Thank you.
Enjoy it.
Thanks, you're so sweet.
Excuse me, how about taking a photo?
C'mon, good chance.
Okay, look at me.
All right,
three,
two...
Wait! Count me in!
Me too!
Come on!
And me.
Group photo.
Here we go.
3, 2, 1,
cheese!
[All the hourglasses in the world]
[have spilled onto this beach.]
[I walk on the fragments of time,]
[trying to reach]
[the sea.]
[If life was treated as an hourglass]
[with the sand]
[slipping away,]
[we'd reflect on the fleeting time.]
[All the hourglasses in the world]
[have spilled onto this beach...]
[... with the sand]
[slipping away...]
[we'd reflect on...]
[Exactly the same.]
[Xu Mengyu plagiarized.]
We need to focus on the view
on the world, life, and values.
These have appeared on past exams,
though I can't say if they'll be
on this year's.
If they do,
expect a five-point question.
Memorize this:
what are worldviews, life views,
and values?
They're
the essence of cultural literacy.
All right,
let's call it a day.
Over!
Stand up.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Bye.
[I want hotpot.]
[I want something tasty.]
Hotpot, stir-fried meat, or veggies?
- Hotpot.
- Stir-fried meat.
Hotpot.
Xiaohua,
what's up?
Nothing.
Wake up, let's head to school.
It doesn't need much water.
Thanks.
When you're troubled,
it's best not to multitask.
Ling Dong,
do you
have any secrets
you want to keep hidden?
I mean,
I found out something
very personal.
I don't know if I should keep it.
But even if I do,
others will soon find out.
So what do you want to do?
I'm thinking of
telling her I know,
but I don't want
to hurt her pride.
Pride can be rebuilt, but losing dignity
is harder to recover from.
Do you want
to protect her pride
but risk her losing dignity
in front of more?
Of course not. I don't want her
to lose her dignity.
Talk to her.
It might help.
Mengyu.
Come with me.
Are you going to tell everyone?
That was not my intention.
Then what are you trying to say?
You're really talented.
You don't need to do this.
Is that all you want to say?
I hope you can
withdraw the article
before the book is published,
so the mistake
stops here.
Xiaohua,
can you keep it for me?
This essay collection
is very important to me.
But it's not truly yours
if you do it this way.
I can't let others know,
especially not my mom.
Do you understand?
Even if you don't do this,
you can still publish a book.
Plus,
your mom is such a famous
and excellent writer.
Precisely because
she's a famous writer,
I've had to be better than others
since I was little.
Stronger abilities, higher expectations.
So I can't let her know
I'm just ordinary,
that I can't write good articles.
I don't want to disappoint her.
Have you
talked to your mom about this?
It's pointless.
She won't listen.
She thinks her daughter
is always the most talented,
just lacking confidence.
So every day,
she tells me to be confident!
I'm scared
she'll find out one day
that I'm nothing.
My grades are average,
and when I don't do well,
my mom gets really mad,
scolds me a lot.
But after every scolding,
she makes me
a nice meal.
Because she loves me,
and she knows
I tried my best.
So I think
you should talk
to your mom again.
I believe she'll understand you.
And...
I won't
tell anyone about this.
You serious?
This is our secret.
Mengyu,
I didn't understand the physics problem
the teacher explained.
Did you get it?
Yeah, I got it.
I'll help you after lunch.
Okay.
Mengyu, what are you looking at?
Nothing.
Go save us a seat first.
Keke.
I didn't get this dish.
Just wanted to try it.
Lan Jinghui, have some of mine.
My apprentice is the best.
But I wanted that meat.
Am I seeing things?
Jinghui, have mine too.
Too late.
Xiaohua,
I got today's special
just for you.
Mengyu?
Thanks.
Xiaohua,
when did you get
so close to her?
You didn't betray us,
did you?
Of course not.
Xiaohua,
you're the first person
Mengyu's been so nice to.
What's your secret?
This is the first time
I've seen this at school.
They made it especially for her?
Maybe she poisoned it?
Nonsense,
Mengyu isn't like that.
Maybe it's because I helped her
promote her essay collection.
Sh! Eat up!
It'll get cold.
Something's off with her.
Just eat, guys.
Mengyu.
Mom.
Take a look at this.
Mom,
I have something to tell you.
Later.
Look at this now.
I picked out a few outfits
for your book launch.
Do you like any of them?
How about this one?
It's okay.
A bit plain, right?
This one?
It's nice.
Right, the details are perfect.
You'll look great in this
at your event.
My daughter is the best.
Mengyu,
what did you
want to tell me?
Nothing, Mom.
Okay, I'll go order the clothes.
Thanks.
Unbelievable.
[She really did this?]
[Yeah.]
[That's like... blatant plagiarism.]
[It's word-for-word the same.]
[How is this possible?]
[I can't believe it either.]
[Is it true?]
[She just]
[turned it into her book?]
Xu Mengyu...
Mengyu...
Xiaohua,
I can't believe you did this.
I trusted you
to keep it a secret.
If you were going to expose me,
why pretend
to be nice?
How despicable!
What's going on?
Xiaohua,
what's this all about?
Xiao Xiaohua,
how did you find out
Xu Mengyu plagiarized?
Yeah, you kept it hidden well.
Any more gossip
to share with us?
Xiao Xiaohua,
[we all misjudged you.]
[Didn't expect you to be so cunning.]
[Because of you,]
[Mengyu is too embarrassed]
[to come to school!]
[Seriously, Xiao Xiaohua,]
[you went too far.]
[You wanted everyone to know,]
[right?]
Watch your words.
Actually,
it's not entirely Xiaohua's fault,
right?
If Xu Mengyu hadn't plagiarized,
none of this would have happened.
This is just justice being served.
This kind of underhanded tactic,
isn't it just personal revenge?
I say,
be more upright.
I believe in Xiaohua.
This isn't something she would do!
Mengyu said
Xiao Xiaohua did it!
If not her, then who?
[Patriotism]
[is the core spirit]
[of the Chinese nation.]
[It's reflected]
[in unity, peace,]
[hard work, bravery,]
[and self-improvement.]
[They complement each other,]
[all reflecting]
[the theme of patriotism.]
[At any time,]
[patriotism unites]
[and motivates the Chinese people,]
[serving as a spiritual pillar]
[for all ethnic groups]
[to stand strong together.]
[Patriotism is not abstract.]
[It's very real.]
[As the Chinese people...]
[Ma'am,]
[are you sure]
[you don't want to reconsider?]
Thank you, Ms. Fang,
but I've decided.
I'll come in a few days
to handle Mengyu's transfer.
[All right,]
[best of luck.]
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Transfer?
[I just heard.]
[I don't know.]
Listen!
you've driven her to transfer.
Are you happy?
What?
Transfer?
Xu Mengyu?
Her mom came
to handle the transfer.
I saw it myself!
How did it come to this?
Is she okay?
Why did you do this?
I didn't.
Ma Yiming,
do you know
what you're doing?
This whole thing is 'cause
Xu Mengyu plagiarized.
Do you know that?
Jinghui,
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Do you know what she's doing?
Does she know
what she's doing?
The plagiarism
isn't even confirmed.
Wait,
she said she didn't do it.
Do you believe her?
Yes, I do.
Mengyu said
only Xiao Xiaohua
knew about this.
But I didn't!
Ma Yiming,
there's no
concrete evidence
that Xiao Xiaohua did it.
So, since there's a dispute,
we should find evidence.
I think Ling Dong is right.
Why don't we look for evidence
instead of arguing over here?
Mengyu said it herself.
Jinghui, don't you know?
Xiao Xiaohua said she didn't.
You heard it too.
See?
I think he's right.
You just don't understand Mengyu.
Why do you think...
Did I ask you to speak?
Can you shut up?
Ma Yiming,
you're just
favoring Xu Mengyu,
do you know that?
I'm not.
But you're favoring
Ling Dong!
What does this have to do with him?
Whatever he says
is right,
and whatever I say is wrong!
With
no evidence,
why believe him
but not me?
I believe whoever
makes sense.
Sense, huh?
Let me tell you,
ever since you started
tutoring with him,
you've been glued together.
Whenever I invited you
to play basketball
or hang out,
you just
refused!
What's your excuse?
Is that your sense?
So
now studying with him
is wrong?
Yes, it is!
Keep studying with him.
Don't come to me.
Ma Yiming!
Leave me alone!
What are you drawing?
It's ugly.
King of the beasts.
King of the table.
What do you see here?
C'mon, look!
Why are you ignoring me?
Is it not good enough?
Lan Jinghui.
Or because...
Recognize it?
[Can you reach it?]
[Give it to me!]
[Just a bit short!]
Lan Jinghui.
What now?
Does it look alike?
Yes.
Really?
Well? Does it now?
What are you doing?
Finally got a photo with Ling Dong.
Too bad,
can't see his face clearly.
Next time...
I must get
a clear one.