[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP27]
Guards!
Give my order:
I am deeply grieved
by the death of Sima Biqiu.
[Investigate this matter thoroughly.]
[From today on,]
lock down the city,
and no one is to leave.
I'll interrogate the suspicious myself.
Yes, Sir.
My lord, thank you
[for helping Biqiu]
[free from his suffering.]
Today,
I still have to go to Nanshan
to console his family.
His father has been
raising pigeons there all his life.
[And now,]
[he would have to bury his own son.]
After I return,
we can further discuss how to
[take down the masked spectre.]
Lord Mo, my condolences.
Raising pigeons?
[I fear that]
Mo Qianzhi, the magistrate of Yingzhou,
might have treacherous intentions, thus
[I command you to secretly investigate.]
Once the red carrier pigeon arrives,
you can send your message.
[Could Biqiu]
[have been a spy planted by]
[the Empress Dowager in Yingzhou?]
[Was Biqiu]
[the middleman for my secret messages?]
It's okay now.
What's wrong?
I think
I know why Biqiu was killed,
but I can't tell you.
It's okay.
You don't have to if you don't want to.
Shen Du,
do you trust me?
If one day,
I stood against
your dearest one,
would you still trust me?
Aren't you my
dearest one?
I apologize.
So it looks like this lead was wrong.
The lead claimed the masked spectres
had been spotted outside the city,
but there's not a soul in sight,
let alone the masked spectres.
Sir,
if I may ask,
what's going on today?
Why isn't there
even a street vendor
anywhere in the city?
[Young man,]
[you must be from out of town, right?]
[What terrible timing.]
Just yesterday morning,
the masked spectre
killed Mr. Biqiu at the yamen.
I heard the scene was gruesome.
[He was even skinned!]
[No one dares to come out anymore.]
[I only came out]
[because I had to bring some medicine]
[to my mother outside the city.]
I really should get going now.
Only we
[and a few people]
at the yamen
knew about the murder
at around 3 a.m.
How did the public
find out about this?
This is indeed suspicious.
[If no one had deliberately spread it,]
[how could a large city like Yingzhou]
have learned about it
and turned into a ghost town in a day?
Lady Yan,
the chief has a message for you.
The masked spectre
is holding civilians hostage at the gates.
[Please go there quickly.]
Like a moth to a flame,
it perishes instantly.
[No reincarnation is involved,]
yet immortality remains.
What are they doing?
They're doing witchcraft.
My lord.
[Good.]
Everyone's here.
Now,
I will perform how to eat people.
That's Machete of Western Regions,
the weapon that beheaded Li Kaixiang.
[Masked Spectre,]
what do you want?
I offer this to you, gods,
and I seek your blessings!
Masked Spectre, if
you don't want to die a gruesome death,
then let them go!
Stop!
What exactly do you want?
Mo Qianzhi,
you came just in time.
The Three Yang's Day is coming soon.
Let these women go!
Let's talk.
Sure.
Then let's see how sincere you are.
[If you agree to]
[stop investigating]
[the masked spectre case from today on,]
I will let them go.
If you refuse,
[then the entire Yingzhou]
will become a ghost town!
Shut up!
How dare you be so audacious!
Biqiu was devoted to the people,
as everyone in Yingzhou knows.
[Yet you mercilessly murdered him,]
[skinned him,]
and tortured him endlessly.
You are utterly ruthless!
So you don't agree then.
Do you want everyone in the city dead
or what?
Kill them!
Damn it.
Kill them all!
Close the gates!
Release the arrows!
Pan Chi!
Qianzhi,
[don't! Stop!]
The Masked Spectre harms the innocent.
[He must be killed!]
How is he?
Much alive.
This dart is poisonous.
We need to stop the bleeding now.
You stay here.
Don't come out no matter what.
Hold on.
Pan Chi, hold on.
Pan Chi, stay with me.
[Wake up!]
Pan Chi.
Pan Chi, wake up.
Pan Chi! Pan Chi!
I never thought
one day you would be
holding a sword to my neck.
Order them to stop the arrows.
I'm afraid I can't.
Now there's finally a chance
to take out the Masked Spectre,
how could I let him go?
For the people in Yingzhou,
I'd rather wrongful kill than to let him go.
If I kill anyone innocent,
I'm willing to repay with my life!
Killing an official incurs death penalty.
My lord,
don't threaten me with the death penalty.
I put the people first
and want to take down the Masked Spectre
to return peace to them.
I would say the same thing
even in front of Her Highness.
Open your eyes and see!
Is this the result you want?
[If Xiuxiu were here,]
would she want to
see you like this?
Xiuxiu...
Stop the arrows!
Xing.
[Guangchun Hall?]
This is the Fire Moth Sect's headquarters?
Good.
It's really you.
[Ji Dafu,]
first, you killed Li Kaixiang,
then framed Li Kairui for it,
and now you're using Liu Zongyuan
as a scapegoat.
What are you really up to?
I didn't frame Li Kairui.
I even paid to help him clear his name.
As for Li Kaixiang,
so what if I killed him?
He deserved to die,
so did Liu Zongyuan.
Those foolish commoners.
They are not worth grieving over.
Perhaps you are
the most foolish of all.
[The people you've killed]
[were all innocent.]
You were a son and a husband.
You also have parents and a wife.
[Do you know how painful it is]
to lose a loved one?
Shut up.
How could I not know
the pain
of losing a loved one?
But when I saw Xiulian,
she... she was barely recognizable,
completely mutilated.
But they had promised me
they would bring Xiulian back to life!
She will be back!
Who are they?
They promised you
they would bring Xiulian back to life?
It's a pity
[that you don't look like her.]
[So I'll just]
take you organs.
Shen Du.
Yan Xing,
are you okay?
I'm okay.
How did you find here?
The Masked Spectre's lost a piece of
his clothes during the fight,
[and it had a strong medicinal smell.]
[It reminded me of the place in]
[Yingzhou with the most abundant herbs,]
[which is also]
[the least likely to be suspected-]
[Guangchun Hall.]
Let's get out of here.
What's that?
Snakes!
Shen Du, watch out!
No matter when,
don't you dare get hurt for me.
Shen Du,
thank you for saving me.
When we get out,
I will
be your real wife.
Did you bring the money I asked for?
The sooner
I can get out of Yingzhou safely,
the sooner you can relax.
The money is ready.
I put it at...
You...
How dare you?
The Lord won't let you off!
I'm afraid you might not live to see it.
Ji Dafu, you murderer,
you won't get away!
Guards!
Lock this criminal in the death cell.
Yes, Sir!
Jing Lin, hurry up!
[The water is almost boiled dry,]
and your meat is still not ready.
What's the hurry?
Don't underestimate
my knife skills.
[Here, kid.]
You're a kid!
[Mr. Pan,]
here is your
[longevity stew,]
[nourishing mutton soup]
and yam and pork congee.
Please enjoy.
Did Lady Yan
ask you
to make these for me?
Lady Yan asked me to make the
[longevity stew]
[and nourishing mutton soup for you.]
And it was him who made the
[yam and pork congee.]
Please enjoy.
What's on Lord Shen's menu?
There's only one dish
on Lord Shen's menu.
It's the
tonic soup that
[took Lady Yan two hours.]
[Mr. Pan,]
please enjoy.
Kid, let's go.
You didn't hurt your hand.
Why can't you drink it yourself?
I hurt my shoulder blade.
I can't raise my hand.
Shen Du,
it's been three days.
You should have healed by now.
Stop lying.
So who was it
that said she'd be a real wife?
It's three days and you get bored?
Maybe
a real wife for three days?
Don't make excuses.
Shen Du,
I still haven't asked you
why you pretended to be blind.
When did your moonless sight
heal?
[You killed the venomous snake]
[with such precision.]
[You couldn't have done it by hearing.]
It's been healed for a while now.
For a while?
Then...
[That time at the bathhouse, he was]
[pretending to be blind?]
Have it yourself.
My Lord.
Speak.
Ji Dafu has been captured.
[Mo Qianzhi,]
stop!
How dare you
stop the Chief of the IG?
My Lord.
Based on my investigation,
[Ji Dafu]
[is the true culprit behind]
[the masked spectre case.]
After the killings,
he gouged out Er Laipi's eyes,
[beheaded Li Kaixiang,]
[and took Liu Zongyuan's liver.]
His crimes are unforgivable, and only
his death can bring justice to the people!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
[Kill him!]
[He killed so many people.]
He deserves more than death!
[That's right!]
[His crimes are unforgivable,]
[and even a thousand cuts wouldn't be]
[enough to bring justice to the people.]
[He deserves more than death!]
[Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!]
[Kill him now!]
[He deserves to die!]
Ji Dafu ran an illegal gambling den
and murdered your families.
[His crimes are unforgivable.]
Execute him now!
Wait!
Lady Yan, what do you mean?
Are you
trying to plead for Ji Dafu?
Some details of this case remain unclear.
Ji Dafu has confessed
to all his crimes,
[and the evidence is undeniable.]
It's time.
Execute him at once!
My lord,
weren't you the one who
wanted to bring justice to the people?
So why are you trying to
save this vile criminal now?
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
I can't die! I can't die!
I don't want to die! I don't want to die!
I don't want to die!
Yeah!
Good! Yes! Yes!
[Good! Good! Yes!]
He deserved it!
Justice to all!
Good! Good!
[Yes! Yeah!]
Yes!
[My lord,]
what I did
was what the people wanted.
[Mr. Mo, you are truly wise.]
The scent on him-
I recognized it from where I was held.
Jing Lin.
Yes, Sir.
Look into it.
He is the Chief of the IG,
the infamous White Death of Xiang'an?
[Why did he try to stop the execution?]
[Who knows?]
[What goes around comes around.]
[Enough of that.]
Let's get out of here.
Let's go. Let's go.
My lord,
secret report from Yingzhou says that
[Ji Dafu is dead,]
[and the situation has changed.]
They need to proceed with caution now.
Forget it.
It's just a trivial matter,
not important.
Yingzhou is only the beginning.
One shot alone can't win the battle.
Stay vigilant in other cities.
[Catching them off guard]
is the key to our success.
Yes, my lord.
How are
the arrangements in Nanlang and Xichen?
[Everything has been done as you ordered.]
Good.
If heaven assists me,
I will triumph.
If not,
I will defy heaven.
The people of Yingzhou
are all happy about
Ji Dafu's death.
That's evident.
Ji Dafu has committed many heinous crimes.
And the masked spectre case
has caused great fear
among the people of Yingzhou.
They hated him deeply.
Now that he's been brought to justice,
of course they would be happy.
Such a shame.
The people are all praising
Mo Qianzhi for his action.
But Ji Dafu
has clearly been severely tortured
and has lost his sanity.
We have lost our lead yet again.
Now the people of Yingzhou
have all seen
Mo Qianzhi's firm stance against evil
and his decision on execution,
and it was me
who tried to stop it.
One is praised by everyone,
the other
is the fearsome
[White Death.]
[To you and Mr. Mo,]
the people hold
completely opposite views.
As long as I am at peace with myself,
I don't fear what people say.
But what people say can be fearsome.
I'm just afraid that...
Lord Mo's
public execution of Ji Dafu might
seems like a way to soothe the people,
but it's a bit odd and
inconsistent
with his usual
meticulous approach.
When the Masked Spectre
was causing chaos in the city that day,
he brought up the Three Yang's Day.
I remember Qianzhi's expression
was somewhat unusual.
What's special about the Three Yang's Day?
It's coming up soon right?
Wait a second,
my mom told me
that this year's Three Yangs' Day
is indeed different from before-
it's the once-in-a-decade
ominous day.
Ominous day?
What does that mean?
Meaning lots of ill omens.
She asked me to be extra careful
and not to go outside.
Of course,
my mom tends to believe everything.
It was only hearsay.
Mo Qianzhi, as I know him,
would not care about such things.
My lord.
Did you find anything?
As you have predicted,
I visited several households
and found that the women
taken by the Masked Spectre that day
were all rescued by the officials
of Mr. Mo's Yamen.
[However,]
there was no news of them
being sent back home.
What?
Then where are those women?
Did Mr. Mo
really take them?
It seems that the Masked Spectre
didn't take those women randomly,
he had chosen those specific women
for a reason.
[But I've looked into it.]
Those women all had
different
family backgrounds.
It's Mo Xiuxiu.
Xiuxiu?
Do you
remember the portrait of Mo Xiuxiu
in the Mo residence?
Including Du Xiaowan,
the five women
abducted by the Masked Spectre
that day all shared
a resemblance
to Mo Xiuxiu.
What if that wasn't
just a coincidence?
Ji Dafu is dead, but
the trouble in Yingzhou is far from over.
If our suspicions are correct,
Mo Qianzhi could have colluded with
the Fire Moth Sect for long.
On the Three Yang's Day,
they will make a move again.
So what do we do next?
-Find.
[-Find.]
Find?
Find.
Those women who were taken
are the key.
Yingzhou is a big city.
Where could he be hiding them?
[In the least likely places]
[of course.]
My Lord,
everything is ready.
[Wait for the timing.]
Good.
Xiuxiu,
no matter what,
[I will activate the formation today]
[and bring you back.]
[Mr. Mo,]
please let me go.
[I have been obedient.]
[Please spare my life.]
[Let me go.]
I don't want to die.
Jing Lin.
Xiuxiu.
Thank goodness we got here in time.
They are all alive.
Xiu?
Qianzhi.
Qianzhi,
how does this look?
[It's very pretty.]
[Qianzhi.]
Mr. Mo.
It's not possible.
Xiuxiu wouldn't call me Mr. Mo.
She only calls me Qianzhi.
[It's not possible.]
It couldn't have failed.
It couldn't have failed!
It's you.
You scared away Xiuxiu's spirit
so she couldn't find the way back.
Shen Du,
how can you be so cruel!
There's no such thing
as resurrection in this world.
He has gone mad
to the point of losing his humanity.
Humanity?
Don't judge
unless you've been in my shoes.
[Shen Du,]
[you should know this]
[better than anyone.]
If it were possible to bring back
those who died unjustly,
what would you choose?
[Xiuxiu]
was the kindest,
the purest person in the world.
But those vile men
forced her to die.
Mo Xiuxiu
didn't die from illness?
What
really happened to Xiuxiu?
Before Xiuxiu died,
she kept asking
'why'.
[What did she do which is wrong?]
[Please give us some food.]
Please give us some food.
What's going on?
[Sir,]
[some refugees blocked our path.]
Give them some food.
[Yes, Sir.]
Qianzhi,
the closer we get to Yingzhou,
the more refugees we encounter.
In the future,
if you take over Gannan,
I hope you will
help and protect these refugees
and give them a safe place to live.
My dear sister,
you are too kind.
[Here, Xiuxiu.]
[Welcome!]
Please, come in.
Let's just stay here for the night.
The horses must be exhausted too.
Come in. Come in.
Miss,
do you not feel unwell?
Let me help you to
rest over there.
No need, no need.
My family needs water urgently.
I must bring it back quickly.
You look very kind.
Will you please accompany me a bit?
Okay.
I'll help you get home.
Thank you, Miss.
Let's go.
Help! Help!
I just ran into some bad people.
My family is waiting for me at the station.
Would you please help me get back there?
Don't worry.
I will help you.
Xiuxiu!
Don't come near.
No!
Don't come near!
[Xiuxiu!]
It's okay now.
Come back with me.
[No one will hurt you ever again.]
No.
I made a mistake,
Qianzhi.
[But I only wanted to help her.]
What did I do which is wrong?
Xiuxiu.
Xiuxiu!
[No!]
[Qianzhi.]
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am.
But if you want to bring back your sister,
I can help you with that.
Bring the dead back to life?
That's absurd.
The world is vast
and full of wonders.
Just because you've not seen it in Cang
[doesn't mean it doesn't exist.]
As long as your heart is sincere enough.
Can you truly
bring the dead back to life?
Of course.
The fire moth rises from the ashes.
That is the essence of the Fire Moth Sect.
[If you wish to follow me,]
then I
can resurrect your sister.
As long as you can bring back Xiuxiu,
I, Mo Qianzhi,
would do anything for you.
[These so-called secrets to resurrection]
are just ploys
to manipulate people.
You were lost in your obsession.
That's why you believed it.
Qianzhi,
did you really not know
that it was because of your protection
that the Fire Moth Sect has ravaged
Gannan for years,
killing countless people?
[How could you still believe]
[they could bring back Mo Xiuxiu?]
Why shouldn't I?
[What reason do I have not to?]
[As long as I can bring back Xiuxiu,]
[what does it matter]
[killing a few more?]
Those bastards,
didn't they deserve to die?
The Masked Spectre of Guangchun Hall
killed them for me.
[Xiuxiu helped those refugees,]
[but then she was humiliated by those]
[vile men and jumped off a cliff.]
[How could I not avenge her for that?]
Help me! Help me!
Someone wants to kill me!
Don't be scared.
Help me!
We are in broad daylight.
Do you have no regard for the law?
Mr. Mo is here.
We will protect you.
It's them.
They want to kill me!
Why do they want to kill you?
Xiuxiu,
I will avenge you.
They all deserved to die!
They should all die for their sin!
[Shen Du, why]
[did you sabotage the sacrificial ritual?]
Why?
You just didn't want Xiuxiu to come back.
Those men deserved to die,
but what about them?
What did they do which is wrong?
Things are just not fair in this world.
[Shen Du,]
you know that well.
By using others' lives as sacrifices,
you're trading five lives
for the resurrection you want?
[Even if you were to succeed,]
do you really think Xiuxiu
would be at peace with it?
Qianzhi,
Xiuxiu is gone.
Xiuxiu is not dead.
I will bring her back.
Guards.
Using resurrection
as a means of manipulation
and performing rituals
with human organs.
So that means,
Lady Tang's removal of the victims' organs
after her killings might also be
influenced by the Fire Moth Sect and
was intended for the resurrecting ritual.
Creating mystery.
Spreading fear.
That's how the Fire Moth Sect
maintains control over their followers-
through intimidation and fear.
Xiu.
Be careful.
Careful.
Lady Yan,
is there really no way
to bring someone back to life?