English subtitles are available
Bright Time EP04
You mean someone did it on purpose?
Exactly.
Who?
I don't know.
You have one day
to find the person.
If failed,
all of your commendations
and extracurricular activities
for your class would be canceled.
Cancel?
I don't know.
Mr. Zhang.
We'll talk about you later.
What if
I succeed?
Are you qualified to talk to me?
I...
You only have
23 hours
and 55 minutes left now.
I'm leaving.
Wait a minute.
It has something to do with you, too.
Write a self-criticism.
I am no longer your student.
Please.
Hurry up.
Fuddy-duddy.
Have you heard?
Director Zhang will
cancel our commendations.
What shall we do?
Everything was fine when Lu Yao
and I left yesterday.
Maybe someone did it
by accident?
Who left last yesterday?
You should be the last person.
Lan Jinghui.
You mean I did it?
It shouldn't be you.
Then, should be
Xiao Xiaohua.
Do what?
You just frame others
without evidence.
We didn't.
No evidence can prove
it's not her.
And she was the last
to leave yesterday.
That doesn't prove
she did it.
That makes sense.
Qingtian.
Don't argue with them.
C'mon, what's the matter with you?
What's the problem?
Enough.
Stop arguing.
Go back to your seats.
Class begins.
Don't be angry.
Go back.
Well. Class begins.
Stand up.
Hello, teacher.
Please sit down.
Let's learn
a poem by Su Shi today.
Don't take it to heart.
We all know that you didn't do it
and who you are.
But I am so sad.
It is true that I was the last to leave.
If I had left later
and cleaned
the classroom more carefully,
it would not have happened.
But now I'm implicating Ms. Fang.
Xiaohua, you always
don't take credit,
but
blame yourself.
Is it an accident
or man-made?
I don't know.
But now
some people doubt Lan Jinghui.
I think
it's not impossible.
After all, he transferred here.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
To convict me?
You and Xiao Xiaohua were the last.
But it can't be
her.
So, I'm the man who broke the flowerpot
and the rack, right?
But
they shouldn't
doubt you so much.
Because there is a doubt.
Something changed?
If you did it,
you wouldn't
have thrown
your cactus.
Sure.
Another possibility exists.
You don't want
to be found out.
So you
threw it down on purpose.
Ling Dong.
Are we enemies?
You just don't like me, do you?
Whatever I do, you will do me wrong.
Right?
Take it easy.
I know it's not you.
In fact, from the beginning,
I believed it was not you.
Why do you believe me?
Because you're not so smart.
Now that you are,
tell me,
who did it?
Look.
This place
is obviously deeper
than others.
I suspect it might have been
hit by something.
If so,
there should be traces
on it.
What if it's not hard?
Not something like
a stone or a hammer.
Not a hard object?
If not...
I see.
What?
You don't know,
do you?
You really don't know.
Well, I'm telling you.
Basketball bag!
I met a man with a bag
when I went downstairs yesterday.
He may be on the basketball team.
But I didn't see exactly
what he looked like.
It was a basketball.
Shut up. That's my line.
I know who did it.
Lan Jinghui, where are you going?
Bye. Bi Peng.
Bye.
No. It's broken.
Just leave it open.
Why is it always broken?
I don't know.
Bi Peng, did you do it?
What are you talking about?
You smashed the flower rack
of my class?
Yeah.
Now you come with me
to Mr. Zhang
to make it clear.
Because of it,
he...
What if I did it?
Can you prove it?
You...
I happened to see
the "Best Ball in the World"
when I passed.
What do you mean, Lan Jinghui?
Are you laughing at me?
I did it on purpose.
But
the rack was not stable at all.
It's not my fault.
So who's to blame?
You, of course.
Because you pissed me off.
I don't mean it.
But now that it has happened,
it can teach you a lesson.
And
it's no use
knowing that I did it.
You have no proof.
Stop.
I'm telling you,
this is between us,
not my class.
Why?
It's all your fault
that your class
ended up like this.
Are you crazy?
Let's fight
one on one.
Don't mess with my class.
Well.
I am not afraid of you.
But first,
solve
your trouble.
I know you're just afraid of me.
Bi Peng! Bi Peng!
Bi Peng!
Everyone, turn the Chinese book
to page 23.
Well.
Today,
you'll learn a poem
created
in the Song Dynasty.
I believe
those who have read it
in advance
know that its author
is the famous
poetess Li Qingzhao.
Her works are mostly
subtle and concise,
different from others.
This has made her
so well-known.
The one
you're
about to learn
was completed
in a
specific context.
What do you mean, Lan Jinghui?
Are you laughing at me?
I did it on purpose.
No. It's broken.
Just leave it open.
I'll take you
to a good place later.
Where?
Just come with me.
Lan Jinghui!
Lan Jinghui?
Hello?
Lan Jinghui. Are you in there?
Is anyone here?
Lan Jinghui!
Lan Jinghui.
Can you hear me?
Wake up.
Lan Jinghui.
C'mon.
Wake up.
Lan Jinghui.
You sprayed me with water?
Make it clear, okay?
I saved your life.
Give me a hand.
C'mon.
Gosh.
You okay?
I don't like being touched.
But you just
carried me.
I made a mistake.
I should have dragged you out.
Why were you
in the gym just now?
Why did you faint?
I asked you first.
You can answer first.
I...
No comments.
Well, me too.
Um...
I'll tell you.
I'll...
tell you everything.
I'm afraid of darkness,
and afraid of
being locked in a dark room.
OK?
Are you satisfied?
I saw Bi Peng.
He's so mean.
Extremely!
He smashed the flower rack
of my class.
I'll tell Mr. Zhang
about it tomorrow.
Do you have any proof?
I...
No one will believe you.
What about you?
No.
Come on.
What the hell
are you
thinking?
Ling Dong. You idiot.
Sprayed me with so much water.
Don't you think I might catch a cold?
Don't say anything
about today.
It is up to you, my nephew.
I already told you,
don't call me that.
It's the last day.
But I have no idea
how to explain to Mr. Zhang?
In my opinion,
the culprit of it
is Lan Jinghui.
It was his fault
to put the heavy flowerpot
on the rack.
Even so,
we can't blame him for it.
Luyang,
it's you
who decided to put it outside.
But...
'cause...
Lan Jinghui led me
to do it.
You shouldn't say that.
We're talking about the person
who broke the rack.
It had nothing to do with him.
We just can't find
that person right now.
It was Lan Jinghui's fault anyway.
Yes, he might have done it.
He's very naughty.
Jinghui, where're you going?
Maybe it was he who dropped
the pot.
But...
For what?
He must have done it.
He's the last one to leave last time.
I think it was Lan Jinghui.
Yes, it must be him.
No one else could have done it.
I agree with you.
Right.
Get out of the way!
You should get back to your seats!
Mr. Zhang.
Did something bad happen?
No.
I know who
broke the flower rack.
Who is it?
Bi Peng from Class 8.
Then call him over.
No.
It's no use
talking with him.
Because he won't admit it.
That means
you have no proof.
Then you're smearing him.
Do you understand?
I...
I have no proof.
But it doesn't matter.
You can assume it's me.
I smashed the flower rack.
But it has nothing to do
with my teacher and classmates.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
If you need proof,
I'm the proof.
I can prove that
I did it.
So it wasn't an accident.
I did it
on purpose.
Are you satisfied with it?
So now you have no right
to blame Ms. Fang
or to cancel
all the activities
for my class.
You can expel me.
I'll face the consequence.
Lan Jinghui.
Do you think I'll
believe everything you say?
No heroics
in school!
Have you finished speaking?
All right.
Then let me say something.
I told Mr. Zhang that
I smashed the flowerpot
and the rack.
But it wasn't you!
Why did you say that to him?
What do you mean?
Why did you do that?
Nothing.
I just don't like
this school
as well as this class.
So I smashed them
in a fit of anger.
And now
I've had fun
and get tired.
So I'm leaving.
Say something!
Lan Jinghui just likes
to play pranks,
but I believe that
he didn't do it.
You...
Say something!
Jinghui,
seeing Ms. Fang
being criticized,
I was so worried
that I said something bad.
Jinghui, don't go.
Lan Jinghui.
You may have
taken the lead on it,
but I'm also responsible.
Let's go explain it
to the teacher.
Jinghui.
Lan Jinghui.
Please don't go.
Jinghui.
Don't go!
What are you doing?
Lan Jinghui, what happened?
Mr. Zhang, I want to tell you...
What?
Sit down first.
Sit down.
Now!
Come on.
Ms. Fang has
something to tell you.
From today on,
all the activities of our class
will be...
What if I did it?
Can you prove it?
You...
I happened to see
the "Best Ball in the World"
when I passed.
What do you mean, Lan Jinghui?
Are you laughing at me?
It's no use
knowing that I did it.
You have no proof.
What if I did it?
Can you prove it?
You...
I happened to see
the "Best Ball in the World"
when I passed.
What do you mean, Lan Jinghui?
Are you laughing at me?
It's no use
knowing that I did it.
You have no proof.
What if I did it?
Can you prove it?
You...
I happened to see
the "Best Ball in the World"
when I passed.
Attention please.
This is an announcement.
Bi Peng of Class 8, Grade 2
seriously violated regulations.
He'll be reprimanded at school
and given a warning.
Lan Jinghui,
you're also responsible
for this matter.
Go run around the playground 10 times.
Jinghui!
Cheer up!
Lan Jinghui!
Come on!
Come on, master!
Hold on!
Do it!
Jinghui.
Go!
Cheer up!
Come on!
Go for it!
Cheer up!
Lan Jinghui, do it!
Come on!
You're so slow!
10 times!
You should try it!
Cut the crap!
Jinghui, come on!
Only one time last.
Come on!
Cheer up!
Wait for me!
Come on, master!
Cheer up!
Come on, Jinghui!
The method works.
What?
So you knew all along that
it's not an accident.
I didn't know that.
I just believed
Lan Jinghui wouldn't do
such a thing.
What do you think
about him?
Well,
he's
like a hedgehog.
If I try to change
his character by force,
I'm afraid I will fail
and hurt him
in the end.
So I'm trying to
find a way
to make him
aware of his problems.
I want him to
accept others
from his heart.
You should pay
more attention to
Ling Dong and Jinghui.
If they can
become excellent,
then your class
will also be better.
I want you to remember that
education is
not about growing flowers.
Think about it.
So conservative!
Not about growing flowers...
Lan Jinghui,
what are you doing here?
It's for you. No need to thank me.
Why?
Ms. Fang told me that
you made the recording.
I just don't want it
to interfere with my studies.
You don't need to thank me.
And thanks for helping me
at the gym.
Don't bother me again.
He's really conceited!
I ought to break your bike.
Lan Jinghui.
I was out of line that day.
Please forgive me.
I'll lend you my
physics notes.
Here are my notes for Chinese.
And for math.
For political courses.
These are my exclusive notes.
These are the
best chips.
Thank you.
Not for you.
Master!
I'll buy you breakfast every day!
What are you doing!
I'm long past being angry.
Jinghui.
Please take care in the future.
Now you know to call
him Jinghui!
So how did you
confront Bi Peng that day?
Tell us about it!
Yes!
Well,
it was very exciting.
Tell us!
Tell us about it!
What was it like?
At that time,
Bi Peng quickly threw
the basketball
out of his hand.
It was a very
dangerous situation.
And I would be injured carelessly.
I had a hundred ways
of avoiding him
in my head.
In the end
I chose a
risky approach.
And the basketball flew
right by my hair.
At last
I dodged his attack
and defeated him
easily with
my killing skill.
What if I did it?
Can you prove it?
You...
I happened to see
the "Best Ball in the World"
when I passed.
What if I did it?
Can you prove it?
You...
I happened to see
the "Best Ball in the World"
when I passed.
What do you mean, Lan Jinghui?
Are you laughing at me?
I did it on purpose.
It's no use
knowing that I did it.
You have no proof.