English subtitles are available
Shooting Stars EP17
Please come in.
Because Mr. Zhang hasn't come,
I didn't clean up.
It's quite dusty.
I hope you don't mind.
Honestly,
good living conditions.
You bet.
Since
he has paid the rent,
I don't need to care
about anything else.
But something
happened to me.
My son is getting married.
I wanna give him this house
for his wedding.
What a joyful event!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Mr. Zhang
has put everything in that room.
You can have a look.
OK.
This way, please.
Then
I wrote him
saying that I planned
to repay him the money.
Anyway no one lives here.
He agreed.
Really?
Good!
Here's the rent.
Here you are.
Please hand it over to him.
OK.
Well,
his baggage's all here.
you can check it out.
Then we'll leave as soon as
we pack them up.
OK, I'm leaving now.
Accountant?
Headmaster of a primary school?
The house turns out
to be rented for the Mengs.
No wonder no one lives here.
Deng Mingyuan and Zhang Runjin...
The Communist Party has paid
such a great price
for the Mengs.
Renting a house, finding jobs...
Even the work permits
have been ready.
Xiang Yuansheng?
Xiang Yuansheng.
Now.
Give me all the documents
of the murder case.
All of them!
Yes, sir.
What is
the exact plan?
Did Deng Mingyuan
send someone to save the girl?
Have you ever met?
What is the name?
Is still in Shanghai?
Deng
did arrange a person
to protect them.
But I don't know the details.
Meng Duoci.
Deng Mingyuan
asked He Youqing
to protect the Mengs.
If
He had gone to Guangzhou,
he'd have taken the name
of Xiang Yuansheng.
But failed.
Because he died
at Van Hwa Hotel.
Then who is the policeman
named Xiang Yuansheng
at the Fourth Station House?
Whatever.
As long as
he uses this name,
he
is Xiang Yuansheng.
Here's the ticket
back to Nanjing.
I learned
from your brother
that you promised
to get on the train on time.
I'm required
to send you the ticket in person.
Young Master.
Thanks.
By the way,
I'll take the train with you
to Nanjing.
I'm gonna work for
the Staff Section
of the Central Military
Academy Camping Office in Suzhou.
Before that, I'll rest in Nanjing for days.
My brother said
you'll be
the Colonel Director there.
Congrats.
I know you fellow
don't care about this at all.
No need
to show off to you.
But as your friend,
I have to say something.
We both
have a bright future.
Everyone is stepping up,
so don't waste your time.
You should be
back to the right path.
I know.
You always
say that.
What happened the last time
I took you to the train station
back to Nanjing?
Listen.
I'll pick you up the day after tomorrow.
You must keep your promise.
Thanks for the ticket.
Enough.
Get away.
I've packed your luggage.
The house in Hong Kong is similar
to the one in Shanghai,
with a good and safe
living environment.
Why don't you eat?
That friend of your parents
is an amiable lady.
She and her husband will take care of you.
And I'll send you
living expenses
every three months.
Anyhow you don't need to be worried.
What's wrong?
Ms. Shi,
do you know ISKRA?
Yuansheng and I
went to a small courtyard in the suburb.
There're many children
and a big tree
hanging full of stars.
This one is the gift
those children gave me.
I also heard that ISKRA
is a project
to protect them.
My dad and mum
are members of it.
You've been
to the orphanage on Xinping Road.
Do you know that?
Actually,
I'm also a member
of ISKRA.
Your parents are super heroes
and they've worked so hard
to protect those children.
The money in the safe in HSBC
are prepared for this project
by your parents.
Now the money
has been sent to the North safely
through multiple efforts.
Only resisting Japanese invaders
and defending our country,
can we help the children
lead a good life.
Do you understand?
Ms. Shi,
can I join you?
Not now.
You're still a little girl.
What about when I grow up?
Ms. Shi,
when did you join
ISKRA?
Let me tell a story.
When I was 17,
I took a boat from Nanjing
to Dalian on my own,
then took a train
to Harbin,
then to Manzhouli.
Finally I took a train
from Manzhouli to Moscow.
I still remember
it's freezing cold
in Moscow then.
But I felt
that my heart was burning.
Qiushi,
you may have to make a choice
when you reach the age of 17.
At that time,
you will
know what to do.
Good.
Great.
Yuansheng.
I'm setting out
for Hong Kong today.
Will you remember me?
Of course.
How can I forget you?
Duoci,
everything in Shanghai is about to pass.
Start your new life
in Hong Kong.
I will.
And I will miss you
and Minmin as well.
Here's the medicine I bought
for Minmin,
but I didn't have a chance
to meet her.
Could you bring it to her?
Yes.
Yuansheng,
do you believe
we'll meet in the future?
Absolutely.
But when?
When you grow up.
I'd grow up quickly.
OK.
What
kind of person
will I become then?
You are just 8.
Your future
is your own the final say.
You
and those 400 children
are all
little stars,
and you'll
definitely shine brightly.
Thank you so much.
I wanna thank you as well.
Please.
Don't leave me alone.
Mister,
did you come to Shanghai
from another place?
I've booked a train ticket
to Nanjing 3 days later.
And I'll pay the bill
for your daily meals.
Besides,
I'm not in charge of you.
Do you agree?
Yes.
Meng Duoci,
I've decided to stay here.
Remember the following two points.
First,
I can't take you to Nanjing
for some reasons.
Second,
we'll refer to
each other as cousins.
OK.
Is your name Li Qiushi?
No, I'm Meng Duoci.
What's your name?
Hua Zhen.
Qiushi,
your parents,
my teacher,
and their comrades
are all true heroes.
Yuansheng,
I miss
my parents so much.
Qiushi!
Are you all right?
Did you get hurt?
Yuansheng saved me.
But can he take good
care of you for this month?
He has
always been doing well.
Qiushi,
if there's any problem
you don't understand,
come to find me at the photo studio,
OK?
Sure.
Thanks, Minmin.
Yuansheng!
I like Minmin
and her family so much.
Do you like Minmin?
Just go to bed.
No...
I don't wanna sleep.
Qiushi, run!
What's Xiang Yuansheng's
sister's name?
Li Qiushi.
Qiushi!
Yuansheng,
what kind of person
will I become when I grow up?
You are just 8.
You can be any people
you want to be.
Qiushi,
when you reach the age of 17,
whether you want to choose the path or not,
you will
have an answer by the time.
Come here.
Don't steal a glance.
Don't cheat.
Are we there yet?
Ready.
Three, two, one.
You asked me
if there's a lounge for policewomen
at the Fourth Station.
There wasn't before,
but there is now.
And fresh flowers.
Are you content now?
Yes.
I'm satisfied.
We've made a deal
that the room is only for you.
Even the director can't get in there.
What are you talking about?
Director.
What do you mean
even I can't get in there?
No way.
What's wrong?
Not accessible for you.
See, rest room for ladies.
If you are a policewoman,
we will let you in.
Your preparation is quite complete.
I just take a look
at the decoration outside.
Nice.
Romantic.
These brats are often
generous at my expense.
This room was my little warehouse
for tobacco, alcohol, sugar and tea.
You can have it now.
Thanks, director!
It seems like you are
having a problem with this.
Who?
Do you?
Or you?
No I don't.
Let me see who dare
disagree with Minmin's room.
OK stop giggling
and don't crowd around
the girl's room.
Get away.
Thanks director.
Thank all of you!
Captain Chen.
Here's the uniform I return to the Fourth Station.
Additionally,
the medicine Qiushi bought for Minmin.
Why don't you go in there
and bid farewell to our comrades.
Here you sing again.
Hello.
Hi, Captain.
All passed the evaluation.
Spread the good news.
Has your suspension been revoked?
Yes.
I'll do this.
Everyone out!
We're coming.
Erbai.
Captain.
I'll announce an important thing.
You've passed
the evaluation.
We've been
officially certified, right?
Of course!
Tian Dongbao!
Sun Hongfa!
Luo Minmin!
Cool.
Come on, Yuansheng.
Good news.
Yuansheng.
You've passed the evaluation.
I'm here today
to say goodbye to you.
Before here,
I majored in
navigation science of the S.M.C.
The holiday is over.
I should go back
for fighting trainings.
It's time
for me to leave Shanghai.
Aren't you a fisherman?
Well,
we've seen your personal file
which wrote fisherman.
Sorry.
But I am not.
And my name isn't Xiang Yuansheng.
but Hua Zhen.
I borrowed this name
out of special reasons.
These are from Qiushi
who knew that you got injured.
She bought the medicine for you.
But she can't
hand it to you on her own.
Thank you.
She asked me to express her thanks
to all of you
for helping her
these days.
Has she left Shanghai safely?
Yes, she has.
Will you...
be back to Shanghai in the future?
Maybe not.
Since you're leaving soon,
let's take a picture together
as a souvenir.
Great.
Good idea.
Let's take a photo.
Right.
A group photo.
We can go to Minmin's shop.
Exactly.
Let's take a photo.
We must do it.
We are all here,
aren't we?
Yes.
It's dark inside.
I can't see anything.
Let me try it.
Let me.
That's amazing.
Is there anything in it?
I don't know.
Look at it.
Don't touch.
Ready?
Leave here.
Yuansheng,
when back to Nanjing,
would you take a boat every day?
That's called warship.
My bad.
If we'll go find you there,
can we have a chance
to take a warship?
We can go to visit Yuansheng
in our spare time then.
No problem.
But I wonder
if we can take the warship
at any time?
Well.
Everyone here.
Let's take a photo.
Let me first, sir.
Hey, mate.
Step aside.
What do you mean?
You want a personal photo?
Dad.
Is it OK?
C'mon,
group photo!
It costs much for a photo.
Come here.
A group photo.
Together.
Where should I?
Well,
you are in the center.
Don't move.
Just in the middle.
Yuansheng,
you are leaving soon.
Stand in the front.
I...
You're the most important today.
Stand beside me.
Captain, over here.
One missing.
Captain.
Hurry up.
Be positive.
Check your hook and eye
and the hat.
Don't be so strict.
Let me check.
You are cool.
Ready?
Yes.
Sure?
OK.
Wait a minute.
Give us a signal.
We have a slogan.
You only have one chance.
Only one.
OK.
Alright,
look at me.
OK.
How about
smiling?
Smile.
Smiling is good for a photo.
OK, smile.
Smile.
That's right.
OK.
Keep it.
Look at me.
Ready?
Speak up the slogan!
Upholding justice
and protecting people.
Would you like
to have a walk?
With me?
Please transfer to the Fourth Station
of Shiliupu.
Sorry.
It failed because of the bad weather.
You can try it again later.
Luo Minmin!
Tianxiang,
Luo Qinqin.
Why are you here?
It's raining.
Dad asked us to bring you an umbrella.
We also brought some food for you.
We'll stay with you for a while.
I can show you
the restroom
that the Fourth Station
prepared for me only.
Come on in.
You see,
I'm welcomed here.
Tianxiang, it's better than your room.
Indeed.
Good.
They are nice to you.
This comb
is also sent by them.
Luo Minmin,
Yuansheng will leave tomorrow.
Don't you know that?
Don't you wanna say something
and bid farewell to him?
No.
You definitely like him.
He brought medicine to you.
You've recovered.
No need for medicine at all.
What are you talking about?
How could you understand
what is it as a child?
Adults don't understand.
It must be that
you've read too many love stories.
I'll be 18 years old
a few months later.
So what?
I'm still
your elder sister then.
If I were you,
I'd concentrate on
college entrance exam.
Focus on yourself.
Gosh.
You know nothing.
When Yuansheng back to the navy,
he'll fight in the battlefield.
I mean battlefield!
It means
you may never see him anymore.
Luo Qinqin,
don't say bad words.
What?
How dare you say
we'll never see each other.
No.
I won't say it.
I'm teaching you about love.
Stop.
Luo Qinqin,
how could you teach me?
I don't need you.
Fine.
I can do nothing.
How could you two
argue with each other
wherever you go?
I'm your sister.
Yuansheng.
Yuansheng is coming.
I...
I'm here for something.
What are you searching for?
The Brochure of Police.
You are here
for the book
no matter of the heavy rain?
I won't be a policeman any more.
I want it as a souvenir.
Are you on duty alone?
You should
have been here too.
No time for the change.
It doesn't matter.
My brother and sister
came for me.
It's here.
I came by car
without an umbrella.
Do you have one?
No.
I don't.
Well...
Then I have to leave
after the rain stops.
Alright.
Chop some sweet potatoes.
OK.
Is the restroom
prepared for you
by Erbai?
Yes,
it is.
It's
only for me.
I know why you
like here
so much.
Congrats!
You're certified as a police officer.
You must admire me.
You've passed the evaluation.
If you want to stay here,
it still has time left.
Are you really in the navy?
I've seen the ship
which is vast.
Can you sail ships
like that?
The reason you became a marine
is due to the conscription
like my brother?
You always talk about a topic
I don't like.
No.
I also have a brother.
My father hopes that one of us becomes an officer
while the other becomes a soldier.
It happens that being in the navy
is my dream.
So, I went to the military school.
How about your brother?
He is a secretary
Office of Aides in Office of Aides.
Similar to
the Grand Council before.
The Grand Council?
The Grand Council.
The Grand Council...
A department for the Chairman
for handling issues.
What about your father?
Undersecretary of the Ministry of Military Affairs.
However,
being in navy is my dream,
no matter whether my family
supports me or not.
If I were you,
I would stay at home
without doing nothing.
If so,
you wouldn't
come back here
after
your dad asked you
to run the photo studio.
But you're back finally.
Because I know that I'm a ball,
which may deflate easily
but
never be broken.
A man with a strong heart
must has
a warm family.
I admire you.
You are strong.
You are a person
supported by the God.
I have a good relationship with my brother.
But I...
rarely see my parents.
My father has always been busy
with his business.
I hardly met him when I was a kid.
After I moved to school,
the situation worsened.
Most peers around me
have similar experiences.
So, after meeting you,
I realized that
there is a completely different
family relationship from mine.
Embrace for joy,
and argue for anger.
You can
show care and love directly.
It seems that I can't do this.
It's so easy.
Just need to talk...
In fact,
it's you
who made me know
what kind of person
I wanna be.
My dad asked me
why I must be a police officer.
Actually,
I'm not being
police officer forever.
I believe that people
must be able
to do something well,
not be
unaware of what they want,
and not be
worthless.
What about you?
Why do you want to be in navy?
Many said
it's a shortcut for promotion
to go to the S.M.C.
from the Army University.
But it wasn't.
Our navy
isn't strong at all.