Mom
Hey, rain and dew, why are you back
My aunt said you were dying
Ah, your aunt got the wrong report
It's okay. It's okay. Are you tired of coming back all the way
Actually, someone sent it back by helicopter
He
Your boyfriend
Ah
Come here
How do you do, aunt
My name is Xu Jinfeng
Is your daughter's boss
Please call me Xiao Xu
Hello, aunt
This lady, my car broke down
Can I rub your car down the hill
Don't use this lame interface I used, okay
What about this
I lost my car keys
Hey
How do you know
I liked this one best when I was at school
Then look at it
Our company's induction readiness is no joke
Actually, I am today
I have something to say to you
Marry me
Marry him, marry him, marry him, marry him
Marry him, marry him
Let's go play that
Sure, would you like a bottle
Thanks
It's for me
You
It's not hot
What are you doing
Hard work
I'm afraid you don't want to see me
Who says I don't want to see you
Come on, debriefing
Remember to invite us to dinner if you succeed in promotion
Refueling
My next plan for my work is
Miss Lam Yuk-lok
Will you marry me
Boss
Oh, no. Did I succeed in this job
Say yes quickly
Don't promise again
I'm going to rush to answer
Boss
I will
Also called the boss
Husband