English subtitles are available
Bright Time EP20
Haha.
Hahaha.
There you are.
Hey,
warming up?
Let me add some firewood for you.
Hahaha.
Hey,
am I not laughing loud enough?
Hahaha.
Huh.
Well,
it's pretty warm.
You know,
Xu Chao and Ruosi
said they had a stomachache,
so I heroically volunteered
for the night watch.
Can't leave you alone,
right?
The weather's great tonight.
Clear skies.
It's pretty foggy.
Rare good weather,
so I'll sing you a song.
I'll sing that...
Shut it.
Fine,
as you wish.
It's kind of creepy, singing at night.
How about
I tell you a ghost story?
That sound...
must be my stomach growling.
Must be my upset stomach.
Must be...
Shut up.
Need to go to the bathroom.
How did you get in?
Hey.
Listen.
Look,
why are you here?
You can go keep watch, you know.
I knew it.
You couldn't just leave me.
It's pretty dark here.
My... my precious phone!
Flashlight, flashlight.
Don't.
That's even more obvious.
Not too bad.
A convenience store!
Hurry, hurry.
Yes,
take this, take this.
Stop hiding. I saw you two.
Go now while we can.
Instant noodles, sausages.
What?
Go!
And instant noodles, sausages...
What's wrong with you?
Lan Jinghui!
Jinghui! Jinghui!
The instant noodles and sausages...
Well, screw it!
Stop!
Get back here!
Which class are you from?
Which class!
Stop!
Stop right there!
Don't run!
You...
okay now?
You run pretty fast.
You...
also pretty fast.
No kidding.
Where'd you get this stuff?
Stop asking
and eat.
If you don't,
I'll throw it in the fire.
I'll eat, I'll eat.
Are they getting along now?
Who's there?
Xiaohua.
Instructor Wu.
What are you doing out here so late?
I... I'm
on night watch, Instructor Wu.
Alright,
it's late.
Go get some rest.
Thank you, Instructor Wu.
Wait!
Don't litter with
those prohibited items after you eat.
Got it.
Thank you.
A little girl running that fast?
Thanks for earlier.
Why thank me?
No matter what I do,
it just proves
I'm not a bad person.
Still mad at me?
Why would I be mad?
I'm just a hired hand.
I was wrong.
When I
found out,
I was furious.
You're my best friend.
I needed
an explanation
from you.
An answer.
I admit,
at first,
it was because of your father
that I agreed to watch you.
Otherwise,
with how
arrogant
and troublesome
you were,
do you expect
I'd willingly get close
and help you?
Was I really that annoying?
Yeah,
you were.
But
as I got to
know you,
I understood what
having a friend feels like.
Lan Jinghui, you know,
even though
you seem unreliable
and a bit silly,
you always
give your all for your friends.
Whether it's Xiaohua, Ma Yiming,
or me,
you always give your best.
I used to be alone,
but you changed that.
Look at you,
you either don't talk
or say
the most mushy things.
Actually, I've always wanted
to ask you something.
What?
Why did you react like that?
Like what?
In the locker room earlier.
I'm afraid of the dark. Yeah.
Just that.
Fine,
not just that.
I might
also be scared of confined spaces,
and
sudden bright light.
Afraid of... light?
My parents divorced
when I was young,
and my mom
insisted on taking me abroad.
I didn't want to go,
so I
made a pact
with a good friend
to hide
until my mom left.
Does that mean we'll
never see each other again?
I don't want to leave.
What if your mom insists on
taking you?
I can hide.
Hide?
Where?
That kid betrayed me,
told all the adults
about my little secret.
You have to keep my secret.
Don't tell anyone.
Pinky promise.
Looking back, it was childish.
I hid alone
in an abandoned warehouse
behind the kindergarten.
No light,
no food,
no water.
All I remember next
is hearing footsteps
and seeing countless
flashlights shining in.
What happened then?
They found me
and took me back.
Maybe
subconsciously,
it wanted me to stay
and made me fear
confined spaces
and sudden bright lights.
Do you still remember
the kid who betrayed you?
No.
I was too young.
Besides,
it's best
not to remember
people like that.
Maybe he didn't mean it that way.
What?
Nothing.
Wait,
why did I
just tell you all this?
No.
No, no.
Hey,
you have to tell me
one of your secrets,
now.
Come on, right now.
I... I don't have any secrets.
I don't believe you.
That face
says otherwise.
Really, I don't.
Did my dad tell you
you're not my uncle?
Yes.
Do you know who he is?
Who is he?
He's...
he's your uncle.
uncle?
Get out. Out.
Go ahead, out.
Ling Dong, about what I said earlier,
what do you say?
Mr. Lan,
I don't think
we're related, right?
And Mr. Zhang said
my sponsor wanted to meet me.
That must be you, right?
Can I ask
why you're sponsoring me?
I...
Well,
it's a long story.
Ling Dong, sit down and let's talk.
Come on.
Sit.
Actually,
you and Shangjin
aren't related.
But
Shangjin, me,
and
your father
have been friends
for over ten years.
With... my dad?
I won't go into details.
Dong,
you know
your mom
is quite strong-willed.
She doesn't like
accepting help,
so we didn't
tell you
to avoid burdening you.
Today, I came
to ask you...
What he means is, he wants you
to help Lan Jinghui improve.
Of course,
without affecting
your studies.
Lan Jinghui is
a bit of a troublemaker now,
but he
used to be
a good kid.
The reason he changed
is partly
my fault and his mom's.
Now,
it's a coincidence
that he transferred here,
and you're in the same class,
even desk mates.
So, I hope
you can
help him out.
Make him improve.
Besides,
your status is different now.
You're his uncle.
Yeah, uncle.
You can use that
to your advantage.
When he doesn't listen,
assert your authority,
right?
He has to listen to you.
If you can
help improve Lan Jinghui's studies,
Shangjin will be relieved.
He's kind-hearted,
so I guess he's agreed.
What a good kid.
Thank you.
Keep it up.
What?
Ling Dong,
you're
too much!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You...
Are you okay? What's wrong?
Nothing,
my leg's just numb.
I'm fine.
Are you dumb?
Is it still numb?
Are you okay?
No, I'm all right.
It's better now.
Nice night,
clear skies.
Lan Jinghui,
I meant it
when I said I'd be your uncle
for lifetime.
Want to keep taking advantage of me?
In your dreams.
Aren't you the one taking advantage?
Show-off.
You're squishing me.
Get off me.
No.
Last warning,
get off!
Buck up!
You starving or something?
Be careful.
I'm alright.
You alright?
We can't afford
to lose another partner.
Left.
Right.
Left, right.
Right. Watch your arm movement.
Wait.
Keep your arms
closer to your body.
Wider swing
is throwing you off balance
and slowing you down.
I don't think so.
If she's still
getting the hang of it,
the big arm swings might help her
keep up with her steps.
No?
Just like this.
No, no.
He's wrong.
Do as I said.
What?
Forget what he said,
listen up.
Trust your body
and how it feels.
What? What makes you
so sure your way
is better than mine?
I've never
claimed that.
I just follow my heart.
Follow your heart?
You've got heart?
Let's go.
But I think
you should
use your head.
You know?
Not just following your heart.
We're all feeling-driven beings.
Let's go.
Ready.
Go!
Go! Go!
Come on, Ruosi.
You ready?
Be careful!
Go for it!
We will.
We're gonna
win the first place.
We will win, for sure.
Cause he doesn't want to lose.
We
You...
We...
We will win!
Class 5!
Remember the drills,
stay focused,
and watch your step.
Ready?
One.
Two.
Three.
Go.
One, two.
Go. Go.
Go.
One, two.
She hurt?
I'll go check on her.
You alright?
Let them deal with that.
These kids
are used to being pampered,
they gotta toughen up
and learn a thing or two.
We're totally
on the same page, Ms. Fang and me.
Are you alright?
Can you keep pushing?
My ankle's sprained.
Can you keep running?
Yeah, I got this.
But...
Qingtian, we're gonna win!
We almost had it!
I promised you
I'd help you win first place.
It's okay, Qingtian.
Now I
kinda like being second place.
We were so close
so close
so close to winning.
We practiced so hard.
One, two.
Go.
Slow down. Take it easy.
Go for it!
Go. Go.
One.
Almost there.
Go.
Come on, Xiaohua.
One, two.
Go. Go.
Go. Xiaohua.
Go.
Two.
Watch out.
One, two.
It's okay.
Slow down.
Take it easy.
One, two.
Go.
Go. Go. Go.
Go. Go.
Be careful.
You're the best.
Good job.
My bad.
We practiced so much for nothing.
It's not your fault at all.
Finishing is winning
in my book.
Right?
And look,
even the "First Place or Die" guy
didn't complain.
It's also a kind of first place.
Just in reverse.
It's a unique experience,
gotta admit.
Heat that?
And our team's a beast, gotta let the
others taste victory once in a while.
Jinghui.
Thanks.
You got lucky this time.
Qingtian.
There's a bonfire party later,
wanna help me start the fire?
Nah, I'm not feeling it.
You still
bummed about
the loss?
Promised I'd help you win.
It's okay.
Qingtian.
Look.
Where did you get them?
I passed by the kitchen and...
Gosh.
Chen. You look
all innocent,
but you're...
Given by the kitchen staff.
But it's raw.
That's why I ask you
to start the fire with me.
I want it roasted.
Go.
Come here.
Get going.
Hurry.
Move faster!
Ma Yiming, chop-chop.
Faster.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Alright, let me explain
the game rules.
Game's called
"King's Game".
King card
gives you power
to pick two cards,
those two
are a team.
You can
make them do anything.
If they can't,
they'll have to
drink black garlic juice as punishment.
Now.
Who's got the King?
Me, me.
Jinghui, Jinghui.
So it'll be...
Diamond ten
and black spade eight.
Who's got black spade eight?
And who's diamond ten?
Diamond ten?
Where's diamond ten?
Who's got it?
Diamond ten.
Now, diamond ten?
Well...
A love song duet
it is.
Sing! Sing!
I'll take the punishment.
No, no.
I cheated, I'll drink it.
Bro, did you just mess up?
That bad?
Well...
Now. Keep the game rolling!
Hand over your
cards.
Alright.
Back to your seat.
Your card, please.
Alright.
Give me your card.
Card.
Okay.
Jinghui.
The juice
is nasty.
Who came up with this?
Glad Mengyu didn't get it.
Mengyu.
Such a troublemaker.
You deserve it.
Mengyu.
Okay.
Now, for this round.
Who's the King?
Me, me, me.
Choose your cards.
Red heart jack.
Red jack is
giving red ace
a piggyback ride
around the field!
Ma Yiming.
Ma Yiming
Now.
Who's the King now?
Me!
You're lucky this round!
So please,
name your cards.
I choose black spade two
and black spade eight.
What do you want them to do?
I wanna see them give each other
a big, tight hug.
Okay, number eight,
please stand up.
Alright.
Okay.
It's Ling Dong.
Great,
the eight is here.
Now, let's welcome the two.
Black spade two.
Isn't black spade two a girl?
This is getting exciting.
Who could it be?
It's gonna be
awkward.
Yeah.
Black spade two.
If black spade two doesn't come out,
I'm collecting everyone's cards.
Three.
Two.
It's me.
Give him a hug.
Congrats.
Hug.
Hug. Hug. Hug.
I can't... Can't...
breathe...
A big one for you.
Mam, two ice creams.
Two?
Here you are.
Mam.
I'll take six.
Six?
Yeah. Six.
Thank you.
Mam.
Give me
three ice creams.
Three?
We only have two.
Only two.
Will do.
It's okay.
A big chicken leg for you.
No veggies?
Here.
What?
Just two?
What about you?
I... I just finished it.
Feeling like I'm coming back to life.
Is it good?
Take a bite, come on.
Eating cold then hot.
Watch your tummy.