Hello Debate Opponent 2 EP16
Where did you go?
I bought you something to eat.
Snacks, fruits, and candied fruits.
When you're bored on the train,
you can eat them to kill the time.
That should keep you going till you arrive the destination.
Whose is that for?
This is for Dango.
She will try to eat yours,
so I bought the same stuff for her.
You are starting to look like
a good boyfriend.
To be a good boyfriend,
I've made three rules for you
in the winter vacation.
First,
Call me
every night.
Make sure I can reach you any time.
Second,
send a small moon sticker before you sleep,
and a small sun sticker after you wake up
to me on WeChat.
Third,
report to me when you leave your house,
do not drink,
when there're other men around.
This is exactly what my dad said
when I first entered university.
This means that
we're going to be a family sooner or later.
- Off with you. - Off with you.
I'm back. Let's go.
Here,
this is for you.
Take care.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Bye. I won't see you off.
Goodbye.
Instant noodles.
Dango.
There's only one left.
You can take it. I'm not hungry.
What if you get hungry
on the train?
Nan Bei has given me
so many things to eat.
Take it.
What a coincidence.
I really...
Calm down.
Seriously?
We take the same train?
There's only one train departing in the morning.
- Dango! - Dad!
Dad!
Where's mum?
Your mum
is cooking for you at home.
Why don't you
hitch a ride in my car?
I appreciate it, Uncle.
But my mother will be here soon.
My mom as well.
Alright. Take care then.
Okay.
Xiaoyu,
I will visit you in a few days.
Watch what you eat.
Don't gain weight.
Alright.
Goodbye.
Girls,
take care of yourself.
Goodbye, Uncle.
Bye!
Be careful on the road.
See you later, Uncle!
Baby girl,
I have gotten your arrival date wrong.
Get a taxi home.
My baby.
Mum!
You're back!
Yin Nan?
Hi, Auntie.
Where's your mother?
Something came up at the last moment,
so she couldn't make it.
Auntie, I'm calling a cab.
Come, let me send you back.
Mum, why
did you ignore me
and talk to Yin Nan only?
It's alright, Auntie.
I can go back myself.
Aren't we living in the same neighborhood?
why bother calling a cab?
Come, let's help her with her luggage.
Why?
She can do it herself.
Why do I need to help her?
That's because you're strong.
I've arrived.
- On my way home. - You just
can't keep your eyes from your phone.
You're going to ruin your eyes.
You should learn from Yin Nan.
Today, your dad
bought a cod for you.
I'll fry it for you for dinner.
I don't wanna eat fish. I want meat.
That's the reason
why you are not smart.
Yin Nan is unlike you.
She eats fish a lot.
It has nothing to do with her.
I inherit it from you.
Do you?
I asked you to take up Finance,
but you chose International Trade.
Yin Nan had also chosen International Trade.
Didn't you say it's great, too?
You two are different.
The prospect of you finding
a job upon graduation
worries me and your daddy a lot.
Why bother
worrying about that?
I can deal with it myself.
Look at you, can you ever grow up?
Can't you learn from Yin Nan?
You manage to displease your mother
the first day you're back.
I've waited for you for half a year.
So funny.
Every time I come back,
you will start to hate my guts
in less than a week.
What are you talking about?
Just wait and see.
Have some fruits. They're full of nutrition.
Thank you, mum.
You don't have these at school, right?
Barely scrape by.
I don't mind food.
What are you talking about?
Xiaoyu.
Are you awake?
It's time for lunch.
I'm still sleepy.
Fine. You continue.
I know it's hard at school.
Mummy
will come again after half an hour.
Mum, I want to eat some fruits.
Mum, I want to eat some fruits!
Can't you wash some yourself?
I'm busy? Don't you see?
What else can you do
except for playing with your phone
and creating trash?
What time is it now?
Get up.
Come and help me.
I'm still sleepy.
Wake up.
Hurry.
Put these clothes
in the washing machine.
Do you hear me?
Xiaoyu.
What happened?
I was nagged by my dad the whole morning.
Zishi,
did you come because you smell the food?
Come.
Eat with us.
How are you, Auntie?
Fine, good girl.
I'll go get the rice.
You dare to take it away?
You won't have enough anyway.
Here's your rice.
Auntie, I can't finish all these.
I know how much
you normally eat.
Are you trying to lose weight
because you've fallen in love?
Come and tell me.
Did our Xiaoyu
get a boyfriend at school?
Both of us are good girls.
How can that ever happen?
That's good. Eat.
Why are you so quiet today?
Normally, you're very talkative.
It's nothing.
Actually,
it's about choosing my major at school.
Actually, I love painting
but my parents want me
to choose editing.
I... Ah!
Your dad wants the best for you.
You should listen to your parents.
They'll never be wrong.
But I like painting.
You kids
are too spoiled.
You do whatever
you want.
You don't have any experience.
You should listen to your parents.
What parents do is for their kids' good.
Mum,
If you get a problem with me, bring it to me.
Don't bully Dango.
You call this bullying?
Zishi is not an outsider.
Then I'll
speak it out.
Your Dad and I
have done our research.
This International Trade major
is like an aircraft carrier.
You have to learn everything.
It doesn't specialize in any field.
After you graduate,
it's as if you know everything
but know nothing.
In the end,
you'll gain no expertise
to help you find a job.
Where did you
get all your big data research from?
I want to ask you.
So, you know my major
better than I do?
I've checked all the statistics
on the employment
for International Trade and Finance majors
of all schools under 985 Project.
I know more than anyone else,
the statistics of these two majors.
Can big data predict our future?
I have good grades.
I'm the top three in our year.
I've obtained first class scholarship
for two years in a row.
If our school is going to recommend students for internships,
I can choose any post I want.
What age is this?
Why can't I find a good job?
Am I right, Dango?
Dango, what do you think?
Guangzhou's 1700 mu (280.1acres) land
has been completely levelled.
Next, it's going into
the large-scale construction phase.
This will strengthen the bond between Macau and Hong Kong, with Australia
and propel the development of the Greater Bay Area.
After the framework agreement has been established...
Bei,
Have you made your mind
in what major to choose?
What's there to think about?
I'll choose Intellectual Property Law.
Good. This is good.
Bei.
Yes.
We support your decision,
but have you considered
something like Civil Law
or Economic Law?
I'm not interested in those.
So you decide on such a big thing
based on your interests?
Mum,
let me make own decisions
on my studies.
Additionally,
I've already studied for two years.
Just believe in me.
Whatever.
Go and wash the dishes.
I still have something to do at nine o'clock.
Then make it quick.
Alright.
What are you still doing here?
I'm going to help Bei.
What are you doing?
I'm watching a debate competition.
So hardworking?
How about you?
I'm also watching a debate competition.
Have you
contacted Ma Nan, Tao Hao,
and the others?
Sometimes.
Sending some WeChat messages and red packets.
Ah, yes.
My parents
just talked to me
about my major.
They're still using
their usual flanking tactics.
After the failure,
I guess
they're planning something.
At least you can still talk
normally with your parents.
What happened?
Are your parents
selectively ignoring your
opinions?
Um...
I'm not saying it.
Why not?
Isn't it my duty
to help you when you're down?
It's hard to explain on WeChat.
I'm not saying it.
Then, tell me what should I do
to make you happy?
Say something nice.
What can I do to make you happy, your highness?
I'm going to beat you.
Xiaoyu, come and have some fruits.
Your mum has something to say to you.
See?
The war horn has been blown.
Um, don't fight. Stay calm.
I'll try.
Put your phone on loud speak,
Avoid a confrontation with them.
I'm resourceful.
I will help you when the time comes.
What do I need you for?
You're not here
when I need you.
Father? Mother?
I'm back.
These are my report cards
for the past three semesters.
My marks fulfill
all the standards for employment recommendation.
I won't have any problem
finding a job after graduation.
An International Trade major takes up a job
related to foreign trade.
What they teach you in school
is not specialized enough.
In the end, you won't have any expertise.
No company will receive you.
An International Trade major
can work in international trade and
business administration departments
as well as foreign corporations,
joint ventures,
and large-scale retailers.
Do your statistics tell you that?
Just by knowing some English,
and some jargon,
you dare to call yourself an expert in International Trade?
The barrier to this profession
is too low.
Unless, you want to work as a laborer?
University education
is meant to let students
understand what they can do
when they're studying.
Mum, do you understand
my capabilities better than I do?
Maybe your data
is reliable in some ways,
but how would you know
if I'm definitely going to be a laborer?
How would you know
that I will fail in everything?
Xiaoyu.
You have to listen to us.
We're experienced.
What we do is for your good.
Everything will be fine if you listen to us.
You always guilt-trip me
whenever you fail to win an argument against me.
Whenever I want to express an opinion,
you will start to repeat these.
You don't understand my major at all,
and you don't even understand what I want.
When you said it's correct, it's correct.
When you said it's wrong, it's wrong.
Have you ever thought about me?
I have my own standards
and my own principles.
This matter
is out of your capabilities.
Mum.
This is not like when I'm little
and caused some trouble,
you only need to talk to the teacher
and settle it.
She is right.
Hello?
I hear the sound of the elevator.
Where are you going this late at night?
Nothing.
I just want to calm down, alone.
What Mr. Wang said just now,
I think it's practical.
Yeah.
Nan, you're back by yourself.
How's school?
It's fine.
Let me check my mails.
Nan, have you had dinner?
Yes.
Well,
I told you the other day
that my school gave me an opportunity
to work as an intern at the Big Four after I graduate,
But,
I want to do a startup with some of my friends.
What do you think?
What did you say?
I want to do a startup instead of an internship.
What's your advice?
You can decide it on your own.
Dad, what do you say?
You're not young anymore.
You need to decide
on your own.
You're
outstanding since young.
We are very proud.
Are you proud, or just feel pleased that I save you from troubles?
I understand you're busy.
I knew that when I was a child.
So, I will solve everything
by myself.
However, no matter how much I try,
I couldn't accept
attending my graduation ceremony alone.
No matter how outstanding I am,
I'm still a student.
I don't have any work experience.
I don't really need
you to do anything for me,
but I really hope you can at least care about me
or give me some advice.
Is that too much?
Nan.
It's our fault.
I don't need
your apologies anymore.
Nan, where are you going this late?
Nan?
Mummy, look!
There's a fountain at the square.
Can we go and have a look?
But, Mummy
needs to go shopping today.
How about tomorrow?
Alright.
Mummy will go to the fountain with you today.
I will go to the mall tomorrow.
Let's go.
Yay!
Do you have a problem?
Don't you know?
You can get rid of your hiccup with a startle.
Who's afraid of you? Childish.
I'm sorry.
This is a public place.
Please keep quiet.
I'm sorry.
Owner,
why aren't there any soy sauce
on the shelves?
Soy sauce?
Hold on.
Let me have a look at the back.
Thank you.
I don't really want to talk
to you.
But since we met,
I want to tell you,
my mum said
we would go to your house for a new year visit
in two days
I'm warning you,
don't say anything about choosing our majors.
That's all. I'm leaving.
My mother won't care
about these little things.
Instead,
I think Auntie
will be more interested
about that fellow
who always hangout with you.
Yin Nan, I will sue you for defamation.
If you dare to talk to my mum about this,
I will tell your mum
that at school,
you always...
You are not only old,
but also bad-tempered.
Won't auntie be pleased
if she knows someone likes you?
Why do you talk so much?
You're annoying.
Isn't it nice to annoy you?
Since your intelligence
did not keep up with your age.
You need someone to take charge of you.
You need someone to take charge of you, too.
Who comes out to buy soy sauce this late at night?
You don't have any adults at home?
Do you think everyone is like you?
You giant baby.
What?
When are you coming?
Next Wednesday.
Auntie didn't tell you?
So, she didn't.
How nice.
Not like my mum.
Alas.
She nags me every day.
She's just like my manager.
Wanting to control everything I do.
24 hours a day.
They are just worried
about you.
Stop.
I know what you wanna say.
Let me tell you this.
I'm already an adult.
I'm twenty.
I've grown up.
I can
be responsible for my own choices.
Be happy about it.
Do you know how fortunate
you are?
I've never been cared
ever since childhood.
I don't even know
how does it feel like.
Young lady, here's your soy sauce.
Come to pay here.
Son.
The major you choose.
Intellectual Property Law.
I heard that it's a harsh job.
Considering my intelligence and talents,
is that really an issue?
After all, I'm your son.
Don't make fun.
I heard
that these cases
usually take up to several years.
I'm afraid that you will starve.
At that time,
won't you feel bad for me?
Don't worry.
If I really starve,
you only need to give me
eight or nine hundred thousand yuan.
That'll be fine.
I'm serious about this.
Stop looking at your phone.
Bei.
Your Mum is worried about you.
She heard from your uncle
that if you learn Financial Law, you can work in a big company
as a consultant.
And
you can also work as a legal advisor
Why is uncle
still so childish?
Stop talking nonsense.
Welcome.
Come in.
We've been waiting for you.
Please come in.
Bei.
Hi, Uncle and Auntie.
How are you, Bei?
Happy New Year.
Bei.
You need to choose your major when school re-opens, right?
That's what we call choosing the direction of your future.
Something like that.
We don't know
anything about law,
so we can't give any recommendations.
Didn't your son's girlfriend
graduate from law school
two years ago?
That girl is outstanding.
She's practicing law in a big company.
She earns a lot
and her work is not so tiring.
Being a legal advisor in a big company
is not that easy.
But,
Bei can deal with it since he gets good grades.
Ah, yes.
She studied Financial Law.
My son should choose
whatever he likes.
Right?
No,
it's about his future.
If he chooses the wrong major,
he'll face a lot of difficulties in the future.
Back then,
Wang who lives at the entrance of our neighborhood
and normally take up small cases,
managed to receive a big case.
Something about copyright.
But it turned out that case
took several years.
Up until now, he's still complaining about earning little money.
It's distressing.
Is it that serious?
Of course.
Bei,
you must choose carefully.
Your major
sounds great.
Something about copyright
but the law pertaining to this field
is not so complete.
Otherwise,
how could it take so long?
What auntie said is correct.
Though he comes first
this year,
his scholarship
is only enough for him to retake one exam.
He's still to pass
the Moral Cultivation and Legal Basis.
It's his third attempt.
It's even an open-book exam.
You have to look into this.
Uncle,
has your daughter found a job yet?
She's been waiting at home
for over a year now.
Why didn't you bring her here for dinner?
I miss her.
What are you talking about? Did you drink too much?
Come on, let's eat.
Come.
Auntie. Uncle.
Stay safe.
Alright. See you.
Take care.
Come again.
Mum.
You're busy all the day. Eat some grapes.
I was
just kidding.
It's not the first time
they know me.
They won't stay upset for long.
I did not mean it as well.
I got too high.
They are saying it for your own good.
Additionally,
they're not wrong.
I know what you meant.
You're kicking the ball here and there,
it's suffocating.
If you want me to change my major,
just tell me.
You've invited for so many people to come.
You've talked my ear off.
Alright.
Anyhow, we think
that being a legal advisor is better for you.
Yes, you're right.
Alright.
Then,
tell me why is it suitable.
A legal advisor in a big company,
is a stable job
It's not stressful as well.
From nine to five.
As simple as that.
What's wrong with that?
You've also heard what your auntie said.
Intellectual property is a difficult field.
This type of legal cases take a long time.
It's very difficult.
What are you looking for?
So, you really think that being a legal advisor of a big company
is safe and stable?
You only need to sit back
and drink your tea?
So, where's the prospect
for advancement?
You must take a long-term view.
Then, what about being a legal consultant?
Mum, you've watched TV series, right?
Which legal consultant
in the TV series
isn't bald
even when they're only fifty?
It's not that simple.
It's harder than copyrights.
I'm no match to you in arguing.
No, Mum.
It's not about that.
You don't understand.
So, don't worry about this.
Leave it to me. I can do it.
It's getting late.
You should go to rest.
I'll go to sleep.
Sleep?
Go clean up the table.
Alright.
Baby, I'm coming in.
Wow.
Your room is too dim.
It's going to ruin your eyesight.
Your face is big,
you don't look good with glasses.
You won't be able to woo a prince charming.
Dad, having a big face means I bring fortune.
Just like you.
Dad, let me show you.
The boys in this comic
are very handsome.
They don't look as good as me.
Dad.
Look at this.
Does this look good?
This is a bear, right?
It's you.
Let me see.
It looks like me.
It looks like me...
Daughter.
Are you sure
you want to take comic design?
You don't want to support me?
Daddy will support
whatever decisions you make,
but I feel that
we
should do what
we are good at.
Treat what you love to do
as a hobby.
Then,
you will live happier.
So, regarding this matter,
is it an order
or a suggestion?
Of course, we can discuss this.
But your mum said
you have to think of three
strong reasons
to persuade us.
Daughter, do your best.
Sleep early.
It doesn't look like him?
I think it does.
Xiaoyu.
She's not returned.
Should we go and find her?
Give her classmate
a call.
Should we talk to her now?
Wait.
Hurry.
I've found it.
Wow.
There's a lot.
Intellectual property.
Copyright, trademark,
copyright dispute.
These are quite difficult.
I'm even more worried now.
But we can't persuade him.
So worrisome.
Why don't we let him do what he wants?
Believe in him.
Am I
someone who doesn't believe in her son?
Stand up...
Let me do it.
You're
too slow.
He didn't tell me
what's in his mind.
I'm worried that
if he makes his decision rashly
he will regret later.
Here.
See if there's anything
supported with statistics.
Yes.
Here.
This one.
I'm still searching.
Stop interrupting.
Look.
Did you get addicted to the net at such an old age?
You scared me.
You didn't make any sound when you walk in.
We're just browsing something.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Even if your son
is talentless,
I can still rely on my face.
Yes.
Just like me.
You're anxious
because of my major,
right?
No, I'm not anxious.
How can I not be anxious?
Bei, Mum is too anxious.
Yes. We're anxious.
You should have said earlier.
You don't need to put up this act.
Sit down.
Sit.
Let me tell you.
Here.
Come and have a look.
Intellectual Property Law
requires someone
who is proficient
at management and law.
At the same time,
it requires some knowledge on science and technology.
It's that hard?
Yes.
So,
regardless if
I'm going to work in this field,
I can rely on my skills
to take care of this household.
Bei, regarding your job...
Dad, don't rush.
In the future,
I can work
in a law firm,
or a company that deals
with patents,
or copyrights.
Additionally, our country
is starting to pay attention to intellectual property rights.
Talents like me
will do very well in the future.
I saw on the news
that there's a novel
that's adapted into a TV series.
In the end, the author
got into a legal suit with the screenwriter.
You see,
we're needed everywhere.
So, you don't need to worry.
No,
we're not worried at all.
I know you can make the right decision.
It's your father's fault.
Who was the one who said she's anxious?
So, I say
our Bei
can plan on his own.
Do what you want.
Don't listen to your mum's nagging.
Hello?
Hi, princess.
You finally pick up your phone.
Let me share something good for you.
Just now,
I used my superior intelligence
to stop
a world war.
My parents
are completely
enticed
by my charm.
Yes.
Why do I feel
as if you're trying to brush me off?
Yes.
Are you still angry?
Don't run away from home, alright?
As an ambitious youth,
I'll fight for what I pursue
till the end.
What are you doing on the first day of New Year?
Are you trying to help scammers earn their KPI?
Where are you now?
Where else? I'm at home.
It's the first day of New Year.
It's expensive to stay in a hotel.
But, I'm telling you,
I've planned
to leave early in the morning.
I have my tempers, too.
What are you saying?
Hey, listen to me.
Don't ever run away from home.
If you might get kidnapped,
What should I do?
What can I do?
Are you going to make me worried to death?
It's hard to explain on the phone or WeChat.
Anyway, don't worry.
I've done this before.
It's all under control.
I'm preparing for
battle.
See you.
Bei.
We've run out of toilet paper.
Can you go down and buy some?
Bei? Did you get them?
Are you surprised?
Why did you come?
You said
you'll be more frustrated if
I'm not around
when you need me.
Then, I can only
come to your side.
Isn't your house far away from mine?
How did you get here?
With the majestic hymn of victory
We sing in praise of our beloved motherland
Toward a prosperous and strong nation
It's alright.
It's not that far from here.
I feel better with your around.
What did you say?
Oh.
However,
it will be more appropriate
if you can
squeeze some tears out right now.
I dare you to say it again...
Ouch...
It's alright.
If you want
to run away from home again,
you can come to my house.
My parents will be extremely happy to meet you.
Off with you.
You and your wishful thinking.
However,
I just realized two days ago,
that parents don't necessarily
want you to listen to them.
They're just worried that
you might regret walking down the wrong path.
So, they will try various methods,
various channels
to obtain these random information
just to be a little closer
to us.
So,
really.
You only need to
reassure them.
But whenever I have an opinion,
she will disagree on this,
disagree on that.
At least let me try.
In the eyes of parents,
we will always be kids.
You only need to let them know
that you've made
your decisions after careful thinking
to make them feel better.
You have to listen, alright?
Don't argue with your parents.
I have to go now.
What's the time?
If I go back a bit later,
my parents will think that
I've run away from home.
See you.
Nan Bei.
What?
Look there.
I'm just kissing you. Why did you back away?