[English subtitles are available]
[Fall in Love with a Fox]
[EP15]
Does it work?
Can you recall anything?
No.
Jin Baiwan, you did it on purpose!
It should take effect this time!
Still not.
Can it work?
Eat it!
Open your mouth!
Just eat it!
How do you feel?
How does it taste?
It tastes
unbelievably terrible.
Still can't work?
Are you sure it can work out?
Don't question me!
No, no, no.
I just think that
such a large pill
is really okay for Baiwan?
Never mind.
As long as I can restore my memories,
I'd like try every means.
I'll eat it!
Hold on!
You've already tried
so many herbs today.
But they took no effect.
You can't eat anymore.
No!
Not until they take effect!
I won't give up.
Baiwan
Zheng
I have to restore my memories this time!
I can't follow your words.
How is it? You recall anything?
I remember!
I knew!
I knew she could remember!
Remember what?
We knew each other before,
right?
What else?
Yes, I do recall it.
We actually,
have fate of love for seven lives!
Fate of love for seven lives?
This life,
we are all little bugs
of the Goddess of Heaven.
You are the blue bug.
I'm the green bug!
We have been
with the Goddess of Heaven,
and flying around her.
Flying.
And flying.
Well, Lord Qu,
it's because the medicine
has drunk herb.
When it wears off, she'll be fine.
Flying!
She'll be fine.
Are you listening to me?
Baiwan
I am listening.
Wow, I'm flying!
I'm flying!
Flying!
Flying! Flying!
Then,
I just knocked over
the censer of the Supreme Lord,
and saved you
from it.
I'm thirsty. I need water.
I...
What did I say?
You just mentioned
our fate of love for the seventh life.
And me,
I'm the Mouse Fairy shut in the censer
of the Supreme Lord.
And you
are my Cat God and saved me.
Mouse Fairy?
Cat God?
It seems like
you are sober now.
I, I just...
You just
told me everything
about our fate of love for seven lives.
I enjoyed that so much.
That's even more excellent than any novels!
I must have taken the wrong medicine!
Please don't mind.
You always
don't really care about me.
What a surprise.
In your mind,
you've pictured
our fate of love for seven lives!
I'm so ecstatic.
I do care about you!
No.
I didn't imagine things like that.
I've told you.
I've taken the wrong medicine!
Baiwan
You just
accidently ate the drunk herb today.
And I worried so much.
Or...
How about you
just let them go?
Will you?
No!
Zheng
You used to take care of me all the time.
And you protected me.
I don't need your protection anymore.
If I can really restore my memory,
I'll know
whether the Nonuple Palace
is our enemy or friend.
By the way,
if I am really
the eldest disciple of the Nonuple Palace,
maybe
I can protect you.
Yifei
You do want to protect me?
I do!
Zheng, don't worry.
No matter who I am,
I will never leave you alone.
You serious?
If you can't believe it,
let's pinkie swear.
We've tried so many methods.
But none of them takes effect.
I don't believe
there's any disease that I,
the highly-skilled doctor Su Zhuozhuo, can't cure!
Yes, yes.
A highly-skilled doctor can cure any diseases!
The problem
doesn't lie in our highly-skilled doctor,
but the disease itself.
You are here to make those snide remarks?
I'm gonna kick your ass.
If I can't annoy you,
I'll just hide from you.
You.
Don't run away!
Weird.
We've tried so many kinds of medicine.
There should be some effect.
I dare to say it's because Song Jianshan
changed my medicine!
Right.
Changing medicine.
Miss
What do you mean?
Don't you think,
Lord Qu is always
not so supportive
in helping you restore the memories?
You're right.
I feel like
he doesn't want you to
restore your memory.
Why doesn't Zheng want me to
restore my memory?
I know the reason.
Baiwan
Do you remember
you've mentioned
that Qi to me.
He tried every means to get closer to you
when you were in the Taoyuan Valley.
This time he even traveled miles
to Tingqin Garden,
and had a fierce fight with Lord Qu.
He just wanted to take you back.
No wonder he always calls you Chu.
So intimate!
In my opinion,
before you lost your memories,
maybe
you and the Young Host of the Palace were a couple.
But Lord Qu
is afraid that you'll leave him
after you remember everything.
So he called Song Jianshan
to change your medicine.
That's impossible!
True or false,
let's have a test.
Did I give you permission to leave court?
Your Majesty, you didn't.
Did I order you to
besiege the Tingqin Garden
in the name of our Nonuple Palace?
I did that without your permission.
Because
I found Chu.
Chu?
Father
Five years ago,
everyone thought that
Chu had died
when she executed her task.
But actually she didn't.
She just lost her memories.
She always stayed in Jin's Escort Agency.
Shut up!
You found that traitor.
Why didn't you kill her!
Five years ago,
she betrayed me.
She betrayed the entire Nonuple Palace!
You saw her,
and you dare to
keep her alive?
Chu was adopted by our Nonuple Palace
when she was little,
and she grew up with me.
How could she be a traitor?
You mean,
I vilify her?
She would never betray us!
There must be something wrong!
You dare to stand up for that bi*ch!
It was because of you.
She got lost and suffered memory loss.
It was all because of you.
How dare you!
How dare you go against me like that!
Guards.
Your Majesty
Qingyun just spoke without thinking twice.
Your Majesty, please spare him.
Take him to the dungeon
and torture him!
Your Majesty
I'll go there by myself!
She wants me to brew the medicine for her?
Right.
Zhuozhuo said
the medicine
needs a close eye to it.
I don't think other people can do it well.
Zheng
You'll help me, won't you?
Sure.
How's everything?
If Lord Qu didn't change the medicine,
it must be Song Jianshan.
No.
How could Zheng
do that to me?
I shouldn't doubt him...
You can't
give up halfway.
Right.
If you confess to him now,
he surely will
get angry.
Zheng
You really did something
to my medicine!
Fiddle with your medicine?
I knew
there was someone fiddling with
my medicine!
Lord Qu
If you don't want
Baiwan to restore her memory,
you can just tell us.
Why did you get me busy trying to cure her!
Why do you three think
I want to
prevent Baiwan from restoring her memory?
Because you think
if Baiwan has taken all her memory back,
she will be with that Young Host of the Palace
together,
and leave you behind.
If I say you all misunderstand me,
Baiwan,
will you believe me?
We saw it!
You were adding
something strange
into Baiwan's medicine.
You did!
What if the "something strange"
is for Baiwan's good?
It's sugar?
My son
How's he now?
I have obeyed your command.
The Young Host was sent to the dungeon
and cruelly tortured.
He was too arrogant and ignorant.
Since I can empower him as
the Young Host.
I also have the ability to
take his title away.
What?
Do you have anything else
to tell me?
Please spare me.
I still have one thing
to report to you.
Say it.
The Host went to the Yinxue Village.
He didn't take me with him.
But,
to ensure Chu's identity,
I secretly went there.
At that time,
I think I found
the person that hurt your Majesty earlier.
His face was covered.
He had excellent swordsmanship and I couldn't tell who he was.
But
he followed
the guard of Qu Zheng
to save Jin...
To save Chu.
So you mean,
that person is Qu Zheng?
He deliberately wield his sword
to conceal his identity?
I was kept
following those canon-delivery people.
Qu Zheng
is deeply involved in it.
In the Taoyuan Valley,
he stopped me from
getting the saussurea.
Does that mean
he is still alive?
Tingqin Garden
Right.
The person that took Qiuer away
was Song Jianshan, guard of Qu Zheng.
The order
must be given by Qu Zheng.
Lord Qu not only took away
Baiwan at the wedding,
but took Qiuer away this time.
What is going on?
He's too unpredictable.
Common sense doesn't work on him.
Anyway,
right now
we must go and bring Qiuer back.
Father-in-law
I won't bother you.
I'll go to Tingqin Garden
and bring Qiuer back safely.
Hi, Zheng!
You're playing the Guqin here?
Yeah,
what a beautiful sound!
Those disciples can't rival.
My Zheng
is really outstanding.
Yes, I am that outstanding.
And I was supposed to treat
my wife well.
But, unexpectedly,
I was mistaken as a terrible medicine-changing guy.
So heart-breaking.
My bad.
Something wrong with my eyes.
My eyes.
No more words, Baiwan.
Just leave me alone.
Zheng
Actually,
you're not only good at playing the Guqin,
but martial arts!
And
you founded
the excellent Tingqin Garden!
I've heard that
since the Tingqin Garden took shape,
every household
has pushed their kids to practice the Guqin,
wishing to
join your Garden as soon as possible.
Baiwan
I feel depressed.
So
flatteries don't work.
I was not flattering you.
I was telling the truth!
Zheng
It's time for meals.
Let's have meals together.
My depression makes any food tasteless.
I'd rather not eat.
Why you are depressed?
Anyhow,
people need to eat!
Or I'll cook for you?
Wait.
I...
Flattering doesn't work.
Cooking doesn't count.
What do you want from me?
Baiwan, you know
what I want.
I...
Madam, the way you coax your man
makes me so worried about you.
When did you come here?
No worries.
I'm here to help you out.
Can you help me make Zheng happy?
Sure!
To coax Zheng,
one move is enough.
Only one move?
What's that?
Tell me.
Coquetry.
Coquetry?
Right.
You can...
No, I can't.
Zheng is poor.
His birthday will be
in five days.
But he will have no present,
and even be misunderstood by his wife.
His wife would not do that lovey-dovey thing...
Birthday?
Zheng said
I couldn't tell you that.
No.
Zheng's birthday is coming.
But I made him upset.
So,
you made him upset.
It's you who should
make him happy again.
Do I really need to
play the woman?
Zheng
It's very late now.
What's wrong?
I'm here to play...
To apologize.
First,
reiterate
the last character of each sentence you speak.
Men can't resist that.
Zheng
Zheng~ Zheng~
Today's thing~ thing~
is my bad~ bad~
Please don't be upset
and forgive me please~
So, Baiwan,
are you being cute here?
You figure that out?
Second,
imagine he has a bug on the back of his hand
and gently scratch him.
Zheng
Don't you see it.
There's a little bug on your hand.
I'll scratch it for you.
Well,
how do you feel?
What feelings
you want me to feel?
It doesn't work?
Last
but not least,
Zheng is tender-hearted.
When he gets upset,
you just need to gently
blow in his ear.
And he will immediately cheer up.
Zheng
Your ears turn red!
You must have scratches on your ears.
I'll help you out.
Baiwan, you know what you're doing?
I am... being cute,
and trying to make you happy.
Baiwan, do you know
the difference between playing the woman and flirting?
I, I'm not flirting with you.
It's Song Jianshan.
Zheng, you just smiled!
You're not mad at me, right?
You've known me for so long.
Have I ever seriously
be mad at you?
I knew it.
I know Zheng is nice to me.
You never get really mad at me.
And you'll never prevent me from
restoring my memory.
Speaking of restoring memory,
I don't quite agree with you.
Why?
These days,
to restore your memory,
you've gone through quite a lot.
So I'm always considering
whether it's the right thing
to restore your memory.
Why would it be wrong?
What if your past memory
is not that beautiful?
I still want my memory back.
In the past,
I never asked to
restore my memory.
That's because
I didn't want my past to trouble me.
I took Jin's Escort Agency
as my new home.
But,
if
I don't restore my memory now,
I can't solve those puzzles.
I can never know
who I really am.
I can never
get rid of those problems.
But, what if
your past memory,
or even who you were in the past,
pain you badly?
What if you wanted to
get rid of your past?
No matter how
my past would be,
that's mine.
I can't throw it away.
Zheng
I believe, if it were you,
you would not appreciate
someone who can't
face herself.
So,
even if I restore my memory
and remember who I am,
nothing would be different
from now.
Trust me, will you?
Lord of Valley Junior
It, it is...
On our way here,
I've heard that Nonuple Palace
had a huge fight with Tingqin Garden
the other days.
It seems like
rumors are true.
So,
Qu Zheng took away Muqiu,
because he wanted to threaten
Jin's Escort Agency and the Taoyuan Valley
to compete with the other martial schools?
If so, I can't keep Qiuer
in such a dangerous place.
Who's that out there?
I'm Yu Linfeng, Young Master of the Taoyuan Valley.
Go ask Qu Zheng
to release my wife Jin Muqiu!
Yu Linfeng
He came here?
Since Mr Yu has come to pick you,
I can spare a carriage
to send you back.
Baiwan
What do you think?
It's you two's stuff.
I'm not in charge.
Okay.
I'm not going back.
Miss
Mr Yu has traveled so far for you.
Are you really not coming back?
Taoyuan Valley has so many rules.
I feel so restricted.
I'm not going back.
This
needs your thorough consideration.
I've decided.
I'm not going back.
She's not going back?
Mr Yu, don't worry.
Mrs. Yu is all good
in our Tingqin Garden.
It's just,
she doesn't want to go back to the Taoyuan Valley with you.
You're lying!
Miss Jin
No, I mean, Mrs. Yu.
Mrs. Yu was clearly
threatened by you.
Lord Qu
I'd appreciated you have saved me once
in the Taoyuan Valley.
If you can release Qiuer
and she's safe and sound,
I'll let everything go.
I just invited
Mrs. Yu to pay a visit to my place.
How could it be threatening?
Cut the crap.
If you don't release Qiuer,
I'll destroy your Tingqin Garden.
Mr Yu, if you still don't believe,
I have one more proof here.
This can prove my words.
What is it?
This is the latest novel written by Mrs. Yu.
It was printed this morning.
If she was
threatened by me,
how could she
take the novel out?
By the way, Mr Yu,
in the novel
there is a new character.
At that time,
a swordsman named Qu Zheng
suddenly showed up
and saved everybody from disasters.
Lord of Valley Junior
Mrs. Yu seemed to
write Lord Qu into her novel.
Mrs. Yu not only wrote me
into her novel,
but intentionally
described me as
a big hero
fighting against a shameless guy named Yu Lingfeng.
Think about it.
If Mrs. Yu was
really abducted,
would she write a novel like this?
Impossible!
You forced her to write that.
Mr Yu
I've already
finished my job.
If you still don't believe,
there's nothing else I can do.
Help yourself.
You.
Stop!
Qu Zheng, stop!
Lord of Valley Junior, don't go any further.
The mist may be toxic.
Qu Zheng
Listen!
Qiuer is
my wife of our Taoyuan Valley.
I would destroy your Tingqin Garden
and bring her back!
Right!
Lord of Valley Junior
What should we do next?
You are seriously reading it?
I saw it by myself that
Qu Zhen took away Qiuer.
He can't trick me
like this.
And Qiuer is very smart.
She can send out
this novel
under threat.
The novel
must have some codes.
If I can crack the code,
perhaps I can
detect the traps inside
and save her out.
It figures.
"At that time,
a swordsman named Qu Zheng..."
Oh, my nose.
I got it.
Lord of Valley Junior
What did you find out this time?
Jueming, check this out.
"Yu Lingfeng always has no shame.
Now he ends up like this.
He deserves it."
Do you find out anything?
Mrs. Yu swore at you.
No.
See.
The last characters of each sentence in this paragraph,
if connected,
become the line:
Wait for me,
and I will go out.
Qiuer is
signaling to me through her novel.
Lord of Valley Junior
We've spent days and nights here
researching Mrs. Yu's novel.
And that's what you found out?
That's too far-fetched.
You don't get it.
Qiuer
Rest assured.
I'll get you out of here!
Enough.
He's our Young Host of the Palace anyway.
Though he made mistakes,
we can't go too far.
Go.
Be careful.
If they dare to
bully you again,
you should fight back.
You got me?
But I can't see.
So what?
As long as we practice hard,
we'll never be afraid of them.
Come on.
Let's go practicing.
One.
Two.
Three.
This arm should be higher.
Qingyun
Is there any good news?
Father said he know a famous doctor.
My eye can be cured.
Really?
So great!
Soon I will be able to
see your face.
You'll see more than my face.
I'll take you to
see the most beautiful landscape
and do what you want to do.
But,
master has assigned me a new task.
I'll wait for you.
You're the first person I want to see.
I'll pass Baiyun Town.
The town has your favorite dessert
Baiyu pastry.
I will buy you some.
Okay.
Chu
Why are you still thinking about her?
That night in Taoyuan Valley,
you helped me prove her identity.
Did you know
that she was doomed.
She betrayed the Majesty.
She was doomed.
What if she didn't?
What do you mean?
You couldn't rival her.
But there would be only one
Envoy Xueyue in Nonuple Palace.
So you wanted her to die.
You think
that I framed her?
True or false,
I will find out.
What a pity.
You're imprisoned now.
Stop.
Go and tell the Majesty.
I want to see him.
Your Majesty
Young Host of the Palace wants to see you.
You've been wanting to
to see me in the prison.
What for?
You've figured it out?
I did, my father.
I owe my life to you, Father.
I should follow your orders.
Last time I did that arbitrarily.
I acted recklessly.
So,
you come to admit your mistakes.
Because you want me to
release you?
I know
Father is still mad at me.
I'll do anything
to ease your anger.
You think I will believe in
your rhetoric?
You just want me to
release you,
so you can
go and find Chu, the traitor. Right?
I do want to see her.
How dare you!
But this time,
I will do it for you, father.
Oh? I would like to hear.
How will you do it for me?
As to Chu and I,
our lives should be decided by Nonuple Palace.
But she knows too many
secrets of Nonuple Palace.
Whether she has lost her memory
or not,
we can't have her on the loose.
Go on.
Before, I couldn't believe
that she's a traitor.
So I want to
bring her back to Nonuple Palace,
so you can investigate by yourself.
If she is a traitor,
I will surely punish her.
I will personally
kill her for you.
Fancy words.
But you
besieged Tingqin Garden with your men.
Except for making a fool of yourself,
you gained nothing at all.
This time,
how can I believe that
you can succeed?
This time,
I will definitely bring her back.
Because I know
the real protector of the Puyuan Canon
is Qu Zheng.