I won't work overtime today
Episode 4
Mr. Li, please go back early
Don't disturb my work
Why do you look like a different person again
I don't forbid them all
Did the regular employee push the job?
Why are you working overtime so late again
I didn't finish it myself
It's quite honest
Show me, I'll show it for you
Can you finish it quickly
No thanks
That's your tea
Can I have a taste
Pour yourself
Can I have a cup of tea
West Lake Longjing
Whether you like to drink or not
How do you know I like it
You went out of your way to investigate my preferences
If you put your heart on me
Half of it is spent on work
You don't have to work overtime
Mr. Li, your time is very precious
So I ask you not to
Waste time on mine
What are you doing
Eviction order
Ai Fei is sleepy
Let's go back to the bedroom and rest
Has been processed
He Mingyue
You must not
Be fooled by this trick again
Trying to touch me secretly
I'm off work
Let's go back
Hello, second sister
What's wrong
You're too old.
But it still looks appropriate
I think Yahan is good
If you don't like it
Let me introduce you to a few more
Done
Don't rush
I'm interested in girls now
I'm busy first. I'm hanging up
This thing called instant noodles
It smells quite fragrant
Don't rush
I'll send you in five minutes, five minutes
What are you sending?
Sister Jiaojiao, you are still working on weekends
Zhao Ting hasn't stopped since eight o'clock in the morning
Been asking me for information
Sister Zhao Ting
I saw her shopping just now
I didn't expect that
It seems that we can't spare her
Sister Jiaojiao, what are you thinking?
Nothing
Just wanted to have a friendly exchange with her
Come on, I'll cut you another steak
Thank you dear
I've eaten enough
Thank you
Today's food is delicious
I especially like it
But my side
There is still some work unfinished
So I might have to leave early
Then be careful
Then we'll get in touch
Remember to call me later
I'm leaving first
Bye
Honey, you've been waiting for a long time
Thank you
My dear
Because I just had something
So I'm late
You don't blame people, do you
You're so kind
That
There is a place I really want to go to
Why don't you go with someone else
Then let's go
It's okay
Honey, your hair is so handsome today
Baby, you still
Please answer the phone
Hello, Sister Ting
Hello
I have sent you the information
You can just send me an email address
I'll read it when I get back then
Like this
But you still
Hurry up and take a look
Is it okay
Hang up
Honey, then let's go
Why don't you finish it first
Hello
Hello Sister Ting
My information
I've been sending it to you for so long
Why don't you watch it
Jiaojiao
It's the weekend and you don't
Settle the bill
What happened to the baby
I
Tingting, who is this
Baby, who is this boy
I have work to do
Give me your phone
Sister Ting, I'm here
I really can't afford to delay
Really
He Jiaojiao, you're enough
Sister Ting
Why don't you reply to my message
Go to bed early. Good night
Momma da
Sister Jiaojiao, why did you come so early
Come to work
Don't you have a lot of rest
Anyway, every day we
It's all sent by express delivery
Organize and organize documents
Screen resumes or something
And there's no other chance
Why are you so energetic
If there is no chance
So the best way to get the opportunity
Is doing everything well
Little Master
Our location is so remote
The emperor won't come at all
He doesn't even see us
You spend every day
So much thought about makeup
What the hell is it doing
Why is our Komatsu wronged
I just can't figure it out
Why waste your mind
This is not a waste of effort
Opportunities are always left
Of a prepared person
Things we can do
Is to do the best that you can do
Dear little masters
Today, the emperor has a sudden elegance
Call all concubines to visit the garden together
Enjoy the spring scenery together
Little masters, please leave now
Thank you father-in-law
The emperor arrives
Emperor
You are the concubine He of the Dawn Moon Palace
Return to the emperor's words, yes
Ai Fei, do you think the flowers are beautiful
This flower blooms so beautifully
The emperor's vision
It's really unbeatable
The emperor's concubines are conscious
All right
I look at the concubines
Poor complexion
Thin clothes
Let's go back and rest
Yes
He Bin
You stay
Love Concubine
I think
Only you are more beautiful than this flower
Everyone, in five minutes, the big conference room
Mr. Li wants to hold a meeting for everyone
By the way, interns also have to attend
Don't be late, everyone
Mr. Li, what's going on recently
Call meetings so frequently
Are you interested in it
Who's in our center
You little brain
Still worrying about the boss
I think he must have a crush on you
The company will expand further in the future
So today's meeting
The main content is
Deployment of the next recruitment work
Director Wu, please report
Past Recruitment of the Company
Meeting Minutes
Already writing
Jiaojiao, don't get me wrong
I didn't mean to rush you
I just wanted to say
What if you can't do it yourself
You can tell me
I can help you
No thank you Sister Ting
That
Come on
We make progress together
In the past year
The resumes that passed the preliminary screening are
Three thousand four hundred and two copies
The pass rate is 2.7 percent
Final admission and passing the probation period
2.729 percent
Received in total
One hundred and twenty-four thousand seven hundred
Sixty-two resumes
Those who passed the primary were
Three thousand four hundred and two copies
Accurate to three decimal places
So the data should be
2.729 percent
If behind
The data is still inaccurate
Then there is no need to report
I'm sorry, Mr. Li
It's because we don't work properly
How was the hiring situation last month
Mr. Li, this
This data hasn't been counted yet
Today is only the third
So
Your entire center
No one knows
Li Jiakai, you come and report
Aren't you responsible for Zhao Ting
You report
He Jiaojiao
I left her in charge
Refuel
Who doesn't know
He Jiaojiao is an intern
It's this evasion layer by layer
If you don't, you will hit it
Is it on the intern's head
Co-author someone else came for an internship
Just to learn
How did you take the blame