[English subtitles are available]
[Fall in Love with a Fox]
[EP07]
I have to make it clear.
Behave well.
Don't talk too much.
Don't look
what are forbidden to look.
Housekeeper, may I ask what this place is?
This is our warehouse.
It is always heavily guarded.
If you don't have anything special,
please stay away from here.
This way, please.
This way.
Where is he?
What are you doing? Keep up.
Coming.
Dear guests,
this is your room.
Call me
if you need anything.
Thank you.
Where we just passed by
must be the warehouse of Taoyuan Valley.
It is heavily guarded.
We can check that later.
Yes, madam.
They are coming for the warehouse
of Taoyuan Valley.
As temporary workers,
if you want to stay in Taoyuan Valley,
you better work hard.
Understand?
It seems like I have to stay here
for two more days before my Miss comes.
Something is wrong.
One is missing. Where is he?
Coming.
The yard is too big. I got lost.
Got lost?
This is not the place you think.
Hurry up! Do your job.
Pour this water.
What the hell?
You did it on purpose?
How dare you split it on me?
Are you blind?
How dare you stare at me?
Do you want me to
rip your eyes out?
The steward has fallen down.
You better take him
for a rest.
Ok.
Steward. Be careful.
I'll deal with you when I get back.
He needs a spanking.
Deserve that.
I'm telling you
if you meet him later,
stay away from him.
Why don't you say anything?
Are you scared?
What's your name?
Qingyun
My father said he knew a famous doctor
who can cure my eyes.
Really? That's great.
I can see you
very soon.
At that time you can not only see me.
I can also take you
to see the best view
and do whatever you like.
You're not freaking out, are you?
Don't you even
know your name?
I am Qi.
I'm Jin Baiwan.
Why are you staring at me
all the time?
Your voice
sounds like a person
I used to know.
Again.
You guys
are all the same.
One said I look like
a person he used to know.
Now you tell me my voice sounds familiar.
However,
She doesn't talk as much as you.
Just joking.
In another word,
the man I said
is not you.
I do listen clearly.
The man in your mouth
was me.
How can you find
here so fast?
I have made it clear
on the letter.
I had no way but to
let you send me to Taoyuan Valley.
I didn't behave well.
Since I am here,
I have no reason
to trouble you.
We were good yesterday.
Why?
You are so cold
to me today.
Besides,
we don't say troubles between couples.
But the marriage
is fake indeed.
As long as everyone takes it seriously,
who cares it is fake?
As the Lord of Tingqin Garden,
because of being used,
you signed the marriage contract.
If everyone knows,
how will they think of you?
If I say,
I don't care.
But I do.
I only meet you
in chance.
I can't reward you
if you treat me like this.
We have a life time
to be together.
You have so many chances
to pay me back.
A life time?
How can you say those words
casually?
I get it.
You are right.
Words like a lifetime
can't be promised easily.
Since this marriage
was put forward by you,
you can cancel that.
But for this,
you have to consider it carefully.
Although we have signed
the marriage contract,
this is still a serious thing.
I won't force you.
You didn't force me.
It's...
I don't want to
trouble you anymore.
What if I'm willing
to be troubled?
Let go in this way.
When you figure this out,
you can come to me
to break the marriage.
Therefore,
I will not trouble you.
Dad
Are you sure this
can attract Mr Yu?
I have already told you that.
He
likes girls
who can do unique romance.
As long as we do what he wants,
this must work.
But
my music
has almost finished.
Play one more.
I can only play this one.
Look, my girl,
why can't you get any advantage
from your mom?
If no one stops your mom,
she could play it all night long.
Her...
Coming.
Fingers.
Mr Jin
Well...
Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Go.
I seek for Spring by riversides on a fine day,
What refreshing sight does the boundless view bring?
I find the face of vernal wind in easy way:
Myriads of reds and violets reveal only spring.
Miss Muqiu
Mr Yu
I never know Miss Mu
has so many talents.
My father told me when I was a little girl
that I have to be
a well-behaved lady.
So these are easy for me.
It's indeed a custom of a famous family.
My girl can't do anything but
talk nonsense
like me.
By a happy coincidence,
I have brought my Xiao.
Why don't we cooperate a song?
Sure.
So let's play...
Let's play The Autumn Days.
Okay.
That's right.
What a relief that
her mother forced her
to learn this song.
Bingo.
Cancel the engagement?
Baiwan told me like that.
Is this because
I told that to Su Zhuozhuo?
Lord
That was because Su Zhuozhuo drugged me.
It's hard for me to find a wife.
Now this has been messed up.
It seems that
I have to be alone to death.
Lord
I won't let you be alone to death.
You've got me.
No.
I will help you to convince her.
Sit down.
Do you forget that
we come to this valley
is for Saussurea involucrata case.
Baiwan not being around is a good thing.
Wait for a few days.
When the young lady of Jin's Escort Agency comes,
she will be protected.
So about cancelling the engagement...
Relax.
This marriage
can't be cancelled easily.
Linfeng
About Tongfu Town,
do you arrange it well?
Mr Jin, you can rest assured.
It has been done.
Ok. Good.
The kite is flying.
Kite.
Miss Muqiu, do you like kites?
My Qiuer
likes kites so much.
Dad
Jueming
Find a kite to me.
Yes.
This is
made by you?
Yes.
Can I write on it?
Of course.
Robe may wet in apricot flowers rain.
Out cool in my face the willows blow.
Go. Let's fly the kite.
Mr Yu, look.
The kite is flying.
It was all my fault.
Miss Muqiu
Don't mistake me.
I am definitely not
that kind of easy guy.
I did not let you kiss me
on purpose, too.
Miss Muqiu
Although we already have engagement,
after these days
with you,
I find that
you are
the one I dreamed of.
So I won't dare to offend you.
Dreamed of?
Is that mean
you like...
Yes.
I fancy you.
I really
appreciate this marriage.
Me, too.
Rest assured.
In my whole life, I will try my best
to not change this feeling.
You all had a long day.
Take down all the things,
and you can relax in the hotel. Hurry up.
Miss, be careful.
Give me your hand, my lady.
Come on. Take all down.
Ok.
Slow down.
Miss Muqiu
Mr Yu
Do you want to
walk with me in the night market
in the town tonight?
Sure.
I want to eat this one
and that one.
I'll have both of them, please.
Ok.
Let's go.
Give it to me.
Sugar figures for sale.
Sugar figurine.
Mr and Miss,
do you want sugar figures?
I want this one.
Ok.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
Let's go.
[Sugar figure.]
Take it.
Thanks.
Appreciate your help.
Here, the money.
Thanks.
Did you record that?
Yes.
I have noted them down.
What are you guys writing?
Our Lord of Valley Junior told me that
all of your favorites
should be recorded
on this little notebook.
So later
we won't make mistakes.
And you
won't be angry anymore.
You are so considerate.
Here, Jueming.
Ok.
Miss Muqiu
This is the first time
I am being with my loved girl.
If there's anything wrong,
please do tolerate me a little.
You did so well.
Here's one more thing.
May I ask you
not to call me Mr Yu
in the future?
After all,
you and I
may marry soon.
Ok.
So
what about I call you as Brother Shu?
Brother Shu?
Yu Linfeng means a jade tree in the wind.
Miss Muqiu
You are really talented.
So, since you
call me Brother Shu,
I'll call you Qiuer?
Ok.
Move.
Be careful.
Oh my God.
The true love
is so sweet.
Qiuer, are you ok?
I'm fine.
By the way,
there's a bookshop in front.
Let's go there.
Let's go.
Bye. Have a good day.
Hi, how about the sales
of Qiu qiuer's books?
Her books are always the bestsellers.
Look.
These are new goods.
I can recommend some of them to you.
Ok.
This one, The Lord didn't Behave Well,
has been the most popular one these days.
Hey, how can you recommend
these tacky books to others?
Tacky?
Sir,
how can you talk like that?
These novels
only catch the shadows
and distort the facts.
And the words of them
are rather filthy and frivolous.
Am I wrong for saying that?
You know what?
Don't ever touch if you don't buy.
What's your attitude to my Lord?
He...
Miss Jin, I can tell you that
two years ago,
there was some bad novel.
It depicted
our Lord
as a
play boy.
We all got mad at that.
Two years ago?
Oh.
It was written by me.
Two years ago dad always forced me to get married.
It was so annoying.
So I wrote that novel.
Qiuer
You are a lady from a famous family.
Don't read this book
out of your curiosity.
Do you understand?
You can't label all of them.
These books seem to
have a good selling.
Maybe,
many people like to read them.
But a true reader
will look down these.
Do you really hate such novels?
He doesn't dislike them.
He hates them!
So
if one day
those writers are standing
in front of you,
what will you do?
Birds of a feather flock together.
If there's really someone
who love this vulgar thing,
then I
will be away from them
and never be in touch with them.
Cancel.
Don't cancel.
He has called me Miss Jin again,
why can't I cancel it?
What should I do?
I guess he did it on purpose.
How can I decide
this kind of thing?
Why do you come?
I offended Steward Wang.
I'm afraid he will be hard on me.
So I want to take a walk out.
Don't worry.
He might forget it tomorrow.
Qi
Where are you?
Get out.
Hurry.
Qi
The business
is not done yet.
Get out!
Qi
Where is he hiding?
He really holds a grudge.
Come out.
Don't worry.
Let me deal with that.
Little thing.
Bast**d.
You think I can do nothing to you?
Get out quickly.
When I find you,
watch out how I will do to you.
Go go go.
Be quick.
Don't let me find you.
One.
Two.
I have seen you.
Get out.
Don't hide.
Wait for me to catch you.
I just look down on people
who bully the weak.
Feel good?
Don't worry.
I can put you under my wing in the kitchen.
He won't dare to do anything to you.
What a freak.
Cancel.
Don't cancel.
Coming here can't avoid me
being a kitchen helper.
So why don't
you come with me
to find Zheng?
You don't need to do that anymore.
Why are you here?
Me?
I want to be the peacemaker.
You obviously like
Zheng a lot.
Why do you have to cancel the engagement?
Nonsense.
Who likes him?
For sure?
Of course.
Think about it twice.
Zheng really stands by his words.
If you really cancel it,
there's no
going back on it.
I will not go back on this.
Next time I see him,
I will tell him clearly.
Zheng
Did you see Miss Jin?
No. No. No.
No.
You wanted to see her?
It has to be her
who has business with me.
Fine.
When I meet her next time,
I will deal with this.
You said you will talk to him yourself.
I didn't say today.
Fine.
I wanted to make a peace between you.
It seems
there's nothing I can do.
Zheng. Wait.
Zheng
I like him?
May...
be.
Lord Xueyue
I have checked it out.
The whole warehouse is truly like an iron wall.
I really can't break it in.
The marriage ceremony in Taoyuan Valley
has gathered many Kung Fu masters.
Do not act rashly.
Yes.
It seems
we can only wait for the night
before the ceremony when their people open it.
Go.
There are two or three days left
before we get to Taoyuan Valley.
It's fine.
It is at the end of the month.
We won't waste good days.
End of the month.
Yes, end of the month.
Oh, shoot...
What's wrong?
The end of the month is the deadline of my writing.
How can I forget that?
And dad,
don't tell Yu Linfeng
and people in Taoyuan Valley
that I write novels. Do you get it?
Get it.
Qiuer
I haven't been writing
for this long time.
No. No.
The contract has said
that I can't delay my writings.
Qiuer
Brother Shu
Do you want to
fly the kite with me?
I have no time.
I noticed that these days when you have time,
you will write things.
What are you writing about?
I am writing some documentary
articles about the Escort Agency.
Qiuer
You are really a talented girl.
Can I have the pleasure to read it?
No.
I have a habit in my writings
that I can't let anyone to see
beside me.
Otherwise, I can't write it.
I see.
I can assure you
I will not look at it.
You have so many talents
and you work so hard.
I really fancy you a lot.
I will not take a peek on it.
I just stay here to company you.
Then you can go there to company me.
There?
I can't be distracted. Continue.
Kung Fu Master takes down the devil
on the bed and laughs.
Laughs.
You are so concentrated.
I think this article
must be very beautiful
and every phrase is a gem.
I thought you said you weren't peeking.
I didn't.
I was focusing on
looking at you.
If I let you mistake this,
it's all my fault.
Here,
I apologize to you again.
Go ahead.
Kung Fu Master laughs that
if you don't be my girl,
I will...
God.
How can I write
with this staring?
If you have time in the evening,
I want to have dinner with you.
I have something to say to you.
Ok.
A man who has engagement
still gets close
with other woman.
A man who has engagement
still gets so close with other woman.
Why are you hanging around
in the valley all day?
Told me to figure out?
Do you figure it out?
I don't believe.
If I hide in the kitchen,
how can you find me?
Who is Jin Baiwan?
Me.
Lord Qu from Tingqin Garden
asks you to be there.
Go.
Lord Qu
This is the pastry cook.
Thank you.
Miss Jin
I know what you want to say.
Just speak out.
So I will say it directly.
The pastry
is chewy.
And this one, too.
In the morning,
Song Jianshan almost broke one tooth.
You find me here
just to tell me this?
Or what?
Don't you think I
will talk with you about that thing?
That thing...
If you want to say, go ahead.
Miss Jin
It seems that you have lost some weight.
Is that what you want to tell me?
It's only one day.
How can you be skinny like this?
It seems that the job in the kitchen
is too hard.
Why are you so close to me?
If there's nothing else,
I'll leave.
Who says that?
Why are you always hiding from me?
Don't play a trick on me.
Is that because of
our engagement?
If this thing can't be settled
as soon as possible,
are you going to keep
hiding from me?
I'm not hiding from you.
It was you who said that
this depends on me.
So you have to wait for me
to tell you the result.
Don't play tricks on me.
When my Miss comes,
I'll wait and see how you will do to me.
Don't know
when she will arrive.
This Taoyuan Town
is really bustling.
Good.
I heard that fifty percent of the
properties in this town all
belong to the Taoyuan Valley.
When you be there,
you will be the first lady in charge.
You are in charge of all the things.
But I don't want to be
the first lady.
No.
Well...
What do you want to do?
I just want to write my novels.
Oh, sweetie,
it's ok to write novels.
But
you have to keep this from Linfeng.
Hiding this is good.
At that year,
when I read your novels,
I just passed out.
No.
I was shocked by your talent.
My girl
Now you're going to get married,
how about stopping writing that?
How is this possible?
This is my only hobby.
Dad
No. No. No. Don't pout.
I can't bear this.
You can keep writing.
Write!
You are the best.
Okay...
But
Linfeng can't know about this.
If he knows,
he will not tolerate you
writing anything like I do.
Don't worry, dad.
I will not let him know.
What's wrong?
Head Escort
The lady's dowry chest was turned over.
Oh, the dowry chest was turned over.
Turned over?
What happened?
Hurry up.
Help the lady pick them up.
Be quick.
Surround this.
Don't let others see.
Everyone helps with the picking.
Uncle
I know Qiuer loves reading.
I don't know she takes so many books
in her dowry.
Readers, you know.
They are supposed to be like this.
Yes. Supposed to be.
Linfeng. You are here too.
We can pick up
these books.
Don't care.
Uncle. Qiuer
Why are you sweating?
Sweating?
Yes.
Really?
No.
Where is the sweat?
How can we sweat?
Yes.
Qiuer
Are you too nervous
to see
my parents soon?
Your parents?
Yes, right?
Yes.
I'm a little nervous.
My girl
doesn't experience this before.
Don't worry.
My parents are nice to others.
And my mother is just like you
who knows unique romance,
You
can share with each other every day.
You will get along with each other well.
Yes, exactly.
Will get along.
Of course.
What?
Steward Wang beat Qi?
Yeah.
Steward Wang
hurt his waist last night.
He stayed in bed all night.
Don't know why.
He said this was done by Qi.
So
he got a bunch of servants
and surround Qi
to beat him.
This...
Qi is coming.
Hurry up. Move.
Do your job.
Qi
Your hand is bleeding.
I'm not bleeding.
Don't be that strong.
It's my fault
to let your hand hurt like this.
None of your business.
How can that be?
Those things
were done by me.
But steward Wang only punished you.
But this doesn't matter.
Wait here.
I'll find you some medicine.
Wait.
Since you asked me out,
what are you going to say?
Mr Qu
I have known that the marriage
between Jin Baiwan and you
is a fake one.
So what?
I have been into you for so long.
Investigating about the Puyuan Canon
is also me asking my father
to do.
Will you consider me?