[English subtitles are available]
[Bright Time]
[EP03]
What happened?
Tires flat.
The same situation.
Me too.
Wait...
Ours are flat as well.
Who would do this?
Look.
[Got flat tires?]
See this.
[Surprised?]
And here.
[Big dummy.]
Who's this mean?
Who did it?
I don't know,
I really don't.
It's on purpose.
[Pump it yourself.]
There's more up ahead.
There.
Over there.
[Keep going!]
This...
Who did this?
Who?
Jinghui...
You're really working hard.
What's going on?
Why is
everyone pumping their tires?
Flat tires?
Then...
what about mine?
Oh, it's okay.
I'm fine.
Let me check it for you,
give it a revival.
Can it still
be saved?
You know, every day when I come home...
Look!
I told you he's arrogant!
Exactly.
Lan Jinghui! How dare you show up here?
Why wouldn't I?
You...
Yes. What?
Take this.
Your behavior is outrageous.
It can't be tolerated!
As the President of the Student Union,
I must sternly
criticize you today.
And I'll tell Ms. Fang,
Mr. Zhang,
and inform the whole school!
I find you really strange.
You're just the Vice President.
The President doesn't say anything,
why are you always meddling?
You're so intense.
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
- Mr. Zhang.
- Hello, Mr. Zhang.
Chen Luyang,
let me show you how to greet properly.
Hello, Director!
You know, our class
always comes together
in such
strange moments.
Hello, Director!
Mr. Zhang,
I have something important
to report.
Lower your voice. I've seen it all.
Don't stand there.
Go home.
Director, our bikes have flat tires.
All of you
with flat tires
should take a taxi home today,
and get reimbursement
from Lan Jinghui tomorrow morning.
Great. Follow my lead!
Let's take taxis together.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
- Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Thank you.
Thanks.
What's the issue this time?
Director,
Jinghui bought water to apologize,
and he also said...
Did I allow you to speak?
Don't you know
why he did this?
Rummaging through textbooks,
invading privacy...
Fine, even if you are
sincerely apologizing,
what does putting salt
in their water mean?
Lan Jinghui,
I understand you.
As a transfer student,
it's not easy to integrate
into this group.
But can't you show some sincerity
and greet your
classmates properly?
Look at what you're wearing.
Does it look like a good student?
Ma Yiming, Lan Jinghui,
you've got a warning.
If you do it again,
you'll be punished.
Yes, sir.
Got it.
I didn't hear you.
Yes, sir!
Usually, you're all
bursting with energy.
What's going on now?
Speed up!
That's it.
Keep up the pace.
Keep pumping
while listening to me.
I'll check back in ten minutes.
If any low on air,
we'll do this again tomorrow, all right?
- All right.
Keep it up.
- Keep it up.
Completely out of air?
You've left me breathless.
That's a figure of speech.
Why not be straightforward?
I'm exhausted.
Keep pumping.
Really?
What else?
You do it?
By the way,
when can we check out
the basketball team?
Oh,
there is a training this morning.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
You didn't ask.
Stop working, let's go check it out.
Jinghui!
Mr. Zhang will be back
to check soon.
No worries, I'll check the training for you.
Keep going.
Jinghui!
Jia Letian, is it you?
Lan Jinghui?
Wait,
why are you the only one working?
The others... are training.
Training?
[This is training?]
Where's your captain?
I want to join you.
Who are you?
Don't you know him?
The Spider-Man swinging around
during the election rally.
That's you?
Join us? No problem.
Start by cleaning like him.
We're joining
to play,
not to clean.
Sorry,
our team's full.
And
we don't take
just anyone.
Look at me.
One-on-one!
Next!
Nice shot!
Jia Letian, come here!
It's training!
Let these guys
keep cleaning the balls.
Listen, you'll pay for this.
Beating me doesn't matter.
Joining the team
is up to our captain.
With your skills,
I doubt
your captain's any good.
What?
Bi Peng.
Who's looking for me?
Are you the captain?
Are you challenging me?
Or you can just admit defeat
and let me join the team.
Interesting.
Fine,
I'll give you three chances.
If you can score one point
on me,
you can join the team.
Don't say we're bullying the newbies.
Fine, after joining the team,
I must have the rights I deserve.
We're not here to clean balls.
Beat me first, then we'll talk.
Hey,
what's going on?
Spider-Man from Class 5
and Bi Peng from Class 8 are fighting.
Fighting?
Yeah, I'm going to check it out.
Nice, you've got some guts.
Let's do this.
Jinghui!
Calm down.
Don't you want to see
if he can beat Bi Peng?
What's the trick?
- Ms. Fang?
- What's going on?
They had a bit of an argument
and decided to have a one-on-one.
A one-on-one?
Yes.
Basketball?
Are you done?
Safety first.
Don't cry
if you fall.
I suggest you tie it.
Nice shot!
You...
What? I won.
I didn't say start.
You didn't say not to start either.
Hello, Ms. Fang, Mr. Zhao.
When did you get here?
Letian,
be here on time for training tomorrow.
Let's go.
Okay.
Wait!
That doesn't count.
We should do it again.
I'm tired.
Let's go.
Watch out!
Are you okay?
What's your problem, Bi Peng?
Is basketball your way to vent?
Come here and apologize!
Apologize!
All right, everyone.
Back to class.
Nothing to see here.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
It's okay, I understand.
Just be careful when playing basketball.
Don't hurt anyone.
How many times have I told you
to change your bad temper!
It's okay.
He didn't mean to.
Thank you.
Is that the apology?
Since it can play
such a big role,
what is the use of the police?
You two, stop it!
Go back.
Ms. Fang, I forgot my uniform.
Go get it.
Let's go.
Ling Dong.
What's up?
Um...
I noticed you didn't bring any plants.
I have extra at home,
so I brought some...
I don't need it.
Thank you.
Good morning, apprentice.
Morning.
Morning, Jinghui.
What are you doing?
Loosening the soil.
Lan Jinghui,
you used tricks
to beat me yesterday.
Let's go again today!
I'm busy.
Can't you see I'm loosening the soil?
What do you mean,
you look down on me?
Ma Yiming, apprentice,
you all saw it.
He made the first move,
not me.
I told you,
green plants are dangerous.
Quicker, veterans!
Show some veteran spirit!
Ma Yiming,
keep up!
Well done, Lan Jinghui.
Excellent.
Faster, faster!
Great!
Faster!
Pause!
How do you like
my six-word title?
It's decent.
Bi Peng's hand
is bigger than mine, right?
How many thorns did he stick in?
Why do you care?
Don't you think my cactus
isn't getting enough sun?
You might be right.
Hang it up?
Good idea.
It just feels a bit lacking.
Outside?
Perfect.
There.
Lan Jinghui
did the right thing.
Ma Yiming, you did well too.
These plants
really don't get enough
sunlight inside.
All right, listen up,
let's move
these plants outside.
We just reviewed the probability
formula for classical models.
So, the probability of A is the number
of basic events in A
divided by
the total number of basic events.
For example,
if we're rolling
two dice simultaneously,
the result
of the second die
could be...
Give it to me.
I wasn't playing.
It's in the desk.
Anyone else in class with a phone?
Take it out now.
Anyone?
Just him?
Lan Jinghui,
how about you?
I wasn't.
Then how did you
message Ma Yiming?
Bring it out.
Don't make me force you to.
Anymore?
None.
None?
Good.
Hello, Xiaoai.
[*Intelligent voice assistant like Siri]
I'm here.
It's here.
It really is here.
Jovi.
[*Intelligent voice assistant like Siri]
I'm here.
It's here.
Anymore?
Is this funny?
Funny or not!
Not funny,
not funny.
Both of you,
call your parents,
or forget about your phones.
Let's continue the class!
Back to where we left off...
What's so funny?
Where's your phone?
I don't use a phone.
Excuse me?
Are you from ancient times?
That's all
for today's class.
Do you remember
what I just taught?
Yes.
Alright, class over.
Stand up.
Goodbye, teacher.
Goodbye.
So many phones.
Impressive.
He has everything.
There's more?
[Sent Ling Dong to my office.]
Ms. Fang wants you
in the office.
[Got it, Ms. Fang.]
How did you know
that?
[You too,]
[and remember to bring your phone.]
You're here.
Yeah.
Put your phones in the pouch.
Ling Dong,
we have two spots
for the city-wide physics competition.
Mr. Guo recommended you.
If you're interested,
fill out this registration
form.
Do I
need to attend every day?
No,
only on Mondays and Thursdays.
Any issues
with the schedule?
No.
Lan Jinghui.
Here.
Your 3,000-character self-critique?
It's in the classroom.
Go back to find it now,
or write a new one here.
If you can't finish,
stay with me for overtime tonight.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Hello?
Mom,
I might
be home late today.
If you get home first,
wait for me
to cook.
I know, okay.
Thought you didn't use a phone?
I mean... I find you
talk nonsense effortlessly.
Aren't you afraid I'll report you?
Well, in that case, I can't promise
to keep your secrets,
big nephew...
Shh!
I'm telling you,
don't tell anyone.
Keep it hidden.
Don't let anyone catch you.
Don't let anyone find out!
Keep it hidden!
- Hi, Xiaohua.
- Xiaohua.
Don't forget
what you promised us, okay?
Please.
Thank you.
We're off now,
bye.
Bye.
That octopus ball place is so good.
I'll take you there now.
Lan Jinghui,
why are you still here?
I haven't finished my self-critique.
Once I finish, I'll leave.
Why haven't you left?
I'm cleaning up.
If my memory serves me,
Liu Shu should have done this.
They had something urgent and left.
Didn't I just teach you
to learn to say no?
You've let
me down.
Come on, I'll clean for you.
No, you still
have your self-critique to write.
See, I've learned to say no.
What...
That's not...
how you use it.
Done.
You're still sweeping?
I'll do it for you.
It's okay.
Almost done.
Leave it to me.
It's okay,
I'll do it myself.
Then...
let me take out the trash for you.
Is that all right?
Okay.
I'm leaving.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Bye.
Who? Who did this?
Don't think I don't know.
Who did this?
I'm talking to you!
Lan Jinghui led it.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Get your monitor here.
I am the monitor.
You're in trouble, you know?
Now, I need you to
take some students
to clean up downstairs.
Okay.
Wait.
Take down the flower shelf.
Director.
To my office.
Fang Hai,
you've been at this school
for quite a while now,
and safety
is our top priority here.
What if something had happened?
I was just thinking about starting
the new semester with a fresh outlook.
I asked the students
to bring their favorite plants
to school to nurture them.
I thought
it would lift their spirits
each day.
Before doing this,
I had already
planned
everything meticulously
and even bought the plant stand.
I fear something would go wrong.
I never imagined it could fall
in the middle of the night.
Spare me the excuses.
Young teachers with new ideas,
I support and commend that.
But if you're going to have plants,
safety measures must be taken.
Can you handle the responsibility
if a pot falls
and injures someone?
Understood, Mr. Zhang.
I didn't consider everything properly.
Please rest assured,
I will handle the aftermath.
Students' task is to study.
Spare the unrelated matters.
Remove it immediately.
What are you doing here?
[It has nothing to do]
[with Ms. Fang.]
I should be
the person who takes
responsibility.
I moved the flower stand
outside.
But, if we step back,
the stand itself
has no issues
with its weight capacity.
If it fell,
it was
deliberate damage.
You can go check.
The cracks on top are all new.
Someone deliberately caused this?
Exactly.
Who?
I don't know.
You have one day
to find out the person.
If failed,
all of
your commendations
and extracurricular activities for
your class would be canceled.
You...
You didn't bring a plant?
I failed again.
Apprentice,
where's my breakfast?
Why do you
walk so quietly?
And
why do you keep calling me that?
You haven't taught me anything.
Just this?
Give it back, then.
It's all right.
A token from my apprentice,
how can I refuse?
I'll manage.
Be careful, it's mine.
What is this?
Narcissus,
isn't it obvious?
Narcissus?
It looks more like
sprouted garlic to me.
It's Narcissus,
just
growing in soil.
Jinghui,
we're asked to bring plants over.
Why did you bring garlic?
Saving it for lunch?
You know,
sprouted garlic
is spicy.
Brought the wrong one.
Well...
just give it to me for lunch.
Let's share.
I don't eat garlic.
That's like losing half the flavor.
Too spicy.
Didn't grandma say
this is potted Narcissus?