English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP01
Practicing the pipa for an hour is more
tiring than examining corpses all day.
Xiao Qin,
can you fetch me some candied fruits?
Yes.
Chief Shen.
What are you doing here?
This is the Shen residence.
I can be wherever
I want.
Yet you have really
taken yourself as the lady of the house,
giving orders late at night
for candied fruits and
playing that awful and disturbing tune.
I'm sorry.
I bought the candied fruits
myself from the West Street.
I'll get them myself next time.
I won't bother the servants here again.
As for the awful tune,
to make it less awful soon,
I can only practice all night
to get better.
So please bear with me.
Performing arts require natural talent.
Last-minute efforts will only
make you a laughingstock.
I suggest you give up on the idea
of pretending to be a songstress soon.
And what if I succeed?
You still won't solve the case.
Don't forget,
the killer targets a man and a woman.
Just you alone are not enough.
You'll need a man who's
so fallen for the singsong girls.
About that,
I do have someone in mind.
I'll have to trouble Chief Shen
to invite him over.
But... I...
Chief Clerk Wu,
I need you to
accompany Lady Shen
to the Kaiyang Festival today.
She specifically requested
you to be her beloved partner.
Chief Shen, it's a misunderstanding.
I was wronged.
If, if you don't believe me,
ask in the Ministry of Justice,
We're not beloved partners,
rather, we are like oil and water.
We can't sit at the same table,
and we go against one another.
-I... -No need to be nervous, Chief Clerk.
Today,
she only needs to pretend to be
your beautiful mistress.
Chief Shen,
but this is...
Why?
Chief Shen!
Don't drag me! Chief Shen!
Why me?
Because your mistress is renowned
among the noblewomen of the capital
for her incomparable beauty.
You...
Let, let go.
Chief Shen,
Lady Shen rarely dresses up.
She's quite attractive.
Instead of flattering me here,
go do something more useful.
Yes.
Follow me.
Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
At the Kaiyang Festival,
I'll escort Her Highness
for the street procession.
You must closely track the lady.
If you see anyone suspicious,
arrest him immediately.
If anything happens to her,
I'll hold you accountable.
Long live the Emperor!
Long live
Your Highness!
Bravo!
What a show!
I wonder
if anyone else would like to
take the stage next?
Everyone,
my beloved concubine
is willing to play a pipa piece
for all of you.
Bravo! Bravo!
Wu Taiming
has the audacity to bring his mistress
into the open.
How can an unwed singsong girl
be considered a concubine?
How must Lady Wu feel?
Long live Your Majesty!
Long live
Your Highness!
I respectfully greet Your Majesty
and Your Highness.
Your Highness and Your Majesty
have come here personally
for the procession and to pray.
We pray for divine blessings,
that bring our nation prosperity
good weather,
and peace.
Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
She's very good.
Look, it's the Splendid Phoenix!
The Splendid Phoenix.
-So beautiful! -What a divine bird!
Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
This is Heaven's will!
Heaven sends auspicious signs,
bringing blessings to Cang dynasty.
What is this strange
fragrance?
A thousand butterflies dance in the spring stars.
Hundred-branch night chamber's bell chime.
What a match!
Lady Shen!
Jing Lin.
Chief Shen,
Lady Shen and Wu Taiming are both missing.
Get on the horse.
Speak!
Who's the real killer behind the murders?
Murders?
What murders?
Where's Lady Shen?
Please spare my life.
Chief Shen, please stop!
This was a family scandal.
My brother-in-law was cheating.
I was just teaching him a lesson.
Is that a crime?
The bodies found in pairs
knew each other
and were often seen together.
However, there are two pairs
where the victims
held grudges.
Oh no.
I'm Shen Du.
Are you okay?
Du!
Du, do you still remember me?
Of course I remember you.
Yan Xing,
I won't forget you.
These aren't real.
Do I need to know you?
Don't even dream of becoming
the real Lady Shen.
Don't expect to survive here
if you're not the one
I chose to marry.
Where am I?
You don't need to know that.
Why did you kill all those people?
You don't need to know that, either.
Why do you
keep talking?
I don't think I will
be able to get out of here today.
So why don't you uncover yourself
and let me see your face?
Everyone knows that you are
remarkably smart.
If I were to reveal
my face to you,
you'll surely
return as a ghost
and expose me to your husband.
What would I do then?
You killed all those people.
Their resentment
has long turned into vengeful ghosts
that haunt you
day and night.
Can't you feel it?
They were nothing!
They deserved to die!
Even as ghosts,
they still wouldn't dare
to haunt me.
Otherwise,
I'll just kill them again!
Do I deserve to die as well?
Those people you are talking about
all had something in common,
and you think they deserved to die.
But do I really deserve to die
in your eyes?
Even if you ask all these questions,
you still have to die.
But,
I'll have to
wait for a while
first.
What are you waiting for?
I'm waiting
for the blood in your body to clot.
So when I take out your heart,
you won't bleed.
But I am the wife of Chief Shen.
If you kill me,
they'll find you,
and they won't let you off easily.
Even if I don't kill you,
when Shen Du catches me,
he still wouldn't let me go.
I'll die anyway.
Might as well
take Lady Shen
with me.
I can plead for you.
He'll leave your body intact.
We're very close to each other.
Everyone in Xiang’an knows that.
He'll listen to me.
Shut up!
You shameless slut!
He won't listen to you!
He's mine!
Mine! Mine!
Stop!
Let go of me!
Xing,
are you okay?
Xing.
Thank you for getting here in time.
It was lucky
you sprinkled bean powder on your clothes.
The hunting dog followed the scent here.
How are you feeling?
I... I'm okay.
But...
Did you catch the killer?
But
I had a dream.
Jing Lin,
take off her veil.
It's you.
Xing.
Take her to the Imperial Guard.
Yes.
Lat's go.
Xing,
you're awake.
Chuichui,
how long was I asleep?
Where is Lady Tang?
Did you interrogate her?
You only slept for an hour.
You just woke up and you're
asking these?
No wonder Shen Du asked me
to keep an eye on you.
So what happened?
Of course she won't admit anything.
But,
Her Highness went to the IG
to interrogate her herself.
Let's see if she'll give in then.
I'll go see now.
Don't.
The drug is still working.
I've been chasing her for a long time.
I know how to make her talk.
No way.
You almost died today.
They can make do without you.
Plus,
Shen Du asked me to watch you.
Are you my friend
or his friend?
Chuichui,
you know me.
Once I make a decision,
no one can stop me.
But right now,
you need to help me with something.
I truly didn't expect that
the one behind these dreadful crimes
would be the widow of
my loyal minister, Tang Chengyi.
Why did you do it?
I remember
you and this Lady Tang
were quite close.
Now that
she's the suspect of these murders,
Prince Ying,
do you know anything about it?
Your Majesty, please investigate thoroughly.
Although I associated with
Lady Tang,
I had no idea about
her killing people.
If I had known that
she was the killer,
I would've never got close to her.
Let me ask you,
why did you kill
so many innocent people?
They weren't innocent.
Cang Dynasty has its own laws.
You don't get to decide
if they were innocent or not.
I'm Yan Xing, a clerk in the Ministry of Justice.
I apology for my abruptness
and ask for Your Majesty's forgiveness.
I haven't managed my household well,
and have disturbed Your Majesty.
Please punish me as you see fit.
It's of no concern.
I have heard that Lady Shen is very
skilled in solving cases.
Now that Meng Ceran
refuses to confess,
do you have any insights on this?
Your Majesty,
all the men
Lady Tang had killed
were engaged,
yet they were drawn to the brothels
and singsong girls.
But the female victims
all shared similar appearances
and had the same hair style.
Moreover,
they were all good pipa players.
Shut up.
Who would believe
your nonsense?
Your Majesty,
all the bodies found
were treated with cinnabar
to slow down decay,
making
the coroner's estimated time of death
inaccurate.
Later, we inferred
the correct date of death
and found it was all
within the Kaiyang period estimated by
the Imperial Astrology Bureau for that year.
Lady Tang,
did you really do
all of this for just
a momentary satisfaction in your heart?
At first,
I thought your killings
were driven by similarities
in the victims' appearances.
But later, I realized
it was more about
a deep obsession
with their identities.
I suspect that
the kind of women you killed
were likely connected to
someone very close to you.
You shut up!
Were you through traumas?
Or
did you suffer from the relationship
with some man from the pleasure quarters
on the day of the Kaiyang festival?
Nonsense!
If one wishes to fabricate a crime,
reasons can always be found.
By the way,
recently,
you have caught a chill at night.
With the weather getting cooler,
you need to be more careful.
I'm much better already.
My Lady,
if you care for me more often,
then I won't catch a cold anymore.
But
you've just got frightened,
why not take some rest?
I'm just
worried about you.
Chief Shen,
do you think the IG is your home?
Lady Shen has even treated this place
as if it were her own bedroom.
I am very pleased to
see the deep bond between you two.
But, Lay Shen,
the case is more important now.
You need to focus on the case.
Yes, I understand.
The Delinquent Xu Xiangren wishes to meet.
I, the Delinquent Xu Xiangren,
greet Your Highness.
Xing.
I take my leave.
Actually,
the delinquents
have found another pair of bodies.
This is the portrait
I created to reconstruct
the face of the male victim.
Give me that.
Give me!
I was correct.
You are the real victim
in your heart, aren't you?
What do you know!
It's not my fault.
They failed me first.
It's them!
It's all their fault.
I was so good to him.
Why did he betray me?
Is the person you speak of
the one in the portrait—
your first husband?
Yes.
When I was young,
my sister was kidnapped.
When we met again,
she had become a singsong girl
playing pipa.
At that time,
I was already married.
But I never thought that
on the day of the Kaiyang Festival,
on the Kaiyang Festival, I found
her having an affair with my husband.
The two people I loved the most.
The two people I trusted the most.
They both betrayed me.
To maintain my dignity,
I gave her poisoned wine.
But I didn't expect that
my husband
would drink it instead.
No!
After my husband's dead,
my sister went missing as well.
I looked for her for so long.
But in the end,
I found her in a grave.
But they...
They
were still holding each other tightly!
No.
It's not true.
It's not true!
That despicable woman!
She was not my sister!
She's just...
She's just a singsong girl who
seduced my husband.
She deserved to die!
She could've been a good woman.
But she had to seduce
a married man!
She deserved to be torn to pieces!
She deserved to be flayed alive!
She deserved to be humiliated
and disgraced by the world!
That's why you killed
all those women who looked like
your sister?
Does it look good?
Yes.
They deserved to die.
And those men.
Why did they have to obsess with
those singsong girls?
In this world,
not everyone
has the right to choose their life!
Many of them were
born into the pleasure quarters.
They can only use their looks.
They have no other choice!
Moreover,
that's not a reason
for you to kill them!
At first,
I've also blamed myself.
If it weren't for me,
my sister wouldn't have died.
Neither would my husband.
If it weren't for
my impulsiveness,
I wouldn't have lost
both of my loved ones at the same time.
That's why you regretted it.
You made the bodies
embrace each other
to comfort yourself.
Lady Shen,
you are indeed very smart.
Straight to the point.
But do you think,
with only your intelligence
you can
keep a man's heart forever?
Do you think
he'll always protect you like this?
He says he loves you,
but he only loves himself!
He will lie to you!
He will lie to you
and leave you heartbroken
and devastated.
What's wrong with loving oneself?
Everyone should love themselves
before they love someone.
In a marriage,
no one should
simply demand,
or ask single-sided protection.
But the husband and the wife should
face the challenges together
and support each other.
That's how a family
should be like!
Your Highness,
now that the case is solved
and the killer has confessed,
it's your decision to make as to
what to do with Lady Tang.
Your Highness,
in my humble opinion,
the killer has turned into madness.
I urge Your Highness not to be
swayed by past sentiments
and to close the case swiftly.
Since she's the widow of a loyal minister,
keep her body intact.
Yes.
Like a moth to a flame,
her life is fleeting.
She is beyond reincarnation.
Her afterlife shall continue.
Jing Lin,
put out the fire!
Yes!
Isn't this exactly what Chen Huo'e,
who was executed five years ago,
said right before he died?
Get this madwoman out of here!
Yes.
Were you this meddlesome
since you were a child?
It was life and death,
how could it be meddlesome?
I know
you especially asked Chuichui to
look after me today.
But if I hadn't barged into the court,
how could Lady Tang's case
have been so easily
concluded?
Today, you...
did good.
You,
are not going to scold me?
Did you make up the
two newly found bodies?
I merely asked Xu Xiangren
to go get the portrait
of Lady Tang's first husband
to provoke her to tell the truth.
Now we know the truth.
It's just...
It's just, it feels like
we've missed something about this case.
What did we miss?
The hearts.
Lady Tang killed this many people
and has taken their hearts.
So where are these hearts?
Lady Tang,
I have something important for you.
Killing is easy.
But moving the bodies,
digging the graves,
reburying them
are not things a woman
can easily manage.
You must have help.
What is
all this effort for?
Like a moth to the flame.
She's turned into madness.
But she's the most important witness.
How come she turned mad?
I will never die.
I will become a moth
and live forever!
I'm flying.
You killed all those people.
Where are their hearts?
I'm flying.
-Meng Ceran. -I'm flying.
Please burn me.
Please.
I want to rise from the ashes.
I'm begging you, please.
Ask her no more.
She's a madwoman now.
Nothing a madwoman says
will be credible.
Burn me. Burn me!
She will be executed soon.
Burn me!
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about Lady Tang's case.
Her love turned to hatred,
then into obsession.
Yet she was torn between love and hate,
unable to let it go.
It's truly a pity.
To devote oneself entirely
in a love affair
is the act of a fool.
And the world is full of
foolish people acting wickedly.
What's there to pity about?
Yeah.
That sounds exactly what a smart
person like you would say.
Chief Shen,
I'm tired.
I'll rest a bit now.
Prince Xian has finished
the disaster relief work
and will arrive safely
in Xiang'an soon.
That's good.
No need
to hang around the pigeon coop anymore.
You got false information,
as the IG don't use carrier pigeons
for their secret messages.
I know.
Those pigeons are all soft feathered
and can't fly long-distance.
But I have to walk around here
from time to time.
You have your orders to follow,
and I have mine too.
I have to pretend anyway.
But I won't really do anything.
Don't worry.
So now can you believe that even
beasts won't harm their cubs, right?
Let alone it's the
mightiest beast...
Stop.
I don't want to hear that.
I won't hear what I shouldn't hear,
no need to invite trouble.
By the way,
I forgot to tell you about
a small thing.
The Ministry of Justice and the Delinquents
are hosting a celebration banquet
and have sent an invitation
to invite both of us.
-I know
you won't be going.
I'm just telling you.
Jinglin.
Yes, my lord.
Tell Zhong,
the blinds he made last time,
make another one.
Yes, Chief Shen.
Such a promising bloom.
What a waste.
Your Majesty.
Master.
Your Majesty’s contributions to
disaster relief are praised.
I've heard that Her Highness
plans to reward you greatly.
Did the journey back go well?
Master, don't worry.
I had the IG's thorough escort
in the journey.
I brought back
some local specialties this time.
Prepare one portion
for the master.
And prepare another
for my royal sister,
as
a gesture of
my regard to her.
Yes.
Your Majesty, your kindness
and strong sibling bond
truly move me.
However, recently
due to Lady Tang's case,
it's going to be tough for Prince Ying.
I've also heard about this
on the way.
My sister has always
been close to Lady Tang and
they both supported the poor,
but the current public opinion
is very unfavorable to them.
Yeah.
Regarding Lady Tang's case,
who would've thought
that Yan Xing would
made a great contribution.
She's just a concubine's daughter,
often quite unreliable.
But she proved to be
capable at a critical moment like this.
Prince Xian,
do you think this Yan Xing
is suitable?
If you think so, master,
then it must be right.
Perhaps,
we'll truly have to rely on her
to resolve the stalemate.
This flower needs fertilizer.
Your Majesty,
many of the ladies who
were invited to the flower banquet
said they were ill and won't come.
I got it.
Those who don't want to come
won't have to come in the future anymore.
They're all useless to me.