English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP05
Regarding today's incident,
thanks for your rescue.
I believe
you should be thanking someone else.
This writing does resemble mine a lot.
But still, it could not deceive you.
Not just me.
The Great Grandmother?
It sounds upright and unyielding.
But between the lines,
there are hints of a woman's touch.
Yan Xing was
earnestly endorsed by the prime minister.
Now, she intends to help you.
I find
the turn of events quite surprising.
Why did Her Highness...
You've found yourself a good wife.
She must
have taken that nursery rhyme
to heart.
The task you're assigned
is indeed a challenging one.
You must be cautious.
Absolutely.
It seems I misjudged Her Lady.
She has shown loyalty
since your arrest.
I could speak for myself
even if she didn't write the statement.
Saving me is merely a pretext.
She aims to use this opportunity
to overturn the case of Chen Baiyi,
and that is her true intention.
She had the guts to take advantage of you?
She actually has the audacity to use me!
What a cunning girl!
Never mind.
She's just trying
to seek justice for Chen Baiyi.
But how did she learn
my handwriting?
She
entered your study.
No wonder she could imitate it perfectly.
I didn't expect
her to have a talent for mimicking.
My Lord,
she tampered with your memo.
Should we...
Just keep her around.
What other tricks could she pull?
There's something
that needs immediate attention.
Your Highness, Your Highness!
This is not good!
He... he's coming...
Prince Xian, receive the decree.
I, Xiao Zhong, am receiving the decree.
By the mandate of heaven,
the emperor hereby decrees:
I hereby order the Prince Xian, Xiao Zhong
to proceed to Fengxiang to conduct an inspection.
Prince Xian, Xiao Zhong,
with both literary and martial prowess,
possessing the ability to govern,
with benevolence as his foundation,
endowed with righteousness and courage,
with both virtue and talent,
to benefit the populous.
A harsh drought is now plaguing Fengxiang.
Planning and coordination are imperative.
The regent holds the authority to govern.
The duty of inspections falls to you.
Supervision is entrusted to you.
This is to enhance our imperial prestige,
and to reassure the hearts of the people.
May imperial grace bless the people.
I, Xiao Zhong,
gratefully accept the decree.
When are we scheduled to depart?
Your Highness,
Her Highness has issued a decree.
This matter is of utmost importance.
There can be no delays whatsoever.
Your Highness' journey will be
fully escorted by the Imperial Guard.
The CO has made necessary arrangements.
Please rest easy and prepare to set off.
Very well.
While I'm away,
you must
take excellent care of these flowers.
Temperature fluctuations are significant.
Watering during the hour of the snake(9am) is ideal.
Especially my
Imperial Yellow Peony.
Yes, Your Highness.
Let's go.
Your Highness,
please.
I wonder if the statement worked.
My Lady!
My Lady,
I've received the news from the palace:
the commander has left the palace alive.
You can rest easy now.
Please get some rest.
Alright.
I'll wait a little longer.
My Lady.
My Lady,
here's the osmanthus lotus seed soup.
Please enjoy it while it's warm.
This maid seems unfamiliar.
Greetings, Lord Prime Minister.
Lady Yan Xing of the Yan Family,
you truly are exceptionally clever.
Shen Du was taken to the palace earlier,
and he has yet to return home.
You may leave empty-handed
if you're looking for updates on the case.
I am aware of Shen Du's whereabouts.
Today, I came to see you
to grasp the Yan Family's stance.
I don't quite understand.
Please enlighten me, My Lord.
Her Highness was enraged upon hearing
the rhyme that has been circulating.
She immediately issued a decree
ordering Prince Xian to proceed to
Fengxiang to oversee disaster relief.
When he departed, he wasn't
even permitted to bring attendants.
Moreover,
the route has been kept confidential.
My Lord, are you implying
that Her Highness suspects Prince Xian
is behind the nursery rhyme incident,
and intends to take action against him?
However,
blood is thicker than water.
It's a long and risky journey.
If something were to happen,
it would be too late to act.
Let me ask you,
the Great Grandma wields absolute power,
disregarding the rightful ruler of Cang.
What's the surname of the late Emperor?
Does the Yan Family
still have clarity on this?
I'm fully committed to criminal cases.
As for political matters,
a mere woman truly lacks understanding.
It's even more challenging to be involved.
What a naive girl!
You wish to enter the court,
while also being embroiled in the case,
and still hope to remain unscathed.
Not only you, Yan Xing,
but your entire family is
deeply entangled in all this.
Her Highness values the empire above all.
Perhaps my husband is mistaken.
A serial case,
and a nursery rhyme,
could they truly
spark such an uproar?
The Buddha Absorbs Sins.
This nursery rhyme is indeed malicious,
accusing Her Highness of illegitimacy.
If it were to affect anyone,
it'd not be limited to just Prince Xian.
What exactly do you want me to do?
According to my sources,
Shen Family employs carrier pigeons
for sending orders and relaying messages.
During Prince Xian's journey,
they will certainly
use pigeons to relay messages.
You need to act fast
to uncover Prince Xian's route.
At that point,
whether Shen Du is
plotting to assassinate him
or genuinely trying to protect him,
we will be prepared in advance.
Carrier pigeons?
Why do you
act so secretively even at home
as if you're a thief?
My Lord,
I have been eagerly
awaiting your return.
When did you get home?
Did Her Highness give you a hard time?
You made me worry all night.
Yan Xing,
why put on such a facade?
Do you believe that by acting like this
you would win my favor?
Not falling for this trick, huh?
Never mind.
Are you content now?
As a clerk in the Ministry of Justice,
you must be well aware of the
consequences of forging memos.
Moreover, your careless words have
stirred quite a commotion in the court.
At that moment,
I was simply desperate to save my husband.
I hadn't written any memos before.
How could I know what should be written
and what shouldn't?
Saving me?
Or rather using me?
The hour grows late.
Lord Commander,
let's head inside and get some rest.
Humble-born scholar Chen Baiyi,
self-immolated in Ming Hall.
His years of hard works
have all been stolen.
There has been no sign of divine favor.
When will this corrupted social ladder end?
Everyone,
why do we labor over our studies,
only to serve as mere
companions to the sons of the gentry?
We are reduced to their shadows.
We refuse to accept this!
We will no longer tolerate it!
Look at you all, so pathetic.
Without the gentry,
you wouldn't even be worthy
to step foot in the Imperial Academy.
Craving success?
For your information,
you were born to be lowly.
What did you say?
You plagiarizing nobodies.
Stop!
Stop, all of you!
Stop, now!
Hey!
This is outrageous!
Outrageous!
Repetitive and monotonous,
utterly meaningless.
Regarding the Ming Hall self-immolation,
Imperial Guard,
any updates?
Your Highness,
Imperial Guard
has further verified and confirmed
that it is indeed as previously stated.
The scholar Chen Baiyi had his writings
stolen by the eldest son of the Jins.
When he confronted him, he was driven out,
and publicly humiliated and beaten.
He was filled with deep resentment.
With no way to appeal to the officials.
Self-immolation was his chosen statement.
The Imperial Academy is still in chaos.
The unrest has not yet settled.
News has arrived from Jiangnan.
Look!
Take a look!
Though papers traverse the earthly path,
they seldom tread the way of justice;
passing the roll may pass the test,
yet hardly heralds fairness to the world.
Is this how the scholars
perceive the social ladder
of our Great Cang Dynasty?
Your Highness, please quell your wrath.
Mother, selecting talents
is a matter of national interest.
The gentry should not use this
to uphold their status,
causing such turmoil.
I believe that
whether from humble backgrounds
or from the gentry,
they should be competing together.
Weigh their talents, select the competent.
This should be the way forward.
I believe this is not acceptable.
Nepotism in office is a dynastic rule.
How can it be changed so easily?
Your Highness, perhaps you spend your days
reciting poetry with
those humble students, and have
momentarily lost sight of reality.
Those of humble origins
are equally subjects of our empire.
I merely speak on their behalf.
Why are you reacting with such intensity?
Lord Zhang, were you
aware of the plagiarism scandal
involving the Jins
from long ago?
Please, Your Highness,
I am solely
concerned with the welfare of the empire.
We can't focus solely on the writings.
Family scholarly heritage is also crucial.
Lord Zhang, this viewpoint is misguiding.
Clinging to the privileges of the gentry
has led to
widespread corruption and malpractice.
Let the worthy hold their due places.
Your Highness,
the victims of the Ximing Temple cases
were all sons of the gentry.
It's possible
that some humble student was misled
into committing those acts.
Misled?
It's better to guide than to suppress.
Ultimately, suppression
won't resolve the issue.
Such a simple truth.
How could you not grasp it, Lord Zhang?
Could it be that
you wish for Her Highness to bear
the blame for the injustices
against the humble families of the realm?
My loyalty to Her Highness
is as clear as day.
Recruiting officials of humble origins
is absolutely unacceptable.
Your Highness!
Alright, Lord Zhang,
you may get up.
You two are in disagreement, but it's
all for the greater good of the empire.
Lord Shen,
regarding the self-immolation case,
haven't you already solved it?
What is your take on this?
Among the scholars of humble origins,
there are indeed talented individuals
who genuinely deserve an opportunity.
I believe
we could implement a method for
fair assessment to identify the talented.
Then they can offer themselves for your review.
I suggest starting with
the Imperial Academy as a pilot program,
choosing talents of humble origins.
Your Highness' wisdom shines!
Oh, it's you
Miss, sit here, please.
Sit.
Thanks to you,
my poor grandson
could finally rest in peace.
Lord Commander,
what should we do with these remains?
Your grandson's articles have
received high praise from the scholars.
I brought a copy for you.
Unfortunately,
I cannot read.
Let me read it for you.
The Song of the Western Continent.
Reflecting on the plum blossoms.
Sending plucked plums across the river.
The apricot blossoms bloom red...
Her Lady is
truly eager to take on responsibilities.
However, the fairness and justice
she seeks are not easily achieved.
Aren't you a big surprise?
You are quite the strategist.
What's the matter?
Her Highness' issued an edict to establish
the Imperial Academy as a pilot program
to select humble talents for enrollment.
Is that true?
I mean
Xing won't take credit for this.
It all hinged on your mediation.
This time,
you will surely earn a reputation
for keen insight
among the humble students.
How wonderful!
Xing is genuinely happy for you.
Do I care about those?
If you plan to pull any stuns again,
make sure to inform me in advance.
Otherwise, you'll be punished severely.
Yeah,
you're the White Death after all.
Reputations surely means nothing to you.
At this late hour,
what trouble are you going to stir up?
I'm just going to stretch a little.
I'll go for a jog.
If I don't run, I won't get tired.
Then how could I possibly fall asleep
next to the White Death?
My Lady.
Does she go for a jog every night?
She believes it helps her sleep.
It's indeed too bright in here.
We haven't changed the lighting at all.
It's still the same as it was.
Do you all find it too bright?
We've already grown accustomed to it.
I recall
there's a type of fabric from Xichen
that can effectively block out light.
Go and make a curtain from it.
Yes, My Lord.
Also,
don't light it up
from that side anymore.
Let's conserve the oil.
My Lord.
Sir!
You've already barged in.
Come on in.
Get down...
The identities of the twelve victims from
Ximing Temple have all been confirmed.
These paired corpses
were mostly familiar with each other,
often seen together.
However, only two pairs
have not been found
to have any connections.
Isn't it said
that the IG is very efficient?
It's been so long.
Why haven't you uncovered?
The male corpses are all gentry.
Based on their appearances
and clothing,
they can be identified quite easily.
But the female ones
have had their features marred.
They don't have household registration,
so it took some time to identify them.
Additionally,
the timeline of their disappearance
does not align with
the time of death.
A discrepancy?
Is this also true for the male victims?
Yes, it is.
It ranges from two to three months,
up to one to two years.
After the murderer abducted the victims,
they were being held for so long.
That certainly would increase the risk.
As for the female victims, do they
match the list of missing musicians
provided by the inspectors?
Exactly.
They are indeed the missing musicians
from various music halls.
So you're saying they were all musicians?
Yes.
That doesn't seem right.
What's not right?
The accessories found
on those female corpses
seem a bit off.
Please take a look at this.
It's truly exquisite.
The quality is clearly outstanding.
Indeed.
I found it odd that day.
These gold ornaments,
compared to other accessories,
seem excessively exquisite.
They aren't like ordinary goldsmith work.
These items
shouldn't be easily accessible
to ordinary musicians.
I'm not very knowledgeable about these,
but Chui mentioned
that renowned craftsmen
often leave their marks
on their creations.
This piece is from the Bijiang Workshop.
It was once part of the royal forge,
crafting jewelry for the royal family.
It has surpassed many
renowned shops in 10 years,
and risen to the top.
Thank you for coming!
Welcome to our humble shop.
What can I do for you?
Hairpins.
Bring out your
finest collection.
Certainly.
Which one do you favor the most?
This one.
You have a discerning eye!
How much is this?
Fifty taels.
I thought so.
Ordinary musicians can't afford this.
Darling,
I'd like to get the best one.
Once the owner shows up, could you
get him to show us his hidden treasure?
The Zisun tea is a royal tribute.
Especially the Yangxian type
is considered a top-tier delicacy.
Previously, I was fortunate enough
to receive some as a reward.
I've kept it at home, reluctant to drink.
Your establishment is quite generous.
This is our owner's cherished treasure.
We are pleased to offer it to
our most distinguished guests.
Has the manager not here yet?
Greetings, Mr and
Mrs Shen.
Your presences honor our humble shop.
What can I assist you with?
If I recognize you correctly,
you are Ms. Yang,
the chamberlain to Princess Ying.
You truly have a keen eye.
You still remember a lowly servant like me.
I'm truly flattered.
Do you recognize
these gold ornaments?
Some of them
indeed come from the Bijiang Workshop.
Excellent.
I want the list of people who purchased
these items.
Sir,
this is quite a challenge for me.
Our shop has been open for years,
with countless customers coming and going.
The amount of jewelry we have sold
over the years is immeasurable.
How could I remember every transaction?
A hairpin that costs fifty taels is
so pricey that even if a commoner
sold everything he owns,
he wouldn't be able to afford even one.
I can't provide the list.
Then you might as well just tell me
who can provide it.
Um...
This is official IG business.
If you dare to hide anything,
just face
the consequences.
Please wait, sir.
I'll go fetch it right away.
This one looks good.
Let's take this one.
The design is simple.
It suits you perfectly.
Are you giving this to me as a gift?
You're not expecting me to
pay for it, are you?
The accessories worn by the female victims
are indeed quite valuable.
The list didn't show
any musicians.
But there are a few familiar names.
They are male victims.
That's correct.
In their quest to amuse fair maidens,
they squandered their fortune with ease.
This seems like a messy account.
Many transactions are only noted as
banquet gifts.
No quantities or specific recipients.
These shops often holds banquets,
inviting the noble ladies of the city.
They must have been given as gifts.
Such a grand gesture!
That Ms. Yang
is indeed impressive.
Definitely someone else
is behind all this.
Ms. Yang
is a trusted confidant of Princess Ying.
Her status are
beyond those of ordinary palace maids.
Yet earlier, in your presence,
she referred to herself as a mere servant,
and willingly handed over
this list.
She seems
to be quite concerned about
offending someone of your stature.
Mask her strength to deceive the enemy.
She wanna prevent you from
continuing your investigation.
It is highly likely that
Princess Ying is behind it.
Maybe they intend to use banquets
to win over various officials
and their ladies,
then through their lovers to gain
insight into the movements
of each household?
No wonder Lord Zhang
is so cautious around her.
Are you familiar with Princess Ying?
She's highly
favored.
She appears to indulge in pleasure daily,
but in reality, she is quite astute.
Don't worry.
She will likely
seek you out soon.
What do you mean?
My Lord.
Enter.
Princess Ying...
Princess Ying invited
Her Lady to the banquet.
Isn't that Lord Commander's wife?
No one is doing her hair or something?
I just noticed
Lady Wu looks unwell.
I heard that her husband
is keeping a musician as mistress.
She was so foolish back then,
insisting on marrying that minor
official from the Ministry of Justice.
Men...
whether they have power or not,
rich or poor,
they're all the same.
Exactly.
I also heard that
Lady Tang
was fond of a poor commoner,
and they were quite close.
In the end,
that man eloped with a musician.
I've never heard of this.
Do you know why Lady Tang
has a good relationship with
Princess Ying?
Why is that?
Because
they are both into poor boys.
Isn't that right?
Exactly.
Look.
Apologies!
It's alright.
I was the one being careless.
Gratitude!
Look.
How gracious
Mrs Shen is!
Isn't she a concubine's daughter?
Look at her now,
pretending to be a refined young lady.
Mrs Shen, it's your first time
attending such a banquet.
You might not be accustomed to it.
Actually, it's not usually like this.
It's just that Lady Liu's
husband was interrogated in IG
just a few months ago.
It's fine.
This is the way of things, right?
When the husband offends someone,
it's the wife who suffers the consequences.
So,
just forget it.
They're just
venting their frustrations.
Your dress
is all wet.
Please
come with me
to get changed.
Let's go.
This place is called the Medicinal Pool.
Soaking in here
can promote health and heal injuries.
You're all wet and you might catch a cold.
You should go inside.
Take some time to enjoy yourself.
This is far too precious.
I really...
I'm currently fine-tuning
the new formula for the medicinal spring.
You could
help me assess
the effectiveness of this new formula.
You even know how to prepare medicine?
I only have a basic understanding.
Right.
This is the scent of Bainao incense.
She was the one peeking
at the gate of Ximing Temple that day.
This is a fire moth.
I've heard a legend about it.
Someone saw a fire moth
and followed it up the mountain.
Afterward,
he actually gained immortality.
Lady Tang,
with your temperament and status,
do you also yearn for eternal life?
Life is just a few short decades.
If
there are things you want to achieve,
don't hesitate at all.
Once youth has passed,
it would be
too late to
pursue your dreams.
You're absolutely right.
Come on.
You are quite astute,
and share a deep bond with Lord Shen.
Regarding the serial murders in the city,
it's truly comforting to
have both of you on the case.
You know, the Liangs
have certainly endured many trials.
My interactions with Lady Liang
have been frequent.
It's truly a pity for such a beauty.
Her husband doesn't even spare her a glance.
And now,
she has lost her son.
She's at odds with her husband?
Apologies for my loose tongue.
It's their privacy,
and it shouldn't be shared.
Please,
don't take it to heart.
Please convey to Lady Liang
that the murderer will be caught soon.
No matter how deeply they hide.
Mrs Shen,
Princess Ying is calling
you to discuss matters after your bath.
Got it.
I've been waiting for four hours.
Why isn't she here yet?
Greetings.
The flowers are blooming beautifully.
I completely forgot about you.
Take it easy.
I called you here today just for a
casual chat, with no ulterior motives.
Well,
investigation is a sure thing.
But certain matters
should be left untouched.
You're a perceptive girl.
Is my intention clear to you?
Choose your battles wisely.
Has your husband not taught you this?
Your Highness.
Mr Shen has arrived
for his wife.
It's only been half a day.
He seems
to be quite concerned about you.
It appears the rumors circulating
are not without truth.
The bond between you two
is truly enviable.
Let him in.
Your Highness.
The flower banquet has concluded.
Yet my wife hasn't returned home.
She must have lost her way in the palace.
I was worried,
so I came to find her.
After all, there are
many household chores
that require her attention.
You're here personally to find her.
If I kept holding onto her,
that would be quite inconsiderate of me.
However, there's one thing
I have to say.
Solving the case is of utmost importance.
Thank you for the reminder.
Are you injured?
I'm bleeding, really?
Did Princess Ying force you
to consume anything?
Have you been poisoned?
Well, you've come a long way to get me.
Once we're in the carriage,
no one will see us.
Er...
Did you foresee that my trip to the palace
would be fraught with danger?
For someone who just learned to walk,
if she never fell,
how would she understand the pain?
Moreover, you've uncovered
a trump card of the princess.
That's why she gave you a good shake.
It was us who revealed her secrets,
yet I'm the only one being targeted.
However,
your rescue...
No need for thanks.
You wrote a memo to save me before,
so consider this a mutual exchange.
During your earlier investigation,
did you discover the discord between
the main couple of the Liangs?
What's the point of investigating
their private matters?
The primary wife has indeed been
fixated on the concubine's son.
She cries and causes scenes daily.
Fortunately, Liang Jiren
is somewhat reasonable, and hasn't
made things difficult for his concubine.
Liang Chenzhong is the only son.
The primary wife has been effectively
deprived of her descendants by the killer.
Many people harbor hatred for him.
Even if he hadn't been disemboweled,
he wouldn't have lived long.
The one who poisoned him
also had murderous intent.
It's just that he was
simply not as fast as the serial killer.