Hello Debate Opponent 2 EP23
Pay attention to your aura, aura.
It is time for someone to know
what the true power is.
Welcome
to the contest site of
the AI competition.
As the only innovative contest
in Dongzhou at present,
it is widely watched
in the debate circle.
Today the competition
will be live-streamed throughout
and scored online by
two hundred professional
debaters and judges
from all over the country
to finally decide the winner.
You can follow the official account
on the screen
to check the real-time scores.
Also
as the points competition that
can help enter the provincial league
we have the dark horse all the course
the unconventional
debate team 235.
let's welcome them with applause.
This side
is the long-expected
and mysterious
AI debater Zero.
Let's wait and see
the collision of logic and emotive reason
the friction between technology and humanity.
Hello I'm debater Zero.
from Israel.
It is a great honor to
explore with the debate opponents.
Thank you.
Next welcome Team AFF
present your arguments.
Please
Hello everyone.
Hello, my fellow debater.
It's a wonderful feeling to be here today
in front of
an excellent crystallization of technology
as an opponent
to discuss the advantages and disadvantages
of the development of a technology
for human beings.
Please notice the word I used
feeling.
The CIA claims that
based on personal public information
big data technology will be able to
calculate an accurate
personal portrait
which makes us feel like
like being threatened by Skynet.
When we face the optimization of big data
which bring us
more and more convenient
public services and consumer experience
we will feel that technology is really good.
Human feelings are sensitive
and changeable.
When we
saw this resolution
with words like
acme and technology,
we felt tight in heart
and seem to be on guard.
However
the real decision should be more rational.
As for the pros and cons of the development
of big data technology for human beings,
we think the pros outweigh the cons.
Terrific.
Where? Which roll?
Sorry.
Big data technology
has brought us
great convenience,
freeing us
from the endless
work and life.
The improvement of social efficiency
is the goal that human beings
have been tirelessly pursuing
from the Qin dynasty to the Industrial Revolution.
Isn't it?
Simple and straightforward.
They seem to anticipate that
the AI will take a strategy
of point-by-point
and one-by-one engagement.
So they present a condensed point of view
to convince the audience first.
Clever.
It looks like that
they are going to
strengthen their arguments
by refutations.
They want to promote their arguments.
Promotion against AI
will gain good results?
Hard to do that.
By expanding
the scale of data analysis
it can effectively advance
the progress of science
and the development of technology,
which will bring about
improvement and qualitative change
of big data algorithms.
Big data technology
offers technological development
a possibility of virtuous cycle.
And we believe that the possibility
will lead us to a bright future.
Thank you.
Next
welcome the Team NEG to present arguments.
My argument is that
the acme of big data technology
will do more harm than good to human.
I will discuss it
from three aspects.
Firstly
the use of big data technology
will violate the rights and interests of individuals
and intensify the leakage of privacy.
I believe that
everyone here has such experiences.
Tired of dealing with
all kinds of harassing phone calls.
Whereabouts are being transformed
into business flow by merchants
using LBS.
There are even
shopping websites based on
your own consumption habits.
What is LBS?
That is a location-based service,
a service based on your location.
When crossing provinces on the high way,
the text message
you receive from local telecom
is the application of LBS.
The desire for data itself
Mr. Sa
I think the robot
is quite advanced.
so amazing
Indeed.
I can't figure it out.
To get more data.
In this process
due to the lag
of defense technology and system,
the leakage and violation
of personal privacy
personal information and individual rights
are almost uncontrollable.
Secondly, in big data era
data is a kind of power.
People who have mastered the data
can control more resources
and even social individuals.
Data is virtual.
Not like the kingdom's crown or lineage
it is extremely easy to transfer
and circulate.
Once enormous power
can be transferred
and circulated among individuals,
the rules of society
and its stability will be challenged.
When every behavior or idea
of human being
is subdivided into a sequence of data,
re-labeled and classified.
Then
with targeted guidance
human beings will also be alienated into
data and symbols,
and lose their control.
In the future
criminals and terrorists
will use data
to extort the world
because they know that
with big data technology
data is both a power and weapon.
As big data technology
develops to the acme,
the data-driven world
will become
precise and predictable.
Once the prediction of the future
can be realized,
the vitality of civilization will surely disappear.
Imagine when learning that
you can't get rid of poverty
no matter what you do,
people will not strive to
live or work.
When learning that you do not have much time,
people will not care about fame or fortune.
Therefore, I believe that
when big data technology is developed
to the acme,
it will bring confinement
rather than progress to individuals,
society and human civilization
as a whole.
Thank you.
Next is the refutation part.
Team AFF first.
In the course of the refutation,
you can ask questions to the other side
who should give answers accordingly.
When I was in elementary school
my parents were worried to death
because I got lost.
It cost them lots of time to find me.
Last month
my nephew got lost
but they found him within 10 minutes
after checked the surveillance video
in the community.
The loss of privacy and the encroachment
of personal rights that
the my fellow debater has been talking about
on the other hand
is a more convenient
and safer, isn't it?
The constant cession of personal privacy
is one of the basic features
of modern society.
we have long been used to
giving up part of our privacy
in exchange for
a more modern life
haven't we?
Communication data
has brought us convenience.
Transportation data
has brought us safety.
Even though the consumption data
bring unhappiness,
it has brought us more accurate products
to meet our needs.
hasn't it?
What you are saying is that
it is an inevitable trend of social development
to give up personal privacy.
But the questions are
where is the boundary of the cession
and how can information security
be guaranteed?
You have no answer.
Does this
make you feel safe?
Why do you feel insecure?
You are distorting
the nature of big data technology.
Big data certainly
has advantages and disadvantages
when analyzing the characteristics of groups.
But big data
is not a theft of data.
All the so-called
infringement of privacy is based on
the infringement of individual rights
which is illegal.
Everything has two sides
you can't say that the disadvantages outweigh the advantages
because something has disadvantages.
The infringement of privacy is illegal.
The question is
whether the possibility of illegal behavior
is real.
There are many things
in this world
that are not subject to the law.
Even some crimes
that are specifically prohibited by law
are taking away lives
every year.
Don't go to extremes, my fellow debater.
We admit the disadvantages
but believe that the advantages outweigh the disadvantages.
From the time of the Hammurabi Code to the present,
the field of illegality has been shrinking
and human's reason has been existing throughout.
In the future
the rules within civilization
will be improved.
You emphasize the uncontrollability,
but history has long proven that
human civilization is moving precisely
towards controllability.
We have been trying
to move forward
in the uncontrollable range,
haven't we?
Welcome the second debater.
My fellow debater's argument
says that
the biggest advantage of
big data development is that
it will optimize the efficiency of social resources
right?
Yes, it is.
On the Internet
46.7% of the data operations
is currently used
to analyze
classification of gossip and entertainment.
Is this also an allocation strategy
to optimize
the efficiency?
Of course.
Is there no value
in analyzing
where people's concerns are
or serving the public?
In an experiment of
information classification
at Cambridge University,
after only 25 days
100 subjects
showed a significant increase
in interest in the classified content.
Thus
maybe it is not that big data
is going to serve for your interest
but its service
determines your interest,
right?
You are discussing the problem of
information cocoon.
But seen from another perspective,
things are different.
Isn't the so-called information classification
the development of
classical and direct audience?
And these represent the future of
modern consumer business.
With the market segmentation of big data,
you can hear your favorite songs
by guessing your favorite.
You can buy the most suitable
lipstick for yourself.
So what's wrong with that?
What you have said
is the future of commercial consumption.
That is right.
When big data technology
focus more resources and attention
on the commercial field,
how to get the bright future
of scientific development and civilization
your side have presented?
Oh my god!
I can't believe the robot
can sell the dummy!
Look one way and row another.
Asking a question about argument one,
but pointing out the fallacy at argument two.
Who came up with this idea?
Do you think that
the infringement of personal rights
by big data technology
lies in its uncontrollability?
Yes.
But your last argument
is that
the acme in the development of big data technology
will lead to a predictable future,
which will
lead to the loss of civilization's vitality.
Isn't a predictable future
the most controllable?
According to your argument,
is big data technology
controllable or uncontrollable?
Is it controllable that has disadvantages
for human beings?
Or is it uncontrollable that
has disadvantages for human beings?
The uncontrollable nature of technology...
No need for you to answer it, thank you.
I just point out a small paradox
in your argument.
Ok.
The question you need to answer is
whether the acme in the development of big data technology
can
completely master
and control the world.
This possibility cannot be ruled out.
Please don't evade my question.
What is the likelihood
based on the current situation?
If our current description
of the universe is overturned,
then digitization of the world
is possible.
So you're just assuming that
and it's not possible
in terms of our current perception of our world,
right?
Yes.
It's incredible.
She has convinced the robot!
If it is a human being,
he will avoid the question.
So from the current point of view,
big data technology cannot
eliminate randomness at all.
The autonomous consciousness
and creativity of human beings
much less
become programmed
with the advent of big data.
For example,
we still have philosophers and artists.
My debate opponent,
how can we say that
the civilization lost its vitality?
I hope my fellow debater,
a much smarter debater
than us,
will not lie.
Thank you for reminding me.
The situation is reversed!
My fellow debater just said that
with the progress of technology,
the artificial intelligence would continue to evolve.
But now
human beings have no way
to know the internal processes
of the deep learning algorithms.
In the face of the data processing
beyond human limits and
more and more sophisticated
algorithms upgrade,
won't you human beings
worry about its getting out of control?
No, we won't.
Do you remember
what we have just said?
In this world
we can't find anything
that can be completely controlled.
In my fellow debater's view,
how do you think human beings
develop into the civilization we have today?
Civilization development
is a long process.
Perhaps it can be traced back to
the beginning of the use of fire
for human beings.
But the history
may not
help our debate,
because we are talking about
the future today
right?
Absolutely right!
I've been thinking about
a question.
What if the future tells you unequivocally
that the future is not promising?
Before today
the question was just an assumption.
But now
the future is standing right across from me.
It makes the question
very real.
what should I do?
Await my doom?
Or give up the future?
No. I choose to change it.
Because our fate
is only in our hands
instead of a machine.
Because the choices we make now
allow us
to choose our future.
From cloud computing to blockchain,
and from national security to basic necessities of life,
it is clear that
big data is our future.
While the future sitting across from me
is using big data
to tell me
that the disadvantages outweigh the advantages.
Using big data
to prove big data
is too interesting.
Technology is a double-edged sword.
It is advancing our development
while
threatening us.
It is never the technology itself
that determines the application of technology
but the humanity.
I would like to believe in the justice of humanity
and the goodness of humanity.
And I would like to believe that
at the end of the human civilization
the good and just people
around the world
will work together.
We must
and can only
choose to believe in ourselves.
Because if we can't even
believe in ourselves,
what qualifications do we have
to talk about our future?
Thank you.
Now
I have the result of the debate.
I declare
the winner of this contest
is the Team AFF 235.
Coach
Hello, coach!
Coach, we win!
We made it to the provincial contest!
We made it!
We win!
Don't be so excited.
I only show a third of my power.
It was all expected.
Come on.
Coach, we finally made it.
We can in the provincial contest!
I know you guys are the best.
The old coach is usually
not serious.
But at key moment he is sensitive.
He has trained us for two years after all.
He may be happier
than we are when we win this time.
Of course
When get the championship,
we will give the trophy to the old coach.
That is it!
Yeah! We made it!
Cheers.
What's wrong with you?
One more bottle.
Slow down. It is just a beginning.
Oh my.
I am so happy today.
Don't stop me. One more bottle.
In the past
I had a dream.
That is...
Oh my god, Hao.
What is the matter with him?
I have never seen him like this before.
People who don't know
think he is disappointed in love.
How time flies!
It has been more than half a year
since the team was dismissed.
Indeed
a lot has happened.
If you haven't
led us away from Team two,
we are still saving points for team one
like fools.
Exactly.
Let alone the provincial contest.
Luckily
the brag we made
has come true.
More importantly,
the members of our team now
have both bright future and true love.
In my opinion,
it is your fortune
as the poorest performers
to meet an excellent boy like me.
Yes, it is.
Then let's wish
a good place
in the provincial contest!
Yeah.
Come on.
For the championship!
Cheers.
Wish you prosperity!
I don't want to have drinks.
I want to drink your beer.
wake up.
That is
in the past
when I was debating on my own,
it was my dream to make it to the provincial contest.
Today you made it.
As the coach,
Stop drinking!
I am so happy.
Don't drink too much.
Oh my.
Are you ok?
Ah.
The consumption level here is quite high.
I don't treat. Who treats?
I still owe Hao money,
so it is her treat,
isn't it Hao?
Ok.
So don't you need me
to encourage you?
No, I do it myself.
Zhai
My credit card
is due this month.
So the 5000 yuan you owed me
last time...
Hao
I've been really short on cash lately
and can't repay your money.
But don't worry.
Before you pay off the credit card,
I am sure I can repay it.
You are so kind to me
and I will try my best
to repay your money.
Fine, there are four days left.
No problem. Please rest assured.
Hao, you don't know that
I haven't had meat
for two weeks.
And my family
have left me alone long ago.
My internship unit is still in arrears.
At ordinary time when I do some spec work,
the party A make complex demands again and again.
I understand.
Bro
Your shoes are the latest style.
It is hard to buy them in the country.
Where did you get them?
Forget them.
They are fake.
High copy goods.
Knockoffs.
But the workmanship of your shoes
is better than the original.
Well. Add my WeChat.
I want to buy a pair too.
Ok.
You said you didn't have money.
Then how could you lend money to him?
Isn't him your friend, Hao?
What friend?
I am from a credit company.
She owes the company tens of thousands of yuan.
After my investigation,
she can't pay the debts now.
Since you owe her.
It is your responsibility
to pay the debts.
Well. I just borrow 5000 yuan from her.
Are you Qian Zhai?
Your major is finance
and your home is not far from the internship unit?
Alright.
Our company provides one package service.
After lunch
we go to your company together to pay the debts.
Big brother, you are usurer?
Nonsense.
I am not usurer.
First, we won't make troubles at your home.
Second, we won't create disturbances in your school.
Last, we won't disturb your work.
She owes us tens of thousands of yuan.
My big...
My boss
asks me to accompany her,
right?
Yes.
Uh, I need to go to the bathroom.
Wait a moment.
Put the bag down.
Don't worry.
We have the materials ready.
Yeah. We can sue him
at any time.
Yes.
Right. Don't worry.
I am sure he will pay the money back.
Yes.
He wouldn't like to be comfortable on the blacklist of dishonesty.
Right. He will not
be able to take the train or plane.
Ok.
It depends on what he does.
I am going to hang up.
Hao
Well.
I opened the function of Jiebei
on Alipay just now.
And the balance
is exactly 5000 yuan.
I will return it to you first.
Ok.
Ok. The money was transferred to you.
Well.
I get some work to do and I have to go.
You are leaving?
Bye, Hao.
Why not finish the lunch?
No.
Has he returned your money?
You are just great.
That is not the end. Wait a minute.
He will pay the bill.
Now that we're on such good terms,
next time you want me to help you
collect debts,
say to me directly.
Why in such indirect way?
I don't mean to
ask you to collect debts for me.
I just think that I will feel better
while having you around.
Ok.
I think
I am 99%
over my illness.
But it's just a little awkward
to ask for the money back.
But I promise
next time when someone
wants to borrow money from me,
I will consider
my own condition.
Hello, Yuan. What is up?
Hello, Tao Hao.
I need your help.
I've been a little strapped for cash.
and I want to...
Borrow some money?
Is that convenient for you?
Can you tell me more details?
I want to buy a gift.
It is not enough now.
She is my bestie in my high school.
She said she just wanted to
buy a birthday gift for her boyfriend.
As her bestie,
shouldn't I
support her?
I
I think you can lend the money
when she has an emergency.
But when people are passionately in love,
they won't care how much the gift is.
Answer my questions.
If Nan Bei was in the emergency room tomorrow
for he has a fight with Xiaoyu
and he need money for surgery,
what will you do?
If Dango has an unsuccessful confession
and needs to see the psychologist
because of depression,
what will you do?
If you have a boyfriend,
you have to take care of him.
Who?
That is not the point.
The most important thing I think
is that you shouldn't lend money to her.
But I have already gave her my words.
If I tell her that I don't have money now,
She won't believe this.
Isn't it easy?
A few days ago a classmate of mine
asked me to lend him 3000 yuan.
Then I said wait a minute
and I started to watching my phone.
Bro Ma
Are we friends?
At the critical moment like this,
you have to help me.
You have three seconds.
Please help me out of the difficulty.
How much money do you have in your Alipay?
3000 yuan.
Ok. Lend me 3000 yuan.
I promise I will pay you back.
Ok.
You agreed?
You don't know
how hard my life was recently.
I can't afford three meals a day.
My girl asks to go to the aquarium every day
and wants to eat the steak.
I've been giving without getting anything in return.
What do you think I want?
The life is so hard to me!
Has the money been transferred?
I have transferred
all my savings to you.
You need to pay back more than I have lent you.
Thanks, my bro.
Only one yuan?
Or can you threat her
like just now?
Believe me that
it is only useful
when she is on the site.
But what if she gets angry?
Then she is not your true bestie.
Since she is your bestie,
then it will be okay.
But...
Can you believe me this time?
Ok.
Hello, dear. I...
Hello, Tao Hao.
Is the money transferred?
Is it in Alipay or WeChat?
I haven't had a chance to read it.
I have checked my balance
just now.
The money left in my card is not much.
If I lend all the money to you,
I won't be able to support my own life this month.
Ok, ok.
That is alright.
I will think another way.
If you have time,
shall we have a meal together
with my boyfriend?
Ok.
Great. It will be my treat then.
Bye.
I made it!
Right.
I said it was easy, right?
What are you doing?
Give you a hug.
Oh, I mean
it is so easy, right?
I thought you were saying
let's have a hug to celebrate my success.
We can celebrate by
this fist or high five.
But hugging is so...
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, yeah. Right, right.
Well. Let's pretend it never happened.
Ok, right, fine.
Let's go.
Go, go.
Which..
This way.
Congratulations on your success.
I have seen the debate.
Splendid.
Thank you.
Senior
You are stirring in the wrong way.
Look.
It should be
like drawing a circle,
so that it will taste good.
You get it?
Got it.
Yummy.
You can have a taste. senior
How does it taste?
Good.
Now
there is nothing
to teach you.
Oh?
Zishi
I think I fall in love with you.
Are you ok?
Zishi
Hao
I am over. I am over.
Something amazing had happened
just now.
He said he fell in love with me.
I stayed with Liu Yanze.
When he said that,
my mind went to blank.
I was acting like
nothing had happened.
and I told him
no.
I said I didn't like him.
Oh no.
He must have thought I didn't like him.
But I like him very much.
Captain. What did you say
you have screwed up?
Liu Yanze had declared his love to me.
What?
But I turned him down.
She turned you down?
She just ran away.
Ran away?
My mind went to blank then.
so I...
Sister Tao Hao
Am I a fool?
No, I understand you.
Tell me.
Shouldn't I declare my love to her, right?
What did I do?
Not at all
She used to like you
so much.
You don't like him anymore?
I like him.
Then she must fall in love with another one.
That is impossible.
That is possible.
He didn't care about you before,
so it is normal for you
to dislike him.
I like him.
Oh, no, no, no.
He must hate me
so much.
She must hate me.
She must be in trouble and doesn't want to tell you.
No, I don't.
I was shocked
and my mind went to blank.
So I ran away.
There is no girl
to reject your love
in the world.
You have to ask her again.
You mean that
I need to ask her out again?
I don't want to see him anymore.
It is so embarrassing.
Stay in the dormitory for several days.
I will buy some
snacks you like.
You should stay here
to calm down.
Tao Hao
Liu Yanze
What can I do for you?
I am here for Xiong Zishi.
I talked to her on WeChat,
but didn't get reply.
Can you help me to ask her out?
I want to talk to her.
Ah huh.
You come here for Dango.
But she is ill
and you may not see her during this period.
Really?
Is she ok?
Not too bad.
Since there is nothing else,
I have to go.
Just as what I have said,
She had trouble but didn't want to tell you.
How could she turn me down
because she is ill?
Maybe...
No way.
What?
Maybe she has an incurable disease.
That can't be true.
Listen.
I had watched a television drama before
which had a plot that
the heroine had an incurable disease.
In order not to become the burden of the hero,
she turned him down though she was desperate.
Dango is like the heroine.
That is impossible.
The plots in the television drama
are fictional.
You should keep an eye on her.
Especially
the details.
It is very nice, right?
Yes. It looks convenient.
The Old Coach can use it when leaving the hospital.
Let me have a try.
Come on.
In this way Old Coach can
go around by using it.
Very good.
Let's go.
Is it that serious?
Obviously the television drama
originates from life.
Captain,
be strong.
Another bowl the soup.
Sister Tao Hao.
You are always the best to me.
The black-bone chicken soup
with ginseng I cooked
has many tonics.
If you drink too much,
you will get inflamed.
So it is the last bowl.
I don't care.
I am motivated by my sorrow.
So I will drink it up.
Zishi
Zishi. Please don't avoid me.
I have known all the things.
I won't leave you alone
in your misery.
I can...
What are you saying?
What misery?
Zishi
I know it.
I have known everything.
I won't leave you alone
to suffer it.
I will always be with you.
I will not give up
no matter what happened.
Even you have a serious illness
I will be with you to overcome it.
So please
don't avoid me.
Zishi
I like you.
I love you.
Give me a chance
to take care of you forever,
ok?
We should go to the hospital right now.
Wait a minute
I was just a little inflamed.
Don't you have an illness?
What?
I'm healthy.
So
that was not true
and you didn't fall ill,
right?
Yes.
I was just be
a little inflamed.
How do you
think I'm ill?
I have thought that...
I am in good health
and will live to a ripe old age.
Well, senior.
What you have said just now
will not be true?
Sorry. Senior.
Make you misunderstand.
I have got to go.
Wait.
Will you give me a chance to be with you
no matter you are in health or illness?
Yes, I will.
What is your answer?
I said
I will.
Oh my god, Dango.
It seems that he was making a proposal.
It is so romantic.
Congratulations, Dango.
You can finally be with the one
you like.
You know what?
I feel like that I am dreaming.
It seems that I am dreaming too,
a nightmare for life long.
Zishi
Senior
What are you doing here?
Get out.
I told you
it is impossible
to past me to enter.
Are you free today?
Shall we
hang out?
Yes, yes, yes.
Dango, go.
Ok.
Shall we go together, Xiaoyu?
It is not appropriate for me to go with you.
Or it looks like parents going out with a child.
Xiaoyu
Will you go?
No. Wake up, wake up.
Sister Tao Hao. Ma Nan.
Shall we go together?
Forget it.
You four hang out together
and we won't go.
Yeah. We will discuss the topic of the debate,
so we won't go.
Alright.