I won't work overtime today
Episode 5
Fresh graduates
And work experience
Only one-year-old ones have
Two hundred and two copies
This information
I have synced to
Everyone's computers
Any other questions
Very good
Would you like to sit down first
According to this data
Recruitment of new people
Can't keep up with company expansion
Increased efforts are needed
Give me a plan within a week
Additionally
Director Wu
Personnel Department Work
What is most important
Knowing people well
Clear rewards and punishments
Very good
Adjourned the meeting
Everyone can go back to work
Well done
Brother Kai
You see how proud she is
Let's go
Sister Jiaojiao
You're too good, aren't you
Those data
How do you know
You're not making this up, are you
How is it possible
Li Su has that kind of computing power
How could I make this up
Then you were ready before
Yes
Neither is it
I didn't know there was a meeting
So there isn't
Make arrangements for meetings
But last month
We've been putting together resumes
Zhao Ting has been asking me to work overtime
So I just dropped the way
Have made all these data
I finally understood
Why did you say
Do everything you can do well
Jiaojiao is back
Congratulations
This time finally
He showed his face in front of Mr. Li
I think you must
It's been carefully prepared for a long time
You're so good
You look like
We regular employees
Can't even compare to you
Where
Sister Ting, you are better
It's just
After you finish your work
But remember
Report to your superiors
Otherwise, you will leapfrog and report it like you do
Those who know know you're serious
Someone who doesn't know
I thought you were scheming
Trying to frame someone else
But it's okay
My lord has a large number of
I won't argue with you this time
Sister Ting
These data
I'm
I've reported it to you
Don't put your thoughts
Is it okay to put it on someone else's head
What
When did you report
Take a look at the WeChat file
It's full of my data
Or didn't you watch it at all
Of course I did
Just such important data
You have to remind me more
Sister Ting
Take a look at WeChat again
I've called you so many times
Isn't it just to remind you
Anyone who knows
Know you're busy
People who don't know
I thought
Are you not serious in your work
You
Don't talk nonsense
What are you doing
Brother Kai
Here's what it looks like
Today, Jiaojiao is indeed
Leapfrog directly to the leader
Reported the work
But her performance
It is also very prominent
I was thinking
Is it possible
Put your resume on this piece of work
Leave it to her
You really think so
And Mr. Li today
Very satisfied indeed
Bright performance
As long as she finishes her work later
Report to me in a timely manner
That's all right
Or do you know the big picture?
But later
And she doesn't have to report to you
Jiaojiao
Mr. Wu told me
What about tomorrow
You bring your information
Go through the formal entry formalities
And then what
You two hand over the procedure
What about the future
You're in charge of her business
You
You said she became a full-time employee ahead of schedule
Yeah
Didn't you also say
Did she perform well
I
By the way, that one
Have some snacks at the handover
Don't give me any more trouble
Brother Kai
Your position
Not as good as here
You don't know
Since the establishment of our company
Only three people became full-time ahead of schedule
What a wonderful thing
It's not as simple as you think
But there's nothing difficult
I'm leaving first
Wait for me, I'll go too
Don't you work overtime
It's all done
You don't have to work overtime
Let's go
Pick me up downstairs in five minutes
Come back after a while
I'll contact you later
He Jiaojiao
Come over
That's how you treat it
The boss who just turned you full-time
Morning boss
Thank you boss
As soon as I turned you into a full-time person, you drifted away
I didn't even work overtime last night
I've finished my work
I'll decide later
During working hours
Get all the tasks done
I believe
This is also your boss
The scene I want to see most
Is the work done
Or are you deliberately avoiding me
Are you playing hard to get for me
How could it be
I have always respected you
Really
Then you
The boss
Please wait for the elevator
I went to climb the stairs first
Work in a hurry, bye-bye
I also climb stairs to exercise
Dear Ladies
I just went out to do some errands
Then I passed a dessert shop
I think they have quite a lot of family members
So I'll give it to everyone
Bought some afternoon tea
Thank you
Everyone has it
Come on to you
Thank you
Sister Yu, hold it steady
Lai Jiaojiao
Why is there one missing
I obviously bought it according to the head
Did the clerk give the wrong count
I'm sorry, Jiaojiao
I
I may have forgotten about you
Let's do this
Why don't I give you this
Thank you, Sister Ting
I like cake best
Thank you
This
Why don't you forget it
What about me
Losing weight recently
This cake
It's also high in calories and sugar
I still don't eat it
But I think Sister Ting
Your figure is pretty well managed
Should usually
Don't eat these things
I
Give me a minute
You all eat
What are you doing
Sneaky
Frontline News
That Zhao Ting
Created a WeChat group
Say bad things about you in there
There is really one
Newly opened paella
Do you want to give it a try
There are group purchase coupons
Yeah
Then go to us
Clockwork link in the group
WeChat Group
What is WeChat Group
Isn't it five women and eight groups
You won't be isolated from an early age
Have you never been in a group chat
It doesn't matter
Anyway, that
How to play the combination of WeChat group
There are many kinds of things
In short, it's a sentence summary
The hearts of the people behind the scenes are not old
Unexpectedly
She's a little palace maid
He actually jumped to the position of concubine
On an equal footing with us
Don't say that
You don't know
Who are they trying to win over
I'm afraid of her
I'd like to see
How long can she be proud
That is
Just a little palace maid
Is it possible that you really want to become a phoenix
Let me see
Everyone should be careful
Everyone has a little more thought in it
Be on guard against her
Don't be bewitched by her
Mingyue, please say hello to all sisters
Everyone is here
He Bin
It's you today
The first day of being promoted to the rank of concubine
Don't restrain yourself
Come
Enjoy the flowers with me
This human heart has never been old
But it's a different carrier
Just doing the same thing
Maybe they have other groups
Specifically speaking ill of Zhao Ting
One more thing
Don't know
Say
That's what they're passing right now
You went through the back door when you turned full-time ahead of time
Why don't you clarify
Let them be
Strength is
The best way to clear up rumors
Get back to work
Wait a minute, there's one more thing
What is it
That is, they still pass on
The two of us have an affair
Have an affair
What is having an affair
Having an affair is
You like me I like you
I didn't expect that
Of course
I like you best
Such a cute brother
Let's go
Mr. Li, I've packed everything
I'll go this way
Why don't you first
Mr. Li, who provoked you? This is
Let me ask you
Our company
Which position is the most bitter and tiring
Assistant to the President
No, no, no, no
That, that, I'm kidding
I'm not trying to help you
Let's live up the atmosphere
Who's messing with you again
I remember Mr. Wei
Isn't it to open up the market overseas
Why don't you ask her
Look at it in Africa
Is there any hard work in mining?
Not bad, it's a place to go
You go and check it out
OK
Xu Tezhu
What happened to Mr. Li recently
I don't think he's in a good mood
You want to know
I still want to know
I eat them all if I don't see them
Quick-acting Jiuxin Pill helped me
Looks like I have to hurry to the meeting
Ask them for it
New recruitment plan
You wait, wait, wait
Help me analyze it
Who the hell provoked Mr. Li
He he
It's not her
Who knows
Sister Jiaojiao
Why are you still here
Where else should I be
You didn't talk to them
Are you going to the meeting together
Have a meeting
I didn't see you just now
I thought you were there
Several of their regular employees
Said the director called a meeting
Talk about discussing the plan
These people can
To isolate me
Don't even call me for meetings
Delay work
Can they afford to be responsible
That
So what if they've already gone
It's okay, I have my own way
Has anyone asked for leave of absence
Chief inspector
No request for leave was received
Then this is
He Jiaojiao
She may have overslept
It's four o'clock in the afternoon and I'm still asleep
Is it the newly turned full-time, right?
Right
It floated on the first day of becoming a full-time employee