[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP15]
[Lord Zhang has arrived.]
Stand still, don't move.
[Hold on.]
Stop!
Let go of him!
Are you abducting people
in broad daylight?
[This isn't an abduction.]
I sent them
to invite him over as a guest.
Your Highness,
since he is a guest,
he should be free to come and go.
[This gentleman clearly]
[doesn't want to be your guest.]
Such a trivial matter
has roused Lord Zhang's interest.
I wonder what the relationship is between
you two.
Apologies, Your Highness.
[I was by imperial decree to visit]
Lord Shen and his wife.
In a fortunate coincidence,
Lady Yan mentioned this to me.
[Her Majesty has always valued Your Highness,]
[and my actions are also]
[for Your Highness' sake.]
I implore Your Highness to think it over.
Since you said so,
I won't insist on keeping him.
I shall take my leave.
Lady Yan!
[I have already made it clear last time.]
[You can protect him for a moment,]
[but can you protect him for a lifetime?]
Lord Shen,
we've received a report stating
that in the ruins of the Jinxiu Workshop,
several pieces of moth-shaped
jade have suddenly appeared.
[And some deceased figure has reappeared,]
[which is quite eerie.]
Let's go!
To the Jinxiu Workshop.
[It's the owner of the shop, Lady Kong!]
[Isn't she already dead?]
[Is that her or a specter?]
[Can the dead truly come back?]
As you saw,
could it be that a ghost is truly at work?
[I never believe]
[that there are ghosts in this world.]
If there are,
it's likely that someone is secretly causing mischief.
We should investigate thoroughly,
and we will surely find clues.
[I found it!]
A miracle has revealed the jade!
This moth-shaped jade must be divine!
There must be more, find them!
There are more for sure, look for them!
I found one!
Amazing!
[I found another one!]
I always feel that
behind this case,
there are two pairs of hands.
One pair of them
wants to quietly erase
this case.
And the other pair
is stirring up trouble.
Moth-shaped jade.
The owner manifested.
The dead come back to life.
All these strange occurrences
seem to have been arranged.
They all emerged collectively this month.
[Stirring up such a storm in]
[the imperial capital is beyond the]
capabilities of a
mere habitual murderer
or an ordinary sorcerer.
Some significant figure must be behind it.
But I can't figure out
what this significant figure's
purpose is.
Creating a deity.
Creating a deity?
The situation
is far too complicated
for you alone to grasp.
There are cases within cases,
and they are intricately linked
to the power struggles among the higher-ups.
What is him trying to achieve
by creating a deity?
What's your take in this?
My only thought right now
is also my only advice to you:
Stop investigating.
Don't bring trouble upon yourself.
Boring.
I thought
you had some profound insights.
I must
continue the investigation.
That's so naive.
Don't recklessly
put yourself in danger.
Are you
concerned about me?
What do you think?
In any case,
you are currently bearing
the title of the wife of Lord Shen.
Be more prudent.
Don't let yourself
get involved in this.
I feel that you actually care about me.
You wouldn't allow me.
But I'm determined to
get to the bottom of this.
My lady!
Lu Chuichui and I are planning to go
to the silk shop in the south of the city.
They received a new batch of fabrics,
including madder red,
safflower yellow,
hazel black,
and locust bean yellow.
The tie-dyeing looks gorgeous.
If I get there late, there won't be any.
Why don't you head inside.
Let's not wake Lord Shen.
He didn't sleep well last night.
Let him sleep a bit more.
Please be on your way.
Morning, my lady.
Where are you going?
Lu Chuichui and I are planning to go
to the silk shop in the south of the city.
We're checking out a new batch of fabrics,
including madder red,
[safflower yellow,]
[hazel black,]
[and locust bean yellow.]
The tie-dyeing looks gorgeous.
If I get there late, there won't be any.
I'm going to a silk shop
in the south of the city.
They received a new batch of fabrics...
Zhong,
what's wrong with my lady?
Safflower yellow,
hazel black,
and locust bean yellow.
Did they have a quarrel again?
If I get there late, there won't be any.
What are you talking about?
Would you like a sugar-filled bread?
They are freshly made.
I was about to send some to Lord Shen.
Wait a minute.
That was a fabricated lie.
What?
[Lady Yan seems to be in a hurry,]
[leaving so early in the morning.]
[She must have some urgent business.]
[I noticed that Lord Shen hasn't had]
[much appetite for breakfast lately,]
so I made some sugar-filled breads.
You should try some as well.
[Jing Lin.]
Lord Shen.
Keep an eye on Yan Xing.
Given her nature,
she's sure to ignore my advice.
My lord.
[During the investigation,]
[one witness was overlooked,]
[about the witnesses]
[who found the corpse,]
[besides Chen Shoujie,]
[there was another one.]
[...cooking herself.]
[She made mutton and smoked chicken.]
[She also baked flatbreads and stuffed breads.]
[She even rewarded me with a bowl of wine.]
[My lady was so good to us.]
[She was cooking herself that night.]
[She made mutton and smoked chicken.]
[She also baked flatbreads and stuffed breads.]
[That servant of Chen Shoujie's...]
[His testimony was exactly the same]
[as what the officials recorded]
[when they questioned him.]
[The testimonies are even word for word.]
[I'm afraid he memorized it long ago,]
[and knew exactly what to say.]
Chen Shoujie,
where is your servant?
Fire moth, fire moth.
Fire moth.
Fire moth!
What fire moth?
Fire moth, fire moth, fire moth!
Fire moth!
You!
On the day Lady Chen was murdered,
what exactly did you see?
Why did you fabricate your testimony?
Why does it seem like he's waiting for me?
Mingsheng Temple?
Sounds somewhat familiar.
Excuse me,
did you just see
anyone come in?
Excuse me...
Help...
Resurrected from the dead...
Resurrected from...
Don't die just yet.
You still haven't revealed
who the murderer is.
- You can't die!
- Who are you?
And who are you?
Why did you commit murder?
It wasn't me.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Are you still trying to deny it?
I truly didn't kill him.
Someone!
I didn't kill anyone!
I just...
Stop!
Greetings, Your Highness!
Your Highness...Princess Runing?
Mingsheng Temple.
No wonder that name sounds so familiar.
The Jinxiu Workshop incident
actually involves her, and she's
currently reflecting at Mingsheng Temple.
Mr. Xu!
What's the matter?
Do you not value your head anymore,
or are you willing to lose your hands?
Why am I so foolish?
I was set up
and fell into a trap.
I really am too foolish.
What's going on?
The powder...
must be what I picked up
at Mingsheng Temple.
It looks just like
the suspicious powder
found around the Jinxiu Workshop.
I need to gather my thoughts.
There must be a connection in all of this.
I'm sure there's something
I've missed.
Ease your mind.
There's someone who is even
more anxious than you.
I followed her closely,
but my horse seemed
to have been spooked when it
reached the outskirts of Chen residence.
By the time I arrived
at Mingsheng Temple,
Princess Runing had already...
Are you certain that after leaving
Chen residence, she was acting strangely?
Yes.
I called out to my lady several times,
but she didn't respond at all.
It was as if she was possessed,
chasing after something.
Whoever it is,
if they dare to target
my woman,
prepare to face my wrath!
But my lady was taken
by Princess Runing.
The water might be deeper than we thought.
There are rules in place.
You are not allowed to enter.
How could Yan Xing possibly commit murder?
You really can't go in.
How's she doing?
She's fine.
She just ate two buns a moment ago.
[By the way,]
she specifically asked
not to inform her family
about this for now.
Who could have schemed against
Yan Xing?
Please, you must uncover the truth!
We also believe
that Yan Xing is not capable of murder.
However, the one who took her
was Princess Runing.
The investigation of this whole thing,
might not be easy to conduct.
What's so complicated about it?
There are witnesses and solid evidence.
Killing someone warrants a death penalty,
and that's only just.
Hey!
Lord Lai,
what brings you to the prison
at this late hour?
About the incident at Mingsheng Temple,
it involves a royal princess.
Her Majesty wishes to interrogate
the suspect, Yan Xing.
What are you waiting for?
Take her.
My lord!
Not so fast!
Lord Shen, what is the meaning of this?
Are you intending to shield your wife,
obstruct the interrogation,
and bend the law?
Are you here on the
order of Her Majesty,
or are you relying on favor and privilege
to disregard the law?
The Imperial Inspectorate has always been
dedicated to serving Her Majesty.
Lord Shen,
are you insinuating something about me?
Regarding today's events,
I must take charge personally
to uphold the trust placed in me
by Her Majesty.
I guarantee a thorough investigation.
Lord Lai,
you may leave now.
Keep a vigilant watch here.
If anyone dares to approach,
consider it a prison break.
Execute without mercy.
Understood.
I didn't expect
Lord Shen to be so firmly convinced
that Lady Yan is innocent.
But I wonder, when Her Majesty
learns of this tomorrow,
will she be swayed
by your deep affection as a couple,
or will she order me to enforce justice?
I advise you,
Lord Shen,
to savor this night
of intimacy.
Let's go.
We shall return tomorrow.
What do you want
- at this late hour?
- Lord Wu.
No more words.
Just follow me.
Can't this wait until tomorrow?
Greetings, Lord Shen.
Jing Lin!
You witnessed it firsthand that day,
after Yan Xing left Chen residence,
she seemed to be chasing someone and rode
all the way to the woods west of the city.
That's correct.
Yan Xing mentioned
that she discovered a servant
from the Chen Family had forged testimony,
and out of suspicion, she went there.
She found he was attempting to escape,
so she chased him to Mingsheng Temple.
That's right.
Yan Xing said that.
Then something doesn't add up.
What doesn't add up?
Jing Lin!
Lift your foot.
So that's how it is.
The ground in the woods is quite muddy.
If he was riding a fast horse,
the cuffs of his pants wouldn't be so clean.
I should have gotten my shoes dirty
while following my lady
to Mingsheng Temple.
But the servant's shoes
are completely spotless.
Then how could the corpse
have appeared at Mingsheng Temple?
This smell...
Could it be?
There are numerous doubts
in this case.
No one is to interrogate
the suspect before tomorrow.
Yet, if...
Yan Xing comes to
any harm in here,
you will be held accountable.
Lord Shen,
where should we start?
To the source of this incident.
This powder closely resembles
what we found at the Jinxiu Workshop.
Could it be that
my lady fell into
the trap here?
[Fire moth, fire moth, fire moth!]
Something was originally stored here.
Lord Shen,
It appears there are no
signs of a struggle or search here.
So much blood!
It seems this is
the scene of the crime.
But how did the corpse
end up at Mingsheng Temple?
[It's a chest.]
Lord Shen, this shows
Prince Xian's whereabouts last night.
As expected.
You had someone
spy on Prince Xian.
If they find out,
- it could lead to...
- Her safety is paramount.
It seems I need to meet
Princess Runing myself.
Greetings, Your Highness,
I'm Shen Du, the commander of the Imperial Guard.
Lord Shen,
you are the renowned White Death.
Are you here
to arrest anyone today?
Your Highness, you misunderstood.
I'm here humbly asking for a favor.
Lord Shen is being humorous.
I have been stripped of my royal title.
I am simply a civilian now.
What could you possibly want from me?
Please, take your leave.
I implore Your Highness
to consider my request.
If it pertains to court matters,
it no longer concerns me.
You needn't elaborate further.
This is a personal matter of mine.
A personal matter?
Yesterday, my wife was set up
and mistakenly entered Mingsheng Temple.
Now she has been confined in prison.
I beg Your Highness to show mercy.
You would actually come to me
to plead for your wife?
This is quite different from
the rumors about White Death.
Are you asking me
to let her off the hook?
I want Your Highness to share the truth.
What do you mean?
Are you implying that I slandered
your wife?
Your Highness would never intend to do so.
But if you wish to protect someone,
you might conceal certain information.
That's absurd!
I'm tired.
You may leave now.
At the time of the incident, was
Your Highness truly the only one in here?
[Were there no others present?]
The Empress Dowager has confined Your Highness.
If she knew you met Prince Xian in secret,
I wonder what her thoughts would be.
Are you threatening me?
I only seek the truth.
He was simply
concerned about his aunt living alone,
in a state of loneliness.
He brought me some gifts,
and shared some tea. That's all.
There was no discussion of state affairs,
and no hidden agenda.
This was merely
a matter of familial courtesy.
Is it really against the law?
The prince values family ties.
But others
may not see it that way.
Sometimes,
a single word
can lead to an innocent person's demise.
I beg Your Highness to reveal the truth
and clear my wife's name.
Open it.
I must admit, I did not
witness your wife committing murder.
When I arrived,
the main hall
only had her and the body remaining.
I didn't want anyone to know
that the prince had been here,
so I asked them to leave
through the back door.
Later, when inspecting the back door,
we indeed found
signs of a break-in.
Among the items
the prince brought,
I discovered this chest,
but I don't know its origin.
Gratitude, for revealing the truth.
I apologize for my discourtesy today.
Lord Shen, act wisely.
Should the prince suffer any harm,
I'll not hesitate to inform Her Majesty
about your spying on the royal family.
Do Your Highness truly believe
I would be so audacious
as to act on my own?
I hope that in the future,
there will be more peaceful days ahead.
Your Highness, don't you wish to know
the truth behind the Jinxiu Incident?
What good would knowing the truth do?
The dead
can never return.
The deceased have passed,
and they have found peace.
It's merely
a comforting statement for the living.
What really happened in that incident?
Back then, no one dared to investigate.
What could be done today?
Today, I promise
to thoroughly investigate the incident
and bring the truth to Your Highness.
Very well.
Then I will await your findings.
Your Highness, the Mingsheng Temple
is a place of controversy.
If Her Majesty learns
that you have been there,
you will surely be accused of
forming factions
and plotting treason.
To fabricate a crime,
there's no need for evidence.
Back then, my aunt was involved in the
Jinxiu Workshop Incident
over a single piece of clothing.
Please be cautious with your words.
Exercise caution!
You just performed a charitable act
that has pleased her Majesty.
You must avoid any actions
that might displease her.
Do not overlook the details,
or you risk suffering great losses.
Shen Du has long been aware of this
but has chosen not to report it.
He is quite astute.
It's already dawn,
why hasn't Lord Shen returned yet?
It's about time.
Take her!
You really are stubborn.
I recall that back then, you were
the one who fell into Shen Du's trap.
Now you're heeding his words?
Her Majesty' decree orders Lord Lai
to interrogate at the hour of the snake(9am.)
The time has not yet arrived,
so she shouldn't be taken.
The Delinquent dare to obstruct
the Imperial Inspectorate's duties?
I'm quite eager to find out
how tough
your skull really is.
[What a magnificent display of authority.]
But it seems Lord Lai
lacks a bit of patience.
In serving Her Majesty,
one must give their utmost effort.
Her Majesty' decree:
The Mingsheng Temple case has many uncertainties.
It's fully entrusted to the Imperial Guard.
A thorough investigation is required.
Lord Shen,
weren't you the fast one?
Let's go!
Why isn't she out yet?
Oh lord!
Come out, now!
Xing!
You finally made it out!
I was so worried about you!
Here, here.
Misfortune, out!
As long as you came out
safe and sound, that's what matters.
You little toots,
what kind of investigation was it
that you almost got yourself busted?
But, you are safe,
and that's what truly matters.
Do you know,
when I heard you had killed someone
and were arrested,
I was worried sick!
Come on, a bit more,
to drive away the bad luck.
A bit more!
Fate has favored me with a robust life.
Now that my suspicions have been cleared,
I am safe and sound, right?
If it weren't for Lord Shen
going to meet Princess Runing
to clarify the situation
and discovering the chest
used to transport the body
to frame you, which was found in
the woods outside the Mingsheng Temple,
do you really think you could
have gotten out so easily?
He went to see the princess?
What did you just say?
The chest used to transport the body
was thrown into the woods?
That doesn't sound right.
What's not right?
You must be in shock.
It's all right now.
By the way,
Mr. Xu and Jiang Langxing
went off to pursue
new leads.
I heard that
the deceased servant of the Chen Family
had been embezzling assets
from the Chen Family.
He was later discovered by Lady Chen,
which led to his betrayal.
It's unclear who
he colluded with.
He was silenced for it.
Too bad, death leaves no witness.
Yan Xing!
Lord Shen,
are you here to take her back home?
What's the point of going home?
I'm feeling incredibly motivated now.
I need to dig into this case
to clear my name.
What are you doing?
From this moment on,
you are not allowed to pursue this case.
Things have already progressed this far.
You expect me to just step back?
How can I simply walk away from this?
Besides,
the corpse of that servant
should be at the Ministry of Justice.
I have to find
clues from him.
I said no, and that's final.
The culprit used the servant
to lure me to Mingsheng Temple.
Without a doubt, they aimed
to make me doubt Princess Runing.
Princess Runing has not set foot
outside the Mingsheng Temple for years.
Who is trying to drag her
into this mess?
Enough already!
This could involve the royal family,
so you want me to stop the investigation?
Leave this case to me.
I will take care of it.
I just want to reveal the truth.
Your apprehension of
the high and mighty
is evident, Lord Shen.
Fine,
I'll investigate this case myself.
You, Shen Du, the mighty Lord Shen,
you're free to
walk your own path.
So this is how you perceive me.
Haven't you always been
afraid of being implicated?
Let's part ways now
to save you from
writing a guilty plea.
Xing!
What now?
Where are you going?
To examine the corpse.
Shen Du had already examined it earlier.
His shoes are clean,
without any dirt from the woods.
He must have been brought to
the Mingsheng Temple after he had died.
What's going on?
Did you discover something?
Take a whiff of this.
This odor, is from something
to slow down the decomposition.
By the time I arrived
at Chen residence,
he was already dead.
As for what transpired afterward,
even though I witnessed it firsthand,
I couldn't be certain
that it reflects the truth.
Are you suggesting that
everything you saw was just an illusion?
Then what is that?
Or what kind of substance can so
effectively manipulate people's minds?
In this vast world,
with all its mysteries,
I can only conclude
that it lies far beyond our grasp.
Furthermore,
what concerns me even more is
the method used on this servant
to delay the
time of death of the corpse.
It's the same technique that
Lady Tang used back then.
Do you really believe there's a way to
bring the dead back to life?
Are you worried that Chen Huo'e
might actually come back to life,
as others say?
Yes.
I don't buy it.
That's why I need to uncover the truth.
So,
you had a quarrel with your husband
and decided to run away from home?
I'm just concerned
that if in the future
White Death isn't around to protect you, what
will you do if someone tries to harm you?
What do I have to be scared of?
I still have you all, right?
If you go back to the Yans and your mother
finds out, she'll give you a good scolding.
Don't worry.
I've already figured out where to go.
[This place houses a collection of]
[case files from over the years.]
[I refuse to believe]
[that I can't find any clues.]
Clerk Yan.
Lord Ji.
What brings you here so late at night?
I'd like to search for all the records
related to the Jinxiu Workshop case
over the years.
You've been managing the archives for years.
Do you know where I might find them?
Jinxiu Shop...
It's from quite a while ago.
It might be over there.
Feel free to take a look.
Thank you.
[This scent...]
[Where have I encountered it before?]
Clerk Yan,
be careful with the candles.
Thank you.
I'll be cautious.
[Haven't you always been]
[afraid of being implicated?]
[Let's part ways now]
[to save you from]
[writing a guilty plea.]
Mother.
Oranges.
The branches of the orange tree outside
happened to fall into the garden.
I know you love oranges, mother,
so I picked some for you.
Did you write
what I asked you to?
I don't know how.
I also shouldn't.
Father was an upright official,
always adhering to the principles
passed down by the Shen Family.
Father was framed;
how can I accept those false accusations
on his behalf?
Enough!
You're now registered as a criminal.
If you don't cut all ties with the Shens,
you'll never have
a chance to rise above this.
I cannot bear
to survive alone
while my father is dishonored.
I prefer
to die nobly,
as my father would.
But if you die too,
then this injustice
will truly be buried forever.
Shen Du,
do you really want them
to never find peace
even in the afterlife?
[If you refuse to write that confession,]
[then from this moment on, you can]
[forget about having me as your mother.]
[For your father's honor,]
[to restore Shen Family's reputation,]
[no matter how hard it gets,]
[no matter how dangerous it becomes,]
[you must keep pushing forward.]