English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP31
Unlimited funds do not mean
that corruption can go unchecked
and enrich themselves.
How much are we talking about?
It could shake the entire court.
They have completely angered
the Great Grandmother.
This matter implicates many,
and the silence now suggests
that the Great Grandmother
plans to investigate secretly,
to eradicate the evil completely,
and destroy them for good.
So, what should
we do now?
Your husband,
disregarding the royal family's face,
has rejected the arranged marriage,
and may be put to
an indifferent post.
My dear wife,
you won't despise me for this, will you?
Your intention
is too clear
to hide from me.
But my feelings for you can be seen
by the heaven and earth.
The Great Grandmother's given an oral decree
to have the Imperial Guard
investigate Princess Runing
and Prince Xian,
and to spy on the Imperial Inspectorate.
Is the Great Grandmother
suspecting Prince Xian?
More than him, I'm afraid.
The decree of the Great Grandmother.
The Imperial Inspectorate
is ordered to probe Zhou's kin secretly,
and watch Princess Ying's moves,
reporting truthfully
without concealment.
Additionally,
secretly monitor the IG,
and report immediately
for anomalies.
Yes,
your servant accepts the decree.
Lady Xu,
I have prepared
the famous tea from Junshan Island,
brewed with snow water from Tianshan.
You might as well stay and taste it.
The nature of this tea is too cold
for me to enjoy.
Lord Lai, there's no need to see me off.
The decree of the Great Grandmother
must be handled with utmost care,
fairness,
and without error.
Yes,
thank you for the reminder, Lady Xu.
A fine tea indeed.
Shen Du's got some nerve,
daring to refuse the empress
dowager's arranged marriage.
It seems I've underestimated Yan Xing.
How intriguing.
I never expected
the cold-hearted Shen Du
to actually fall in love.
Nonetheless,
this is a good thing
for us.
If Princess Ying gains
the support of the IG,
it will be much more difficult
for you to secure
the position of regent.
Don't you find it strange
that the empress dowager didn't
punish Shen Du severely?
With Mo Qianzhi's death,
the position of the governor of Yingzhou
has been vacant.
I've heard that
someone tried to assassinate Shen Du
before returning to Xiang'an,
and then he met
the empress dowager in the nightfall,
after which
the arranged marriage was proposed.
Too coincidental.
I wonder what information
he might have discovered in Yingzhou.
Shen Du might have
distanced himself from Great Grandmother
due to the arranged marriage issue,
and recently he's rarely been summoned.
I've heard that
some maids have reached the age
to return to their hometowns,
and Great Grandmother
called Lai Luozhi
and bestowed upon him several maids.
It's clear to everyone that
Lai Luozhi is now favored
by the empress dowager.
It seems inevitable that the Imperial Inspectorate
will outshine the IG.
It's too early to draw conclusions.
Zhang Baohuan's sudden serious illness
is quite suspicious.
I always feel
that something significant
is happening in the court.
Human hearts are inscrutable.
I will send more people
to spy on monitor Princess Ying.
Lan,
he's on our side.
Men from Dacang cannot be trusted!
He's also trying to capture that person,
who not only deceived
the Holy Maiden Dai Si.
Do you trust him?
I trust him.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Lan,
you have served
Dai Si for many years.
We two wish to know
about the events of the past
in the most detailed way possible.
It's been more than 10 years.
At that time, Dai Si
was the Jinwu Tribe's Holy Maiden.
Ever since Jinwu sent envoys
to pay respects to Dacang,
Dacang returned the gesture
by sending envoys to Jinwu.
Since then, the Jinwu Tribe and Dacang
have had mutual exchanges,
and the two peoples have been free to
come and go.
One day on the street,
as the Holy Maiden was blessing
and praying for the people,
Don't worry, we have it for everyone.
she encountered that person.
It was just a coincidental encounter.
She didn't pay much attention.
She soon forgot
about him after returning.
As a Holy Maiden,
she is bound to a life of solitude.
She locked her heart,
dedicated to her tribe.
But fate had other plans,
and they met again
not long after.
This time, however,
it was at a court banquet
of the Jinwu Tribe.
How could it be such a coincidence?
The Holy Maiden,
cut off from men for long,
was innocent and virtuous.
But once love stirred,
she was like a wild horse broken free,
her feelings impossible to hide.
After the banquet,
as the envoys lingered,
Dai Si,
leveraging her sanctity,
sought Dacang's envoys' company.
And all of this
was to get closer
to that Dacang man.
What is this?
Dai Si.
That's your name.
Unexpectedly, the Dacang man
proposed to learn
the Jinwu language from her.
He had an
extraordinary talent for languages,
and in just a week or so,
he had picked it up quite well.
It was from that day on
that the Holy Maiden
learned his name.
Those three characters
should have been
etched in her memory.
But no matter what,
they remained a blur afterwards.
Their relationship blossomed rapidly,
and soon
they were deeply in love.
But she had her duties,
and she had to be
reserved in public.
But at that time,
in her heart and eyes,
there was only that Dacang man;
she had forgotten
all her responsibilities.
But this joy didn't last long,
and soon
something went wrong.
Would you accompany
me back to Dacang?
I know your status is special,
and meeting you has
used up all the luck in my life.
How could I dare to ask for more?
Yes,
I would.
Of course I am willing to.
After that,
no one could find
the Holy Maiden anymore.
Some people claimed
to have seen her dressed in
the traditional dress of Dacang women,
riding a horse
towards Dacang with him!
Jinwu Tribe wanted to avoid a scandal,
so they announced
the Holy Maiden had died of illness,
erasing her existence.
Jinwu ceased
all interactions with Dacang since then.
I had thought
that this man
would protect her
and they would live a loving life.
But I never expected
that soon after,
in this dilapidated house,
I found the Holy Maiden
on the brink of death!
Holy Maiden! Holy Maiden!
Holy Maiden!
How could this have happened?
I am no longer the Holy Maiden.
Holy Maiden,
come back with me.
Everything will get better.
It's too late.
Where is that person?
Where is he?
He deceived me,
tricked me into revealing
the secrets a Holy Maiden should keep,
and coaxed me into teaching him
how to control moths with powders.
I was so foolish.
How could I have trusted him?
When I discovered
his ill intentions,
his practice of the dark arts,
and his attempts to manipulate
others to do his bidding,
he wanted to kill me.
Holy Maiden! Holy Maiden!
Holy Maiden...
Too late,
it's all too late.
I am guilty of grave sins.
-I deserve to die. -No, no!
Holy Maiden!
This man truly
deserves a thousandfold punishment,
and even death is too lenient!
Calm down first.
We will eventually catch him
in his crimes
and expose them to the world.
Lan,
take a look at these portraits.
Do any of them resemble him?
This mole!
It's him!
It's that Dacang man!
Have you found him?
Where is he?
Tell me!
-I'm going to kill him! -Lan,
leave it to us.
Rest assured,
I will make sure this man
pays the price he deserves
to honor the death of Dai Si.
If the Holy Maiden's spirit watches,
that evil man, laden with crimes,
will face his just deserts
and die unburied.
She once
saw the unfaithful man
teaching an incendiary spell
to burn a granary down.
She reprimanded him
for disregarding the people of Dacang,
but he mocked her, saying that
it was not him who disregarded
the people of Dacang,
but...
but the
Great Grandmother
of Dacang.
And it was her own kin,
the Zhou family, who ordered
the burning of the granary.
When Dai Si fled,
she stole the token of the transaction
between him
and the arsonist—
this very jade pendant.
Yan Xing,
I hope it's not too late.
Great Grandmother,
your servant has a report.
What is the matter?
I wish to impeach
Chief Inspector Sun Tan of Gannan
for dereliction of duty.
In the case of the masked spectre,
Sun Tan led
Gannan's Delinquents
to offer support,
and I saw it firsthand.
Why blaming him when we should
give him credit where it's due?
Great Grandmother,
the Imperial Inspectorate has gathered
much evidence of Sun Tan's
malfeasance and corruption.
Now, I present them one by one.
Please review them.
Dacang's law states
stealing what's not yours is theft,
those who steal from his duties
shall face punishment.
Bribe-takers
deserve hanging.
Sun Tan, using his post,
stole and colluded with bandits.
The evidence is solid.
I request Great Grandmother to allow me
to punish him according to the law.
Great Grandmother,
under torture of the Imperial Inspectorate,
confessions might be forced.
Whether Sun Tan's crime
is severe enough for hanging,
please consider it thrice.
Lord Shen,
your IG
is famously known
as the Avici Hell,
with tortures
even harsher.
Now you are showing mercy
in front of the court,
trying to protect Sun Tan.
What is the meaning of this?
Enough.
Today, I am a bit tired.
Leave the evidence,
and we will discuss it another day.
-Your servant takes his leave. -Your son takes his leave.
Leave us.
Prince Xian...
When trimming branches and leaves,
one must be very careful
and not be distracted at all.
Well,
isn't it much better than before?
Prince Xian, you...
Prince Xian,
Lai Luozhi is domineering
in the court,
often arresting officials
on trumped-up charges,
and now he's trying to
interfere in Gannan.
When you
become the regent,
he will also be a great threat to you.
How about this?
I will have someone impeach him
at the court session tomorrow.
Lord Zhang,
withered leaves will eventually fall.
Can we stop the autumn wind,
stop the winter snow?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Those folks from Xichen and Nanlang
are new in town, right?
Yes.
Lately, Dacang's been a hub
for talent from all over,
and these folks just
come to Xiang'an
for a living.
Recently,
keep your eyes peeled
during patrols.
Yes.
Your Highness,
it's Shen Du.
I'm just so frustrated.
That White Death had the audacity
to reject the arranged marriage,
making Princess Jia'an look bad.
You should
have taught him a lesson.
Shen Du,
just like his father,
cannot tell good from bad.
The Queen Mother meant well,
but he fails to see
the value of a strong backing.
You've known Jia'an
longer than I have,
so I understand
you're concerned for her.
But the royal family's
honor is paramount.
Queen Mother's been disrespected,
and Shen Du's future
won't be smooth sailing
even though we don't interfere.
Xing,
you're a gem.
You're the Chief Clerk now,
yet still sorting files for me.
When I was just a clerk,
I don't remember you
ever turning your nose
up at me.
Oh,
try this.
From Gannan?
It's sweeter than Xiang'an's.
Try one.
Gannan's honey
is exceptionally sweet.
The place's not just for preserves,
but also for human flesh, you know.
Yan Xing,
I hate you!
Lu Chuichui.
How dare you, Lu Chuichui,
having Yan help you
with your files?
What were you thinking?
It takes one
to know one, right?
I...
That's history now.
Right, Chief Clerk Yan?
Chief Clerk Yan,
time has changed.
Now, we share equal
official ranks.
Plus, you are Lord Shen's wife.
In the future, I'll have to
rely on you for more guidance.
Mr. Wu, you flatter me.
Although I've been given
the title of Chief Clerk,
I'm still under the Ministry of Justice
and will need your advice
on cases, Chief Clerk Wu.
In the future,
I'll need your guidance.
Of course. Of course.
Your bureaucratic talk
is making me sick.
Feng Gui.
Sit. Sit.
Since you still
regard me as the Chief Clerk,
I will speak frankly with you
behind closed doors.
Now you're
both the wife of Chief Shen
and have been promoted,
you claimed your fame
among all female officials.
But as the old saying goes:
the higher you rise, the harder you fall.
Do you know that
the Empress Dowager
now favors the Dark Demon
and disregards the White Death?
You...
The wives of other high-ranking officials
are good at acting and diplomatic,
so they can
gather useful secrets for their husbands.
Unlike you,
who are always
buried in case files and the mortuary
like a clueless fool.
Here's what I mean.
Chancellor Lai is powerful
and has been
frequently arresting court officials.
And the Empress Dowager's
favoritism towards him
exceeds that of Zhang Baohuan.
Whenever he requests an arrest,
the Empress Dowager always approves.
Every court official
is on the edge now.
Is he domineering like this?
So,
Xing,
think about it,
how could the Dark Demon
possibly tolerate
the existence of the White Death,
who's his equal.
If I were
in his position,
I would also prefer
to have only one
Lord of Hell in this world.
Thank you for your kind reminder.
The more
I know my husband,
the more I realize
that despite his high position,
he's constantly walking a tightrope.
I don't know much about court politics
or how to help him,
so I just focus on my duties
and hope
not to cause him trouble.
You?
You won't cause trouble?
Lai Luozhi disregards life like this,
is no one going to do anything?
What's going on?
-What's going on? -Chief Xu?
If the Ministry of Justice won't act,
then I will go to the palace
and ask the Empress Dowager!
Isn't there law
in Dacang?
You! Shut your mouth!
-Move along, move along! -Move along!
Keep it like that if you want your death,
but don't get Ministry of Justice involved
and get so many of us wounded
midnight as well.
Xiangren,
what happened?
Lai Luozhi arrested Sun Tan.
Sun Tan?
Chief Sun of the Delinquents of Gannan?
Wasn't his case file
delivered to the Supreme Court
after court was adjourned today?
The Empress Dowager hasn't decided yet.
Why Imperial Inspectorate started arrests?
She hasn't given a verdict yet,
and the Inspectorate already arrested him.
But we all know
what it's like
in the prison of the Inspectorate.
If it continues like this,
Sun Tan probably would not
live to see
the Empress Dowager's verdict.
Chancellor Lai has been
domineering long in the court.
At the end of the day,
it's the business of the Supreme Court.
You're barking up the wrong tree
here at the Ministry of Justice.
Is it your first day to know
ministers of the Supreme Court?
They've always been timid cowards.
Since it was the Inspectorate
that started the case against Sun Tan
and the Delinquents are also involved,
they've already
handed it over
to the Ministry of Justice.
The Supreme Court... I...
My head hurts!
Feng Gui.
I'm here. I'm here.
What's wrong with you now?
Mr. Wu, take your time to recover.
If the Ministry of Justice
cannot deliver justice for Sun Tan,
I'm prepared
to go to the palace again.
Be careful. Be careful.
Let's go. Let's go.
Chief Clerk Wu
is not much bolder than
the ministers of the Supreme Court.
I think you've come to the wrong person.
Yun Que,
what are you doing here with Mr. Xu?
I'm a Delinquent too.
Why can't I be here with Mr. Xu?
Go back to your work.
Yes, sir.
I'll take my leave.
Xiangren,
you've always
been straightforward
and outspoken,
so why are you
being so cautious today?
Xiangren, did you forget
that I'm also
the Chief Clerk
of the Ministry of Justice now?
With my rank,
I have the same authority
as Chief Clerk Wu to oversee cases.
I can apply to
preside over Sun Tan's case.
What did I say?
You should've asked Xing for help.
Xing,
this would be a blatant offense
to Lai Luozhi.
Didn't you say
you wouldn't cause trouble for Shen Du?
Yeah,
I did say that.
Xing,
I know
the court is full of schemes now, and
Her Majesty is hard to read,
so Shen Du's life must be tough either.
You should
stay out of this.
But this concerns you.
Plus,
Sun Tan has been very helpful
to us in Gannan.
I believe
if the roles were reversed,
he would have helped me.
Xing,
much obliged.
Since I've agreed to help you,
we'll need to plan this carefully.
Come with me.
Let's go.
My lord,
Sun Tan is truly very stubborn.
We have tried every
non-lethal method,
but he still wouldn't give in.
When did the men
at the Inspectorate
get this soft?
Whether he talks or not is not important.
As long as he's not in Gannan,
the Delinquents there
won't become a threat.
Anyone who tries to obstruct me
will not end up well.
Xiangren,
do you know if Lai Luozhi
has any
concrete evidence on Sun Tan?
Do you know
why are we called the Delinquents?
The wanderers from Jianghu appointed as
investigators or enforcers by the court
are called the Delinquents.
Quite so.
The Delinquents
are well-connected
and can obtain information more easily
than other departments in the court
because they only
recruit people
from all sorts of backgrounds
in the first place,
and named them so.
Many of them
were either notorious bandits
or skilled thieves like me
before joining,
and they usually
keep their connections
after they've joined.
Lai Luozhi can easily
fabricate some charges if he wants to.
I'm worried that
Sun Tan's arrest
is not as simple
as it seems.
Lai Luozhi
has always been domineering,
but he has never dared to
mess with the Delinquents before.
The masked spectre case
has just been closed,
Gannan is still in disarray,
and he's already taken Sun Tan.
Is his real aim the Delinquents,
or Gannan?
Xing,
you just got back.
You probably don't know
what has happened
in Xiang'an.
Princess Ying's carriages
have been showing up much more
frequently at
Mingsheng Temple of Princess Runing.
Princess Runing and Princess Yong'an?
The current Emperor is still very young.
How much longer
can the Empress Dowager rule over Dacang?
Many now believe
that Princess Ying is more likely
to become Regent than Prince Xian.
So Princess Runing has decided
to help Princess Ying?
Princess Runing
is the highest-ranking princess
of the royal family.
If she were to decide,
it would surely
impact the court's dynamics.
Additionally,
the reconstruction of Ming Hall
was nearly completed,
then it suddenly slowed down,
almost as if it had
completely stopped.
This happened
shortly after
we got back from Gannan?
Moreover,
there are more
people from
Nanlang and Xichen in Xiang'an recently.
Seen alone,
these events might not mean much,
but if you connect them...
Could there
be some underlying scheme at play?
Xing,
I meant what I said.
There are many eyes
on you and your husband
in the court now.
You must be aware of that.
I won't blame you
if you don't help me with this.
Xiangren,
on the way back from Yingzhou,
we faced many assassination attempts.
It was the
delinquents that got us out of the harm's way.
Without this token,
I probably wouldn't be
standing here in front of you today.
Now that I'm back in Xiang'an,
I should return it to its rightful owner.
Xing,
I know it would be hard for Sun Tan
to get out of this unscathed.
But if he has been wronged,
or if he has anything to say,
I will definitely do my best
to help him for the brotherhood.
Can you find a way
for me to see Sun Tan?
I'll draft and submit the report and
apply to be the chief examiner now.
Even though
Sun Tan is being held at the Inspectorate,
as the Ministry of Justice is in charge.
I could go question him in prison.
Xing,
I will go with you.
He...
He has bled so much.
Will he die?
Once in the custody of the Inspectorate,
who really cares
about a prisoner's death?
If you're scared,
go back and wait for me there.
I, Yan Xing,
Chief Clerk of the Ministry of Justice,
the chief examiner of the Sun Tan case,
am here to take Sun Tan for interrogation.
He is a major criminal of the Inspectorate.
The Ministry of Justice can't take him.
Then I can still question him here,
can't I?
Only two people are allowed in.
Wait for me at the Ministry of Justice.
Then... Then I'll wait for you outside.
Mr. Sun.
It's me,
Yan Xing.
Have you allied with Lai Luozhi too?
I'm the chief examiner
of this case.
I'm here to seek justice for you.
The Inspectorate
is accusing you of embezzlement
and working with bandits.
If you have been wronged,
tell me.
I'll bring it up for you.
No use.
It's no use.
If you've been wronged,
Xiangren and the other Delinquents
will do anything to save you.
I will also do everything
to clear your name.
You will just get yourselves killed.
Get out of here.
Sun Tan,
I'm not dead yet.
Mr. Xu.
This token
is still waiting for you to take.
You must hold on for me.
Lady Yan,
I have something to say.
Okay.
Okay, I'll record it.
Most of the Delinquents
come from the Jianghu,
and were won over
by Mr. Xu's charisma,
joining the Delinquents out of loyalty.
At Gannan,
I naturally hoped to follow his example,
and have built many connections.
And they call it 'working with bandits'?
Then,
what about the embezzlement?
I can't deny this.
I did take the money.
Many merchants pass through Gannan.
The Delinquents
would protect them from bandits,
and they would give us money as thanks.
I used the money
to build more connections.
You can bring it up and explain,
or find the merchants
to testify and get a reduced sentence.
Xing,
how can you still not understand?
What Lai Luozhi wants
is for the Delinquents at Gannan
to have no leader.
Mr. Sun,
then do you know why?
After Mo Qianzhi died,
most of the new officials of Yingzhou
are Lai Luozhi's men.
Gannan is a crucial border fortress
that directly connects Xichen.
Even those from Nanlang in the far south
can use Gannan as a detour,
if the Delinquents can't defend it,
then the border fortress...
Recently, there have been
more people from Nanlang and Xichen
in Xiang'an.
It seems
that Lai Luozhi
wants to take complete control of Gannan.
But his ambitions
go far beyond Gannan.
He may be plotting to ally with
foreign forces and stage a rebellion.
Mr. Xu.
If you intend to frame me,
you should at least have some evidence.
Lady Yan,
you came to the Inspectorate as guests,
but made
accusations against me.
This really puts me in an awkward position.
I am the chief examiner for this case.
I'm here to question the main suspect,
Sun Tan, and to record his statements.
The Delinquent serves as the co-examiner.
We just go by books.
Is that so?
Lady Yan, you are
becoming more and more sharp-tongued.
This is the preliminary questioning.
I'll review
and report the case files when I go back,
then I'll come here for a second time .
During this time,
you must ensure
the suspect's safety.
That is up to
his own fate.
The prison of the Inspectorate
is not known
for ensuring the inmates' safety.
How dare you!
Mr. Xu,
Lady Yan,
please go back.
I wasn't planning on keeping
you and Lady Yan here today.
Don't be nervous.
However,
I must advise you,
once the Inspectorate has arrested someone,
you don't just get to
reverse the case as you want.
You'd better think carefully
about what you listen to,
what to report,
and what
to keep to yourselves.