[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP14]
Lord Commander, please.
Why are you here, exactly?
So many lanterns. So bright in here.
Over here.
Put it here.
Is this how it usually is at your place?
Far brighter.
Lord Commander, here.
Mr. Han,
on such a full moon night,
do you also think of
your family like I do?
I...
My parents died at young age.
[I have no family left.]
Once I marry Caiwei,
the Yans will be my family.
Right, right.
Parents gone,
what about your siblings?
Regarding marriage,
out of courtesy,
shouldn't you inform them?
Before the wedding,
the two families should meet.
That's right.
No need for that.
I left home to study at a young age.
I've long lost contact with my relatives.
[As long as we truly love each other,]
that's enough.
[As for formalities,]
they don't matter to me.
Is that so?
I can't help but feel
that these formalities
are quite necessary.
Even if you're truly in love,
you should still hope to
gain recognition and blessings
from each other's family and friends.
[More importantly,]
this will help you have a clear
understanding of your background
and avoid any deception.
That's true.
But actually, my marriage wasn't
hindered by such formalities.
What matters the most is that Mr. Han
is deeply devoted to my sister.
[It's getting late,]
[and a bit chilly.]
How about
we all head back to our rooms?
Yes.
We shall take our leave.
Right, right.
[Lord Commander,]
we'll head back now.
Let's go.
Mr. Han.
Should your love be sincere
and reciprocated,
[there is no need to dread openness.]
You should face the future together.
My love,
let's go.
What exactly do you want?
Why did you have to snack here
and scare everyone off?
I really didn't want it either.
Even though it had to be said,
I shouldn't have been the one to say it.
C'mon,
stop it.
You're just
willfully confusing!
It's getting late.
Let's head back.
It's so late. Do we need to go back?
[Lord Commander.]
Sir.
We've prepared a bedroom
for both of you.
Such
being the case...
I won't go back.
Please feel free to leave, my love.
What are you doing?
What?
He said that a room
has been prepared for us.
If only you stay,
how are you going to explain tomorrow?
You want to stay as well, fine.
Just put me down!
It wouldn't be proper if someone saw us.
So what?
I want them to see.
To confirm our harmonious marriage.
That way, you won't have to explain.
Hey.
Let's go to sleep.
Alright, alright.
Now that the show is over,
it's time to sleep.
Here is not like your place.
You'll have to make do tonight.
Just bear with it.
I'm someone with wounds.
Sleeping on a bamboo chair
isn't appropriate, right?
It was you who...
You look even healthier than I do.
Never mind.
You can have the bed.
If you're willing to share,
there's still half a space here.
You can sleep in there.
[If you are not,]
you could go outside
and sleep with the stars all night.
Let's leave it at that for tonight.
Just make do.
But the necessary rules
must still be followed.
No one is allowed
[to cross this line.]
I can't sleep.
I might as well go out and
share the night with the stars and moon.
Why are you coming out?
I've already given you the room.
The candles in the room are out.
It's too dark for me to sleep.
You should have someone
light the candles.
Shen Du,
it's the middle of the night,
are you trying to disturb everyone?
You weren't asleep either
when the candles were lit, right?
Tossing and turning,
it made it hard for me to sleep.
Even the candles were lit,
it's not bright enough.
Still a bit dim.
You're really quite strange.
My father even specially
lit a few more candles tonight.
You still think it's dark?
You're going to sleep,
not studying or writing.
Why does it have to be so brightly lit?
It's not like you're blind and can't see.
[Now I understand]
[why Shen Du is called White Death.]
[Look at this place,]
[it's like a mourning hall during the day.]
[At night,]
[it's still as bright as day.]
[Who brings a lantern]
[to kick some ass?]
[I can't do it without light.]
[Could it be that he's been]
[cursed with the moonless sight?]
Tonight is truly rare.
Look, the
Azure Dragon's Seven Stars in the east.
And
the Vermilion Bird's Seven Stars in the south.
You can see them all.
Look over there.
Those four stars are connected.
Do they like the four corners of a square?
Those four over there
are the Dituhe constellation.
There are four more below,
which are the Horned Serpent Stars.
[Indeed, he can't really see.]
[There are no stars at all.]
You know so much
about the names of these stars.
You're quite impressive.
What about that one over there?
Looks like a rabbit.
What's that one called?
That's called the Celestial Crow.
What about this one here?
[I think it looks like]
a flower cake.
And the one in the south,
[it looks like]
the outline of a
cherry.
It's called the Jingmu'an.
That doesn't sound nice.
Let's change its name.
I think
we should call it
Cherry Stuffed Bread.
Next to it is
the Flower Cake.
It's better, how?
Such strange names.
And they're all pastries.
You wouldn't understand,
but naming them after food is better.
When I was little, I had a poor appetite,
so my mother gave the stars in the sky
names of pastries.
[She led me to believe that the]
[stars' shine signaled more pastry eating.]
Otherwise,
that star
would never shine again.
[Today,]
[you need to eat more flower cakes.]
[Because today, the star that looks like]
[a flower cake is shining.]
[My mother said,]
[if you don't eat it,]
[that star]
[will go out.]
[Help yourself.]
What are you doing?
[Could she be]
[you?]
Sir.
What's the matter?
Mr. Han went to see
Lord Yan earlier,
saying that he's gonna say something.
[He asked me]
[to invite you both to join them.]
Okay!
We will be there.
[Lord Commander.]
No formalities.
Greetings,
Lord Commander.
[Thank you for giving me]
chance to be honest with myself.
My love,
what exactly do you want to say?
Caiwei,
[I lied to you.]
My parents still have one son living.
He's a confidant of Her Royal Highness and
serves as the Deputy Minister of Rites,
Zhang Baohuan.
Lord Zhang?
But there's one thing I don't understand.
Since you are Lord Zhang's brother,
then why doesn't he
use his resources to protect you
from the persecution of Princess Ying?
Brother?
Princess Ying, having discovered
[our relationship,]
[wished to enlist me as her courtier,]
[motivated by a wish to]
challenge the Great Grandmother.
I have repeatedly refused,
[but it's hard to escape.]
[Although we are siblings,]
he is unworthy of being my brother.
He didn't save my sister.
Sister?
The owner of Jinxiu Workshop
was your sister, Zhang Baoying?
Caiwei,
I'm sorry.
I lied to you.
[Back when the incident happened,]
[our whole family was exterminated.]
[Zhang Baohuan used his connections]
to save me.
I have always wondered,
he saved me already,
how come he couldn't save my sister?
[I hate him for not being able to save her.]
[I also hate myself for being powerless.]
[At that time,]
I made up my mind
to cut ties with the Zhang Family.
My mother's surname is Han.
I took her surname, and
changed my name to Han Shiyuan.
Your brother may also
have unavoidable difficulties.
You should know
[how difficult it is for him]
[to stay by Her Royal Highness' side.]
Serving the monarch is like serving a tiger.
You should be
well aware of this.
Without witnessing the bloodshed,
how could you possibly
understand the pain?
Don't be afraid.
I will never forget that day.
[If you were me,]
you wouldn't be able to say such things.
You're wrong.
[It's precisely 'cause they died unjustly]
that you should rely on yourself more.
You must find a way
to seek justice for them,
instead of deceiving yourself,
and severing ties with them.
Fated yet ill-fated love!
It's all fate.
Mr. Han,
[regarding your marriage with my daughter,]
please allow me to think it over.
I humbly seek your understanding.
[A small place like our place]
is too frail to face the gales.
Today, I share these thoughts,
fully aware of the consequences.
I haven't slept all night,
[and I finally realized]
[I can't continue deceiving Caiwei]
[while marrying her.]
Apologies for the disturbance
I have caused during my stay.
I respectfully
take my leave.
My love!
Caiwei!
[Caiwei...]
Mr. Han is indeed
blood of
Lord Zhang.
The Jinxiu Workshop case
involves royal affairs
and is closely related to
Her Royal Highness' inner circle.
We must act with caution.
Right.
I will be careful.
Actually,
there's one more thing.
Back in the prison,
there was a little girl
who often came to see me at midnight,
bringing me food
and news from outside.
But starting one day,
I never saw her again.
I thought I would never see
her again in this life.
But yesterday,
I seemed to have found her.
Or perhaps
someone deeply resembles her.
Many years ago,
you asked me to check
the entry and exit records of the prison.
It was to find her,
right?
But the records showed
no young girl entering or leaving.
So I couldn't help but doubt
whether this girl truly exists or if
it was just a figment of my imagination.
If she entered at night,
then most likely she
wouldn't have been recorded in the log.
That place of criminal confinement,
was also where I was confined.
Looking back now,
I still have nightmares about it.
If she dared to
enter the prison at night to care for you,
she must be a truly kind maiden.
If you truly share the fate,
and cross paths again,
you must treat her with all your heart.
If we destine to cross paths again,
there's no need for formal recognition.
Now I have become the most notorious
cruel official in the empire,
spoken of by all,
brutal and unjust,
releasing dogs to harm others.
I am ashamed to see
my childhood friends again.
"Releasing dogs to harm others?"
Are you referring to the time at Ming Hall?
If it weren't for you unleashing the dogs
to weed out the criminals,
everyone on site would
likely have perished under the arrows.
Chief Xu, though deep within the palace,
sees far and is fully aware
of the outside world.
Don't flatter me.
This incident is
well-known in Xiang'an.
It has become
another mark of shame
against your name, White Death.
Shen Du,
bearing such a notorious reputation,
do you think it's worth it?
Yan Xing!
You're overstepping your bounds again.
You still insist you haven't overstepped?
This is a classified document
sent by the Imperial Guard.
It's for your eyes only.
Originally,
the cases from the Imperial Guard
are intended for you.
But it must first be archived
and then distributed from the top down.
How could it go directly to you
without passing through me?
This matter,
you must
seriously remind the Imperial Guard about.
Alright, Lord Wu,
I will make sure to inform them.
All documents and
evidence sent over
must be reviewed and approved by you
before they can be distributed.
That sounds more like it.
What on earth is this?
A landmark code?
Grand Victory Stars?
Flower Cake Stars?
Cherry...
This must be my husband's
recent fascination
with astronomy.
While observing,
he sketched the constellations
and gifts them to the Ministry of Justice
for reference in investigations.
How peculiar.
Are these things even useful to us?
Are they?
This is the Ministry of Justice,
not the Imperial Astrology Bureau.
How absurd.
He believes we have much free time, huh?
[Without consuming pastries,]
[the stars remain shining high up.]
[It's impressive that he remembered all the]
[positions and names I rambled about.]
[Shen Du,]
[I will find a way]
[to cure your moonless sight.]
[People have clear vision during the day,]
[but at night, they cannot see.]
[This condition is called moonless sight.]
[To treat moonless sight, nourish the liver.]
These are the offal my lady requested.
They will be served to my lord as meals.
Are you cooking?
It looks more like you're casting spells.
Why is everyone gathered around?
There's nothing to see.
Back to your works.
Gujing herb.
You too, out.
Alright!
Now.
Let's get out.
Night vision grain.
My Lord.
This is the lamb's liver jelly
made by my lady for you.
Sir,
my lady has specifically instructed
that you must have a bowl of
herbal steamed chicken liver for lunch.
Lunch too?
There's no end of these, huh?
I'm not eating!
[I know why you're lighting]
[that many lamps at night.]
[If you wish to gaze the starry sky,]
[have these along with meals.]
[Otherwise,]
[read the second note.]
[If you don't want everyone in Xiang'an]
[to know White Death's secret,]
[then properly nourish yourself.]
What did you just call this
vile crap?
Sir,
listen
carefully,
it's steamed
chicken liver
with Gujing herb,
and you know,
night vision
together.
I know what Gujing herb is,
but what is this
night vision grain?
Sir,
are you sure
you want to know?
Bat droppings.
Yan...
Yan Xing!
Sir,
why don't you just skip it?
Go to the Ministry of Justice
and bring her here for me!
My Lady, please stay alert.
After Mr Shen finished the chicken liver,
his mood hasn't been normal.
I shall oversee guardsmen's training.
Stop watching!
You too!
[Yan Xing,]
if you desire to murder your husband,
just stab me clean through.
Why go through all this trouble,
making these nauseating soups?
Shen Du!
You're repaying kindness with ingratitude.
I've searched through
all the medical texts
to come up with this recipe.
Ancient medical records state
that moonless sight should be treated with
[liver-nourishing and vision-enhancing foods,]
like animal offal, and...
Not just animal organs,
but also animal feces.
What are you talking about?
Are you referring to
night vision grain?
The herbal
steamed chicken liver is
mentioned
in the "Theory of Various
Disease Sources".
Night vision grain
is the most crucial medicinal ingredient.
Chamberlain Shen
ran all over the city's pharmacies
to procure it for you.
[I steamed it all night to prepare it.]
Don't mistake my good intentions
for foolishness (it mentions liver).
Don't mention the word "liver" again!
Good medicine is bitter to the taste.
[Expressing your desperation]
like this is pointless.
I...
If you have
nothing important,
I'll head back to the office.
Chen Shoujie has been
recuperating at the healing house lately,
clear-headed now, and dazed then.
I've already brought him here.
If you want to question him,
just follow me.
Mr Chen,
could you tell me
what exactly happened?
Why do you have
the embroideries from Jinxiu Shop?
She is my concubine.
She used to work at the Shop
as an embroiderer.
She even took on apprentices.
Her skills are truly remarkable.
During the Shop incident,
she happened to be away.
Afterward, the authorities searched for
the accomplices, and she hid everywhere.
Then she ran into me.
[Impressed by her diligence and resilience,]
I chose her to be my concubine.
These embroideries
are just her way
of passing the time,
Fire!
You may retrieve
nothing more from him.
So, Mrs Chen
was an embroiderer at the Shop.
[The murderer chose to silence her,]
trying to eliminate
everyone related to the Shop.
They wanted to wipe them all out.
If so,
does this mean
there is a big secret
behind this case?
A secret so crucial that the murderer
would go to the lengths of silencing others.
But right now, it's all just speculation.
There's no evidence.
Indeed,
further investigation is needed,
and it must be
targeted.
I'm gonna
write and submit a request
to the Ministry of Justice tomorrow
to merge the case of Chen Huo'e
with that of Jinxiu Shop
for joint investigation.
That might be challenging.
[These two cases involve]
[too many people.]
I don't think they would want a resurface.
They'll do everything in their power
to obstruct the investigation.
Without trying,
how could you know the outcome?
What's going on?
Princess Ying's men are giving
Han Shiyuan a hard time,
blocking the way.
Mr. Han,
Her Highness requests your presence.
Wait!
Don't be restless.
Jing Lin!
Go find Zhang Baohuan!
[Yes, sir!]