Remember to save the circuit maintenance file at 9 o'clock tonight
Thanks
Did you kiss last night
You see the way she came out of his house
I'm drunk. I must have kissed
Maybe
Why do you have to kiss when you drink too much?
You can control yourself if you drink too much, okay
Did you see last night's update, too
We're talking about last night's update
The days of living with the boss
Isn't that what you said
Yes
Hello
All right, team leader. I'll be right up
That one last night
How dare you say last night
It can't really be
You don't remember
Is it too much
You don't think you can default on your debts by fragments
Be responsible for what
Everyone is an adult
What's the responsibility for kissing
Job number 0079 What are you talking about
I'm talking about my car wash last night
Are you not going to be responsible
Brother
These projects are prepared to be promoted by the company at the meeting
At the board meeting in 2 months
It is estimated that Liu Dong will talk about your project and experience
Thank you, brother. It's so kind to me
But
I went back to China this time because I was optimistic about a project
Decided to push it forward
Oh
I also like this project very much
It was developed by a man named Wang Wei
This boy is quite talented
I guess he is not the talented one
Our company
No need
A person who takes credit for other people's works
You won't have to come again
Go to the finance department to sign and claim the compensation
Hey, hey, help. Come and block it. Hey, me
I'll go
Would you
Waiting for me to drink plenty of water
Ouch, what meat shall I cut? You cut the back row
Do you see how the assassin across the street cut it
Why do you play in a group
My big lady
Are you lying to your wife that you are not at home again
I went on a date
What's the matter
My mother is coming to our house
Butler's supplement: My wife found out that Xu's son is still in the company
Butler's supplement: I thought you accompanied him to work overtime to Wonderland culture
Waiting, waiting, coming right away
Yulu OS: I won't do it for my boss