English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP16
You didn't sleep well, did you?
You wouldn't listen when I told you to
go home, insisting on going
to the History Archive to look for leads.
Looks like you didn't find any leads,
but you've caught a cold instead.
Don't get me started.
There were so many.
All those pages.
Those men sure can write.
Every tiny little detail
was documented!
You didn't stay up all night, did you?
I couldn't sleep anyway.
I think you should
go back to the Shen residence first.
At most,
just say a few
flattering words to Chief Shen.
Why me?
I'm just stating the facts.
I saw what happened
with my own eyes yesterday.
Maybe you really
misunderstood him
this time.
What did I misunderstand about him?
The day you were taken,
Lai Luozhi showed up quickly,
but thankfully, Chief Shen
also arrived in time.
The reason you're able to clear your name
so quickly
was all because of him.
It's only been a few days,
so many new sects
have already emerged,
all claiming they can resurrect the dead
and grant immortality.
I've already sent people to investigate,
but most of them
are constantly on the move,
mainly spreading heretical beliefs.
It's difficult to predict their next move.
The Fire Moth Sect?
This Fire Moth Sect
stands out
as the most powerful.
There's even a rumor that
their core figure is none other than
Chen Huo'e, the one who was resurrected.
Mom!
Let's go.
Wait, it's not finished yet.
Xing, what...
Mom,
what are you doing here?
I came to pray for you and your father.
Don't believe everything you hear.
Let's go.
Get away from here.
But the...
-The apparition is about to appear! -Let's go.
What's going on?
No one
is to gather here without cause.
Leave here at once!
Why are you asking us to leave?
We didn't do anything wrong.
Those who try to stop the Fire Moth Sect
will face divine retribution!
Arrest them all!
All of you
will face retribution!
You will face retribution!
Let go of me.
Let's go.
Mom,
what were you doing there?
It was so dangerous.
Keep your voice down.
I was just
praying for you and your father,
so you could live a long life
free from harm.
It's all lies.
Throw this away right...
No, don't!
There will be retribution.
The holy relic of the Fire Moth
is the embodiment of a deity
and must not be violated.
Anyone who offends it
will be tied up
in the shape of a moth
-and burned as punishment. -Mom,
where did you hear all this?
Where what?
Even children on the street know that
those who offend the Fire Moth Sect
will be burned alive!
I didn't expect that this
had already bewitched so many people.
I must investigate this thoroughly.
Mom,
if you keep getting involved in this,
it could get you killed.
Listen to me,
stay at home.
Don't go anywhere these days.
I will take this.
Wait.
Give it back.
You ungrateful daughter, give it back!
Wait, you!
Just... Just don't offend them
and don't rebut them!
So hot.
Fire!
There's a fire at the History Archive!
Fire! Fire!
Quickly!
Go get water!
Go get water quickly!
Here! Here!
Go get water!
Quickly!
Over here!
-Here! -Quickly!
Go get more!
Xing!
Quickly!
Go get water!
Shen Du!
Shen Du.
Xing.
You're awake.
You took in a lot of smoke.
Get some rest these days.
I'm sorry.
And thank you for saving me.
Get some rest now.
Don't talk too much.
Sometimes, I tend to
speak without thinking.
If I had said something offensive,
don't take it to heart.
I got it.
Do you think
the fire might have been set on purpose
to destroy
the county chronicles and records inside?
Or maybe you were the target.
Me?
Are they afraid I'll find out the truth?
I doubt we could find anyone else
bold enough like you.
What are you doing?
I got this powder at the site of the fire.
What is it exactly?
Perhaps only my master
would know what this is.
Be careful.
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
No.
I... I'm fine.
Now do you know
how dangerous it is outside?
Get some rest.
Stop running around.
Master,
we're just having tea.
Why did we have to
come all the way here?
Only here
can you find the taste you truly desire.
If you don't believe, try it.
You're not drinking tea.
You're chugging it!
Master,
this power was found at the crime scene.
It was also found
at the old site of Jinxiu Shop.
But we don't know what it is.
Don't smell it.
Interesting.
Highly flammable.
Leaves no traces.
It's not something common wizards
would use.
It might be
from a foreign land.
A foreign land?
Maybe someone at the Gui Market
will know where
this comes from.
Master,
it's really a shame for someone with
your talents to stop working on cases.
You've already mastered
nearly everything I know.
Maybe
it's time for me to step back.
At my age,
I just want some peace of mind.
Live one day at a time
and make the most of each day.
As long as I can enjoy my tea
and live at ease everyday,
I'm content.
It's hot!
You
are just too impatient.
It's the same with cases.
If you rush for results,
you are likely
to be misled
by what you see.
Misled by what you see?
That's right, master.
The evidence I have now
feels like
it was deliberately
fed to me.
Investigating
isn't just about uncovering the truth.
It's also a contest
with an unseen enemy,
to see who can
seize control of the situation first.
If
the Jinxiu Shop case back then
was meant to suppress Princess Runing,
and undermine the ties among
Her Highness, the Princess and
the influential Xiao gentry behind her,
then it's still unclear
what the person behind this is after
this time.
Stay calm.
Solving cases is like savoring tea.
It requires a lot of efforts.
Everything is like savoring tea to you.
That's exactly so.
It's also like this between a couple.
Master,
I'm talking about the case!
And I mentioned nothing else.
Discuss heroes over wine,
discuss love over tea.
The more
you savor this tea, the richer the flavor.
People are the same.
Only time reveals their true nature.
Good tea.
Such good tea!
Xing, wait!
Come here.
Didn't I
tell you to rest at the Shen residence?
Wu Taiming, that crafty old man,
was worried you'd bring bad luck
and didn't want you to come.
It's all my fault.
Ji Fangming didn't get implicated
and get scolded, did he?
He's the guardian of the History Archive,
and the place was nearly burned down.
But Wu Taiming
dared not to be angry at you.
So Ji Fangming
took all the blame.
I should think
how to apologize to him.
By the way,
from what I heard,
you were carried out by Shen Du
in front of everyone.
What else could he do?
Watch me die?
Look at you.
Like a mule,
you're so stubborn!
Look at you.
Always talk without thinking.
You have no filter.
Look at you yourself.
You've only gone back for a day,
and you're already radiant.
Let me see
what tricks the Shen residence has that
have made you
so bright-eyed!
But,
it might really be true.
I fell asleep as soon as I lay down
when I went back last night.
Perhaps it's because
I'm used to sleeping with the lights on
and the lights burning all night there?
Here, however,
I find it hard to sleep.
Sure.
I'm serious.
This is...
My savior,
to express my gratitude,
I've specially prepared
some dishes that can
help with your eye recovery.
From now on,
I will keep preparing nourishing meals
for you, my lord.
I will continue this
until your eyes are completely recovered.
Why aren't you eating?
Is the Chief of IG
a picky eater?
Or you're not hungry?
This is
all from my heart!
Don't waste the food.
I should go now.
What's the hurry, my lady?
When did you pick up
a new bad habit of
needing a company for meals?
Isn't this all from your heart?
I'll eat better
looking at you.
I said,
what's the hurry, my lady?
You're a grown man.
Do you
need someone to feed you?
This meal is truly thoughtful.
My lady,
eat.
From now on,
remember to dine with me everyday.
Will you agree?
Living under someone else's roof,
do I have any choice?
As long as you know that.
What's wrong?
You have no table manners.
That's not true.
That's not true!
What is this?
This is true harmony.
Others can only be so envious!
This must be what they mean by
thick as thieves.
I just wonder
how much longer can they keep this up.
Every debt has its own debtor.
Leave me alone!
It wasn't me. It wasn't me.
Leave me alone! Leave me alone!
Leave me alone!
My lord,
when we got here,
he was tied to the roof eaves.
We didn't want to disrupt the scene
and waited for you to decide what to do.
My Lord,
Chen Shoujie is still alive.
Fortunately, those we sent to watch him
managed to save him just in time.
However,
he seems to have been severely shocked.
He was already quite unhinged.
Now
he can't even speak
a complete sentence.
It's exactly like
what happened at Furong Theater.
Han Shiyuan and Caiwei
were also tied up and hung high,
with burning charcoal below.
But it was the cold flames
used in Western Regions' acrobatics.
Looks like
they are about to kill.
Who is it?
Not only did they want to kill him,
but also with such cruel method.
Let's go.
How did this fire happen?
It's so tragic.
Who is that?
Why is he hiding?
Jing Lin.
What's going on?
They arrested someone.
It's you.
This is Ji Fangming,
the guardian of
History Archive at the Ministry of Justice.
We still need your testimony and seal
regarding the fire at the History Archive.
I was just on my way to the Shen residence
when I saw you
hurrying here.
My Lord,
someone was burned to death east of here.
What?
Burned to death?
Who was it?
A guard from the IG,
squad leader Sun.
Him?
Do you know the Fire Moth Sect?
Fire Moth Sect?
It was Chen Huo'e
who punished this person in person.
You know,
the fire at
the Ministry of Justice a few days ago
was to punish
Mrs. Shen!
Mrs. Shen?
She almost died!
Maybe the White Death
has done so many bad deeds that
retribution has fallen upon his wife.
The wind and rain come at night,
yet one remains as steady as a clock.
Too much late-night food,
better go with a few more drinks.
Did you find out where that powder
came from like I asked you?
It's from the Western Regions.
Quite mysterious indeed.
I
have put in quite a bit of efforts
to find out.
You want to ask me for more money?
No way.
You memorized the secret code for nothing.
Did you really come here empty-handed?
You could
at least bring a couple of bottles of liquor
to reward me.
If you admit
you're the renowned
detective Pan Chi,
I might consider
treating you
to the finest osmanthus wine in Xiang'an.
I am him.
If I really were him,
would you truly
pay me
some more?
You wish.
It sounds nice just thinking about it.
You should go home now.
It's not safe at the Gui Market lately.
My Lord,
you've asked me to look into
Ji Fangming from the Ministry of Justice.
I found out that
he has written
a prescription for himself.
He was sick?
I didn't know that
he has some medical knowledge.
We followed him for a few days
and found that
his health is quite poor,
most likely a chronic illness.
Give this prescription to the pharmacy.
I want to see
just what kind of illness does he have.
Are you suspecting him, my lord?
The fire at the History Archive
was too much of a coincidence.
Chief Shen must be busy.
I'm just here to ask
what kind of tea does he want.
There's no need.
Miss Yun Que, please go back.
Did you find anything about
the Jinxiu Shop case?
Don't worry, Miss.
When it's necessary,
Chief Shen will tell you.
I got it.
This powder
was ground from a plant
unique to the Western Regions.
When burned,
they release a distinctive aroma
that can cause those who smell it
to feel unusually excited
or even hallucinate.
It is said
that if someone
gives some subtle hints,
people who smell the powder
might experience
the same hallucinations.
Is there someone
selling this at the Gui Market?
No.
I heard this plant
is very common in the Western Regions,
but it is difficult
for it to survive
outside its specific soil.
So, to maintain
its strong
hallucinogenic effects,
the powder
cannot be stored for too long.
Could it be
that someone has managed to cultivate
this plant secretly in the capital?
Is this information true?
My friend, Pan Chi,
from the Gui Market told me this.
His information wouldn't be wrong.
Did you know Ji Fangming was sick?
Only focused on some friend, you've
overlooked the clues in front of you.
At Chen Shoujie's residence,
his appearance and reaction
were indeed very suspicious.
The others were all curious
about what had happened,
but he was more interested in
our reaction to what we had seen.
That's right.
I also remember
smelling a faint scent
on Ji Fangming once.
I didn't pay much attention at the time.
Thinking back,
that scent was very familiar
but is quite rare.
I've only smelled it in one place before.
Mingsheng Temple.
He's been to Mingsheng Temple?
I asked Chuichui
to look into Ji Fangming's background
and gather some information
on him.
He got into the Ministry of Justice
through someone's recommendation.
Guess who it was?
Was it...
Yes.
It was Chen Shoujie.
But besides that,
his past was quite clean.
We didn't find anything suspicious.
The cleaner the more suspicious it is.
There must be more to it.
Chen Shoujie had
done him a favor and recommended him,
but the other day at the crime scene,
he pretended not to know him.
Chen Shoujie recommended him?
But I have checked and found
that they have no connection whatsoever.
So that means,
there must be a mediator
that connects the both of them
that we have not
found yet.
Looks like
I'll have to ask them myself.
Ji Fangming,
here.
Ms. Yan,
this is?
Finally, no more dealing
with those fragmented records.
So...
you found the culprit?
Yes, we did.
Chen Shoujie
was behind all these cases.
He was pretending to be dumb,
misleading everyone.
But,
he was just talking nonsense.
What?
He confessed?
Yeah!
Don't you know who my husband is?
He's the one people call the White Death.
Chen Shoujie
confessed everything within a day.
He was playing dumb?
How could it be possible?
Why isn't it possible?
It was him
who deliberately hid crucial evidence
in the Jinxiu Shop case,
causing so many innocent deaths.
He was bribed
with a thousand taels of gold
and he buried them in his own yard.
It took
several hours
to dig up the taels.
I never thought,
truly never thought
he would hide it this well.
Yeah.
If it weren't for my husband's sharp eyes,
we would still be deceived.
Is he still being held
at the IG?
He's in the prison of the Ministry of Justice.
The execution
will be carried out in secret tomorrow.
Carried out in secret?
Why?
It's the officials' order.
There might be
more to this case
than meets the eye.
If Princess Runing
was truly wrongfully accused
and confined at Mingsheng Temple,
then the Jinxiu Shop
was merely
a pretext
to frame the princess.
What?
You are saying that
all those lives at the Jinxiu Shop
were only...
You can't say that out loud.
That's why
we had to stop the investigation.
It's all my fault.
Who made you to kill over a
dozen people at the Jinxiu Shop?
Still playing dumb?
Today, you'll face your own death!
You're not Chen Shoujie?
Those who offend the Fire Moth
will suffer the Fire Moth's punishment!
Ji Fangming,
it's really you.
You said those things
to me on purpose to lure me here.
You've had many chances
to kill Chen Shoujie,
but you didn't.
So we figured,
maybe what the culprit wanted
was not for Chen Shoujie to die,
but to torture him.
No one wants him to be lucid
more than the culprit,
so the torture
will be more satisfying.
Ji Fangming,
now that we have all the evidence,
do you have anything else to say?
I'm not the culprit.
And I don't know
how did I end up here.
Maybe I was misled by someone,
and came here unconsciously.
My lord, my lady,
you've seen
such things before.
Surely you can understand.
I have no reason
to kill Chen Shoujie.
It was for Kong Xianrong, the owner of
the Jinxiu Shop, wasn't it?
It's been so many years,
and few dare to mention the names of those
involved in the Jinxiu Shop case.
I never expected
someone still remembered his name.
You burned down the
History Archive at the Ministry of Justice
not just to harm me,
but to
destroy everything there,
to erase any traces
showing you,
Chen Shoujie, and Jinxiu Fang's owner,
Kong Xianrong,
knew each other.
Clerk Yan,
are you going to
convict me just based on this?
So you admit?
Xianrong and I met first.
We made our acquaintance
for avoiding rain in a teahouse.
Xianrong was eloquent
and talented.
We hit it off right away
and had a great conversation.
And soon we became close friends.
After I failed the exams,
he introduced me
to Chen Shoujie,
allowing me to become an official.
Yet,
as fate would have it,
Jinxiu Shop was wrongly accused
and Xianrong's whole family was killed.
I stood in the crowd,
watching them die.
The blood was flowing like a river.
How did you know
Kong Xianrong was framed?
Over the years,
I went through every county record
and criminal case file.
And it finally paid off.
I finally found
a lead.
Xianrong saw Chen Shoujie as a brother,
but Chen Shoujie
betrayed this trust
for his own interests.
So,
you killed his wife
and went to great lengths
to torture Chen Shoujie?
She deserved to die!
His wife deserved to die!
Chen Shoujie even more so!
Was the murder of
squad leader Sun
your doing?
What does his death
have to do with me?
Then who taught you to impersonate
Chen Huo'e and commit these crimes?
Like a moth to a flame,
here today and gone tomorrow,
escaping the cycle of reincarnation,
yet immortal forever and ever.
Take Ji Fangming to the dungeon
and await further orders.
I avenged the
innocent people at Jinxiu Shop.
I didn't do anything wrong!
Chen Shoujie deserves to die! To die!
Is the food not good today?
Why are you not talking?
Provoking Ji Fangming
was a very reckless move.
If anything happens...
But I got him to confess, didn't I?
Sometimes,
simple and direct methods
work best.
The rest
is up to how you,
the chief of IG,
will conduct the interrogation.
I'm afraid this is not that easy.
Ji Fangming is already in custody.
If we find enough evidence to convict him,
can the case be closed?
If Ji Fangming was
indeed behind all of it,
then closing the case
would be fine.
But there's a thing
that doesn't seem right.
In what way?
The deification of the Fire Moth Sect
is going faster
than we thought.
Someone deliberately committed a crime
in the east of the city
at the same time
when Ji Fangming tried to kill Chen Shoujie
shows a total lack of concern.
The Fire Moth Sect.
Could the one behind it
really be
Chen Huo'e, who was resurrected?
Your cooking skills
haven't improved at all.
But after a while,
it doesn't taste so bad anymore.
Even if my skills haven't improved,
your appetite has grown.
That's what counts.
The man you caught
was avenging the Jinxiu Shop case?
I risked my life to get the
evidence about the Jinxiu Shop,
so I want to
go with you too to the interrogation.
Ji Fangming,
you killed
Chen Shoujie's wife,
and are arrested
while trying to
murder Chen Shoujie.
What had really happened,
and who else were you working with?
Confess truthfully.
Such an imposing presence, my lord.
I've seen plenty of this posturing
at the Ministry of Justice over the years.
This doesn't work on me.
Ji Fangming!
At this point, just be honest and confess.
Don't try these useless tricks.
If you wouldn't say it here,
then we'll take you to the IG.
I have plenty of methods to make you talk.
My lord, so you're going to
force a confession through torture?
Chancellor Lai, you're just in time.
It's better to be timely than early.
If I hadn't come,
how could I have witnessed
such a display of authority of yours?
This case has been fully entrusted
by Her Highness to the IG.
I will handle this matter properly.
You just stay aside and observe.
Don't cause any trouble.
Or you'll be charged with
obstructing the investigation.