English subtitles are available
Just in Time EP05
Let's get a divorce.
Wanzhen, we...
Can we not joke about this?
Yeah, I came with a colleague today
to check out some houses.
But
I had no idea
how did we end up here.
She dragged me along.
She said she wanted my advice.
You know,
I'm really into buying houses,
right?
I've bought so many houses.
Keep making things up.
No, seriously,
I'm being wronged!
I really just came with her.
I don't care if it's a misunderstanding.
I want a divorce.
Did you hear me clearly?
No, no, Wanzhen.
We've been married for ten years,
and we've never
mentioned divorce.
This is the first time you've said it.
Where's your wedding ring?
You usually
don't wear it either, do you?
No, I just find it
uncomfortable to wear,
but you always wear yours.
Yu Hai,
in the past ten years of our marriage,
I haven't
brought up divorce, right?
This is the first
and last time.
This isn't a warning,
it's my decision.
This marriage,
I'm determined to end it.
Wanzhen,
We, the two of us...
we built everything
from scratch together.
And our child is only eight years old.
What are you trying to do?
Wait, is it because
of what happened with your mom?
How about
we see a therapist?
What the hell do you want?
Why do you keep calling me?
Yeah.
I forgot
about the dinner with Mr. Zhang.
Okay, got it.
Wanzhen,
well...
I have to go to dinner
with someone tonight.
A very important investor.
If I don't drink too much tonight,
I'll definitely come home, okay?
Let's talk properly at home tonight.
Alright?
You quit your job first, okay?
I'm leaving now.
See?
They've set up tents, right?
Can we negotiate
the price again?
My car
has never been in an accident,
and it's regularly maintained.
Sure.
Okay.
Then give me a call
when you're free
or I can drive it over.
Alright?
There's a puppy.
So cute!
Alright, alright.
Thank you.
Let's keep in touch.
Where are the things?
She didn't let me take them.
Why?
Ask her.
It's been half a year,
and we're only camping once.
Do we really need to unpack everything?
I wanted to sell them online
for a good price.
These are enough.
Why sell them?
We bought those tents and chairs
for camping, didn't we?
Yeah,
look,
see all those around us.
Every family has a tent, right?
If we lie here without one,
don't you think
we're a bit out of place?
I think it's fine.
Are you upset today?
I'm happy.
Really happy?
Really happy.
How else should I show it?
So nice.
The sun is out.
Block it a bit.
No need.
Maybe I should
rent a tent
and get a lounge chair or something.
No need, it's not that sunny today.
Do you want some barbecue?
Ask your dad to rent a grill.
How's that?
Then...
Just lying like this
counts as camping?
Feels too basic.
Let's play a game.
It sounds good.
Sure, sure, sure.
What do we play?
Truth.
Truth?
How to?
I know.
Truth or dare, right?
They go together.
Yes, but this
has no dares.
Wait, how do you know?
When I'm out with Mr. Zhang for business,
sometimes we need
to liven up the mood.
Not good.
Just know a bit.
Quick, tell your dad
how to play.
Truth is like this,
we play Rock-Paper-Scissors.
and the loser
has to answer a question.
It must be the truth.
Wanna play?
Sure.
Come on.
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
See?
Perfect match.
Here we go.
Oh, I see.
You ask, okay?
No getting mad.
I'll ask.
No getting mad!
You and Liu Siming...
Since Liu Siming joined your class,
has he affected
your studies?
I knew you were going to ask that.
You promised not to get mad.
I'm ready for this.
Why would I get mad?
Actually, I know what you're
worried about.
It's just about puppy love
affecting studies, right?
Don't worry.
I didn't do well on this exam
because
I haven't been studying well lately,
it has nothing to do
with puppy love.
So, you and Liu Siming...
Next question, okay?
Honey.
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
You and Liu Siming...
Liu Siming is just like a husky.
Chased by a husky?
I'd rather hide myself.
This is pretty much what I expected.
Back when you were in school,
did you have someone chasing you too?
And
did you
find it romantic?
No.
It was all just trouble.
Everything was out of sync.
And I was overly scrutinized.
No way.
I'm different from your aunt.
She really enjoys
being chased.
You know,
that's so great!
Amazing!
So, how did you handle it?
I didn't need to handle it.
Just let him chase.
If you ignore him,
in two or three months,
he'll move on to someone else.
Take note.
Learn from that.
That guy was not as handsome as my dad.
Of course.
Your dad
is incredibly handsome.
Come on, let's continue.
Come on.
Let's go.
Continue.
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Oh my.
Alright, Dad, let me ask you.
I choose Dare.
No way.
You know how to play too?
Didn't you just say so?
Really?
Why don't I believe it?
Ask him,
Sweetie.
Okay.
Truth.
Did you lose your job?
Your dad
had a temporary issue at work.
I guessed it.
Dad,
I believe in you.
You're so capable,
you'll
find a new job soon.
Don't worry.
Plus, with such a handsome dad,
you could be an actor.
Let's continue!
Come on.
Again?
Come on, come on.
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Alright, Ms. Xu Meng'an,
I've got a question for you.
Do you want to sell
our family car?
How do you know everything?
How did you find out?
I'm also part of the family, you know.
Some things,
even if you don't tell me,
I still find out.
Listen,
Ms. Xu Meng'an,
the car cannot be sold.
It's part of your
CEO image.
Unless
you sell it to buy a better one.
What's up with you two?
Why don't you look excited?
Excited, sure.
Excited.
Alright.
Let me share a secret with you.
My secret, okay?
What secret?
I've mastered a special skill.
I can mimic both your signatures.
They're almost
indistinguishable from yours.
Even teachers can't tell.
Have you signed?
How many times?
Any failed papers?
The teacher didn't notice?
There are big bubbles.
Let me take a look.
In calligraphy,
this is called copying.
It's part of the process.
Our girl has grown up.
She knows how to comfort us now.
Haowen,
what do you mean?
You didn't come to the check-up today.
Do you really
want the baby?
Honey, honey,
I'm sorry.
The new product launch at the company
is starting soon.
Look.
Mr. Jia.
It's so lively.
Mr. Jia,
they're selecting products over there.
Are you coming?
I'll be right there. You go ahead.
Hand out some benefits to the customers.
Go ahead.
I'll join you soon.
Okay, okay.
Xin,
It's starting soon.
I'm going over now.
Wait.
Who is that woman?
A collaborating influencer
invited by the company.
An influencer?
How come I didn't know?
Honey, I'll make sure
to inform you immediately next time.
Be good.
Check the trunk.
There's a secret.
A surprise for you
Don't try to fool me with this.
Always trying to distract me with stuff.
I don't care.
I wouldn't dare, honey.
I'm hanging up now.
What are you filming?
Mrs. Jia,
hello, hello.
How do you know I'm Mrs. Jia?
I know everyone
in this neighborhood.
It's unethical
to take candid photos.
I'm just following.
Following, you know.
Mrs. Jia, if you need
anything followed,
you can contact me.
I'm not into that kind of thing.
I mean,
if you
is curious
about your husband's whereabouts,
you can add me on WeChat.
I don't need it.
Keep it anyway.
It might come in handy.
It's delicious.
I was just wondering
what to have for lunch.
And then you brought it to me.
Such a great bestie!
Of course!
If your place were closer to our office,
that'd be great.
I could come over
for meals every day.
Nice wish.
I still have to work.
By the way,
how's your work going?
Are you adjusting well?
Pretty good!
Even though I do some
tedious tasks every day,
I feel fulfilled.
After being away from work for so long,
I have to start from the bottom.
Anyone bullies you?
No.
Everyone's been nice to me.
That's a relief.
Does Yu Hai know?
Yes.
He took Huang Sisi
to look at houses that day.
And he even
made a scene with me
How dare he!
He's been house-hunting with Huang Sisi
and still causes trouble with you?
What does he want?
He's gotten so full of himself.
It must be
suffocating for you.
Did you do it on purpose?
What do you mean?
I was just out for a meal,
and you sent the project plan
with the base price
to the client group.
What were you trying to do?
Director Xu,
I didn't know that.
I can't retract it now.
Do you know
the whole company is waiting for it
to get paid next month?
Director Xu, I'm really sorry.
I won't make the mistake again.
Again?
Rachel will make sure
you remember this forever.
Mu,
sort out the resources
and come to my office.
Sit down.
Yes.
We'll increase service items
within the cooperation framework.
Or how about
we offer you a new proposal?
Is that okay?
Alright, thank you!
Goodbye.
Adding services items
and extending service time.
Isn't that just a loss?
Take an extra shift
to make a new proposal.
You follow up
on this project.
Put aside profits for now,
focus on retaining the client first.
What about Yu?
Ignore him!
He's upset
because he wasn't laid off?
How could I make
such a rookie mistake?
What should we do?
Since this has happened,
don't dwell on it.
Let's think together
about how to resolve the issue.
Think about it.
How about
I'll pay for it.
How much do you make a month?
Can you afford it?
The company is laying people off now.
And I make such a rookie mistake
at this critical moment,
I'll definitely get laid off.
It's so hard to find a job right now.
If I get laid off,
how will I pay rent next month?
Mu,
how about
you go talk to Director Xu again?
If it wasn't for the layoffs,
short-staffed and overloaded,
Yu wouldn't have
made such a rookie mistake.
Let's wait for the result.
Director Xu
has already gone to talk to Rachel.
Went to Rachel?
It's over.
I'm definitely getting fired.
Director Xu said Rachel
will make I remember this forever.
I'm doomed.
Yu, don't be like this.
Let's wait for the result, okay?
It might not be you.
So,
no bonus this month,
right?
Forget the bonus for now.
I came to see you
mainly because I think
this matter
deserves a penalty,
but can you make it a lighter one?
No way!
I lost my bonus,
yet you want me to go easy?
The stuff you sent
can make up my bonus?
If you go hard on him,
we'll lose another person!
We just had layoffs
and we're short-staffed.
If you kick out another one,
forget the bonus next month,
as we might not even get paid.
It's not up to me.
You're in charge of HR.
How could it not be your call?
I only handle the result.
Regardless of Yu's mistake now.
The loss he caused
is up to Mr. Zhou to calculate.
If Mr. Zhou knows,
Mr. Zhang must know too.
You know it well,
he's not on our side.
Why don't you talk to Mr. Zhou?
Better forget it.
Anyway, no matter what,
when it gets to you,
make sure to keep my people.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
Your health report.
It's been here for two months.
And you didn't come to get it.
I really forgot.
These checkups
are just formalities, right?
A formality still takes blood.
The calories are a bit high.
What's wrong?
It says I have a hormonal imbalance.
I really didn't get my period this month.
Could it be menopause?
Or a second pregnancy?
Menopause sounds better.
Let me tell you,
It's early menopause.
What's early menopause?
Look it up yourself.
This looks good.
That's fine too.
Hey, aren't you giving them to me?
Stingy.
Insomnia.
Of course.
Night sweats.
Night sweats?
Nope.
Anxiety, definitely.
Irritability.
Absolutely.
Who isn't irritable at such an age?
Scientific term.
Menopause.
Menopause?
What day last month?
Milk.
I don't drink it.
What day?
What are you reading?
Menopause?
Why are you reading about menopause?
How could you
be going through menopause now?
Don't touch me.
So annoying.
Got your period?
I'm checking for menopause.
And you're asking about my period?
Are you doing this on purpose?
Guess you don't care me anymore.
Let me tell you,
if my days
are over,
so are your good days.
Throwing a fit?
What's going on? Let me see.
Everything looks fine.
Where did you go?
I went to buy medicine.
So hurtful.
Hurtful?
Hurt who?
I just got diagnosed with early menopause,
and you went to buy me medicine.
Let me tell you, Li Lin,
even if I am going through menopause,
only a doctor can prescribe my medicine.
Not you buying it randomly.
No, I didn't buy randomly.
And it's not
menopause medicine.
You vomited,
you might've overeaten.
Try some digestive tablets.
If it gets worse,
it might be poor digestive motility.
Try Motilium to help.
When you were brushing your teeth,
you gagged.
80% chance
it's pharyngitis.
Try some pharyngitis tablets.
At worst,
it could be pregnancy.
Take a test.
I just found out I'm in menopause
and you're telling me it's pregnancy?
Mocking me?
No, I'm not.
The health report
doesn't say anything about you.
Don't
dig yourself into a hole.
You mean I'm being dramatic.
Don't act like you're in menopause,
okay?
Act?
No.
No, no.
I'm in menopause.
Get away.
Meng'an,
I...
Get away!
Okay, okay, move aside.
Those who go through menopause
have their husbands care.
I'm in menopause now,
and you said I'm acting.
Do I need to do that?
Okay, okay.
I'll comfort you.
I'm here to comfort you.
Get away from me.
Meng'an
Get away!
I'm trying to comfort you.
Back off.
Alright, alright.
I'm leaving now.
I'm rolling to you.
Hey, stop!
What are you doing?
Alright, you're
not in menopause.
Besides,
our married life
is pretty harmonious.
Just shut up!
Okay, I'll be quiet.
What have I done to deserve this?
Congratulations!
You're pregnant!
I guessed it!
Let's start with an ultrasound
to check it out.
There's already a heartbeat.
Look.
Right here.
Well.
Can I still have a baby?
Why not?
Don't you want it?
It
was unexpected.
Getting pregnant now
shows you're in great health!
Let me tell you,
a lot of people these days
have to go through IVF,
and it's a struggle for them to conceive.
But you got pregnant naturally!
At your age,
it's kind of like the last chance.
Go home and talk it over
with your husband.
Think about it carefully.
Hello?
Yunjie is almost done with class here.
Where are you?
Well,
I... I'm still at the hospital.
I still have to
go back to the office for overtime.
You take her to my parents first.
What did the doctor say?
Just
a common issue.
We'll talk about it at home.
I told you,
it's definitely not menopause.
You're just overworked.
Later, let
brother-in-law
prescribe some herbal medicine for you.
No, no, no need.
By the way,
did you tell the teacher
about stopping Yunjie's piano lessons?
Not yet.
Make sure to tell them.
Okay.
Yunjie,
for this piece,
we need to handle the staccato
and legato properly.
Practice it more
when you get home.
Mr. Li,
Yunjie played
very well today.
Just keep practicing
at home
and she'll be ready
for the exam.
Ms. Huang,
I'd like to finish the lessons
for this month
and then stop for a while.
I'm in my third year of middle school,
and I don't have time to practice.
So, you're not signing up for this exam?
That's right.
Yunjie,
who told you to stop classes?
Playing the piano is
something you love!
You shouldn't give it up!
I'm not giving up.
I just don't want to take the exam.
Besides,
I'm not going professional,
I can just play at home
for fun.
I'm in my final year of middle school,
and I don't have much time for it.
How about
after my high school entrance exams,
I'll come back for lessons if I have time?
That's really a pity.
We've prepared for so long.
Mr. Li,
is this
your family's decision too?
Thank you.
Your yard
is really nice.
Really?
This yard is
much bigger than before, isn't it?
Of course.
See
our old house?
After living there for so long,
we got attached and didn't want to move.
So my second daughter and her husband
bought this yard as well.
After connecting them, it's bigger.
That's true.
Your second daughter
bought herself a villa
and got you a house too?
I'm so jealous.
You raised two great daughters
and got two good sons-in-law.
Lining,
I remember
at your younger daughter's wedding,
I always thought
she's so pretty
but married
such an ordinary guy.
Turns out he's wealthy!
That's not fair.
Let me tell you,
when Mengxin got married,
my second son-in-law
had nothing.
No looks,
no money, no education.
But my
elder son-in-law was a graduate.
After Mengxin got married,
they two worked hard together,
and their life just
kept getting better.
I've realized
my daughter brings luck to her husband.
Oh, that's true!
Yes, yes, brings luck!
Mom, Dad.
Look, here they come!
Auntie.
So many people! Go ahead and chat.
Alright.
Mom,
I'm not eating at home.
I have a meeting later.
Mengxin bought all of them.
Hello, Aunties.
There's more in the car. I'll get them.
Share with you all.
Great, thanks!
I'll go get it.
See, my son-in-law,
whenever he comes back,
never comes empty-handed.
Always with big and small packs,
and
always well prepared!
You're really living the life!
I'm so envious.
We're just an ordinary family.
Oh, come on.
Yunjie,
when you see your grandparents,
don't mention anything
about our family.
Because
it won't solve anything
but only make them worry, right?
Okay, got it.
Don't worry.
Good girl.
Auntie's here!
Lin,
what a coincidence!
Quick,
give me a hand.
I bought these.
You bought them all.
I can't carry so much, Lin.
Come on, help me out.
So much stuff!
How much did you buy?
What do you mean by that?
I bought these.
And you bought those.
I brought some wine.
Enjoy a couple of drinks
with Dad at lunch.
Wait, it's too much.
I can't carry it all, Lin.
You sure know how to show off.
I bought these.
And you bought those.
All from you, Lin.
Don't say anything like
I bought them all.
Mom.
Lin is here.
You're here.
Where is Meng'an?
She's working overtime today.
Lin, you came just in time.
I was about to ask,
when are you moving
into that riverside apartment?
I'm off.
It'll be ready in six months.
You know?
The riverside apartment he bought
is gorgeous!
And it's close to here,
just a five-minute walk.
If I bring hot soup over,
it won't even get cold.
That's great.
Lining,
you're so lucky.
Not like me.
I still have to pay for my son's house.
Having daughters is better.
Yeah.
two daughters,
one pays,
one helps.
What a happy life!
Exactly.
Why are you standing up?
Sit down, come on.
I'm a busy bee.
I still have to go home
and cook for the kids.
See you.
I wouldn't dare to keep you.
Are you all leaving?
Yes, we're going.
Come visit again.
Sure thing.
Wait, wait!
My son-in-law brought you some gifts.
Just a token, take it.
No, no, thanks.
I'm telling you,
the riverside apartment he bought
is just across from the bus stop.
You can see it clearly.
It's really nice.
I have a good eye for it.
The size is just perfect.
Take another turn and look.
Stop.
Your hair
doesn't quite fit.
Your hair is so black and shiny,
so smooth and thick.
Your phone looks old.
I'll get you a new one.
How about that?
No need.
I can't bring it to school anyway.
I can only use it at home after school.
Then I'll buy you a tablet.
You can use this, right?
I already have one.
Yours is old.
I'll get you the latest model.
It's got a huge screen.
For watching movies,
drawing,
and doing homework,
it's really convenient.
How about it?
No need.
Then I'll trade you my piano.
I'm not planning to learn it anymore.
Why?
Piano lessons are too expensive.
Each class costs 400 to 500.
So what?
You've been learning for years.
I have the high school entrance exams,
and Piano won't give me extra points.
Xiongxiong can learn.
He's at the perfect age
for it.
So,
Xiongxiong,
come on, say thank you to your sister.
She's giving you the piano!
Sis, please!
I don't want to learn piano!
Here, this is for you.
Keep the piano for yourself.
Naughty kid!
Don't mind him
He's not cut out for the piano anyway.
Seen anything you like lately?
I'll buy it for you.
No need.
You know what?
I've been selling stuff online lately.
Selling things?
Things you don't need can be sold,
and you can buy too.
It's quite a deal.
I've swapped for some good stuff.
Are you short of pocket money?
Tell me,
and I'll give you some.
No.
We have too much stuff at home.
So I sell them online.
Does your mom
know about this?
Of course.
Auntie,
do you have anything to sell?
I can
help you sell it.
No, I' m not selling anything.
I couldn't part
with my treasures.
At first, I was reluctant too,
but then I thought,
if I can help my mom make some money,
I'm happy.
I'll show you.
These are all things I've swapped.
See for yourself.
Mr. Xiao,
are you satisfied
with our new proposal?
I can assure you,
within the provided budget,
we will
offer you the most comprehensive
digital marketing services.
This price
is a bit surprising.
With this quote,
how much did you use
to earn from us?
Not really.
You know
how the market is nowadays.
Even our suppliers have cut prices,
so we can't
overcharge you.
Don't you agree?
Alright, Meng'an,
let's go with this new proposal.
In the future,
our products should follow this pricing.
We'll see then.
If prices go up,
we can't do business
with you at a loss,
right?
Alright, that's settled.
Meeting adjourned.
Okay,
goodbye.
If it weren't for you,
we wouldn't need to work extra hours.
And I wouldn't have to lie to people.
Now Mu is in charge
of this project,
so learn from him
and don't make such mistakes again.
It's not about getting credit,
it's about not making mistakes,
especially such basic ones.
Got it?
This is too short, isn't it?
Not at all.
With this batwing sleeve design,
if you think it's too short...
It shows the waist.
Wear a high-waisted skirt
or pants underneath.
That'll cover it up.
But does your mom even have a waist
for that high-waisted skirt or pants?
This design looks nice.
See the batwing sleeves?
And the color
makes your skin look so fair and youthful.
It's great.
Yeah, yeah, the color is youthful,
but your mom is old.
Old?
Are you kidding?
Not old at all.
This one, you'll surely like.
It's pleated,
see?
It's a bit longer.
This can go with anything.
Black or white, you name it.
Right?
This one's okay.
Long enough.
Only care about the length.
Check them out later.
I bought you so many.
You can mix and match them yourself,
okay?
Alright.
But you're
spending money too recklessly.
Bought so much stuff.
Buying things for you
isn't wasting money at all.
Spending money is how you make money.
Alright, alright.
Everything you bought looks great.
Let me ask you something.
How much did my sister borrow
for that house they bought?
I heard they borrowed a lot.
She's paying back
tens of thousands each month.
You see,
now she works overtime every weekend.
It's too much pressure.
Did something happen
with them?
Do you know?
No, I don't.
But I saw Yunjie
selling stuff
on a phone app.
Selling their home stuff,
I feel like something's not right.
Wait,
selling their home stuff?
You remind me something.
You know, Lin
used to be so busy with work,
he often had no time to pick up Yunjie,
and he'd ask me and your dad
to pick her.
But it's been a while.
He doesn't need us to pick her up anymore.
He goes to pick up the kid from school
in the afternoon.
Also,
once your dad said
he saw him
at the supermarket
fighting over discounted groceries.
So your dad thought
to check
if something was up.
He didn't say anything.
And you see,
they two don't say anything.
We don't want to pry.
Then I'll ask my sister.
Don't go.
You know
how your sister is.
She's quite touchy about her pride.
Your dad and I
decided
that regardless of what's going on,
we'll support her.
So how do we support her?
Flip it.
Go ahead.
Guess the lid.
Why guess the lid?
We have to guess it.
We need to know who goes first.
How many rounds and wins?
Just one round, done.
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
I'll go first.
Let's settle the rules first, Dad.
The flag can only be carried by sappers.
You novice.
You think you can
beat an old hand like me?
Come on.
Let's go.
What's the point of all this talk?
Look.
Heavenly fire burns the ice cellar.
Blow up your commander.
I have such bad luck.
I died as soon as I flipped.
Bad luck.
How much are eggs per catty
at the supermarket now?
The cheapest
5.98.
How much?
I bought them more expensive.
They were over 7.
You must have gone at the wrong time.
What's the right time?
When the supermarket opens
in the morning.
At 9:00 AM.
Dad, let me tell you,
from 9:00 AM to 9:30 AM,
just half an hour.
That's when it's 5.98.
A special offer.
So?
I went too late.
I... I...
I didn't know before.
It was
just a coincidence.
I was passing by the supermarket
on my way to work.
That's how I knew
it was 5.98.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have known.
How's your business
going
with your boss?
Not bad.
Opened the market?
It's ongoing.
Wait.
Aren't you in research?
Why are you dealing with the market?
Well,
Dad,
didn't I tell you that day?
The boss asked me to handle it,
so I had to do it.
They said getting familiar with the market
would help with the business.
What about the design part?
Don't you care?
I do care.
Of course.