English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP20
Let me take it.
You're quite perceptive.
Let's take a look at that.
It's really fascinating.
They have fortune sticks here.
Let's draw a fortune stick.
Steer clear of the supernatural.
You're already at the Mingsheng Temple,
so take your foot out of your mouth.
Let's go.
24.
Try it.
Me?
It's 24 again.
That's not right.
I must have inserted it incorrectly.
One more time.
Another 24!
Emm...
Alright.
Since we got multiple 24s,
let's see what
24 reveals.
Over there.
24...
In the past life, there was a connection.
And now, the fortune has come.
What does this mean?
How come there isn't anyone here
to interpret the fortune?
This isn't right.
This one must be ineffective.
I think it's quite accurate.
"Steer clear of the supernatural."
Fate.
Isn't this quite accurate?
Chui!
Are you interested in me?
Ignore her nonsense!
Mr. Xu,
In my heart,
you truly are different from the others.
That's because
you've never disrespected women
in law enforcement
like the rest of the officials.
I've come to
see you
as a big brother
because of your
sincere assistance.
But it's purely out of respect,
with absolutely no other intentions.
I knew it!
Good, that's good!
You see,
if
you don't mind, and are
willing to recognize me as a brother,
then I would be genuinely delighted!
Brother!
Good, my sister!
Since that's settled,
let's make it official today
in front of the
Mingsheng Temple.
From now on,
we'll be sworn siblings.
You should have this command token.
Holding this token
gives you authority over all the Delinquent
in the domains you traverse.
This is unthinkable.
This is your token
as the Chief Inspector.
I wield authority
over all the Delinquent in the realm,
and it's not due to this piece of iron.
Here, take it.
No, I can't accept this.
It's fine, just take it.
In times of peril,
it might save your life.
I really appreciate it.
That's more like it!
Now, I'll take my leave.
Alright, my sister.
You're not even considering Chief Xu?
Yun Que, you should
learn some good qualities from Chui,
not just the eccentric ones.
You're quite strange.
It's understandable that you are not
interested in The White Death.
Chief Xu is chivalrous and bold,
full of passion and heroism.
Shouldn't he be the hero
in every woman's dreams?
How come you are not attracted to him?
Yan Xing,
do you have a
screw loose?
What the...
The way you are acting now
seems just like
when you criticized me
for not liking Shen Du.
Could it be
that you have feelings for Chief Xu?
Is there a problem with that?
He once saved my life.
Besides,
he is so manly.
He faces his doubts head-on,
asking directly and honestly,
without a trace of jealousy or suspicion,
in stark contrast to men who
keep their feelings to themselves, giving
the impression they're always scheming.
Your preferences change
rather fast.
Anyway,
Chief Xu is my ideal partner,
handsome and charming.
Fortunately, you're not competing with me,
so I don't have to share
the same husband with you anymore.
We shouldn't have to share anyway.
I've made my decision.
What's that?
I'm leaving the Shen residence.
I've had enough of that
moody The White Death.
I want to join forces with Chief Xu
and become a chivalrous
the female Delinquent.
Wonderful!
I fully support you.
If Chief Xu doesn't take you in, I'll join
you in a silent protest at his door.
Long live the sisterhood!
Girls, huh?
Where's Jiang Langxing?
He's too uptight.
Too dull for me.
I shook him off on the way.
This serpent lady is breathtaking.
So gorgeous!
Why are there so many people here?
It's not even the main hall.
Xing?
Lady Lu?
What are you doing in here?
Pan?
Lu Chuichui.
How many are there on your list?
How many people did you plan to bring?
I didn't invite him.
What's the issue?
Shouldn't I be here?
This place is so lively!
I'm Pan Chi, alright?
Joining the fun is in my blood.
Are you also here for the serpent lady?
- Serpent lady? - Serpent lady?
Pan, are you Alright?
I'm fine.
Fine...
Stop hiding!
I saw you already!
My lady,
I...
Jing Lin?
Why are you here?
I...
I'm here to watch over my lady
on Lord Shen's behalf,
in case someone has ulterior motives.
Who are you referring to?
You're asking who I'm referring to?
It's the very person you have in mind!
Shen Du sent you to follow me, right?
Is he alright?
He is not.
He is definitely not alright.
My lady,
during your absence from the residence,
Lord Shen has
lost all appetite for tea
and food,
and has visibly
slimmed down.
She's only been away for a short while.
How could he have lost weight?
Not only has he lost weight,
he's also looking quite worn out.
Every night,
Lord Shen calls out my lady's name.
Like this:
Xing, my love,
please don't leave me!
My sweetest Xing!
He
really said that?
I'm surprised that he is so atta...
If so,
I'll go back with you
to ensure he doesn't get any aftereffects
and end up blaming me.
Xing,
are you leaving already?
Shen Du is bearing wounds,
so I have to return and take care of him.
Stubborn toots!
I'm off.
Alright, alright, let her be.
She's such a buzzkill.
Let's watch the serpent lady.
Serpent lady!
Excuse me.
Excuse me, coming through!
Oh my!
She's truly a serpent lady.
So breathtaking!
She gave up
the chance to ascend to immortality
and came to the mortal realm
to share the elixir she has cultivated
for a thousand years.
Elixir?
This elixir is called "Elixir of Youth."
A woman who consumes this elixir
will boast a complexion fair as snow,
and her natural allure will be enhanced.
Those unwed may attract a suitor of high esteem.
Men, it makes a splendid offering
for the one you hold dear,
May the serpent lady bless all lovers
in the world with
everlasting affection.
Please grant us the Elixirs of Youth.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Elixir of Youth is invaluable
and in scarce supply.
If anyone wishes to obtain it, they can
exchange ten gold bars for a bottle.
- Boast a complexion fair as snow? - That's quite a steep price!
Natural allure will be enhanced?
Do you think the
high price is justified?
That makes sense.
Let's get it!
Alright, alright.
Today, they have been completely sold out.
It's all gone?
I've been here three times already
and still haven't managed to get any.
If anyone wants to get it,
come back in three days.
Let's return another day.
Let's go.
How are you feeling today?
Are your wounds still bothering you?
No.
Why do you look
so gloomy?
Do I?
My lady, how come
you seem quite happy.
Have you found a good match?
Didn't Jing Lin mention...
I see you're doing quite well.
Indeed.
With my lady away,
I relish the tranquility,
and, naturally, I'm doing splendidly.
So you went to meet Xu Xiangren?
That's right.
I just happened to run into him. What?
You just happened to run into him, huh?
At that temple, where people seek marriage.
He even gave the token of
the Chief Inspector to you?
He gave me this as a gesture
of being my sworn brother.
Don't take it the wrong way.
I...
I'm not taking it in any way.
Yeah.
You don't have anything to worry about.
Once you're healed,
you should also visit the Mingsheng Temple
and pay your respects.
It's quite effective.
Who knows,
you might actually get what you wish for.
What could I possibly wish for?
Crying and whining.
What are you making a fuss about?
Auntie!
My belly really hurts!
Can I get down for a moment?
You shouldn't have
eaten anything at night.
Take it easy.
Don't get that costume dirty.
Thank you, auntie.
Bao, come out for a moment.
Stand at the door and keep watch.
OK.
Tricks and deception.
Some immortal serpent lady you got here.
It's evidently a hub for
human traffickers dealing in girls.
Miss,
farewell!
You...
I don't have anything
of value on me.
Perhaps this is
the only thing worth something.
Please take it.
Here.
You should have it.
How do you have a fire moth jade?
Are you from the Fire Moth Sect?
This isn't mine.
My belongings
were all taken when I was sold
in Gannan.
This is from the one who abducted me.
So you were
sold in Gannan?
Is the person
who sold you from Xiang'an?
Based on his accent,
he should be a Gannan local.
The Fire Moth Sect rose in Xiang'an,
and it only took a short time.
How did it spread
to Gannan so fast?
No, wait.
When were you sold?
I can't recall the exact time,
but it's been a few months at least.
Miss,
do you know the way home?
I have a way to travel to
the Western Regions and the Jinwu Tribe.
Let's do this:
Just follow me,
and I'll lead you to
the trading post to the Western Regions.
Really?
Let's go.
Are you able to attend the assembly?
Your wounds haven't healed yet.
It's not wise to move around too much.
It's just assembly as usual.
It's not like I'm going after a murder.
If I don't show up again, people will
think you're going to be a widow.
Then be careful.
These days,
- Than... - Lord Shen!
Greetings, Lord Shen, my lady.
There's an oral edict from the palace.
Her Majesty
requests my lady's presence at the palace.
Greetings, Great Grandmother.
Yan Xing, a clerk from the Ministry of Justice
pays respects to Your Majesty.
It's just us here.
No need for such formality.
Please rise.
Regarding the Chen Huo'e case,
Shen Du's made significant contributions.
I haven't yet decided
how to reward him.
What do you think?
How should I reward him this time?
Whether we receive reward or face wrath,
they all stem from the sovereign's grace.
We as humble servants, are deeply grateful
regardless of Your Majesty' decision.
Though you hold no official rank,
you've certainly mastered the art
of diplomatic pleasantries, young lady.
I, your humble subject, tremble with fear.
Your Majesty,
why must you make it difficult for her?
Lord Shen has already
taken command of the Imperial Guard.
He's also in charge of the capital garrison.
He cannot be
promoted any further.
It'd be better to reward clerk Yan
with some tangible benefits.
You seem willing to protect her.
I just feel
that clerk Yan
is determined to become a female official,
which reminds me of how I was in my youth.
So I feel a connection with her.
If so,
then promote clerk Yan Xing
to the position of scribe.
Your Majesty,
I also intended to participate in
this year's female official examination.
I want to rely on my own abilities
to reach the position of scribe.
You should apparently rely on
your own abilities for the examination.
The female officials' promotion or
demotion are based on merit.
Her Majesty granting you
the title of scribe is intended
to present you with a greater challenge.
If you take the exam as a clerk and fail,
you will still remain a clerk.
If you pass, you will become a scribe.
However, if you
take the exam as a scribe,
the risks will be much greater.
If you fail, you will lose
your chance of serving in a public position.
But if you pass the exam, you will have
the chance to be promoted to archivist.
Are you willing to take that risk?
Yan Xing vows to honor the trust of
Your Majesty and Lady Xu.
Good.
Lady Xu has made a wise choice.
Scribe, Lady Yan,
then I
look forward to seeing your results.
You and Shen Du truly share a deep bond,
which is quite enviable.
Actually, he...
Actually, he has already sent me a message
to ensure that I look out for you.
He worries that you might be nervous
and make mistakes during the meeting.
He
might be concerned that I
would embarrass the Shen Family.
Is that so?
I don't see it that way.
I have known him for years,
and I have never seen him
care so deeply for anyone.
Lady Xu,
thank you for your support today,
and for sharing all this with me.
I'm truly humbled.
Thank you for putting your trust in me.
On that day,
when Jing Lin handed me the memo
regarding the Chen Huo'e case,
I immediately understood your intentions.
Although we don't interact much,
you entrusted your own life
to me.
I trust you
and I'm sure that Shen Du
sees you accurately.
I do believe
my wife is wonderful.
Let's take this one.
The design is simple.
It suits you perfectly.
Although in your heart,
there's still someone you can't let go of,
you have treated me sincerely.
Since the three-month period isn't up yet,
I should cherish
every remaining day.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Very well.
I heard that Yan Caiwei and Mr. Han
are about to get married.
I summoned you here to congratulate you.
Gratitude, Your Highness.
What are you thanking me for?
You are the one getting married;
what does it have to do with me?
You,
have high aspirations.
I heard that initially, you
didn't even take notice of Lord Shen.
What a shame.
Your judgment really isn't that great.
Today, if you drink a cup of tea from me,
then I will wish you
all your wishes come true.
If the wedding doesn't happen,
don't blame me for causing trouble.
Excuse me.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
My lady, my lady!
My lord asked you to go home.
Your sister is in trouble.
Mr. Han,
let me take a look at her.
What is this?
Her condition is getting worse!
Please, save Caiwei!
Xing,
during the day,
we called the Healer from the palace
to come and check on her.
But after the checkup,
he couldn't tell what this is.
Have you ever seen such symptoms?
I can't identify what this is either.
But seeing her like this,
it doesn't seem like she's sick.
It looks more like she's been poisoned.
Poison?
Which scoundrel
wants to harm my daughter?
Poison?
It was Princess Ying.
Caiwei went to see
Princess Ying earlier.
Wasn't harming my daughter enough?
Why are you even
involved with Princess Ying?
Enough with the nonsense!
Why would Princess Ying
poison Caiwei?
Xing,
stop showing off.
Even the Healer from the palace was here.
How is it that only you noticed
that she has been poisoned?
I have a suspicion that it's poisoning.
But I can't identify what poison it is.
And I certainly can't identify the poisoner.
She has thread-like strands on her,
which look like silkworm cocoons.
Silkworm cocoons?
Could it possibly be
Chen Huo'e?
No, that's impossible.
Chen Huo'e has already been executed.
I witnessed it myself.
She couldn't have poisoned anyone again.
I knew what was going on.
I visited the Imperial Guard.
I asked Jing Lin to check the records.
When the Fire Moth Sect caused chaos,
there was a type of poison that
could cause similar symptoms.
Mojie,
Chen Huo'e has already been executed.
Are there any remaining supporters of the
Fire Moth Sect that we can track down?
This is the challenge.
After Chen Huo'e's death,
the Fire Moth Sect seemed to
vanish all of a sudden,
leaving no trace behind.
The records in the Imperial Guard
offer no leads.
Where else can we look?
Should we...
seek out Princess Ying?
Since the poison was administered
by Chen Huo'e, let's not bring up
Princess Ying again.
If this involves her,
implicating the royal family
would be a serious crime.
Have you forgotten the incident with
the destruction of the Jinxiu Workshop?
Since it's the Fire Moth Sect's poison,
it may not necessarily
have been Princess Ying's doing.
Yan Xing,
you might have
caused trouble for your sister.
-Han Shiyuan, you... -Mother.
What Mr.Han said is true.
This time, I fear that Caiwei might truly
be caught in the crossfire because of me,
and face Fire Moth Sect's retaliation.
This is all my fault.
Ease your mind.
Even if it costs me my life, I'll
do everything in my power to save her.
Stop right there!
Where do you think you are going?
Do you want me to
lose another daughter?
Father.
Xing,
you are also my daughter!
Father, don't worry about me.
I will be extremely cautious.
I promise that
nothing will happen to Caiwei.
Not this one.
The cocoon poison...
Where could the recipe of
the antidote possibly be?
Mom, I haven't
had the chance to visit you lately.
Are you upset with me?
I genuinely wanted to visit you.
It's just that
I'm afraid of encountering someone.
That person
is usually a formidable villain,
who chills everyone at his name.
But when he disguises himself as the maskman,
he becomes quite intriguing
and surprisingly charming.
It feels as if he transforms into a
totally different man from his usual self.
Mom,
you've met him before.
I even considered him a friend back then.
His mother
must have
become good friends with you.
Mom, you don't
think he seems like a bad person either,
right?
So,
what should I do?
You can just think of me
as a mysterious figure,
the maskman.
You...
You're here...
I've always been around.
Lord...
Chancellor Lai...
I've mentioned it before,
in this place,
you can continue to see me
as maskman.
As a friend.
Does the Dark Demon need friends too?
Perhaps,
I should give it a try.
Indeed,
even The White Death could get married.
Then the Dark Demon
certainly needs
friends too.
However,
my friends and I
engage in equal exchanges.
And friends should
support each other through challenges
and share secrets with each other.
Can you...
Why don't you start first?
Let me hear what you have.
Share a secret?
Honestly, I seem to have
no secrets at the moment.
However,
I have run out of pocket money.
I went to the Shen residence for a meal.
Does that count?
Alright.
Now it's my turn.
So you do have a secret
to share with me.
I know you and Yan Xing
are colleagues and besties.
I heard that her sister
has been poisoned with the cocoon poison
from the Fire Moth Sect.
And I
just happen to have
an antidote recipe for that poison.
How did you get the antidote recipe?
Chen Huo'e was captured and interrogated
twice by the Imperial Inspectorate.
You should be aware of this.
It was during that time
that I obtained the recipe.
So why
are you offering it to me?
I can give you the recipe,
but I have one condition.
What condition?
Just don't mention that it's from me.
Why not?
You've done a good deed.
So why can't it be said
that you provided it?
You can certainly doubt it.
Yan Xing can also choose to doubt it.
First of all, this recipe
has not been verified for authenticity.
If it fails to cure the poison
or if the condition worsens,
I won't take any responsibility.
Secondly,
there's an ingredient in this recipe
that is extremely rare:
the blood of a doppelganger.
Whether it can be found
depends on Caiwei's fortune.
Xing,
have you been searching for all night?
I'm sorry,
but I can't hang out with you today.
I'm searching for a
life-saving recipe.
Xing,
would you like to take a look at this?
The antidote recipe for the cocoon poison?
How do you know
that my sister was poisoned?
Where did you
get this recipe?
I... I got it from a friend.
A friend?
When did you find
such a resourceful friend?
Well,
anyway, this must be the recipe, right?
It seems to have leaked
from the Imperial Inspectorate.
It's said to have been obtained
during the interrogation of Chen Huo'e.
But as for this recipe,
I can't tell if it's genuine or not.
I have no idea if it will actually work.
Imperial Inspectorate?
Chen Huo'e?
The creator is also the antidote-bearer,
so who could the poisoner be?
How did you just happen to
come across this recipe?
I...
Don't worry about the recipe for now.
I think it would be best that you
visit a healing house.
Have them verify whether
this recipe is authentic,
and whether it might be poisonous.
And even if it is genuine,
it still requires
the heart's blood of a doppelganger
as an ingredient.
But...
In this world,
there was only one doppelganger,
and that was Chen Huo'e, right?
Besides,
she was decapitated by your
sweet The White Death, right?
Yes, that's true.
Chen Huo'e is dead.
In today's world,
where can we find
another doppelganger?
Master Chen went into the mountains,
and his return is uncertain.
Lady Yan, you should be aware of this.
Chief Xu?
Not just you,
I haven't seen him lately either.
Excuse me,
do you know where Pan Chi is?
Looking for Pan, huh?
He left several days ago.
I heard he was chasing after
the Xichen merchant
with a beautiful lady.
Young folks nowadays...
Ridiculous...
Your Highness!
Yan Caiwei has been poisoned.
She has been poisoned?
I heard that
it's a deadly poison that cannot be cured.
I intended to give her a mere warning.
So I slipped some
herbs that
induce nightmares
into her tea.
I've already consulted the imperial healer,
and there's no danger to her life.
So it seems
someone is trying to frame Your Highness.
Indeed.
Framing...
While Yan Caiwei's life
may not seem significant,
her father, Erudite Yan
is a subordinate of Lord Zhang.
Her sister, Yan Xing,
is Shen Du's wife.
If she were to die,
I would be at odds with Prince Xian,
and also with the Imperial Guard.
I would be making enemies.
It's clear that the one who poisoned her
must have had malicious intentions.
Kick his ass!
Harder!