English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP37
You cannot provide me
with a peaceful and carefree household,
nor do you hold your husband in the highest regard.
You are always competitive,
always wanting to stand out.
You are not someone I can
envision spending my life with.
What?
Is this how you see me?
Do you genuinely believe
that you are a good wife?
Your thoughts are consumed by
investigations and case files.
What kind of wife
does a man truly desire?
Have you ever pondered this?
You are merely a stand-in bride.
And you bear the identity of a spy.
Let's not forsake the agreement we forged.
The three-month pact is over.
I, Shen Du,
am resolute in my decision to divorce you.
If so,
then let's proceed with the divorce.
From this day forward, I, Yan Xing,
will sever all ties with you,
Our paths will diverge.
Everything related to you, The White Death,
I will no longer involve myself with.
The honor and disgrace of the Shen family,
from now on, are no longer my concern!
Xing!
Xing,
what's the matter?
You look unwell.
What has happened?
Mother...
Xing?
Xing!
Xing, Xing.
Shen Du!
Shen Du.
Shen Du...
Xing,
You're awake.
Your fever
has truly frightened me.
Where are you going?
I need to see Shen Du...
Don't go!
What do you want with that scoundrel?
You braved the snow to seek justice
for him, but what did he do in return?
After he got released,
he didn't even care about your condition.
And...
And what?
What's wrong with your voice?
And what else?
He even brought the divorce papers!
Mother.
Where are the divorce papers?
Where are the divorce papers, Mother?
Where are the divorce papers...
Mother!
I still can't wrap my head around this.
Lord Shen seems
so principled.
How could he
so openly ally with the Dark Demon?
In the past few days, Shen Du has been
leading the Imperial Guard in apprehending
many officials who have not
sided with Lai Luozhi.
The Imperial Guard has now
completely degenerated into the
enforcers of the Imperial Inspectorate.
With his choice made,
what will become of our Yan Family...
Mojie.
Since Shen Du
has even delivered the divorce papers,
then from this point forward,
whatever he chooses to do,
it will have no further connection
to our Yan Family.
In light of the current situation,
divorce might actually be a blessing
for the Yan Family to avoid turmoil.
But Xing
is bound to be heartbroken.
Her sorrow will likely
extend beyond this, especially considering
that the Chief Inspector, who has always
been close to her, and Lady Yun Que,
were executed by the Imperial Inspectorate
under the guise of quelling chaos,
on the very night they assisted her in
entering the palace to seek justice.
Xing...
Xiangren and Yun Que
are gone...
Xing!
You've just recovered from your fever,
are you trying to endanger your life?
Xiangren,
Yun Que,
I am to blame for your tragedy;
I owe you my deepest apologies!
Even if it weren't for your sake,
they would still have met their end.
Shen Du...
Don't hold their deaths
against yourself.
You're not that significant.
Xu Xiangren was seeking evidence
of Chancellor Lai's treason,
which is why he had to die.
Did you truly align yourself with him?
On the night Xiangren and Yun Que fell,
you were set free.
Could it be that you...
Shen Du,
what is happening to you?
Have you forgotten your aspirations?
Have you forgotten the grievances of
the Shens and the
countless innocent lives lost?
I came here today to urge you
not to complicate matters further.
For the sake of the Yan Family,
you should sign the divorce papers.
With your blood,
let us part ways.
For Xiangren and Yun Que,
for all those who died unjustly,
Shen Du,
from this moment on,
we shall be strangers!
Xing!
Xing,
what's the matter?
We went to the Yan residence,
and your mother told us you weren't home.
Jiang Langxing and I
rushed over to find you.
Have you been to the grave?
Xiangren and Yun Que
lost their lives because of me...
Xing,
please don't think that way.
The reason Lai Luozhi resents Chief Xu is
that Chief Xu saved me from his clutches.
Yet I remain unharmed...
Chief Xu and Yun Que,
they departed peacefully.
I believe
they are happy
in the afterlife.
Are you injured?
Shen Du has resolved
to ally with Lai Luozhi.
Has The White Death
truly joined forces with Lai Luozhi?
He is no longer
the Shen Du I once knew.
From this moment on,
I won't have anything to do with him!
Xing!
Xing...
If you're worried about her,
why not go and talk to her?
A parent knows their child best.
She's always been independent.
In light of such a significant event,
if we just approach her like that,
she will definitely
put on a brave face
and conceal her true feelings
to spare us from worry.
That's right.
She has always been considerate of others.
Women,
we always bottle up
our grievances.
It can lead to illness!
Let her have some time alone.
You'll have to make do tonight.
Just bear with it.
If you're willing to share,
there's still half a space here.
You can sleep in there.
As if it were fate,
she became my wife.
I want to let her know
that in my heart,
from the very beginning,
the one has always been her.
You cannot provide me
with a peaceful and carefree household,
nor do you hold your husband in the highest regard.
You are always competitive,
always wanting to stand out.
You are not someone I can
envision spending my life with.
The three-month pact is over.
I, Shen Du,
am resolute in my decision to divorce you.
She still hasn't eaten yet?
She hasn't taken a single bite.
She refuses to take her medicine,
and she hasn't even bandaged her wounds.
She won't even open the door.
What should we do?
I just got divorced myself, and I've
been eating well and sleeping soundly.
Life is much more enjoyable than before!
She can't keep up like this.
Let me go talk to her.
That sounds good.
Father!
Father, bad news!
I just went to buy some snacks for Xing,
and I noticed that men from the Imperial
Inspectorate are all around our house!
Are you certain it's them?
Having worked for the IG for so long,
I can easily spot
these operatives.
It seems the Imperial Inspectorate has
set its sights on the Yan Family!
A disaster!
A true disaster!
I have served as an official for years,
and I've never experienced such a situation.
The political landscape is ever-changing.
Lai Luozhi has its influence everywhere.
Now that Shen Du has just divorced Xing
and has allied himself with Lai Luozhi,
what does this signify?
What?
It signifies that
our Yan Family is in peril.
Your Majesty,
with spring approaching,
the annual grand assembly
is about to begin its preparations.
This agenda is drafted by
the Ministry of Personnel and the Ministry of Rites
based on the usual procedures.
Then, officials from various regions
and military commanders from all garrisons
will return to pay their respects.
However,
since Your Majesty ascended the throne,
the assemblies have always been scheduled
on the second day of the second month,
during spring plowing.
But this year,
Her Royal Highness is unwell.
Should we select another auspicious day?
The grand assembly
is a significant event for determining
political affairs each year.
It also involves regional officials
and commanders from various garrisons.
It should not be postponed lightly.
The second day of the second month it is.
If Her Royal Highness
is still unwell by that time,
I will accompany
His Majesty to host
the grand assembly.
Chancellor Lai,
are you truly going to
preside over the grand assembly
on behalf of Her Royal Highness?
What's wrong with that?
Chancellor Lai,
the grand assembly
is an annual event for all officials,
showcasing the emperor's authority
and the royal prestige.
The Empress Dowager, who is presiding,
is acting in the role of the emperor.
As for you,
what gives you the right to do so?
Because Her Royal Highness trusts me,
and because she has entrusted me with
the responsibility of overseeing the court.
I must take on the duty
for various affairs in the court!
I believe
Your Majesty would also be very willing
to have me accompany you
in hosting the grand assembly to meet
with officials and generals, right?
His Majesty is
inviting Chancellor Lai!
It's evident that His Majesty
wishes for Chancellor Lai to stand by his side
during the grand assembly!
Indeed.
Her Royal Highness has entrusted Lord Lai
to oversee the officials.
It is only fitting for him to preside
over the grand assembly.
It is entirely justified for Chancellor Lai
to take charge of the grand assembly.
You rascals! Boldly distorting
the facts without a shred of shame!
And you,
Lai Luozhi,
you dare to overstep your bounds with
your treacherous intentions laid bare!
You deserve the severest penalty!
Lord Shen,
you have said nothing today.
Why not speak up?
To insult a high-ranking official,
Are there any legal consequences
for a situation like this?
To insult a high-ranking official,
one should be imprisoned in the dungeon
and subjected to waterboarding.
Very well!
Let's proceed with it.
Shen Du, you...
Lord Shen,
when did you
become so loyal to him?
Lord Zhang,
Princess Ying,
it seems you
are quite displeased with me?
Are you afraid that I will
uncover your
dirty and sordid affairs?
Nonsense!
Princess Ying,
Lord Zhang, you were
colluding with the rebels of Gannan,
plotting treason!
Lai Luozhi,
don't you slander us!
Chancellor Lai,
you have always suppressed
the officials who oppose you.
Today,
is it finally my turn?
But everything must be based on evidence.
With God watching,
how dare you twist the truth
and turn things upside down!
Evidence?
Of course, there is evidence!
I obtained from the Imperial Guard
the booklet
from Mo Qianzhi, which clearly
documents each and every case.
You cannot refute it!
You...
Isn't that right, Lord Shen?
According to his earlier testimony,
Princess Ying colluded with the garrison in Gannan,
and Lord Zhang allowed his subordinates
to embezzle funds from Gannan.
They should be confined in their residences
for further investigations.
The empire belongs to the Xiao Family.
We will not tolerate your insolence!
Palace Guards!
Where are the Palace Guards?
Your Highness,
can you not see it yet?
Now, in the imperial court, most
officials have already sided with him!
With your status,
it would be better
to leave with some dignity.
Do you want me to send
the Imperial Inspectorate and
the Imperial Guard to arrest you?
Shen Du, you scoundrel,
you actually collude with the Dark Demon!
You lot,
who cannot distinguish right from wrong,
traitorous scoundrels,
you will surely meet a miserable end!
you will meet a miserable end!
I've never expected,
that despite my sincere efforts,
I cannot repay the grace of
His Majesty and Her Royal Highness,
yet I am slandered by
these shameless individuals!
Now that I bear heavy responsibilities,
I can only serve with utmost loyalty
until death, caring not for
my reputation in life or after death.
Isn't that right,
Lord Shen?
Then,
should we proceed
as discussed earlier?
What was that?
You lowly
commoners dare to enter the academy?
You truly tarnish
the reputation of the Imperial Academy.
It must be thoroughly cleaned.
I
was admitted to the
Imperial Academy through the exams,
and knowledge knows no class distinction.
Why do you insult us like this?
You are merely
a stray dog
the academy let in.
Do you really believe you can stand
on equal footing with us, the gentry?
Remember,
a dog, even if it enters the house,
is still just a dog!
Chancellor Lai
also has no gentry background.
You all, as gentry,
are eager to flatter him.
Seems like you are quite willing
to be his dogs!
Outrageous!
Get him!
Stop!
My lord,
these gentry students
are teaming up to bully us!
The Imperial Academy is the most
prestigious institution in the empire.
It is directly overseen by the emperor.
You are not focusing on your studies
but are here making noise and fighting.
This is outrageous!
I...
It was them...
Yeah,
it was him.
He is the one who spreads rumors
and disrupts our studies!
Yes, yes, it's him!
It's him who spreads rumors!
My lord,
that's not true.
It's them...
Since you are here
disturbing other students,
you will be detained in the dungeon
to reflect on your actions!
What has happened
to the Imperial Guard?
Have you really sided with the treacherous?
It was Lord Shen
who escorted us here to take the exams.
He said the Imperial Academy
accepts talents regardless of background.
Now,
are you telling me
that the students from humble origins,
who strive to study,
have made a mistake?
Ignoring the signs and lacking the
wisdom to act accordingly
is indeed a mistake.
Take him away!
Dare to challenge us?
Yeah.
You brought this upon yourself!
Get out of the way!
Everyone, move aside!
People refer to us as
White Death and Dark Demon.
Now, you and I are side by side,
taking a stroll in the mortal realm.
It really is quite a unique experience.
With such a spacious street,
can't the Imperial Inspectorate
proceed properly?
Why must you charge around like this,
bullying the civilians?
Allowing lowly scums
to obstruct Lord Lai's passage,
you delinquents are doing a lousy job!
Our duty as the Delinquents
is to defend the capital
and ensure the safety of the civilians,
not to serve as anyone's lackey.
They are truly an eyesore.
The security of the capital falls
under the Imperial Guard's jurisdiction.
These useless
petty thieves should not be allowed
to stir up trouble in the city, right?
Indeed.
Shen Du!
In aiding the oppressor
and failing to see the truth,
how could you honor the memory of
Chief Xu and Yun Que? How can you face
Yan Xing with a clear conscience?
A lowly delinquent dares to challenge
the commander of the Imperial Guard?
It seems you have never experienced
the Imperial Inspectorate's waterboard.
Arrest him!
Wait!
Since he has insulted me,
I will
take this upon myself then.
Today, I will spare your life
so you can return
and keep your men in check.
Inform them
that our
past friendship
is a thing of the past.
If you dare to speak out of turn again,
you will find no sanctuary in life
nor an escape in death!
Chui!
I've heard that Jiang Langxing
was publicly humiliated by White Death.
What?
He publicly humiliated Jiang Langxing?
Yes,
that's what I heard.
It's because he brought the Delinquents
to confront Chancellor Lai.
Shen Du?
He...
has sided with Lai Luozhi?
White Death and Dark Demon
have joined forces?
Shen Du...
I'd like to find out whether his
conscience has been eaten by a dog!
Where's the man in charge?
Let me go!
Move!
Behave yourself!
To what do we owe the pleasure of your
visit to the Ministry of Justice today?
Greetings, Chancellor Lai...
Poker face.
I'm fine.
I received a report that the records from
the Ministry of Justice are unorganized,
full of inconsistencies.
I wonder who is responsible for this?
It's...
Greetings, Lady Lu.
Talk about a storm in a teacup!
Who dared to file a complaint
against the Ministry of Justice?
Doesn't he know that
Lady Lu is under
my protection?
Take him away!
My lord!
If anyone
dares to disturb Lady Lu again,
then they are directly opposing me!
Chui.
Ease your mind.
Wherever you go,
you will always be under my protection!
In your dreams!
Is that so?
Lai Luozhi!
Villain!
Unhand me! If you're
man enough, let's duel to the death.
You, someone I am
stepping on like an ant,
dare to request a duel with me?
Do you even think you're worthy?
Lai Luozhi,
what exactly do you want?
What's the matter?
Feeling heartbroken?
You're actually shedding tears for
such a lowly creature.
I truly feel sorry for you!
Honestly, I don't want
to make things difficult for you at all.
It's just that I couldn't sleep last night,
and I remembered
the song you used to sing.
Why don't you sing it for me again?
Maybe if my mood improves,
I might be inclined
to show him some mercy.
Chui,
don't listen to him.
Don't sing!
Be quiet!
Don't!
♪Speak not in jest.♪
♪Grandma grumbles,♪
♪as mother picks flowers with no end in sight.♪
♪Speak not in jest.♪
My sweet Zhi.
♪Grandma grumbles,♪
♪as mother picks flowers with no end in sight.♪
♪Grandma grumbles...♪
I've told you before,
as long as you stay by my side,
you will get
everything you desire.
As for those you care about,
I won't make things too hard for them
out of consideration for you.