[English subtitles are available]
[Shooting Stars]
[EP23]
[This is Xiang Yuansheng's]
[elder brother.]
[He came]
[specifically from Nanjing.]
[Nice to meet you.]
[Mr. Hua?]
[Captain Chen,]
[thanks for your kindness.]
[For the man on the left,]
[I'm certain]
[that he's related to]
[Peng's disappearance.]
This way, please.
[We can't see the face of the man on the left.]
His wrist is the point.
[The scar thereupon]
[looks like the letter Y.]
Gosh, man!
I'm sorry.
Oh,
Captain Chen?
I'm here to wash face and keep sober.
Look at me, all thumbs.
No worries.
Hand me some tissues.
Sure.
Are you on duty here?
I got this
[by accident while teaching]
Yuansheng how to drive.
You two are close.
Alright.
You go on.
Wipe yourself off too.
Why are you here?
On duty.
Tell the truth.
Wash face and keep sober.
Still playing dumb?
You don't need to stay here.
Go back to the station.
You're back early this time.
Hello, Captain Chen.
Hi.
[Hello,]
is this Ms. Shi?
This is Chen Hao from the church.
I accidentally took away
the teaching materials the other day.
[Would it be convenient for you]
[to pick them up now?]
What's going on?
The figure
in the photo is Hua Liang.
How do you know?
He's here in Shanghai.
I recognized him while he's
dining with Tan Shiyuan.
I've compared the photos
and confirmed it's him.
Okay,
I'll contact the Power Bureau.
We can't wait.
The banquet
is about to end.
He's with Tan Shiyuan
right now
and will soon find out
Mrs. Peng was taken in
by Xiang Yuansheng.
He will definitely take her away.
I need to intercept
them first.
Are you planning to go alone?
Yes.
[I'm the only one]
[with the credential.]
[I'm requesting to carry out this mission.]
What if you run into
Xiang Yuansheng?
I'll handle it.
[Mr. Hua, please wait.]
Mr. Hua.
What is it?
The wife
of the reporter
is hiding in Jiangnan Shipyard.
For specifics,
you might
need to ask your brother.
Hua Zhen?
Yes.
Feng Guangyun saw him
driving her
into the Shipyard.
Feng's team
were stopped at the gate.
If
not convenient for you,
I'll have to notify the headquarters
to contact directly with the Security Dept.
Then,
the police will handle it.
For any issues with my brother.
I must handle myself.
Good,
I await your good news.
Heading to Jiangnan Shipyard.
Any credentials?
Go ahead.
Where's the Gastroenterology?
On the second floor.
Thank you.
You sneak in here like this,
still trying to
help Feng Guangyun?
It has nothing to do with him.
I'm a friend of Peng,
entrusted to
take care of his family.
I've found
a safer place
for Mrs. Peng outside.
I'm coming to move her out.
I just brought
her here last night,
and this morning
the police came for an arrest.
What exactly is Feng trying to do?
I'm not very clear
about the affairs at the station.
Two months ago,
when she went to report,
you told Luo Minmin
not to get involved.
You knew
what was happening then,
right?
Yes.
Does the disappearance
have something to do with Feng?
Is the closure of
the Fourth Station related to this?
I can't answer
these now.
Fine,
I can ask nothing.
But today,
outside the Shipyard,
I played along with you for half the day.
You at least
owe me an explanation
of why you're working under Feng.
You want her from me,
but not willing
to explain anything.
The Shipyard is already secure.
Why move?
What are you guarding against?
Me?
[I got this]
[by accident while teaching]
[Yuansheng how to drive.]
[You two are close.]
If you still trust me,
let her
come with me.
I can't explain everything now.
I used to
trust you unconditionally,
but I can't do that anymore.
If I catch you
here again,
no matter how,
I'll immediately notify the Security Dept.
to arrest you for attempting to
steal military secrets.
Hello, Mrs. Peng.
Thank you
so much.
I heard that
the police have come for me.
[Something wrong?]
It's true.
Has Ganwen been found?
I'm afraid not.
The disappearance
seems more
complicated than we thought.
I didn't have a chance
to talk to you.
Can I ask you
a few questions now?
[Ganwen is a reporter for Shen Bao.]
Recently,
Shen Bao assigned him
to cover a story about refugees
in the Chinese community.
So he went to HBS
for more info.
HBS?
[It's a charity]
[run by Japanese,]
quite well-known around here.
The person in charge is Nakamura Naoki.
Nakamura Naoki?
I remember
he's honored
as a model law-abiding citizen.
There was a news article
and a photo
of Deputy Director Tan
awarding him a medal.
Why did Peng
go to Shiliupu Wharf then?
I'm not sure about that.
He didn't tell me.
But I know
he took a lot of photos.
[I suspect his disappearance]
[is connected to them.]
[They're about ships,]
containers, US dollars.
But there's a photo
of people.
[Three men drinking.]
One of them was Nakamura Naoki,
another
was the man
you just mentioned,
and the third I don't know.
Only his back was visible.
Hello, did you
admit a patient
for stomach issues yesterday,
registered under Hua Zhen?
One moment.
Thank you.
Yes, we did.
Under Dr. Liu.
Has Dr. Liu arrived yet?
On the afternoon shift.
He'll be here in an hour.
He told me that
this patient
also has some lung issues.
She needs a check-up today.
Could you take her to Room No. 2
of the Respiration Dept.?
[Sure, we'll take her right over.]
Thank you.
Is the third one male or female?
It's a male.
Looks
younger than the other two.
Any distinctive features?
There's a
noticeable scar on his arm,
shaped like the letter Y.
Which arm?
The one he's holding his drink with.
Should be the right arm.
What's up?
[Come in.]
Is the patient feeling better?
Can you walk?
Yes.
Good.
I'll bring you to do lung checks.
Why?
I don't feel any discomfort there.
Dr. Liu noticed
something
potentially wrong
with your lungs
during yesterday's examination,
[so he requested]
[a pulmonary consult.]
[Let's head down now.]
[We can go.]
[Take it slow.]
Please show your ID.
The patient needs a check-up.
You please wait outside.
Sir, the patient is here.
Take a seat.
Here, slowly.
You can go back now.
I'll have someone bring her back
once the check-up is complete.
Okay.
Sir, is there
a problem with my lungs?
Mrs. Peng,
you asked me to order
five books for you.
One of them won't be in until next month.
Which one
are you referring to?
Flowers in the Mirror, by Li Ruzhen.
You're a friend of Ganwen?
Yes.
He told me before,
anyone who matches the code
can be trusted.
Yes,
he shared the code with the NSO.
It's not safe here.
I need to bring you out immediately.
Okay.
[Why hasn't it ended yet?]
Hello?
Mr. Hua,
your younger brother
did bring over a patient.
She's in the
Internal Medicine.
We'll exit through the back door.
Captain?
I've already told you,
seeing you again,
I'll immediately alert the Security Dept.
Move aside.
No way!
Now!
What
are you doing here?
Take Xiang Yuansheng away.
Is there misunderstanding here?
Take him away!
Calm down.
Mr. Xiang is not a bad person.
He helped me.
[Mr. Xiang, I've confirmed]
that he's a friend of Ganwen.
He came to take me away.
Whether you agree or not,
I must take Mrs. Peng
with me today.
Get out of my way.
You know who's involved
in Peng's disappearance?
Move aside!
Hua Zhen!
I heard you brought a woman
to the hospital.
Leave now.
Liang.
What's wrong?
Making a mistake
makes you afraid to speak?
Doctor.
Could you direct me to the Internal Medicine?
I know the way.
Follow me.
Hurry.
Lead the way.
You're complained
by policemen.
On my official business here,
I have to firstly
deal with your mess.
Wasn't the last investigation
enough to teach you a lesson?
Don't be
childish!
When in Jiangyin,
I asked you about
a missing reporter.
Do you remember?
Yes.
He
committed the crime of murder.
The woman you brought in
is his wife, and also the accomplice.
The police got information
and came here to arrest her.
But you ordered the guard
to stop them outside.
What's your problem?
You must transfer her
to the police immediately.
Don't make trouble,
or you will be disciplined.
Understand?
Come on.
Liang,
I heard yesterday this
Dermatology Dept. is well-known.
The scar on your wrist...
Alright.
If you care about me,
save me the trouble.
Where is she?
Has she not completed
her lung examination yet?
Are you asking me?
Where is the consulting room?
On the first floor.
[Has a patient]
from the Internal Medicine
been sent to my place?
During the noon break,
a pulmonologist
asked us
to send the patient here.
Who?
What's the name?
[I didn't ask for it.]
This man was there, too.
He saw me leading the patient
with the help of her company.
She had company?
Yes.
A young lady
came with her.
There's a doctor in the room.
I can't get in during the examination.
So I stopped at the door
and left.
[Mr. Zhao,]
[where is my overall?]
I hung it up here
after my meal.
I didn't pay attention to it.
Whose bag is it?
You need to
take medicine by advice.
Three times a day.
I will.
Mrs. Feng,
take good care
of yourself.
OK.
Thank you so much.
Are you okay to go home yourself?
Captain,
why did Xiang Yuansheng's brother
come for Mrs. Peng?
What happened between Yuansheng and you?
I can't explain now.
The Fourth Station was dissolved.
I feel sad
as I see you both
like this.
Go home, Minmin.
Is Xiang Yuansheng safe
there?
He will be OK.
Go back home.
I had asked Dr. Liu.
He didn't take the woman
for a lung examination.
The pulmonologist at noon is a fake.
[Should we]
[inform the Security Dept.]
[to block all exits?]
No need.
They should
have already left.
Wait here.
I walk him back to his dorm.
Do you
know Peng...
Be quiet.
Go back first.
Is this your dorm?
Yes.
Hua Zhen,
give me some answers.
[How did you know]
[Mrs. Peng?]
Days ago, I went back
to the Fourth Station.
Unexpectedly,
it's dissolved.
I encountered her at the gate.
She begged me to help her
avoid being persecuted.
Then I brought her back.
What else did she tell you?
Nothing.
Did she mention her husband?
No.
The nurse said
she had company.
Who is that?
Someone beside her.
I don't know.
What did you wanna ask me?
Go ahead.
Do you know
why is Mr. Peng missing?
I've told you he's not missing,
but arrested for homicide.
[Hua Zhen,]
do you know
how the woman
left the hospital?
I'm asking you.
No.
No matter what the truth
of the matter is,
it's none of our business.
Don't forget
what happened to Wei Daiqing.
What you say
is not only about yourself,
but about
the whole family.
You'll stay in Shanghai
for 7 days, right?
Just stay here.
Don't wander about.
Once the mission is done,
go back to Jiangyin immediately.
What else can I do for you?
No more.
Take care of yourself.
[What do you like to eat?]
[Your call.]
Excuse me. Any hot chow here?
Steamed buns.
Two steamers, please.
[No problem.]
[Have a sit.]
Excuse me.
Are you majoring in
navigation science at the S.M.C.?
Yes. What's up?
Class 3 has a man
named Hua Zhen.
Did he come back to the dorm?
He is out.
Alone?
No.
With some classmates
by a ride.
Was he ever
in trouble?
Nobody dares to make trouble for him.
[Are you here for him?]
I just asked.
Thank you.
That's all right.
[You are back.]
Dad.
Why are you
staying up so late?
Qinqin told me
you told her over the phone
that you stayed at a friend's house last night.
Yes.
An old friend came back.
You are a girl.
Don't stay the night outside.
OK, dad.
Don't wait for me so late.
You should go to bed early.
Go and sleep.
Luo Minmin.
Give the warmer back to me.
Stop it.
Dad bought it for me.
Answer a few questions.
I'll give it to you.
Where were you last night?
And why did you come back late tonight?
Did the instructor
of the training camp
invite you again?
Xiang Yuansheng is back.
Have you been with him?
Do you ask him
why he didn't write to you?
No.
Do you tell him
you've been waiting?
No.
C'mon.
I know how you struggled
in the past 2 months.
You're tied up with
your work
to avoid
thinking about him.
You've been waiting for his letter
for 2 months.
Why didn't you tell him?
He's here for a mission,
and will be back in a few days.
After all,
the past
is the past.
Can you put it down?
Give it back to me tomorrow.
You're not too bad yet.
[Go to bed now.]
Mr. Hua.
The Corp needs to know
how much the reporter found.
He once boarded a freighter.
But we found that
two days later.
From the photos we've got,
he had known
what were
in the containers.
Something else?
Hiding on the freighter,
he's probably
heard some details
about the deal.
But he hasn't said anything now.
Then
we're not sure what he knows.
He is only a reporter.
How did he spot the freighter?
[He's a member of the NSO.]
He investigated HBS in secret
in the name of doing news.
[He'd have followed me to the dock]
[and got aboard amidst the crowd.]
[Luckily,]
[the freight]
[has been unloaded.]
[Just like before,]
waiting for another batch
to arrive in Shanghai,
all will be shipped to Japan.
The NSO has close connections
with the Communist Party.
The Party
is definitely involved in this.
[The Army Ministry]
doesn't wanna see
our business affected.
Neither does the Corp.
But the premise
is that QX JV Corp
can't be exposed.
[For this dilemma,]
[both the Shanghai Police and HBS]
[are to blame.]
[On behalf my boss,]
[I'd like to ask you]
is it possible for news
about QX JV Corp
smuggling military supplies
to Japan to occur?
You know
that what is loaded
in the containers
is not ordinary tea.
[Since I can ensure]
[that they're safely transported]
to Shanghai Port
and depart for Japan,
I can resolve
such a change in between.
You mean,
we can rest assured.
But a small problem.
Your younger brother.
[He]
[took away the reporter's wife.]
We can't find her.
Did you ask him
about it?
You
should know how he
met the woman.
[Out of sympathy,]
[he brought her to]
[the affiliated hospital of the Shipyard.]
[That's all.]
As for how she
got out of the hospital,
he had no idea about it.
About he being investigated
in Shanghai,
Mr. Nakamura and I had heard of it.
He's accused of a communist.
I don't believe that.
But,
what if
[he is connected to the Party?]
Otherwise,
why would he
get involved in those
that have nothing to do with him?
Is it possible
for her to be asked
to look into our business?
The Corp sells
goods
[to the Army Ministry.]
[But you're]
[criticizing my family, even accusing]
[our relations with the Party.]
Given the status of our family
under the National Government,
I think nobody is qualified
[to suspect us.]
Tan just
expressed our concerns.
As long as the freight
can arrive on schedule,
how to deal with Hua Zhen
is a family affair.
Mr. Hua,
I have no intention
of offending.
Actually,
I kept the reporter alive
for the sake
of the film.
But so far,
he hasn't said anything.
I'll wait for
another week.
If no result
by then,
he will be killed.
How to handle a case
is the duty of the police.
But for my brother,
this is my own business.
I mean, myself.