[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP18]
Lord Shen had successfully cleared the name
of the Jinxiu Silk Workshop,
bringing the real culprit to justice.
It's truly satisfying to see.
The injustice has been redressed.
It's truly wonderful.
The position of the lady of the house
will be mine from now on.
What are you still doing here?
Something's happened!
Lord Shen insisted on reopening the case
and has displeased Her Majesty.
His entire household will be executed!
But Shen Du
didn't defy Her Majesty!
[Xing,]
didn't you have
a strong desire for the truth?
And yet, you now
feel pity for Shen Du?
I didn't.
This isn't fair.
There's no such thing as fairness.
Even with my knowledge and skill,
I still couldn't attain a title
because of my humble origins.
The truth,
or keeping Shen Du safe?
You can only choose one.
I won't choose.
I can't choose.
Move out of here now!
My lady, please help Lord Shen.
[Please think of something.]
[Xing.]
[Make your choice now.]
[This will all be mine from now on.]
[My lady,]
[we'll all be executed today.]
[My lady!]
[Don't you want to know the truth?]
[What are you waiting for?]
I'll never have to
fight for it with you again.
My lady!
Shen Du.
Put down.
What are you talking about?
Put down
Put down one
Put down one cow.
What's put down one cow?
My lady, you're finally awake.
[Lord Shen has to talk to you and has]
[been waiting in his study for a while.]
He,
what time is it?
My lady, you've slept
until 6 o'clock in the afternoon.
[The sun is about to set.]
Could it be
that something is really about to happen?
Over here.
I heard you need to talk to me.
Yes.
Did something happen?
These are the
files for the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case.
[I've organized them,]
they'll be easier to review from now on.
What do you mean?
Her Majesty has already agreed
to reopen this case.
Really?
Do I look like I'm
joking with you?
Then why did you make me
worry for so long?
I thought...
Are you worried that I would act selfishly
and rush to close the case?
Or that I will report this
and upset Her Majesty?
Is there a difference?
Yes.
Which one is it?
Why do I still have to choose
after waking up?
I'm not choosing.
So?
What do you think?
I... I don't think anything.
I think you are a fair person.
This is exactly what someone
in a position of authority should do.
Besides that,
you don't have anything else to say?
What should I say?
Did I say something wrong again?
No.
So confusing.
I heard that Lord Shen
had fiercely debated all in court,
showing no fear,
giving a rousing
and impassioned speech
and made Her Majesty to agree to
[reopen the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case.]
And you
must have been
giving him advice all along.
You've made great contributions!
What contributions?
I was the one who got drugged by Pan Chi
and ended up knocking myself out.
I only
heard about this after I woke up.
Have you gone silly
from working on the cases too much?
Such a shame.
I could only hear about it
and couldn't be there to see
how imposing Lord Shen must have been.
Him?
He sure loves to flaunt his authority
in front of me every day.
You don't know how good you have it.
Lord Shen holds a high position
[and has a prestigious reputation.]
[Most importantly, he's very handsome.]
He always keeps a cold face.
So hideous.
Jing Lin.
My lord.
Am I
hideous?
Yun Que,
I have something to tell you.
I advise you not to
bother Lord Shen right now.
Mind your own business.
Have you ever thought about why
Lord Shen was dubbed
'the White Death'?
I'm different from the others.
Just now,
even his expression has changed!
If you keep pushing,
twisting your head off
when he gets mad
is not entirely impossible.
You won't be able to scare me.
If you don't believe me,
go ahead and try.
I'm just curious about
the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case.
Jing Lin,
you're always
working on cases with Lord Shen.
Now that Ji Fangming's been interrogated,
but who was really the one
behind the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case
back then?
You must know some insider information.
I
don't know anything.
You must know.
Just tell me.
Then let me ask you,
what's your family's relationship with
Kong Xianrong of the Jinxiu Silk Workshop
that you would work this hard
to overturn his case?
You wouldn't get it even if I tell you.
If you don't explain,
how will others understand?
What do you mean?
Your family had many dealings with
the Jinxiu Silk Workshop back then,
yet you were never implicated.
Why was that?
Are you interrogating me?
Or are you maybe
suspecting my family?
I...
[Have you heard?]
[Hundreds of moths]
[flew into Princess Ying's residence.]
[It was horrifying.]
[I heard]
[that they flew from the]
[Jinxiu Silk Workshop.]
They say it's the wrongly spirits
crying out,
seeking justice.
Was Princess Ying
the one behind
the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case?
Back then,
she did not
get along with Princess Runing.
Aunt Runing,
[Mother has agreed to]
[reopen the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case.]
The injustice that has burdened you
[for so long can finally be righted.]
The old case can be overturned,
but the wrongfully executed
would never come back.
Your heart is still filled with hate?
[I could open my door to you today]
was because I have already
let it all go.
The dead are gone,
but the living
must carry on.
Now everybody's saying that
I was behind the
Jinxiu Silk Workshop case,
[that I killed your husband.]
Don't you have anything
to ask me?
So?
It wasn't me.
If that's so,
why are you feeling unsettled again?
That invisible force
has returned,
[targeting the royal family this time.]
It wants to
bring us into chaos and turmoil.
I wasn't the first.
And you wouldn't be the last.
Since there's nothing that can be done,
might as well take things as they come.
I refuse to submit to fate.
Whether it's the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case
or the unsolved case of Chen Huo'e,
the IG,
the II,
the Imperial Court and Ministry of Justice
are all trying to solve the case.
The truth
will see the light of day.
The world is full of conflicts,
but I seek only a clear conscience.
Aunt Runing,
do you want to spend your whole life here
at the Mingsheng Temple?
The affairs of this world
are mere trivial matters.
Here,
it's peaceful and quiet.
Fine.
I'm embarrassing myself here.
[It's still the same as always.]
I can't stand your high-mindedness,
and you despise my frivolous ways.
I heard that when Prince Xian came here,
you have drawn a divination for him.
[Could you]
do that for me too today?
I've only been practicing here
for a few short years.
My spirituality is not strong.
I'm not very skilled
at interpreting signs either.
[If there's nothing else,]
you should head back early.
So you're asking me to leave.
I know when to take a hint.
To meet is already a good omen,
[so why worry about more?]
Your Highness.
Shen Du.
Your Highness, did you come here at night
because you're concerned about the case of
Chen Huo'e and the Jinxiu Silk Workshop?
Well
Are you also suspecting me now
and want to ask me questions?
Your Highness, you misunderstood me.
Your Highness,
I have a plan to help you
avoid unjust accusations.
[Here, here.]
[Bring it inside.]
[Okay, put it here.]
[My lord, my lord!]
-[Father!]
-Yun Que.
-Mother.
What are you doing here?
It was... It was this
young man
that tied u...
that escorted us here.
[Yeah, escorted us.]
How did you manage that?
I got them here for you, didn't I?
[He also said]
[you are getting married]
to Lord Shen.
Lord Shen,
[if you mean it,]
you could just tell me first.
There's no need for such a surprise.
Xing!
You
handle this thing.
My lord, my lady,
you came all the way here to Xiang'an.
You must be
tired from the journey.
[Why don't you get some rest first]
and we'll talk about this
and make plans later.
Please,
come rest in the hall.
This is how you 'invited' them?
You didn't tell me how should I do it.
They wouldn't cooperate anyway.
Plus,
it's safer this way.
By the way,
I found out something else
that you would be interested in.
Lord Shen, please.
Yun Que is not here,
so let's be straightforward.
[My lord, my lady,]
we didn't invite you to Xiang'an
for Yun Que's wedding.
[Lord Shen]
is just hosting Yun Que here.
He never
had the intention to marry her.
I hope
you can tell the truth about
the Jinxiu Silk Workshop this time.
Lady Yan, what do you mean?
[We don't understand.]
It hasn't been safe for you
to come to Xiang'an.
I don't need to mention the assassins,
you must have heard about them yourselves.
At this point,
if you keep hiding it,
perhaps even Lord Shen
[could not protect you anymore.]
That is true.
The Shen residence surely doesn't
need to protect those who are unimportant.
My lord,
[since they're not willing to talk,]
then we
don't have to waste more time.
[There has been many wrongful spirits]
near the Jinxiu Silk Workshop lately.
I am timid
[and do not wish to cause trouble.]
[Why don't we]
pack up their things and
[send them on their way before dark.]
Whether they live or die,
we should just let it be.
Sure.
-Wait.
-My lord.
Yun Que is innocent.
Lord Yun,
we wouldn't want to
see you in danger either.
[But now,]
[someone's been using the Jinxiu Silk]
[Workshop case to stir up troubles.]
Even if you conceal what you know,
will the instigator
truly protect you?
[We have wronged Jinxiu Silk Workshop.]
We have wronged Lord Kong.
[But,]
[we had no choice.]
[If we]
[didn't keep it to ourselves,]
then our whole family
would have been killed as well.
[When I reviewed the evidence back then,]
I did find something strange and
[was going to tell Lord Kong right away.]
But that very night,
someone threatened me
[and told us to keep our mouth shut,]
[or]
they would've killed Yun Que.
[So we]
[had to keep that deal and didn't]
[dare speak up for Jinxiu Silk Workshop.]
And it's been many years,
but the one that had threatened us
has never stopped watching us.
[If this is the case,]
then how did the evidence
end up in Yun Que's hand?
And how did she get to Xiang'an safely
and go to the court by herself?
It was that person
who asked us to do it.
[We couldn't figure out either]
[why such a request suddenly.]
But
we had no choice but to do it.
[So we had to put on a show,]
[and let Yun Que find out a little bit.]
[Given her temperament,]
she would certainly take those evidence
and go to court.
Who is the one that had
threatened you?
It's...
It's... It's Chen Huo'e.
-Que.
-[Que.]
So,
you knew long ago
that the Kong family was framed.
[But to protect yourselves,]
[you ignored the grievances of all those]
people from the Jinxiu Silk Workshop
when you knew there were hidden truths.
[Que,]
we had no other choice.
Your mother and I
dared not risk your life and
the life of everyone in our family for it.
Father,
Mother,
then what's the difference between us
and an accomplice?
[Yes, we were coward.]
[If there is any retribution,]
let it fall upon us.
[Que,]
[Lord Shen and Lady Yan know]
[you have nothing to do with it.]
As long as you stay here,
you'll be safe.
Please, Lord Shen, we beg for mercy.
[Father,]
Mother,
no matter what happens in the future,
I'll face it with you together.
Que.
[So,]
[what's really more important,]
[the truth, or the safety of the people]
[around you?]
Who would've thought,
Chen Huo'e again.
So she didn't come back to life just now,
she has actually never died.
It's been more than five years.
No matter what Chen Huo'e
has been planning,
she must believe the timing is right.
That's why she's
using all the evidence and testimonies
that can prove her resurrection.
What is she really after?
The resurrection as an act of deification,
or even,
the re-investigation of the Jinxiu case.
Princess Runing was implicated in
the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case.
[Now that it's reopened,]
[they are using the moth to mislead]
the public and making them think
Princess Ying was behind it back then.
So that means...
To make the most favored royal member,
Princess Ying,
to be suspected,
doubted,
and even criminalized.
If we want to investigate
the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case thoroughly,
it will inevitably involve
Princess Runing,
Princess Ying,
Prince Xian,
even the relations between major officials
like Lord Zhang and Lai Luozhi.
If we look at who benefits more,
it is indeed hard
not to suspect that the mastermind behind
is connected to Princess Ying.
Chen Huo'e's act of deification
further misleads the public
to believe
that Princess Ying
is the one that needs to be punished.
What is it?
I finally understand now
how much risk and pressure
you need to take to
propose reopening a case.
If Princess Ying gets implicated,
how many forces within the court
will be drawn into this as well?
By the way,
Pan Chi mentioned
another thing this time.
-He said...
-[My lord,]
Princess Ying
is holding a family banquet
and has sent an invitation
inviting you to go.
At a time like this,
Princess Ying still
has the mood to host a family banquet?
I didn't think she would be this fast.
Since you're curious,
come with me then.
Looks like there are no
other women attending.
Then let's use this chance
to dispel the rumors
of discord between us.
You have a point.
Then
let's show them clearly.
Lord Shen.
Why did Princess Ying
follow your suggestion
and hold this family banquet?
Given her nature,
she would never allow such rumors
to go unchecked.
She would surely strike first,
trapping her enemies.
Are you that sure
Chen Huo'e will take actions?
If Chen Huo'e wants to
attract more followers,
she must keep creating wonders.
And punishing the culprit
behind the Jinxiu Silk Workshop case
is the perfect opportunity for her to
prove herself and win people over.
You've always stayed away from factional conflicts,
aren't you afraid that attending
this banquet today would make others think
you're siding with Princess Ying?
Would the so-called
'the White Death' care about these people?
My lady, you are very smart.
If Chen Huo'e really shows up later,
what's your plan?
I'll adapt.
[Princess of Jia'an is here.]
Princess of Jia'an.
May Princess of Jia'an be safe and well.
Mother.
May you be safe and well.
Come here.
This is a family banquet.
There's no need for too many formalities.
Everyone, enjoy.
Sit down now.
Princess of Jia'an is truly outstanding
[and extraordinary,]
[and as graceful]
[as the legend says.]
[You're truly Her Highness' daughter.]
[It's truly an honor]
to see you today.
[Jia'an has always been frail, so she]
[has grown up in the suburban gardens.]
[And so we]
[have spent little time together.]
Recently she just came of age and was
called back to the city by Her Majesty.
This banquet
is for her,
to welcome her.
I heard Her Majesty is personally
overseeing the marriage arrangement
[of Zhang Luo, Princess of Jia'an.]
[She'll find you a remarkable husband.]
I, on the other hand,
wish she could stay by my side
a little longer.
Did you notice anything?
She outshines the stars when she smiles.
She's truly in the prime of her youth.
Look,
all these singing and dancing
are indeed delightful.
Be careful. Every rose has its thorn.
I really hope nothing goes wrong.
A moth.
I saw that.
Look.
Your Highness.
[Guards,]
catch her alive.
Yes.
All that effort you put into this show,
are you really leaving without seeing it?
You got me.
Just some cheap tricks
and you think you can deceive everyone?
[Since you're able to control the moths,]
it's only natural that they will lead me
to you, their master.
[Not bad.]
But,
do you think you can
stop me alone?
It's far from enough.
You're so clueless.
Then today,
I'll make sure
you won't return.
[If you refuse to ally with me,]
[you will be doomed.]
[You won't be able to return.]
Did you have anything to do
with the Shen case back then?
You father was nothing
more than an ant.
No one would care even if he died.
[How about]
you believe me
and beg me resurrect him?
Your flattering words
are just empty talk.
The person who framed your father
is by your side,
and yet you've sided with him
and assisted in his tyranny.
Shen Du,
you father won't even rest in peace!
Die!
Could someone that
has come back from the dead bleed?
I've never believed
in resurrection.
If you kill me,
there will be one less person
that knows the truth about the Shen case.
Xing, be careful!
[Xing!]
Shen Du,
are you okay?
I've figured out
the secret behind her resurrection.
Let's go.
[Your Highness,]
[Princess of Jia'an was terrified.]
She's taken a calming pill and is resting.
Okay.
[Your Highness,]
we caught the culprit.
Lord Shen
really kept his words.
Who sent you?
No one.
Take her out
and torture her until she speaks.
Yes.
[Today, you all saw it yourselves.]
The Fire Moth Sect
and their so-called boundless wonders,
they're nothing more than
a bunch of swindlers
deceiving and misleading the people.
From now on,
anyone who
spreads rumors in the name
of Chen Huo'e
will face the same ending.
Yes.
[How could you be this careless?]
It was...
It was Shen Du,
and Yan Xing.
They ruined my plan!
After today,
there probably won't be another chance to
get close to Princess Ying's residence.
I will eliminate foes for my lord
without hesitation.
Forget it.
Taking down Princess Ying
is no easy task.
You fell into Shen Du's trap.
He wanted you to make a move.
As long as you can't punish Princess Ying
like the prophecy says,
you will be used by them and
lose the followers and the public's trust.
No.
I won't let Shen Du get his way.
[All that defy the Fire Moth Sect]
must die!
Very good.
Then go and show your
miraculous resurrection again!
Stay still.
Next time we see Chen Huo'e,
we must not let her get away.
You want there to be a next time?
Now that we know
she is not immortal,
it would be easy
for you to take her.
So,
news from Pan Chi said that
among the people
the Fire Moth Sect had killed,
there was an old doctor
who once mentioned treating someone
with reversed internal organs.
And from that one sentence,
you deduced that
Chen Huo'e's heart
is different from other people's,
that it's not on the left side.
I wasn't completely sure before.
Until my hands on her,
I confirmed that
her heartbeat was on the right.
[My lord.]
Come in.
The guards watching the Fire Moth Sect's
followers reported that
[there has been some findings.]
What's going on?
[This morning, Chen Huo'e]
[showed up in the east,]
[west, south, and north of the city,]
[claiming that they possess great powers,]
[not only can they resurrect people,]
[but can also create numerous replicas.]
[All of a sudden,]
the people of Xiang'an have all
set up various offerings
to the fire moth in their homes.
Looks like the Fire Moth Sect's ambition
goes beyond just their sect.
Pass my order
for a citywide search for Chen Huo'e.
Yes.
Keep an eye on Lady Yan.
Don't let her run around anymore.
Yes.
[Let go of me! Let go of me!]
Take them all to the dungeon!
Yes.
My lord, something's happened!
My lord,
Lady Yan is gone.
She's gone?
Outside,
those thugs from the Fire Moth Sect
are hurting people and causing chaos.
Those people need help.
Open the door.
Lord Shen has instructed before he left
that the door
is not to be opened before he comes back.
If something really happens
to the people outside
today,
it will put Lord Shen
into a bad position.
Then we really won't be able to
open the door.
Open the door.
Help them!
[Lady Yan and I went to help the people,]
[but it was a trap.]
Lady Yan was gone
in just a second.
Go look for her!
Let's go.
[Like a moth to a flame,]
[here today and gone tomorrow,]
[The moth resurrected!}
[The moth has manifested!]
[The moth has appeared!]
The moth has manifested!
Like a moth to a flame,
here today and gone tomorrow,
escaping the cycle of reincarnation,
neither dying nor being reborn.
[Like a moth to a flame,]
[here today and gone tomorrow,]
Like a moth to a flame,
here today and gone tomorrow,
[Shen Du,]
you won't be able to kill me.
Give up!
You dare to pretend to be immortal
with your substitute?
What a joke!
Shen Du.
[Today,]
we'll fight to the death!
Xing.
Shen Du,
don't let Chen Huo'e get away.
Shen Du!
[Shen Du!]
[Shen Du, wake up!]
Jing Lin!
[Shen Du!]
Shen Du!
Help!
[Someone, help!]
Shen Du!
Jing Lin!
My lord, my lady!
Shen Du.
Take him back to the residence, now!
Now!