English subtitles are available
Fall in Love with a Fox EP19
Jin Baiwan from Jin's Escort Agency
pay respects to Host Jing Yuan.
The first time I saw you,
you were just eight.
You did not have
the feeling of horror like today.
Do you really know me?
You joined my Nonuple Palace at eight
for the whole ten years.
Now,
don't you forget everything?
I come to the Battle of martial arts by the lake
just for the Lingyao Herb,
so as to restore my memory.
Then I could know
who I am.
What could you do
if you restore your memory?
I will do what I should do.
When you
joined Nonuple Palace,
I had asked you
why you
wanted to join us.
You told me that
you don't want to be bullied by bad guys.
You want to enforce justice on behalf of Heaven,
and do what you want to do.
It seems that
whatever you
have suffered,
you didn't change.
Host Jing Yuan, I wonder
what you
want from me.
Do you know
why I fish here?
For me,
there's no need to
make effort to lure the poor fish.
All I need is to wait for the right time,
and they will be hooked voluntarily.
Host Jing Yuan, if you do things like this,
I am afraid that instead of getting what you want,
it will be counterproductive.
Host
I did an unfavorable work,
and couldn't stop Qu Zheng.
Leave.
Yes, sir.
You took my wife away
without my consent.
It's not what a gentleman should do.
If there's nothing to do,
we will leave.
Don't worry, Lord Qu.
I asked Miss Jin here today
just for reminiscing about the past.
Host Jing Yuan, I'm afraid
you will be disappointed.
You didn't find
the right person.
Oh, really?
True or false, it depends...
I might get things
wrong sometimes.
But fortunately,
everything will be
in public soon.
What?
Qu Zheng is here?
He sucks.
How dare he come here?
He also threatened you
for not getting the Lingyao Herb.
Yeah. He's living right opposite.
Certainly,
men are all irresponsible.
I've been told
the same words by Yu Linfeng.
Do they really think
that without them,
we can't do anything?
This time,
we won't allow their tricks
do work.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Do you know how dangerous
the Battle of martial arts by the lake is?
Not to mention anything else,
just the first round of the knockout,
it's still a question
whether you two will be eliminated.
Knockout?
What is knockout?
You wicked girl.
Meet me here,
and you will know
how I will deal with you later.
Muqiu
I really shouldn't let you
accompany me in the competition.
How could I
explain to Head Escort Jin
if you get injured.
Look where we are now,
and you are saying this kind of stuff.
Many hands make light.
Muqiu is right.
Contestants, attention please.
This is the first prize
of the Battle of martial arts by the lake,
Lingyao Herb.
The first round of the knockout
will start soon.
In this knockout,
all the contestants will be divided into
two camps, red and blue.
Both of the two camps have to
find out the 70 tokens hiding in the forest.
After six hours,
the camp with more tokens will win.
And the other one will be eliminated.
Oh, no.
A large half of contestants will be out in the first round.
During the competition,
the number of tokens in both camps
will be reported three times.
At the second report,
the members of two camps can choose
whether to change their camp.
The introduction of the first round is done.
Members in the winner camp
will enter the second round.
One-on-one wheel battle.
The final winner
will get Lingyao Herb.
Now all the contestants
come to the stage and choose your camp.
Go...
Baiwan
Which color do you want to choose?
Red?
Okay.
It seems that you
have made your choice.
He will choose red like you.
Then I will choose
blue.
How could he choose blue!
The game has not started yet,
Baiwan, will you
consider changing you camp?
I don't want to be in the same camp with you.
So there must be one
to be eliminated between you and me.
And the person,
is definitely not me.
Sir
Qu Zheng chose the blue camp.
After all,
he's the final winner of the last competition.
Let's choose blue.
Okay.
Wait...
What do you want, your Majesty?
You're the representative of
the Nonuple Palace this time,
so you must win.
Especially in the first round.
I know it.
Then,
choose blue.
Yes.
This is the signal rocket.
And this is my secret smoke.
Generally speaking,
it is unlikely that
life-and-death struggles and injuries will occur
in the early stages of the competition.
What about the next stages?
If there is danger
in the next stages,
fire this signal rocket.
And the disciples from Nonuple Palace
and Yan School
will come to heal.
So if I fire this signal rocket,
I will be eliminated, right?
Then I don't want it.
Take it!
Do you expect
you can win
by your lousy kung fu?
Nonuple Palace chose blue
this time.
It seems that
the blue camp
will win this year.
It's not certain.
You know the rules
of the Battle of martial arts by the lake.
Maybe,
some of them will be rats.
Rats?
That's right.
If there are some rats,
it's probably
your chance to win.
I won't lose.
The Battle of martial arts by the lake officially starts now.
All the people go to the forest, please.
Come on, girls!
It scared me!
That's okay.
It's just a bird. Go!
Who's there?
It's okay, Muqiu.
Two ladies
How did you follow us?
The Battle is so dangerous,
how can I let you
participate it alone,
while I am sitting there?
Leave me alone.
Sister Qiu'er
-Muqiu -Sister Qiu'er
If I knew it earlier,
I wouldn't bring you with us.
Didn't you just help us
drive away two thieves
and arrange a table to eat?
Arrange something to eat?
Wasn't that you?
Then... Was that Baiwan?
Then who could it be?
Baiwan
Is that a token?
Awesome!
This is really a token.
Hey girl!
If you want to
leave this forest alive,
just give me the token
in your hand.
Yu Chen, you again!
He is the ugly and stupid young master
of the Yu family
you mentioned?
How dare you
ruin my reputation like this?
OK!
Then let's settle
the past together today!
You two go quickly,
I am more than enough
to deal with them.
Hurry up!
Move!
Baiwan
You go first.
How about you?
I can't leave him
alone here.
Hurry!
Muqiu
Grandmasters
All the contestants
are in the forest.
Please go back to Lake Manor
and wait for the result.
This competition is
rather fierce,
it will produce
more martial heroes.
Go!
Let's wait in the Lake Manor.
Host
Please!
Your Majesty
It seems that
Qu Zheng and Jin Baiwan are not in one mind.
No matter what
he is up to,
he just needs to
show up here.
Then...
What about Jin Baiwan?
Qu Zheng is here for her,
we must ensure her safety.
Yes!
The token is counted as a score
by handing it over to the stronghold.
But where is the stronghold?
It's you.
I said you should believe me.
What do you want to do?
Aren't these what you want?
You're in the blue camp.
Would you want to give me
all these tokens?
Going further east,
and it is the stronghold of the knockout.
Take these tokens to the stronghold,
and your camp can win easily.
But in this way, you will be eliminated.
Don't worry,
I will help you get the Lingyao Herb.
I won't be eliminated.
If you do like this,
don't say you won't be eliminated,
the whole camp will lose.
Those are mine.
What are you doing?
Put them down!
But I see with my own eyes
those are from the member of our blue camp.
How could they become yours?
I gave her those tokens.
Put them down.
If so,
I can't put them down.
Give me the tokens.
I don't know whether you
care about me
or Qi.
Wait for me.
Give them to me!
I give you these,
so you can give it to her,
and make sure she will not be eliminated?
How I act has nothing to do with you.
Do you really think
it is good for her to let her stay
in the Battle?
You are just afraid that
when she gets the Lingyao Herb,
she will remember everything before.
I used to be like this,
but now,
no matter what she wants to do,
I will be with her.
I'm not interested in how you think.
Stop!
You are in the same camp,
why do you fight each other?
I don't even know that
the Battle has the rule
that the member in the same camp
could not fight?
Then you can treat me
as nosy, Mr Qu.
Just some rabbles.
I can handle with them.
Take care of yourself.
Dare to hit me!
I don't care if he's
the Young Master of Taoyuan Valley,
you must find him!
Yes!
Go ahead!
They finally left.
What you did just now
can prove that
you have me in your heart.
I was forced
by circumstances.
If that is by circumstances,
you look into my eyes,
and tell me that you never
have me in your heart.
I...
You see,
you even can't admit this lie.
I know that you are still angry about
burning the novels.
But it has been passed
so long,
why wouldn't you get it over?
I don't get it over?
Qiu'er
I know,
we have so many rules in Taoyuan Valley.
But how could we
stay with each other
if you don't obey the rules?
Could it be that
the price of my marriage with you
is to destroy my novels?
I absolutely know
that you love novels,
but it's really hard to accept novels
in our Taoyuan Valley.
Are you going to break up with me
for the sake of novels?
So in your heart,
my novels
are always a plaything that
Taoyuan Valley can destroy at any time,
right?
You... Why are you crying?
Is... Is that I said something wrong?
My novels
are never
just playthings.
Mr Yu, if you still
think like that,
I think we should break up.
Sister Qiu'er
Bear the pain.
Dry Su
Please treat the injured, doctor.
Why is the injured from the red camp again?
The blue camp is so powerful this year.
Take a rest there.
Okay.
It will be fine soon.
Zheng in the blue camp,
'cause they're in an overwhelming victory.
Why are you here?
You didn't take part in the competition?
It's just
a sh*t Battle.
Zheng could win
with his eyes closed
with or without me.
If Zheng wins,
what does Baiwan do?
Don't worry.
With Zheng there,
Baiwan doesn't have to worry about it.
By the way,
Qu Zheng is
really powerful.
Only after a while,
he grabbed 15 tokens
for the blue camp.
If we knew it earlier, we would go to the blue camp too.
That's it.
What could I do?
It's all Qu Zheng's fault.
You think about me
all the time,
and it makes me happy.
Why do you come here?
Could it be that you
have been following me secretly?
It is because of following you
that I will have more gains.
We have so many tokens,
we will surely pass the knockout this time.
That's it!
You two!
I remember
you're the disciples from Feng Mount.
Er...
Yes.
Hello, Lord Qu.
One year earlier,
I have saved the Grandmaster of Feng Mount,
and the Grandmaster has promised me that
he would pay me back.
I wonder if this is true?
Er...
But this is the competition.
If we surrender the tokens
submissively,
I'm afraid...
That's it.
You're right.
I have no intention of breaking the rules of
the Battle.
Then we will follow the rules
and compete squarely.
Please make a move.
Hit him!
That's right.
You're right, Lord Qu.
We Feng Mount
must pay you back.
Yes!
Here you are.
Is this Okay?
Isn't it a foul?
We guard of the strongholds
just count the scores of each stronghold.
The tokens are for those who are highly skilled.
Oh, my god.
Highly skilled?
I think the rules of
the Battle
are so fair.
Fair?
Fair what?
What do you want to do
by following me?
There is the Battle of martial arts by the lake,
I'm here
for the competition.
You...
This token is mine,
don't you want to take it away.
Baiwan, you worry too much.
The scores of our blue camp is
far in distance.
This mere token
has no effect at all.
Envoy Xueyue
What do you call me?
I... I want to ask you
what is the score now?
Plus the four tokens Mr Qu has,
15 for red camp, and 21 for the blue.
The blue camp keeps ahead.
Why is the gap so big?
What can I do?
Do you want to know what you can do?
What the hell are you up to?
I'll tell you
as long as you quit the competition now.
Not gonna happen.
What is it?
The report about the first half.
The first bell rang.
It seems that we have made right choice
in choosing blue camp.
The first bell rang.
Notify others to start the second half
of switching the camp.
Yes.
Switch?
Switching camp?
You even attacked the blue members,
seemed that you are ready
to be the rat.
We red camp
is clearly behind so much,
why you...
You...
You are not qualified to ask me questions.
Stop!
Stop there!
You... Go away!
Don't get close to me!
I'm Fang Ding.
I'm switching from the red camp to the blue camp.
Follow me to the stronghold to do the record.
Okay.
What does it mean?
Don't you know it, Baiwan?
The most exciting part of the knockout
is to switching the camp
in the second half.
The number of tokens that
the two camps grabbed in the first half
is a foregone conclusion.
The weaker camp
is unwilling to be eliminated,
so they will snatch the cuff
of the opponent's camp.
Under the confirmation of the disciples
of the Nonuple Palace,
they can change the camp with the cuff.
Isn't this a big mess?
They want the mess.
In fact,
it is unfair to eliminate half
of the contestants in the first round.
If you are on the weak camp,
you must go through the cruel choice
of either losing
or betraying the original camp.
Betray?
Isn't it just a competition?
For the martial heroes,
changing camps randomly
is no different from apostasy.
So,
they will not only be flanked
by the two camps in the game,
but will be scolded by people from all martial arts
and even all over the world after the game.
They will not switch camps
easily if they are
not in the last resort.
So this knockout
is not measuring the strength,
but people's hearts?
You are brilliant, Baiwan.
So, do you
want to lose
or carry the scolding
from the people around the world
to fight desperately?
That's your choice.
But luckily,
the red camp
you are in
is the weak camp,
and no one will attack you.
Shoot.
The red camp will undoubtedly lose
if this continues.
If you do want to win,
come to our blue camp.
I will welcome you
with my opened arms.
No way!
Want me to rebel?
Not a chance.
I can beat you even if
I don't change the camp.
Silly girl
The farther, the more dangerous it will be.
I can't put you in danger,
and I will win the Lingyao Herb for you.
What?
He switched to the red camp?
Yes.
The Young Host of Palace had been
helping the red team grab the tokens before.
It seems that he had planned for this earlier.
He represents for our Nonuple Palace,
how dare he
do such humiliating things
in front of the people of the world!
Maybe the Young Host of Palace
has his own consideration.
His consideration?
He was just
for that woman,
how dare he disobey me again and again!
Why is this gap getting bigger?
There are more and more rebels,
and the scoring gap
will be huge.
You think that the blue camp
is set to win,
so you deliberately make fun of me here,
don't you?
I said it before,
if you want to win,
you can switch your camp,
or just quit.
Until now,
you still want to stop me
from recovering my memory.
In your heart,
am I such a low life person?
This time,
you will not achieve your goal,
and I am bound to win the Lingyao Herb.
Why is it ringing again?
The third bell rang.
The game entered the 15 mins countdown.
You didn't learn any rules
of the Battle?
The last quarter
is the moment
to decide win or lose.
What do you mean?
The last quarter,
'course everyone will
show what he has got.
Everyone will use their own methods
to win the game.
If you
are unwilling to be eliminated,
then I advise you
to give it a go.
Count.
Qi
You actually...
I told you
I'll help you to get the Lingyao Herb.
I'm wondering
how you can make up the remaining tokens.
There are a total of 70 tokens here,
even if you find the rest,
it is not enough.
Be at ease.
I will let you win.
You just said that
everyone can use
their own methods.
Does that mean that
the last 15 mins
is irrelevant to rules?
The Battle has its own rules.
What is that?
Not allowed to hurt the disciples of the Nonuple Palace.
Nothing more?
Nothing more.
Okay.
I see.
Do not follow me anymore.
If you dare to stop me from winning the Lingyao Herb,
I won't let you go.
Seems that
Miss Jin doesn't appreciate
your protection
along the way.
As a referee,
you just told me about the situation.
Is it fair to say?
I'm just doing things impartially.
Then I wish you
a success
in the game.
The selection of the blue camp
is indeed correct.
We have got it in the bag
this time.
Thanks to Qu Zheng,
most of our tokens here
are sent by him.
Go ahead, let's look over there.
Who's that?
It's me.
Brother, don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
If you are not here to hand in tokens,
why are you here?
Someone is chasing me
all the way,
so I can only come
to the place of your Nonuple Palace.
In this competition,
we Nonuple Palace will only be the judges.
We do not participate in the competitions.
I heard that
as long as people from Nonuple Palace won't be hurt
at the last 15 mins,
all other rules can be broken,
is that so?
So what?
Then take a look,
what is this?
I'm sorry,
I just fainted you,
it shouldn't be a foul, right?
I can't be eliminated
in the first round.
With these tokens,
our red camp will certainly win.
You chick
How dare you
to grab tokens in front of us?
If you are smart,
put down the tokens.
That's him.
He was
in blue camp,
but he grabbed a lot of tokens
from us and handed them to the red camp.
It turns out that
you were ready to betray before.
Isn't he the Young Host of Palace
of the Nonuple Palace?
In the Battle of martial arts by the lake,
who cares who he is.
As the Young Host of Palace,
you did such
disgraced move.
Is it a humiliation to
Nonuple Palace?
Shut your mouth!
Cut the crap,
let's go together!
Many of our red camp tokens
have been snatched by you.
We are all contestants,
why should I quit?
Bullsh*t,
You made the choice, right?
Don't get close!