English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP35
Chui,
here, take a look.
This is exquisite silk
brought in from Jiangnan.
See the patterns and the texture.
I'll have the embroiderer make you
a wedding dress. What do you think?
Chui,
look,
I'll wear this outfit on that day.
Isn't this fitting?
Are you insane?
I absolutely refuse to marry you!
You will marry me for sure.
One day,
you will come to accept it.
Look,
these two outfits
look so perfect together.
Let go of me!
You jerk, let go of me!
Before you come to like me
as much as you like Jiang Langxing
and are willing to marry me,
you are not going anywhere.
I will never have feelings for you!
Is that so?
What,
are you still waiting
for someone to rescue you?
That won't happen.
Neither Jiang Langxing nor Yan Xing
will come to your rescue.
I am warning you,
don't you lay a finger on them!
I won't harm them,
unless they bring it upon themselves!
Chui...
Chui,
in this world,
everyone only looks out for themselves.
No one can be trusted.
You only have me to depend upon.
Only me...
What?
You're not going to punch me this time?
Chui,
I genuinely have feelings for you.
From now on,
I won't push you anymore.
I will patiently wait
until the day
you truly fall in love with me.
Madame Jin.
Excuse me.
Coming through.
-Yan Xing! -Slow down.
Xing!
Mother!
You've been released?
Your father has a conscience.
He wrote a petition,
stating that I'm no longer a Jin,
and I'm already part of the Yan Family.
It was Lord Zhang; he sent someone to
convey the message, telling me to do so.
Lord Shen arranged
for guardsmen to escort me
while I retrieve your mother.
My lady,
my lord has entered the palace.
Mother,
you have suffered!
I'm fine.
it's just that your uncle...
He is...
Her Majesty' wisdom is unparalleled!
"Melancholy and Mirth" was composed by me,
and it has nothing to do with Prince Xian.
It has even less to do with my family!
His Highness and I share a deep bond,
appreciating each other's music.
This is all
a conspiracy orchestrated by Lai Luozhi!
Her Majesty is astute
and will vindicate Prince Xian.
Jin Zang!
-Mother! -Jin Zang!
Your death is imminent; stop the nonsense!
Someone!
Burn him in jar!
Lai Luozhi! You've crossed
the line to carry out a public punishment!
Chancellor Lai, there's
something I'd like to let you know.
This secret
is something I can only share with you!
Step back, step back!
You, a mere musician with no strength to
harm a fly.
I'm eager to find out
what your
dying words are.
It is because of you
that my family and I
have faced this calamity!
-Uncle! -Zang!
No one moves!
-Zang! -Step back!
Uncle!
His chest...
Fire moth...
Xing,
ensure this blood letter
reaches Her Royal Highness,
and take good care of yourself
and your mother.
Zang!
Uncle!
No!
Mr. Jin!
Lai Luozhi,
are you trying to openly snatch
the testimony for Her Royal Highness
in broad daylight?
Step back!
What?
Jin Zang is dead?
I...
When did I ever
order his death?
Mr. Jin, unable to bear the humiliation,
cried out for Prince Xian's injustice
during the public shaming,
claiming it was all
a conspiracy orchestrated by Chancellor Lai.
He then took his own life in public.
This is the blood letter
written by Mr. Jin before his death,
for Your Royal Highness' review.
Your Royal... Your Royal Highness!
When did I...
When did I ever demand
the destruction of the Jin Family?
Your Royal Highness, Jin Zang has
stirred the hearts of the people,
spreading deceitful words.
Before his death, he even tried to frame me.
I've been unjustly accused, Your Majesty!
Chancellor Lai has blown this out of proportion,
turning a simple feast
into a bloodbath.
Now, with Mr. Jin dying tragically in public,
the court is rife with rumors.
The Imperial Inspectorate should
withdraw from this case immediately.
I implore Your Royal Highness
to place the Jins
under the custody of the Imperial Guard.
Your Royal Highness,
don't.
Enough!
Even now, you wish to compete for power?
You really don't make it easy for me.
Lord Shen, since you're
not afraid of getting your hands dirty
and insist on intervening,
then you should take over
the case of the Jin Family.
Gratitude, Your Royal Highness.
Greetings, Your Royal Highness.
You are indeed a clever one.
But aren't you afraid
that without my summons,
I might punish you for entering
the palace at such a late hour?
If Your Majesty wishes to punish me,
I can only accept my fate with gratitude.
Do you know?
Until midnight,
I have been reviewing
the musical scores left by Jin Zang,
only to realize
that he has been by my side for so long.
My beloved Huan isn't
showing any leniency towards me.
How can this game allow for leniency?
Even if you lose,
I won't punish you.
If losing brings no punishment,
then what about winning?
Is there a reward?
What reward do you desire?
If Xu wins this round,
my beloved, could you
grant me the position of crown princess?
Aye,
it's a deal.
A wise man sees potential before it blooms.
Your Double Flying Swallow move,
may seem simple,
but it has endless follow-ups.
In this round,
I have actually lost.
My beloved, please keep your promise.
Aye,
I grant you that.
From the moment I entered the palace,
every time I performed a dance,
to every significant occasion in my life,
and every sleepless night,
his zither
has always been there.
This score remains unfinished,
he intended to perform it at the
grand ceremony after the Ming hall
is completed.
He was never one to speak much,
never...
And his silence was so profound
that I often forgot
there was such a person.
It felt as if
only a zither
was placed behind the curtain.
Whenever I felt on edge,
this zither
would automatically play
soothing melodies.
But now,
this one will never play again.
I am the one to blame.
But Prince Xian
is my only son.
You know,
when I was little,
an oracle warned that
my power and influence would be too great,
capable of harming those around me.
He also predicted
that I would ultimately end up alone.
At that time, I was furious
and even had someone
beat that oracle up.
But now, reflecting on it,
he was indeed correct.
No one can walk with me
until the end without being unharmed.
Lord Shen,
I understand you have
also been searching for an answer.
Once this whole thing
is fully resolved,
I will provide you with an answer.
Why are you still awake?
I was thinking about my uncle.
I know you were very close to your uncle,
so it's natural to feel sorrow.
Tomorrow, I'll take you back to the Yans
to spend some quality time with Madam Jin.
Death cannot be reversed,
and sorrow serves no purpose.
I was reflecting
on what my uncle said
before he passed,
"his chest"
"fire moth"
Could it be that Mr. Jin
knew something about the Fire Moth Sect?
My uncle was as weak as a newborn,
and he clearly knew it was impossible
to harm Lai Luozhi.
Yet, in his dying breath,
he found the resolve to surge forward
and tear at his collar.
What was it for?
Was it merely to humiliate him?
Has Chui returned?
Have you found Chui?
Where could she be...
If something happens to her,
how will I face
her mother in the afterlife?
Ease your mind,
I'll go look for her again
and I will definitely bring her back!
Alright.
You are indeed bold.
A mere lowly delinquent like you
dares to intrude into my residence?
Where's Lu Chuichui?
Do you even realize what you're saying?
Jiang Langxing, a mere delinquent,
sneaking into my residence at night,
Words beyond propriety, faults irredeemable.
Detain him in the Imperial Inspectorate.
There will never be another Sun Tan
among our ranks.
Your skills are lacking;
be gone at once.
Chief Xu, you harmed my subordinate
without discerning the facts;
I deserve an explanation, don't I?
Lai Luozhi,
You know precisely
what you did.
Who will suffer the consequences
if the things escalate
is still uncertain.
And let's not forget, within the palace,
I can retrieve anything as simple as
plucking fruit from a tree.
If you're hiding something inappropriate,
I assure you,
I have the means to retrieve it.
Chui!
Chui?
She's just an ordinary girl,
yet you seem to care so much.
What do you know!
In this world,
I am utterly alone, and she's
the only one who truly understands me
and cares for me sincerely.
We share the same blood!
I am your sister!
I will show no mercy to
anyone who thwarts my plans.
I will eliminate
every
last one of them.
Eradicate them all!
I've been contemplating
how I could make you
vanish forever
from this world,
without him ever realizing it's me.
But unfortunately,
when it comes to poison and murder,
he is far more adept than I am.
However, I've come to understand
that instead of letting you die,
it's better to ensure he can never
have you!
Mr. Xu?
Chui!
Chui, Chui!
How are you?
Let me see,
are you hurt?
Chui!
It's me!
Dummy,
what took you so long?
You're such a big fool!
I rushed to the Lai residence to save you,
but I ran into Chief who came to my aid,
and only then did I realize
he had already rescued you.
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry!
I thought
I would never see you again.
It's my fault for failing to protect you.
I promise
you will never face harm again
from now on.
Chui!
Sorry!
I'm truly sorry!
What?
You were taken by Lai Luozhi?
When did this happen?
How come I had no idea at all?
He didn't hurt you, did he?
I'm fine.
See? I'm right here,
sitting right in front of you.
Why did Lai Luozhi
abduct you all of a sudden?
I'm afraid Chui might
have been caught up in this because of me.
No,
that's not true.
Xing,
I'm really sorry,
but there's something
I've been
keeping from you.
Actually,
the friend I mentioned
from the Imperial Inspectorate
is none other than Lai Luozhi.
It's him?
At first,
I kept seeing him
at my mother's tomb.
I thought
he was a masked friend
who missed his late mother.
Later, he
happened to save me once,
and I...
I just...
The recipe of the antidote he provided
when your sister was poisoned
was indeed an authentic one.
He also cautioned me
not to speak of it to anyone.
I...
I thought I could take a chance,
wondering if he might
actually want to be a good person.
How could you possibly believe him,
Chui?
Have you been watching
too many operas?
How could you fall for his words?
Chui,
if Jiang Langxing and I have
shown up a little later,
you would have been forced
to marry the Dark Demon.
By the way,
Chui,
I remember your father
had spent a great fortune
on your mother's tomb.
Why does he
often visit there?
His mother's grave
just happens to be
near my mother's tomb.
I've visited it once,
and it appears to be a rather
unremarkable lone grave.
There's even a name on it,
called Bi Luo.
Bi Luo?
The name of
Lai Luozhi's mother
is surprisingly beautiful.
But I suspect he was merely
putting on a show of
filial piety for Chui.
I can't help but wonder that
Lai Luozhi's intentional moves
to get close to Chuí
are part of
a larger scheme.
By the way,
I think I spotted something
in Lai Luozhi's secret chamber.
It was the
coronation robe!
Lai Luozhi probably thought
I didn't know
much about it,
so he boldly
showed it off to me.
At first, I pretended to be indifferent,
but later,
when I took a closer look,
I noticed that it isn't embroidered
with loongs,
but Taotie!
The loong has nine sons,
and the fifth son, Taotie,
is the greediest of them all.
It seems that
Lai Luozhi's ambitions
are becoming increasingly clear.
I have pressing issues to attend to,
so I'll take my leave.
I'll go see him off.
Don't do it!
Have you forgotten about Sun Tan?
Sun Tan was well aware
that Lai Luozhi had ulterior motives,
but without solid evidence,
he could only die in vain.
Now we know exactly
that he possesses a coronation robe,
and you're going to stop me?
I understand your eagerness
to avenge Sun Tan,
but don't forget that
Chui was rescued by you last night.
Lai Luozhi knows very well
that she has seen that robe,
how could he not be on guard?
Is it harder to infiltrate the
Lai residence and the
Imperial Inspectorate than the palace?
There's no obstacle
I can't overcome
when I'm determined to steal.
I will turn over
every stone to uncover
what Lai Luozhi has hidden.
Your reputation as a master thief
is indeed well-deserved,
but the Lai residence and the
Imperial Inspectorate have likely
already set up a trap for you.
They are waiting for you to barge in.
It will be far more dangerous there
than in the palace!
Shen Du,
why have you become so hesitant?
Do men really change so drastically
after getting married?
I am afraid you'll soon
find yourself just like this too.
Xiang'an doesn't
smell quite right lately.
There are people from Nanlang and
Xichen everywhere in the alleys.
And they're all gathered at the corners,
looking to rent houses and shops.
It feels like something big is brewing!
We are keeping a close watch on them.
But the ones that can be kept track of
are likely just a handful.
Shen Du,
if anything happens to me,
please look after Yun Que for me.
Anything happens to me; do the same for me.
I'm off, Lord Commander.
Jin Zang,
play something light and cheerful.
Jin Zang!
Your Royal Highness...
Your Royal Highness!
I'm fine.
Today is the eighth day of the last month.
Her Highness should grant rewards.
Why is it already at this hour,
and she still hasn't appeared?
Indeed,
Lord Shen hasn't shown up either.
Her Royal Highness feels unwell,
so today's rewarding ceremony
will be presided over by Chancellor Lai,
following last year's precedent.
He has the authority to decide as he sees fit.
Gratitude, Your Royal Highness.
We respectfully bid farewell to Your Majesty!
I'll temporarily act on behalf of Her Majesty
to oversee the rewards and penalties for
the officials based on performance.
How could Lai Luozhi be qualified
to assume this responsibility?
Exactly!
How could II, tasked with mere oversight,
possibly overstep its authority?
This is unacceptable!
This is a direct decree from Her Majesty.
Do you insist on troubling
her further while she is unwell?
You!
Or you!
Are you all
planning to defy the decree?
Chancellor Lai,
I'm the Chief Clerk of the Ministry of Rites.
I am the scribe of the Ministry of War.
Reward!
Reward! Reward!
Gratitude, Chancellor Lai!
Auntie.
Now that Mother is gravely ill,
she won't allow anyone to visit her.
Prince Xian's confinement hasn't been lifted yet,
and Lai Luozhi wields immense power.
Auntie!
Half of the officials have gone to
the Lai residence to pay loyalty, while
the other half are waiting for their fate.
The court is on the brink of chaos!
The court hasn't descended into chaos yet,
but your heart is already in turmoil.
When the heart is unsettled,
the spirit disperses.
Auntie,
how can my heart get settled?
No matter what,
you are still a princess;
Why are you so flustered?
Auntie,
you know better than anyone
how much weight
this title of princess carries.
The emperor still
cannot speak.
Despite the healers' claim of
"wisdom prefers a delayed speech,"
what if the emperor
remains unable to speak?
Now that Mother is gravely ill,
if anything were to happen...
Auntie,
then the position of regent
would become the key to
controlling the fate of the entire empire.
Do you want me to assist you?
Absolutely!
You just mentioned
how much weight
the title of princess carries.
I have practiced Dao for many years,
and the ways of the world are clear to me.
No matter what unfolds,
just remember this one thing:
support the Emperor diligently.
Auntie...
Ease your mind.
This
is just the beginning.