Hello Debate Opponent 2 EP24
Bring me the pepper please.
Thank you.
Me too.
What are we going to do later?
Let me have a look.
How about this?
What's up?
Why are they all shopping,
watching movies
and eating dessert?
That's boring.
There's no place
to find something exciting.
I've played these before.
Who did you play with?
Why do you care so much?
What are you two doing?
Eat spicy food.
Don't flaunt your superiority.
Don't be in the bathroom
all afternoon.
We still have to date.
Sorry, I can eat spicy food very well.
You forget it.
Last time you ate Sichuan dishes.
You've been allergic for a week.
Since I was with you,
allergic drugs are on standby.
Xiaoyu, has your boyfriend's IQ
reached the pass line?
I don't know.
How about
karting?
I always want to drive
but I don't have a driver's license.
I think I can try this.
This is okay.
This one has a special track.
I'm fine.
How about you two?
How about karting?
Okay.
I,
I like to play karting.
That's it.
Pass unanimously.
We have something to do now.
Before we go,
we can watch a movie first.
Okay.
If time is enough,
I think we can go bungee jumping.
This is specially prepared
for you two.
I think it's good.
At that time,
you can push each other down.
If you are lucky,
you will never see
the other person tomorrow.
No problem.
What do you mean by saying that?
What's fun
about karting?
Let's go bungee jumping.
We have a new
set here.
Do you want to know about it?
No, thank you.
Thank you.
Have you decided?
I want two tickets for that one.
This one.
You see.
"The Invisible Guest".
This one has a good reputation.
It feels like the modern texture
of Agatha's novels.
As a suspense inferential film,
the rhythm is compact, and the plot is full of ups and downs.
Towards the end,
the truth was revealed suddenly.
This top film review on Douban
is written by me.
The most handsome of DUFE.
Don't you feel ashamed?
I was in Spain
when I watched the Spanish version
of the film.
Why don't you stay there?
Do you think Liu Yanze
is quite similar to Nan Bei?
I feel both of them are silly.
We're miserable.
We make a contribution to others.
Let's go to eat delicious food.
Okay?
Sure.
Okay, let's go.
Look, does this suit me?
You look good in this.
Come on.
Be gentle.
You see
the red one.
I was also called
the great race driver.
Don't be afraid, Xiaoyu.
I tell you.
When turning,
you can see the curve
according to your speed.
Be careful. Remember to brake.
Braking
is the key and fundamental to drift.
Dango, don't be afraid.
When turning,
your body leans to
which side you take.
In this way, the center of gravity of your body
can offset part of
the centrifugal force of turning.
Are you playing karting?
Do you think
you can pick up props on the track?
Can you still drift
by pressing the shift button?
Can you drive?
Which one shall we play?
I think we
choose an elementary one.
I'm afraid I can't play well.
It doesn't matter, Zishi.
As long as you follow my train of thought,
we can definitely come out.
It shows your ability.
If you don't follow me,
I'm afraid you'll get trapped inside.
Let's choose the twelfth.
Xiaoyu
Let's play the sixth.
What do you mean?
We don't play together, right?
No.
I'm afraid that some people
will slow down my speed.
I'm afraid we both come out
and you are still trapped inside.
Go.
Wow
Isn't this cool?
Nan Bei
What is the contradiction
between you and Liu Yanze?
Why are you so awkward?
That has to start with the joint military training
between our university
and Western University of Science and Technology.
Liu Yanze and I were
assigned to a dormitory.
Nan Bei, your water.
I want warm water at 50 degrees.
This is at 70 degrees.
You're going to burn me.
I'm sorry, Nan Bei.
It's my mistake.
Please pardon me.
Please forgive me.
Nan Bei
Please be serious.
Stop daydreaming.
Okay?
Ah.
I just add a little drama.
Come on. Be serious.
And then...
Nan Bei
The girls of the broadcasting department
are training on the playground.
Do you want to go and have a look together?
Look at beautiful girls, right?
You're still looking at beautiful girls.
No, no.
No.
I didn't know you
yet.
Besides, before I saw the beauties,
I went straight back to the dormitory.
You give my wife back.
You return my wife.
You are foolish.
You...
Come here! Don't go!
Don't go!
Come here!
Come on!
Ah...
It's just a video game console.
What's the big deal?
Game console is a small thing.
But there are my archives in it.
Shi Zhi,
Wei Xu,
Shan Cai...
Who are they?
My wives.
That's what I spent
hundreds of days and nights.
I read all the strategies,
spent all the time,
and bought all the gifts
to make their heart rate
reach the highest.
That's my first love memory.
Nan Bei
I thought I was your first love.
But I didn't expect you to be married.
Ah!
That's the Two-dimensional.
The Two-dimensional is different.
You are disgusting.
What do you know?
That's a man's romance, okay?
In short,
from that day on,
I lost my love forever.
From that day on,
Liu Yanze and I have being incompatible.
Nan Bei, you are so childish.
Oh, my God.
But you have me now.
I won't play that game anyway.
You're growing up.
Listen to me.
For Dango,
for our debate team,
make up with him.
I won't quarrel with him in the future.
Okay?
Yes.
You are a mature man now.
Senior
Why do you always
compete with Nan Bei?
Did you have any conflicts before?
That guy...
When we were freshmen in military training,
we're in the same dormitory.
Unexpected inspection.
The instructor is coming.
At that time, Nan Bei came back.
He misunderstood that I delete
the record of his game console.
I haven't had time to speak.
The instructor came in.
From then on, Nan Bei have held a grudge
against me.
And he keeps playing pranks on me.
Nan Bei is so childish.
So you're not going to
explain to him.
It's not your fault.
There's no need to explain.
But...
It's already over.
Anyway, I am not so angry
at his pranks anymore.
The door opens.
Let's go.
I forgive you.
What?
It's what happened at the time of military training.
I forgive you.
You were so childish at that time.
I won't dispute with you.
Hey, what's your attitude?
I said I forgive you.
You don't know to apologize to me.
Forget it.
Anyway, during military training,
your shoes
are hidden by me.
I cut your buttons.
I spilled the water, too.
I'm sorry.
What are you laughing at?
Then it's a tie.
Are you still pretending to be cool?
Liu Yanze, do you think
you're a handsome guy
by pretending to be cool?
I'm telling you,
your style is out of date.
Do you know?
Actually,
as the captain of team one,
I didn't unite
the relationship between team one and team two.
I'm also responsible.
So,
for the debate team,
and Zishi,
I won't have conflicts
with you anymore.
What are you pretending?
You still like to pretend to be cool.
What are they talking about? I can't hear.
Yeah, I don't know.
What are they talking about?
Forget it.
Let's just play by ourselves.
They won't fight.
Look, look over there.
There are so many cats in the store.
why do you like it?
Because other cats are very outgoing.
Only Charles is always
alone.
The more lonely it is,
the more I want to protect it
and take care of it.
It is so happy to have you.
It is also very happy to have you.
You can spoil it.
I'm in charge of it,
just like mom and dad.
Okay.
There are two nails.
Don't worry.
All right, let it go.
Here we are.
Then I'll go first.
See you tomorrow.
Oh.
Ma Nan
You are so cowardly.
Hey,
you get up early.
You're not strong enough
at a young age.
Didn't we three
withdraw together last night?
Because we
played the game last night,
I didn't answer Xiaoyu's call.
She wants to break up with me again.
I searched
a hundred ways to apologize yesterday
before I coaxed her.
Hao didn't call you?
We're all adults.
She doesn't care about this.
We're sailing in the same boat.
I'm not like you.
It has nothing to do with playing games.
I have a good chat
with my new girlfriend.
We talked all night.
I have to send a photo
to report my situation in real time.
Hey,
there are activities in the game at ten o'clock. Will you go?
Yes.
My girlfriend may not wake up now.
Why don't you ask me?
Okay.
Do you need to ask
Xiaoyu?
Hey,
since I become an adult,
I don't need to tell Xiaoyu.
Come on.
Go.
No, you can't.
hello
You wake up so early.
Don't drop the mouse, Dandan.
Okay.
Then I'll pick you up now.
Okay, I'm coming.
I'm sorry, brothers.
I'll leaving now.
What happened?
What happened? You abandon your teammates.
My game is over.
Your phone is ringing.
Hey, I'm with Ma Nan.
Does it have to be now?
Wait a minute.
Coming.
Brother, I have to stop now.
I'll leave it to you.
Wow
Good
Come on.
Hello
Where are you?
Would you like to have a meal together?
I'm playing games.
What do you want to eat?
Then I won't bother you.
You can play first.
No.
Hero's journey is destined to be lonely.
Come on.
Xiaoyu, I'm wrong.
Why don't you answer my phone?
I'm really wrong.
It's all because of Ma Nan.
He plays such a boring game
and has to collect
my cell phone.
You're late
again and again.
Is it a sprained ankle
or a twisted waist?
I...
When I cross the street,
I meet an old lady.
I saw that the traffic light
was about to turn into a red light.
She's still standing in the middle of the road.
Do you think I can leave her alone?
I can't.
I must help her.
I must wait for
the next green light.
I wait for
five traffic lights.
Ten minutes passed.
Come on.
I just think
I have to run faster.
I can't let you
wait for me.
Right?
Ah...
Just when I was about to
sprint for 100 meters,
guess what?
What did I hear?
You heard someone scolding you.
I heard three kittens
in the grass.
They're screaming badly.
Then I went to the shop
to buy some milk
and sausage.
I feed them.
I thought that
I'm late.
Although I'm late,
our Xiaoyu
will never be angry with me
because
I save small animals.
Am I right?
Why don't you be a screenwriter?
Hey,
the requirements of screenwriter are too easy.
I don't care.
I'm wrong.
I'm sorry.
What's your mistake?
I'm wrong in everything.
You have no sincerity at all.
I'm sincere.
About my reasons for late,
What do you think is the problem?
Nan Bei, I'm telling you...
Look.
I really
went to buy sausage.
I didn't lie to you.
Come on.
Xiaoyu
Let's stop
talking about
breakup from now on.
You won't leave me alone.
Okay.
Our civil law adjusts
the social relations
between equal subjects.
However,
not all social relations
between equal subjects
are adjusted by civil law.
China's civil law
only adjusts...
What?
The property relationship and personal relationship.
That's the relationship
we call...
Civil relations.
Yes, that's right.
How to correctly
adjust civil relations?
I'm going to
test you here.
I can't understand your class.
Why do you have to let me accompany you?
I usually accompany you.
I hope you can stay with me this time.
Come on.
Otherwise, our classmates
don't even know I have a girlfriend.
It's so shameless, isn't it?
I can testify.
Nan Bei tells everyone
you take the initiative to chase him.
But no one believes him.
He assures everyone that
he will bring you here
to show others.
What's wrong?
Too fast. I didn't see it.
Too fast.
Can you be a little polite to me?
Anyway, I'm quite famous
in the class.
What's going on?
Ah...
Xiaoyu
When will we
have a fellowship with your team?
Call Dango and Hao.
It's late.
Everyone has a partner
except Sa.
What a pity.
Okay, let's stop for a minute.
Let me say something first.
Every year, our college
has several places for internships in the service center.
The purpose
is to help students
apply the knowledge
learned in books
to our
practical services.
Our class
also has a quota.
The student
I called
starts to
report to the service center tomorrow.
It can't be you, can it?
How could it be me？
We have to prepare for the debate.
Besides,
this probability is one-fiftieth.
If I were so lucky,
I would have married Ayaka Miyoshi.
Nan Bei
Ah.
Report for duty tomorrow.
Ayaka Miyoshi is not as good-looking as you.
What's the matter?
Too fast. I can't see it.
Come with me, please.
No.
Anyway, your teacher
also asks you
to participate in internship.
I major in international trade.
Why do I go there?
Even if I go to the service center,
it doesn't count.
I don't want to waste time.
You can imagine
those who come to the service center
to solve the problem
have trivial matters.
Those are trivial things in life, like relationship between mother-in-law and daughter-in-law,
and all kinds of
unexpected plots.
This is simply a party
of various people.
Nan Bei
This kind of family chore
suits you best.
I won't go
to join the trouble.
You will know
how important
speed and eloquence are.
How to seriously block the mouth
of various people?
That is simply an art.
Have you ever seen anyone
who can speak more than they can?
Why do sows scream late at night?
Why does the hair salon suddenly catch fire?
Why does Zhang suddenly disappear?
Is it the loss of morality
or the lack of human nature?
These signs
and reasoning
rapidly
enhance our ability of logical thinking.
You
take an example
on the debate.
Which opponent can answer?
All right.
I'll accompany you for a while.
If we pool our efforts together,
we can achieve anything.
Come on.
Maintain my image.
Dango
Hao
I'm going to
see the exhibition in the afternoon with Liu Yanze.
I won't go to you.
It's okay. Go ahead.
Anyway,
I don't plan to train.
Where shall we go this afternoon?
I'll go wherever you go.
Zishi, there are something on your hand.
Hey,
show us your sweetness.
Hao, I'll hang up first.
Bye.
It's a little disgusting.
I've got goose bumps.
Then you save body lotion.
Do you like this?
What?
I mean
girl like Dango.
Like Dango?
I don't know. I haven't tried it.
Why don't you try it?
Where shall we go later?
Anywhere.
I want to eat hot pot today.
Will you go with me?
Sure.
I can't open it.
Come on.
I'm joking with you.
I still prefer
the original you.
At least it's not annoying.
Hao
Where are you going?
If it's training, I didn't say it.
I'll take Tao Hao to eat.
Let's go together.
Is it your treat?
I'll go if you treat me.
On me.
Let's go.
Go.
Hello
Now I...
I'm not as important as
a cell phone.
Right?
I've been studying photography recently.
When do you
begin to study photography?
I don't even know.
Now.
You should say
ever since I was with you.
To make you look better,
I just decided to study photography.
Look at us.
You're really
not romantic at all.
I'm different from
you guys.
Action speaks louder than words.
What are you eating?
This is ice.
Your menstruation will come in a few days.
If you feel uncomfortable,
I have to bear it.
So sweet.
What's up?
Come on.
It's definitely because
you haven't been in love for too long.
Are you flattered?
That's cool, Hao.
Take the initiative.
I think
there is nothing to care
about feeding.
Have you ever heard of
male territorial consciousness?
It might sound a little bit
strange.
But
this is an instinctive reaction.
It's just that one side is stronger and the other is weaker.
In ancient society,
the same-sex consciousness
of competing for territory
has long been engraved in their hearts.
Just like
the elevator effect.
Once people enter the elevator,
they will imperceptibly
set a safe distance.
Once the others enter,
the safe distance
will move with them.
This is the universal sense of territory.
So I
admire you very much.
What are you doing?
Go into your territory and have a look.
It's so cold.
You have always been in my territory.
You can't run away.
Did I say too much
at the dessert shop?
No.
I was worried that I wasn't doing well.
You feel embarrassed.
Am I
not good at playing the coquetry?
Tao Hao, I think
you don't have to
change for me.
What I like
is you.
Besides,
if you're not good at playing the coquetry,
I can do it for you.
It's so dark.
I'm a little scared.
How is it?
It feels good.
That's good.
This debate
is already
a common topic.
But combined with daily life,
without exception,
they are all defeated by their girlfriends.
Do you have any ideas?
I think there is something wrong with this resolution.
Why do you have to give up one side?
This is the implicit message.
Every resolution
has implicit conditions.
Take this resolution as an example.
This resolution
must be set in a situation.
That is, if
your girlfriend
calls you
while you are playing a game,
are you going to answer it or not?
But
it didn't say this.
Can't I make an argument
to blame my girlfriend
but it has nothing to do with the game.
In this case,
the other side
can't break my argument.
Then you can't break others' argument.
Debate must have
the significance of it.
You're completely
avoiding the important and dwell on the trivial.
It's meaningless, you know?
I think we should give up girlfriend.
You think,
there are priorities.
When playing a game, it doesn't have a pause button
and can't stop.
Maybe it's not urgent
for your girlfriend
to call you.
This is an idea.
How to refute it?
If this game is lost,
we can have another round.
If your girlfriend dumps you...
Then we can find another one.
Senior,
how would you refute it?
If I'm debating,
I will say like this.
My fellow debater,
if you don't even know that
your girlfriend's affairs
are major events,
I am very worried about
your future love.
Senior, do you have a girlfriend?
Of course.
But my girlfriend
is relatively weak
in life.
She can't take care of herself.
I am her lighthouse
in the sea.
I'm wrong. I'm sorry.
There are so many people here.
Help me save my image.
Which girlfriend of yours
is too weak to take care of herself?
Of course, I'm talking about you,
who are kind, beautiful, smart and generous.
I'm complimenting you here.
By the way, set up my image as a man.
In order to establish your own image,
you spread rumors outside, right?
Break up.
No.
Why do you break up again?
We can't break up.
Why?
I won't be separated from you.
Hurry up.
We have to report to the service center.
Oh.
In my opinion,
it's okay to make a bowl of rice at night.
I'm getting old and I can't sleep well.
I am woken up by your doorbell every night.
Are you nuts?
You do this every time you go out.
Keep your head down
and play with your phone at any time.
You...
What's wrong with me?
Tell me
if you have another boyfriend outside.
You and I are diagonally opposite.
Not to mention anything else,
the doorbell
is so small that I can't even hear it.
I have asked the takeaway
to call me.
I just want to know
how you hear it.
How did you
hear it?
What?
That's my job.
Leaders come to me at any time.
I'm tired
after going back from work every day.
you still treat me
with this attitude.
If you want to break up,
don't make excuses.
Speak directly.
He said
he doesn't ring the doorbell.
He asks the takeaway to call him directly.
Ah?
He said he doesn't ring the doorbell.
He asks the takeaway to call him directly.
He has to make Ciba at night?
It's too noisy. No.
Maybe you can't look at this thing
like this.
Don't look at it that way.
How do you look at it otherwise?
Do I look horizontally
or vertically?
This afternoon
I drank five bottles of water.
I didn't expect it to be manual labor.
I came here to practice my throat.
Why are you looking at me like that?
There is a couple this afternoon.
The man cheated and wanted to get divorced.
So?
So
if you are like this
in the future,
I will let you feel
what the dual stimulation
of spirit and body is.
What does this have to do with me?
Can you trust me a little?
Think about my merits.
For example,
we will live together till old and gray.
You talk about
the breakup all day long.
If we really break up,
where can you find
a good man like me?