[English subtitles are available]
[Bright Time]
[EP10]
[Bi Peng.]
[Stand up.]
Ma'am...
Now!
This is unacceptable.
You.
[And you.]
[Up.]
Ma'am,
Lan Jinghui didn't hand in his either.
When did you collect them?
I... I had no idea.
Hand it in now.
I really didn't know.
Stop pretending.
It's been standard procedure for years.
You don't know that?
I really... you little!
Enough!
I've memorized
all your names.
I'll let Mr. Zhang know about your doings.
Just reflect on yourselves.
Is that clear?
Sit down.
Get back to your exam.
The rest of you, stay focused.
Yo, Bi Peng,
you're quite despicable, aren't you?
Stop whispering.
Class is now in session.
Stand up!
Good morning, madam.
Morning class, be seated.
Guys,
you've all seen
the midterm results, right?
Yes.
This time, a few of you
have made significant progress,
especially Xiao Xiaohua,
Li Ruosi,
and Lan Jinghui.
Easy-peasy.
Of course,
our class's overall ranking
has also improved a lot.
You all did an excellent job.
Ms. Fang,
is there a reward?
Sure!
What is it?
I'll give each of you a set
of simulation questions as a reward.
This is
a collection of my years of
learning experience and teaching essence.
I hope you will take it seriously,
OK?
It never gets old, huh?
Chen Luyang, pass them down.
Thank you, Ms. Fang.
You did great this time. You've improved.
I only moved up fifty places.
If I hadn't had a rumbling tummy,
I could have done even better.
Really?
Absolutely.
Lan Jinghui.
After school,
go to Mr. Zhang's office.
The teachers want to see you.
No problem!
Ms. Fang was trying to keep it low key.
Praising me in here isn't enough,
she has to praise me again in private.
Please take a look at the exam papers.
I have something
to let you know.
During this midterm,
these students
brought cellphones into the exam room and
are suspected of cheating.
So,
we asked you all to come today
to discuss
how to proceed next.
Mr. Zhang...I'll
make sure he receives a proper punishment.
Apologize to Mr. Zhang, now!
Sir, I was wrong.
I promise there won't be a next time.
Sorry, sir.
We were wrong.
Since you've all admitted...
No, wait.
Mr. Zhang, why am I here?
I didn't cheat.
I just forgot to hand in my cellphone.
What did you need that for during an exam?
If it wasn't for cheating, then what?
I was wondering
why you did so well in math this time.
Come on, just admit it!
Wait...
What's wrong with me doing well in math?
The other day,
I aced the junior high olympic questions!
Alright, stop making things up.
Junior high...
Why don't you show off your
elementary school diploma?
A man
should own up to his actions.
You don't believe me?
How could I possibly believe you?
You're always last in class,
and now you did so well.
Now we've got the phone here,
and the exam paper is here too.
What else do you have to say for yourself?
Mr. Lan,
please calm down.
Since you all
have admitted your mistakes,
then I will announce
the school's decision on your punishment.
The results of these subjects
have all been canceled.
No, why cancel mine?
It's rare for me to do so well on a test!
I've earned it!
Don't interrupt Mr. Zhang!
So doing well means I cheated?
I'm always last in everything I do,
right?
Then why should I even bother studying?
You're aware that you've got a home, huh?
Look at the time.
Where have you been?
I'm talking to you.
Did you hear me?
I heard you.
What was your attitude at school today?
Just look at
the other two students.
They realized they were wrong.
They admitted it, and that was it.
And you?
In front of so many parents, teachers,
and students,
you talked back to me.
Do you even consider me your father?
Listen carefully,
I've got a business trip these days.
You better behave yourself
and don't cause any trouble.
I'll deal with you
when I come back from the trip.
Why were you yelling?
Can't you speak nicely?
Jinghui,
it's OK now.
Let's eat.
Grandma, I don't have an appetite.
Jinghui...
You...
We'll now take attendance.
Ling Dong.
Here.
Chen Luyang.
I'm here.
Xiao Xiaohua.
Here.
Lan Jinghui.
Where is Lan Jinghui?
Ma'am.
Lan Jinghui didn't show up.
Didn't show up?
This is unacceptable.
Ma Yiming.
Here.
Xu Chao.
Xu Mengyu.
Here.
[Lan Jinghui, are you coming tomorrow?]
[I'll bring you breakfast.]
[Duncie,]
[the cafeteria has fried chicken lately.]
[If you don't come, you'll miss out.]
[Jinghui, when are you coming back?]
[The basketball team can't be without you.]
Hey, you guys!
Lan Jinghui is going to be expelled.
For real?
Yeah,
Skipping classes, cheating.
No way,
Jinghui can't possibly be expelled.
Of course it's possible.
Which of the things Li Ruosi said
does not apply to him?
Correct,
as a student,
it's his job
to focus on his studies.
This is really dangerous for him.
Yes.
Yeah.
Say that again?
Is this the way to talk about a classmate?
You're too cold-blooded.
Exactly.
I'm just worried about him.
Just worry about yourself.
No,
I have to find him.
I have to persuade him to come back.
I'll buy him good snacks.
I'll stop by his place every day
to bring him breakfast.
Xiaohua,
is that going to work?
I...
Ling Dong,
do you have any ideas?
Yeah,
Ling Dong,
you got any good ideas?
Well,
just relax,
I'll go and talk to Ms. Fang.
OK, I got it.
Here's the thing.
His class advisor
and all the staff from
student affairs
are trying to contact him,
but they couldn't reach him.
Please
don't worry.
Alright,
you're out of town.
I don't think you can be of assistance.
Once I've got anything,
I'll let you know.
OK, later.
This kid is so
hot-headed.
He cheated and thought it was justified.
He cheated and didn't show up at school.
Mr. Zhang,
it hasn't been cleared up yet.
What if we wronged him?
How could we have wronged him?
I've told you so many times.
Lan Jinghui, Ling Dong.
You keep a close eye
on these two kids.
I didn't handle this right.
Start making calls. Find him.
How's it going?
How is it?
How did it go?
One moment.
I'll be right back.
Mr. Zhang, Ms. Fang.
Why are you here?
I can prove
Lan Jinghui didn't cheat.
Ms. Fang,
I've been tutoring him
recently.
These are his own work.
It's indeed Lan Jinghui's handwriting.
Especially these competition questions,
he could get them all right.
So I don't believe he would cheat.
He is fully capable
of earning those scores
on his own.
It seems Lan Jinghui has indeed
been putting effort into it.
I told you we might
have wronged him.
You, just go back.
We'll discuss this after we find him,
alright?
Sir,
he might not be
in good spirits right now.
He's in bad spirits?
What right does he have to be moody?
Ling Dong,
I got it,
and I understand his position.
Don't worry.
Mr. Zhang and I
will certainly ensure
justice for Lan Jinghui.
Just go back to class for now.
Where on earth could he be?
I don't know either.
He's not picking up calls
or responding to texts.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
Maybe he's just sleeping in at home.
That's not possible.
I called his grandma.
Even she didn't know he didn't show up.
Let's not complicate this.
So where could he possibly be?
It's him.
Yo, Jinghui,
if you didn't call back,
I was about to call the police.
Put it on speaker, speaker.
Speaker.
[Don't bother the police.]
I'm perfectly fine.
I'm calling just to let you know
not to worry.
I'm glad you're OK.
If you're fine,
why didn't you show up at school.
Why bother if I'm always last?
Then,
tell us where you are,
we'll come to you after school.
Nah, don't come here.
I've got something urgent.
Peace out!
Bravo!
Awesome!
Good job!
Neat!
Come on, that was awesome!
You're good!
Really.
Incredible.
Lan Jinghui,
let's rematch.
Didn't we just finish the race?
What's the point of rematch?
Hey, let's have another round.
Don't you understand Mandarin Chinese?
I said,
forget about rematch.
You won't win even if we go for 11 rounds.
Say that again if you dare!
I said,
even if we go for 11 rounds,
or even 100 rounds,
he will still lose to me.
Come again? I dare you!
You're so screwed.
You want to fight me, huh?
Come on!
Stop!
Lan Jinghui,
what's this madness?
Lan Jinghui?
Lan Jinghui,
why didn't you show up at school?
What does it have to do with you?
It becomes my business if you're leaving.
I'm about to be
out of your life for good.
I'm leaving,
don't you get it?
Besides, after I leave,
your life will be a lot easier,
right?
It wasn't so tiring.
Never mind.
You've tutored me for so long,
and I'm still at the bottom.
You've made great progress already,
you know?
To them,
I'm always the same loser.
Let go.
Lan Jinghui!
Jinghui.
Lan Jinghui,
What's going on?
What's with your face?
Alright,
We've been searching
everywhere for you.
Let's go back to school
and talk this through, OK?
I won't go back.
What did you say?
I said I'm not going back.
Skipping classes and getting into a brawl,
you think you're in the right, huh?
Mr. Zhang,
it's not entirely his fault.
After all, there's a reason behind it.
Yeah, Mr. Zhang,
[anyone would feel upset]
[being wronged.]
[Exactly.]
[This whole thing,]
[it wasn't his fault from the start.]
[Jinghui, come back to school with us,]
[alright?]
Come on, let's go.
I'm not going back.
Lan Jinghui,
your friends have come all this way
to take you back to school.
What more do you want?
Do you really
need to be disciplined?
Lan Jinghui.
You've made significant progress already.
Do you really want to give up so easily?
Moreover, Mr. Zhang
just called your dad.
He felt very guilty after
learning about the truth.
He wanted to make it up to you later.
What you're doing now is just
intensifying the conflict, isn't it?
Ms. Fang,
please don't
bring up my dad, OK?
Right now, I just don't want to study.
I feel like no matter how hard I study,
everyone still sees me
as the last in class.
Lan Jinghui!
Alright, Ms. Fang,
I know you've wasted
a lot of energy on me.
But I think
there's no point.
[Do you realize how]
[serious this is?]
I have to discuss with the higher-ups
about how to handle this.
Can you please take this seriously?
Please!
Mr. Zhang,
I am serious,
seriously.
How about this?
Just make it quick.
Please expel me.
You...
Hey,
what's with this kid?
Mr. Zhang,
Ms. Fang,
actually, I think
you owe
Lan Jinghui an apology.
[Guys, now, we will discuss]
[the fundamentals of philosophy.]
[The fundamentals of philosophy]
[is the relationship between]
[thought and existence.]
[Different perspectives to this]
[are the sole criterion for distinguishing]
[materialism from idealism.]
[Well, the evolution of idealism,]
[has been divided into two stages:]
[objective idealism]
[and subjective idealism.]
[Materialism,]
[is divided into three forms:]
[the first is]
[naive historical materialism,]
[the second is]
[modern metaphysical materialism,]
[and there are dialectical materialism]
[and historical materialism.]
Grandma, I'm home.
What are you cooking? Smells good.
[Welcome back, Jinghui.]
[Look who's here.]
Who is it?
What are you doing here?
What do you mean, what am I doing here?
Hey...
of course, I came to visit my dear...
aunt.
Who's your aunt?
Jinghui,
be polite talking to
your uncle.
Wash your hands and get ready for dinner.
Alright?
Does your grandma know
you don't want to go to school anymore?
Keep it down!
Are you coming back with me or not?
Who do you think you are?
Nope.
Grandma!
Don't you call her that!
She's my grandma, not yours!
Do you need anything?
No need to shout.
Are you hungry?
Come over, boys, time to eat.
Alrighty.
Grandma, we'll be right there.
Watch your mouth,
and behave yourself.
Here, have some soup.
Thank you, auntie.
Dong, darling,
How has Jinghui
been doing at school?
Watch what you're saying.
Only tell what's necessary to her.
What "tell to her?"
Haven't you told her yet?
Auntie,
Jinghui might be
a bit shy,
so he wouldn't tell you.
You might not know about
his great deeds at school yet.
What great deeds
could he have at school?
Look at the corner of his mouth.
Jinghui,
show me.
Take your hand down and show me.
Let her see.
Let her see it.
Jinghui,
[Why must you cause me so much concern?]
[Got into fights again?]
No, no.
Grandma, I definitely wouldn't
fight with anyone.
Listen to me,
this is definitely
a misunderstanding...
Hey,
help me out here.
Would you mind
covering for me?
How should you address me?
Uncle...
Dear uncle, sir.
My uncle...
My uncles knows it.
Just ask
him, my uncle.
Then please
tell me.
Here's the thing.
Jinghui loves playing basketball
and he's been training so hard.
He got injured
once during training
by accident.
He's really good at basketball.
Absolutely, Jinghui's
physical condition is top-notch.
I'm in superior shape!
Yeah, he is fit.
Go ahead, eat,
and stay nourished.
Stay nourished.
Yeah, stay nourished.
Have some of these.
Here.
How thoughtful of you.
Are you coming back to school with me?
No, I'm not going back.
That won't happen.
Auntie,
something just popped up in my mind.
I have to let you know.
OK, go ahead.
Once, he managed to
offend students from other schools
all over the place.
Jinghui...
Grandma, there was no such thing.
Grandma, that's not true.
Don't listen to his wild stories.
Hey, hey,
Can we talk about it after we get back?
Don't start with me.
Are you coming back or not?
There was no such thing, grandma.
We'll talk about it later.
Auntie, here's the thing.
He formed a band
for our school
and then they entered
a talent competition.
They outshone other schools and won.
Isn't that
making students from other schools
green with envy?
Our Jinghui has
had a knack for music since he was little.
Isn't he great!
For sure.
Not only is his musical talent great,
but he's also well-liked.
He's always ready to lend a hand.
When other students' bikes broke down,
he helped pump them up
and even provided the pump.
He also treated the whole class to drinks,
remembering everyone's
favorite flavors.
Right?
I remember once,
one of our classmates
got pricked by a cactus,
hands full of thorns.
Lan Jinghui carefully
pulled them out one by one.
Right, being meticulous is the key.
Jinghui, sweetie,
that's doing good deeds,
being willing to help others,
helping classmates.
You should be commended.
Alright, grandma,
stop praising me for now.
I just remembered,
Ling Dong must have something
he hasn't done.
Let's go.
I'll accompany you to take care of it.
You haven't finished your dinner yet.
What thing do I have to take care of?
Yes, I remember very clearly.
You definitely have something. Let's go.
There is something.
Is it something at school?
Yes, you definitely have something there.
Yes.
Auntie,
I just remembered,
there is indeed something at school.
I have to go now.
I'm telling you, my dear,
you should come to our house often.
Any interesting stories at school,
Jinghui will walk me out.
just let me know.
I'd love to hear them.
Make sure to visit us again!
Hey, enough is enough.
Mr. Zhang has cleared things up for you.
It's time to go back to school.
Forget it.
Don't lie to me.
No one cares about me.
No matter how hard I try,
no one will notice me.
This is from Xiao Xiaohua.
Even knowing you won't return to school,
she still buys you breakfast every day
and takes notes for you.
When hearing someone badmouthing you,
Xia Qingtian rolls up her sleeves
ready to beat them up.
And there's Ma Yiming,
he practices
basketball every day,
saying it's a dream he shares with you
and he won't give up.
So you see.
It's not that no one cares about you.
It's that you choose to ignore it.
Only she would
do such a silly thing.
Alright,
I've delivered the notes,
and I've said my piece.
See you tomorrow.
Dear nephew.
I've told you many times.
Stop calling me nephew!
Xiaohua,
do you think Lan Jinghui
will come today?
Ling Dong went to persuade him.
If he still doesn't show up
that would be really ungrateful.
Who's badmouthing me behind my back?
Lan Jinghui?
Master, you've finally returned!
What bad things did you say about me?
Master, I was just kidding.
Look,
I even brought you breakfast.
Well done.
Master,
you haven't been to class these days.
What do you plan to do with the teachers?
Ease your mind.
Since the great me has shown up,
I have a plan in place.
Let me see the rest.
Come in.
Lan Jinghui,
you've finally shown up.
Haha.
Everyone's here, huh?
I figured you'd be
looking for us these days.
So, you've sorted things out, huh?
Yes.
Regarding my...
Sit down. It's all good, help yourself.
No, I'm good, I'm good.
I'll just stand here.
These past few days,
I've deeply reflected on
my mistakes.
Apologies.
You don't believe me? Check this out.
Ms. Fang,
what is this character?
Hey...
I'm not able to recognize it.
This is...
Now I see it clearly.
Jing!(thornbush)
The "jing" from "bearing thornbush to apologize."
Exactly.
Nice attitude.
But,
just apologizing to me isn't enough.
Got it.
I,
and Ms. Fang are practically family now.
I understand
our family rules.
Good.
Lan Jinghui,
you've matured.
Now, see if his
self-criticism is good enough.
If it's not profound enough,
let him add a few thousand words.
Alright,
no problem.
OK,
I'm just kidding with you.
Ms. Fang and I
actually forgave you a long time ago.
In handling this incident,
Ms. Fang and I
indeed didn't grasp the full story.
We wronged you
and made you suffer a lot.
Today,
Ms. Fang and I formally
and sincerely apologize to you.
Sorry.
Nah, it's OK.
We are cool.
I've already forgiven you.
Oh, so you're Mr. Sunshine
now that you've got a little attention.
Yes, in this whole thing,
indeed we
handled it inappropriately.
But,
do you realize how badly
your skipping classes, fighting,
and blatantly violating school rules
has negatively affected
the school's reputation?
Yes, yes, I get it.
That's enough, Ms. Fang.
Don't scare him anymore.
I've just discussed
with the higher-ups.
Regarding this incident,
your punishment is inevitable.
Let it serve as a lesson,
and don't make the same mistake again.
Yes, Mr. Zhang.
I'll keep that in mind.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
I'll take my leave now.
You won't stick around and chat?
I'm good, I'm good.
I won't make the same mistake again.
I'll heed the advice.
I'll go back and be a good boy.
Go back to your class.
Put on your jacket.
OK, I'm leaving.
Why are you here?
That was really silly.
What nonsense was that?
A strong man is adaptable to any situation.
King Goujian of Yue
became a winner in life
by doing just that.
I think you'd better
read the biographies
of Lian Po and Lin Xiangru.
You didn't just come here
to laugh at me, did you?
Do I look like I have that much free time?
So you're actually concerned about me.
Well, I'm your uncle after all.
Caring for my nephew
is what an elder
should be doing.
No need for thanks.
Ling Dong!
Thanks.
For what?
You know what I mean.
You don't have to thank me.
You've helped me before.
Now we're square.
What are you doing?
Now you owe me again.