English subtitles are available
Just in Time EP01
Hello, everyone.
I am Xu Meng'an,
content director of
Chunjiang Xinmiao Media.
Welcome all of you.
Today I want to talk about
the Internet industry...
Director Xu.
There will be no press conference.
The company went bankrupt.
We are all unemployed.
Nonsense.
Let me finish
the slides first.
Where's everyone?
Where are they?
Xu Meng'an.
Your mortgage is overdue.
Please pay within the time limit.
Xu Meng'an.
This month's
credit card bill is as follows.
Please pay back in time.
Xu Meng'an.
Your company
has gone bankrupt and been liquidated.
No severance package for you.
Xu Meng'an.
I've been telling you about
customer pain points.
What about the pain points?
Director Xu.
Sorry.
He.
Such a simple
slide file.
You adjusted it three times.
And you asked me what the problem was.
How about
I feed you meals,
and you swallow it.
Is that good?
Well.
Stop it. Hang up.
She pissed me off.
I think she's been working
on it all night.
So her brain isn't functioning.
Do it yourself
if you can.
What about her role?
Well, I'll get you something
you can swallow without chewing.
He.
I have sent
the revised file to your inbox.
Take a good look.
Don't make
the same mistake again.
Porridge.
Wake Yunjie up.
Put your mobile phone around.
Yunjie.
Get up.
Yunjie. Come on.
Li Lin. Are you ready?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You haven't finished yet?
Hurry up.
Dad, you are so handsome today.
He has been handsome
recently.
What for?
Meet a customer.
You going out for marketing?
My boss let me,
so I have to go.
Competition is fierce now.
Market is more important than
research and development.
That makes sense.
Just put it there.
I'll come back to clean up later.
You'll be back soon?
It doesn't take much time
to meet the customer.
I will slack off my work.
Go to the company in the afternoon.
You are still not enterprising.
Good.
Are you going or not?
Yeah, right away.
Yunjie.
Let's go.
OK.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
How to break dilemma in workplace?
How to expand your career?
40 must-learn workplace courses.
Full analysis of private domain cases.
Help you realize your career leap.
This is your company's
lecture?
Yeah.
How much is it?
About 300 RMB.
Does anyone buy it?
Of course.
I sold over 7000 copies in two days.
It sells well.
About what?
Experience of success.
Spend hundreds of RMB
to know others' decades of
experience in success.
It's a great deal.
You don't have to
go through decades
to sum up.
It's too late.
Dad, change the channel.
Why?
Listen to something relaxing
in the morning.
You are a student now.
So you feel bored.
When you
reach our age,
you will know
what you have learned in school
is not enough.
Don't fire me up.
No. No. No.
This is called never too old to learn.
You know?
Who said that?
Solon,
Athenian statesman,
Greece.
International common language for
more than two thousand years.
Mom.
Compete with
your colleagues,
not with me.
OK?
Don't dislike
others' efforts
if you don't
work hard.
I just want to be relaxed.
But you have to fire me up.
No.
This is the way to survive.
To develop better in the workplace.
So what does the workplace want?
Yunjie.
Let's listen to it. It's good.
Let's study.
There may be
more opportunities.
I love to hear that.
The opportunity
is so rare.
Where shall I take you today?
I...
I am
with Yunjie.
Witness the promotion of
thousands of senior professionals.
A career mentor
with over 10 million fans.
Here are the online courses for working people.
It's not that easy.
Practical skills developed by
Professor Shang.
Decipher six major workplace skills.
Improve your delivering ability.
Diligence.
Transition.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Take a picture of me.
Director Xu.
Why do you take pictures here?
We are leaving today.
So we take pictures to remember.
OK.
Has it started?
Mr. Li.
For how long did you leave your job?
More than three months.
To be exact,
three months and 21 days.
In the meantime,
what are you doing?
Looking for a job.
And do some odd jobs.
Mr. Zhao.
Mr. Li.
There you are.
We're waiting for you.
Look at it.
OK, leave it to me.
Here are the clothes.
OK.
Do odd jobs?
Do some technical output.
Just
help the installation team
outsourced by the former company
commission the equipment.
You are willing to do it?
Well.
You're adjusting well.
It's a serious situation.
You'll be the next.
I talked to Mr. Zhang.
He promised not to lay us off.
Everything changes.
I don't accept it.
I need to talk to him.
It's useless.
The situation is worse than
we thought.
Where are we going
after being laid off?
I looked at your resume.
You have worked in this company
for about eight years.
But your position
has never changed.
Yeah.
It hasn't changed.
That's because
my major is technology.
I am good at technology.
Do you find it
hard to work
in a technical post
at your age?
No.
I can still do it.
Okay, I see.
Wait for the notice.
Director Li.
You see,
about my current situation,
your company...
I want to know
the reason
for your leaving.
Well.
Our local branch
was downgraded
to an office.
So my whole department
was laid off.
You see,
you graduated from a famous university.
And
you have a lot of work experience.
But to be honest,
this is
a junior post.
We prefer to hire young  people.
You are forty years old.
I suggest
you can be
a manager
if possible.
I'm not good at
management.
I...
Director Li.
Actually,
I can accept
a pay cut.
Man struggles upwards.
Yeah.
You can go to other companies.
You still have a lot of chances.
Sorry.
Get the next one in.
Mr. Zhang.
Director Xu.
He's not here.
He asked me to
get him something.
OK.
Mr. Li.
You see,
all the equipment in our company
is handled by you.
We trust you
most.
It's my duty.
I have commissioned
all the equipment.
I'll check it again.
OK.
I'll take this call.
Well.
Hello.
Excuse me, is this Li Lin?
Yeah.
Mr. Li.
Your loan account
is overdue.
Please deposit enough funds
into your account in time.
Your credit record will be affected
if it exceeds ten days.
Yes.
Okay.
I'll handle it.
Goodbye.
Mr. Zhang.
Get something and I'll leave.
I know.
Just a few words.
Another time.
Just...
Just a few words.
A few words.
This is
the project I mentioned to you
before.
I've inspected it.
In the past six months, it has
received special attention abroad.
As long as we can start early,
we can still
make a profit.
Oh, no.
What exactly do you want?
I want to do something.
And of course I need staff.
But I don't need to recruit.
Just those people I have now.
Enough.
The new project has stopped.
Just do
the paid projects well.
Do you want to
talk about layoffs?
It's settled.
You promised
not to lay off my people.
It's no use.
The investor quitted.
I have no money
to invest in new projects for you.
Are you sure?
I won't lie to you.
When did this happen?
It's been a few days.
I have been keeping it from you
for fear of causing turmoil.
I'm looking for new investments.
Are those
employees
really going to be fired?
Content Department is very important.
They are all experienced staff.
Juniors and seniors make no difference.
Just keep
useful employees.
And
I don't want to do that.
It's embarrassing.
I think we have done quite well
in recent years.
How can they
just quit?
How can I know
what the investor thinks?
I'll tell you when I become
an investor.
Now the company
has no money.
Well.
With layoffs,
the company may survive.
If not,
it will be over.
Mr. Zhang.
Director Xu.
Please understand Mr. Zhang.
He has been very anxious recently.
He has an infusion now.
Cut it and go ahead.
Wait a minute.
I'm
going to work.
Take care of yourself.
Hello.
Miss Xu Mengxin.
I prepared
some cakes for kids.
No, thanks.
Everything is ready.
Did you
make all these yourselves?
Yeah.
It's all made by us.
That's amazing.
Kids should eat
healthier.
These finished products
contain pigments
and preservatives,
which are not good for them.
Right?
Is everything ready?
Yeah.
Hello.
It's all arranged.
Please ask them to come over.
Thank you.
We're leaving.
Bye.
See you.
My god.
You didn't wash your face?
Not yet.
Why are you looking for me?
Director Xu.
Sorry.
I don't want to hear that anymore.
If I have to clean up
your mess again,
you will bear the consequences.
I have studied
your revised materials.
Why didn't I think of that before?
I will definitely
work hard.
Just go home and sleep.
I won't go home.
No.
I am not sleepy.
I slept for two hours just now.
I still have a lot of work to finish.
Brush your teeth and wash your face.
Have breakfast.
I'm not hungry.
Your image is important,
so is your health.
You know?
I will wash my face first.
No water here.
It's a material to assess
your staff in the department this year.
This is for your reference
for layoffs.
You are looking for food again.
You ate everything
my husband bought me.
What about chocolate?
He didn't do well enough.
He didn't replenish the goods.
There is no chocolate left.
How's it going?
Do you have anyone in mind?
No, I don't want to fire anyone.
It's hard for you?
Are you excited?
It's rare.
They are all
recruited
and trained by me.
I can't decide.
It is not as simple as
giving up.
Start with
employees with poor performances.
He
is reckless all day.
I met her several times
in the bathroom,
brushing her teeth and
washing her face, with water all over.
I'm embarrassed to remind her.
She was working overtime
all night in the company.
Work overtime?
But her performance is still poor.
She is competent.
So you bullied her?
Don't be ridiculous.
Oh, no.
Competence
and hard work
are two things.
Hard work is also a talent.
No.
It is a quality.
Perhaps it is a choice.
It is valuable.
Let me tell you something serious.
Today they are all talking about
Mr. Zhang selling his house.
He wants to
save the company with the money.
Can his wife agree?
I don't know.
He may be helping me lay off staff.
So he deliberately let the news out
to make them feel sorry for him.
You think too much.
He left with a real estate certificate.
Then I have to hurry.
You too.
Can't we delay it?
It's not my call.
Add delicious food.
There is no chocolate left.
Go find a boyfriend.
I failed.
Li Lin.
Why did you
come to me today?
It's been a long time since we met.
Yeah. Long time no see.
I
passed by here
today.
I thought,
are you still here?
So you still run your shop?
Sure.
Here is
a treasure land.
Yeah.
It's
average,
but I do online business,
with an annual turnover
of 100 million.
100 million?
You are getting better and better.
What about you?
I'm still the same.
At that time,
I resigned and
wanted to invite you to work with me.
But you don't want to.
You are
in an awkward position in that company.
You are forty years old.
There is no future.
Right?
I have been thinking about you.
I want to
take you with me
to get rich.
Right?
Realize our
ideals back in college.
I'll tell you
what I've got.
What?
I'll give you a chance.
You see,
it is an opportunity.
What?
Look.
Your oral liquid?
Yeah.
What did you give me this for?
I...
Let me tell you.
It's
a
national exclusive.
Only I sell it.
And I only do online now.
I haven't started selling it offline.
I'll give you
the right to sell it as
a national general agent.
You just need to
give me the money for the sample.
I'll help you
make money.
Jun.
You don't have to
give me this chance.
But today
I want you
to help me.
Hello.
Let me tell you.
This exercise book is really useful.
My child
has made great progress in English
after doing these exercises.
I mean it.
Hello.
Have some fruits.
Hello,
everyone.
I am Xiongxiong's mother.
I just moved here.
My name is Xu Mengxin.
I want to
ask you how to
educate children
to be as excellent
as yours.
You're welcome.
First,
thank you for the fruit.
You are welcome.
But recently,
we are all cutting back on sugar.
We won't eat this fruit.
It doesn't matter.
We are mothers
for the first time.
So we are all studying.
Let's go.
It's time for our study.
Let's go inside.
Let's go.
They are
just
too idle.
They are so hypocritical.
They live tired.
Are you new here?
Yeah.
My name is Xu Mengxin.
Hello.
Are you also a stay-at-home mom?
No.
I'm not like them.
So your kid?
You had children before marriage too, right?
Who said that?
They said it.
Or
why aren't they with you?
What else did they say about me?
You are
an online influencer and gold digger.
You not only gave birth to a child,
but also a second child.
But I don't think
reputation is important.
They don't talk to you.
I do.
Nonsense.
I'm legally married, okay?
I'm not like you.
You...
I...
This exercise book is particularly good.
My child has been doing
this exercise recently.
Hello, everyone.
Let me explain it to you.
I didn't give birth before marriage.
I have a husband.
I got a marriage certificate, registered
in the household register.
My husband can't do such a big business
without me.
If you don't believe me,
I'll call my husband.
Hello.
Xin.
Dear.
Hurry back.
They think
I'm too young
and I'm
a mistress of you.
Lady.
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine. I...
I am a doctor.
Just tell me.
Lady.
But today
I want you
to help me.
I bought a house.
So I am short of money.
I want to borrow some money
to turn around.
All my money is put on my business.
It didn't flow back yet.
Maybe
a few days later?
I'll see what I can do.
Director Xu.
You scared me.
Why are you hiding here?
Will the company
lay me off this time?
You should
ask yourself.
Director Xu.
I always give you trouble.
But if I
lose this job,
I can't afford the rent.
You are not the only one
who can't pay the rent
without a job.
But you should
reflect on yourself.
You have been here for almost two years.
But you left too many
loose ends
for everyone else.
No company
can hire you for two years.
You can't even pass probation period.
If you are fired,
you have to accept it.
Just go home and sleep.
Well. Director Xu.
Hello.
I sent you
the progress of our real estate project
this month.
Indoor wall
and basic interior finish
has been completed 50%.
Aluminum wall
is also half installed.
Your house
is expected to be delivered in advance.
Honey.
How do you think?
Pretty good.
We choose
this one, okay?
I think it's good.
Its location is also good,
and it is close to our mother's place.
Yeah.
Just a little expensive.
It's
beyond our budget, right?
Yeah.
But we can scrape up
the down payment.
That means we need to scrape by in the future.
Let's discuss it with him.
We cancel the decoration.
Let's decorate ourselves.
Okay.
Good.
No big deals
buying a house anyway.
We need to work hard
in the first few years.
But we get all
we want for a house.
Well.
I will repay
the loan.
I'll do the rest.
Yunjie.
How do you think?
Excellent.
Let's buy this one.
I like this big terrace so much.
Mr. Li.
Your loan account
is overdue.
Please deposit enough funds
into your account in time.
Your credit record will be affected
if it exceeds ten days.
Honey.
You're back.
What's Yunjie doing?
Doing homework.
Did the salesgirl send you
the progress of our new house today?
I haven't seen it yet.
I saw it.
It's good.
Really?
It can be delivered in advance.
In advance?
Why so quick?
But what about
the quality,
all good?
Sure.
That's great.
What do you want to decorate it?
You have an idea?
Sure.
Go ahead.
I want to
decorate it better.
Should be different
from this style.
Nordic style or modern style.
It makes it more spacious.
Well.
Why don't we go to
the building materials market some day?
OK.
Agreed.
Have you had nightmares recently?
No.
You have nightmares?
Always.
And I keep sweating.
I'm not sure I am going through
menopause recently.
Don't talk nonsense.
You are
young.
Don't be paranoid.
Honey.
You just
have too much pressure at work recently.
You are a little anxious.
So, don't think so.
Take it easy.
Drink a glass of milk
before going to bed
to calm the nerves.
What if it doesn't work?
Let our brother-in-law get some medicine
to recuperate.
Don't worry.
I also think it's a little early
to be in menopause.
Way early.
Alright.
Look.
He sent it to my home.
I can't explain it to my mother
if she sees it.
Husky and School Beauty's Partner
has been serialized again.
What School Beauty?
I am the joke of the whole class now.
Don't laugh.
Aren't you friend of mine?
That's
signature pillow of the city's champion.
I can read his thoughts.
I don't want his stuff.
I had better not have anything
to do with him.
You are awake.
How long have I slept?
Your hypoglyc-emia,
coupled with fatigue,
gave you a long sleep.
Can I go now?
Just a moment.
Dr. Yu asked you to wait for him.
Dr. Yu?
What about the patient in Bed 3?
She has already left.
Left?
Go ahead.
What?
Oh, no.
I've only been gone for a short time,
and it's changed so much.
Oh, no.
Did you call Mr. Liu?
It's signed?
All right, hang up.
What's the matter with you?
Why don't you answer the phone?
I wasn't feeling well.
Not feeling well?
I'm not feeling well.
Why didn't you pick up
the children this afternoon?
I went to hospital.
Same old ailment.
That's not
an emergency.
Nothing is more important
than children.
The teacher called me
and said two children
were long waiting for us.
You didn't answer the phone.
So she called me.
I'm in a meeting to negotiate.
Do you know?
You just said
nothing is more important
than children.
Well.
You've got me.
I suggested hiring a nanny
to take care of the children for you.
You said you could do it yourself.
But you didn't.
What else
can you do?
Forget it.
I will stay in a hotel tonight.
Drink the milk
to help you sleep.
I brushed my teeth.
Drink it first.
Good for you.
Then brush your teeth again.
That's easy.
Well.
You've been tired all day.
Let me give you a massage.
Dad, you are so handsome today.
He has been handsome
recently.
What for?
You decided to tell me?
Tell you what?