[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP36]
Lord Geng,
that villain is getting bolder
by the day.
We need to think of a countermeasure!
Lord Geng?
The petty thief is hanged,
the great thief wears a crown.
My beloved,
you must resent me, so you torment me
with nightmares every night, right?
Are you under the impression,
like those seasoned officials,
that I'm not cut out
to be the sovereign?
My beloved,
Qi
is still unable to speak;
Xichen and Nan Lang are predatory,
and I alone
bear the weight of the entire empire.
What have I done to earn such suffering?
You Royal Highness.
Facing the current political turmoil,
you should prioritize your well-being.
It's nothing.
With the Royal Advisor gone,
and the internal and external threats,
I can't help but feel anxious.
Have the matters of the court
been arranged properly?
As per your decree,
Chancellor Lai is in charge
of court affairs.
He implores you
to set aside your concerns for the empire
and focus on your recovery.
Good.
I still remember how the Royal Advisor
dedicated himself completely.
In his final moments, he's still making
efforts to foresee the future.
I sincerely hope
that the empire's fortune
can align with his prophecies,
leading to peace and prosperity.
Go! Faster!
Qi Yeyun, Qi Yeyun!
- Come out now!
- Coming!
- What's going on?
- We need to close right away!
Why do we close during the day?
You've been cooped up indoors,
do you know nothing of what's happening?
Disaster is upon us!
Her Royal Highness is gravely ill,
and the Dark Demon is taking over.
I heard that
a few loyal officials
who opposed it
have all been assassinated!
In such chaotic times,
what do we need business for?
With the political situation in turmoil,
isn't this the perfect opportunity
for our pawn shop?
You're being foolish!
Let me ask you,
is money more important than life?
Hurry,
close the shop!
What brings Chancellor Lai to the Imperial Guard
with such a
grand military escort?
As it stands, the Jin Family
is being detained here,
yet their case remains unresolved.
Does Lord Shen believe
that Her Royal Highness'
illness
justifies your inaction?
The Imperial Guard still requires
additional evidence.
Evidence?
What I have brought serves as evidence.
I urge Lord Shen to
review and render a judgment on it.
How can I make a ruling
based solely on side's testimony?
You refuse?
Very well,
I'll take it upon myself then.
Lai Luozhi,
are you openly challenging
the authority of the royal court?
The affairs of the Imperial Guard
are not for the Imperial Inspectorate,
of equal rank, to interfere with.
If the II is not qualified,
then I, Lai Luozhi, is.
Let it not be forgotten
that Her Royal Highness has granted me
the authority to order the officials at my discretion!
Imperial Garrison, on my command!
Shen Du, of the Imperial Guard,
is hereby arrested for dereliction of duty
which occurred during
Her Royal Highness'
period of indisposition.
What?
Going up against the Imperial Garrison?
Lord Shen, are you plotting a coup?
If you kill the commander of the Imperial Garrison,
you will be charged with treason today,
and the entire Imperial Guard
will pay the price!
Don't you dare!
Lai Luozhi,
you actually mobilized the
crossbow unit of the Imperial Garrison?
The Imperial Garrison's proven to be more
in tune with the times than the Imperial Guard.
Those in the Imperial Guard who refuse
to comply will be executed on the spot!
Lower your weapons!
Please,
Lord Shen.
My lord! My lord!
Bad news! Something major has happened!
Lord Lai has surrounded the Imperial Guard
with the Imperial Garrison!
Lord Commander and
everyone in the Imperial Guard
have been detained in
the prison of the Imperial Inspectorate.
Has Lai Luozhi really
made a move against Lord Shen?
Yes, really.
The IG and the II
have always been fierce rivals.
Given Chancellor Lai's usual temperament,
he must be eager
to eradicate everyone
in the Imperial Guard
and wipe out their entire families!
Everyone!
Wu Taiming!
What are you up to?
Are you going to hand over Xing?
Arm yourselves!
Yes, my lord!
Feng Gui!
Bring over my and Lady Yan's
appointment documents
from Her Royal Highness!
If he dares to come after her,
I will make it clear to him:
Yan Xing is not just
the wife of the commander of
the Imperial Guard,
but also Her Royal Highness' appointed
rank six chief clerk
in the Ministry of Justice!
Follow me!
Barricade the main entrance!
My lord! My lord!
How long has it been?
The men from the Imperial Inspectorate
still haven't shown up!
How many times must I remind you
not to let your guard down?
Stay vigilant!
Keep watch!
But they haven't shown up...
Alright, alright...
Who is it?
My lady.
Xing!
It's your brother!
-Xing!
-Mojie?
My lady!
-Xing!
-Uncle Zhong?
Open the gate!
Mojie!
My lady!
Uncle Zhong!
Father sent me to bring you home.
We will protect you as a family.
Mojie,
thank you.
Uncle Zhong,
today,
I will return to the Shen residence!
My lady...
Please!
I, Yan Xing,
extend my gratitude to all colleagues!
My lady, please.
Is this really our once-mighty
Lord Commander, Lord Shen?
I can hardly recognize you now.
Shen Du!
You truly lack wit.
Your stubbornness is impressive!
In the Imperial Inspectorate,
I've encountered all sorts of
tough men.
After a few rounds of torture,
if they refuse to comply,
then they would rather seek death.
Yet here you are, glaring at me
with such defiance.
I must admit, you have been
a truly worthy opponent
all these years.
The torture devices of the II
are indeed as fearsome as they say.
I, Shen Du, have finally
experienced them in my lifetime.
You are quite capable;
if you were to die,
wouldn't that be a great loss?
People call you The White Death,
and me the Dark Demon.
If we were to join forces,
The White Death and the Dark Demon,
who in this world
could stand against us?
I, Shen Du, a decent man,
would be ashamed to be
compared to someone like you!
You refuse to see...
It is widely known that
the two of us are
the Empress Dowager's right-hand men.
But do you realize
that she has long harbored suspicions
about our true intentions?
She has set us to spy on each other,
to fight among ourselves.
And she,
sits back to reap the rewards.
After all, she is the
most formidable woman in the world!
Everyone is under her thumb.
You are,
and I am as well.
Even the Shen Family
back then...
Has no one ever told you that
the downfall of the Shen Family was
orchestrated by the Empress Dowager herself?
And you,
you fool,
have knelt on the blood
of dozens from the Shen Family
for all these years,
acting as a lackey for your true enemy!
Any proof?
Proof?
Stop deceiving yourself.
You must have
come to understand that
during Shen Bingzhu's treason case,
there were several individuals
who took the opportunity
to exploit his downfall.
Why?
Because everyone knew that it was the
Empress Dowager who ordered his death!
Dozens of lives,
not a single one spared...
only you, a lackey, remains!
You're talking nonsense!
It's a lie!
A lie!
Yes,
you saw it.
The fire moth is me!
I am the true master
of the Fire Moth Sect!
Shen Du, you have witnessed
the might of the Fire Moth Sect.
Why not join me
in achieving something great?
My lady.
My lady,
Xiang'an City is now
under the control of Lai Luozhi.
Many officials who opposed him
have been assassinated.
You must exercise extreme caution
on your journey there!
Uncle Zhong,
no matter the challenges I face
on this journey,
I will not back down.
What happened back then
will not repeat itself.
I, Yan Xing,
must enter the palace
to seek justice from Her Royal Highness.
Remember to leave the door open for me.
Yes!
We bid you farewell, my lady!
Yan Xing, be wise,
don't go any further!
What if I refuse?
Do you intend to
continue assassinating
officials in broad daylight?
Has justice completely disappeared?
Are you alright?
Xing,
proceed with what you need to do.
Silly Yan Xing,
if you're trying to rescue your man, hurry!
Thank you!
Let's go!
I, a rank six official of the Ministry of Justice,
chief clerk, Yan Xing,
accuse the treacherous official Lai Luozhi
of abusing his power,
distorting the truth, and wrongfully
accusing Shen Du of the Imperial Guard!
Lord Shen Du, his loyalty
is unwavering, as clear as day.
I implore Your Highness to restore his honor!
I, a rank six official of the Ministry of Justice,
chief clerk, Yan Xing,
accuse the treacherous official Lai Luozhi
of abusing his power,
distorting the truth.
Lord Shen Du, his loyalty
is unwavering, as clear as day.
I implore Your Highness to restore his honor!
Her Highness is not seeing anyone now.
You should go back.
All is fated;
what you're doing is futile.
I, a rank six official of the Ministry of Justice,
chief clerk, Yan Xing,
accuse the treacherous official Lai Luozhi
of abusing his power,
distorting the truth.
I implore Your Highness
to restore Shen Du's honor!
Chief,
do you think I can be
considered a heroine today?
Absolutely!
Without a doubt!
Why are you smiling?
I was just thinking, how could
a girl like you wish to be a heroine?
Because only a true heroine
is worthy to be with a hero!
By the way,
how's your dowry coming along?
You've been the Chief Inspector for years;
you must have saved up
a fortune, right?
Once this is all over,
I will definitely throw you
a grand wedding
and invite all the delinquents
to attend it.
so you can marry me in style!
Really?
Of course!
A distress signal
from the brothers of the delinquents!
It's outside the city!
Chief...
Fear not!
Your attempts are futile,
- you petty villains!
- Yun Que!
On my command,
bail!
Bail?
Yes.
Return to the city and get Jiang Langxing;
bring reinforcements back.
This is an order from the Chief Inspector,
and you have to carry it out!
Yes, sir!
[This isn't right.]
[Xiangren wasn't asking me]
[to find reinforcements.]
[He knows there's no time for that.]
[He was trying to cover my escape!]
Xiangren!
Yun Que...
the grand wedding...
that I've promised
may not come to pass...
How should you address me?
My...
dear wife...
Let's face our fate together as family.
Good!
Now the power in the court
is firmly in my grasp.
Only that group of
obstinate delinquents
remain so uncontrollable.
The remaining pedantic scholars
are much easier to coerce
than those rascals.
Now that the delinquents are leaderless,
they won't make any real impact.
Now that the Chief Inspector is gone,
the commander of the Imperial Guard
should also see the reality.
Why did you bring me here?
On such a winter night,
you're invited here
to enjoy a different view.
If I hadn't been aware
that Yan Xing was a spy
sent by Lord Zhang to keep an eye on you,
I might have felt a pang of
sympathy for your deep affection.
I could almost shed a tear for you.
Your wife,
today, for your sake,
bravely stormed the palace gates
and knelt in the snow
for an entire day.
You didn't bring me here so late
just to see my wife, did you?
I find myself envious of you!
Why are there always so many people
willing to follow you into danger?
You might not realize yet, but to
ensure your wife's entry into the palace,
the Chief Inspector and his woman
have even sacrificed their lives.
What a tragedy!
How lamentable!
Lord Shen,
I believe after all these days,
you should have a sense of how
the situation will unfold, right?
You must have the answer already.
Do you still remember,
when I gave you
that vial of blood,
you promised me something back then.
Whether you're genuine or feigned,
I need you to be on my side.
Of course.
That's reassuring.
I believe that Shen Du
is certainly not
someone who would go back on his word!
My Lady!
I'm perfectly fine. Just some snow.
It's a pity, though, that
I couldn't meet Her Highness today.
I will try again tomorrow
to seek an audience.
Shen Du...
You've been released?
Did Her Royal Highness
allow you to return?
It was Chancellor Lai.
Chancellor Lai?
Lai Luozhi agreed to let you go?
He actually showed some kindness?
What happened to your face?
Let me take a look...
My love,
what's going on?
Yan Xing,
let's get a divorce.
What did you...
You and I
should get a divorce.
Divorce?
Why?
Did you encounter
some kind of danger?
Did Lai Luozhi
force you in some way?
What on earth happened?
Shen Du, you know me.
I am Yan Xing.
I'm a chief clerk of the Ministry of Justice.
Though my rank is modest,
I've handled
numerous significant cases
as a female official.
I'm not the kind of girl
who relies on her husband
for protection and support,
but someone who can stand by your side
and weather the storms with you,
like a steadfast mountain.
I'm not afraid of challenges
or hardships.
No matter what happens,
I can face it
alongside you.
Are you worried about implicating the Yans?
Shen Du,
if Lai Luozhi
was determined to target us,
even if we were to divorce,
he wouldn't spare my family.
We should work together
to find ways to protect them.
For instance,
we could send the Yans
out of town to avoid what's coming.
And also...
Yan Xing!
This isn't about your family,
and no one coerced me.
The reason is quite simple.
After everything I've been through,
I've come to realize
that weathering many storms,
what my family truly needs
is a graceful woman who can support me.
You cannot provide me
with a peaceful household, nor do you hold
your husband in the highest regard.
You are always competitive,
wanting to stand out.
You are not someone I can
envision spending my life with.