[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP22]
Xing is already married.
[And Caiwei]
is getting married soon.
[Yijiao,]
you're determined
not to go back with your husband,
[but what future is there for you here?]
[He came to call me back]
just for the sake of his family
or our family's
reputation.
[I finally have to return to the]
[seemingly glamorous yet desolate life. ]
Why can't I focus on studies
and take exams
to be an offcial like Xing did?
Even if being just a seamstress,
I can earn a living
with my own hands.
But if you divorced,
you would inevitably face scorn,
[and the entire family]
[would lose face.]
[Even your sisters]
would be belittled
by their husbands.
Father,
ever since I was little,
you've always stressed the importance
of our family's reputation.
It's certainly important,
but to trade for it
with Yijiao's lifelong happiness,
that's too much of a price to pay.
[Recently,]
[our family has endured many hardships.]
[But we didn't get through]
[any of them by relying on reputation.]
My dear,
please sit.
[Father,]
Shiyuan certainly would never
think less of me
because of Yijiao's divorce.
I'm sure Lord Shen
wouldn't look down on Xing
because of this either.
[As long as our whole family]
[doesn't think less of Yijiao,]
[then who else would look down on her?]
Caiwei is right.
My dear,
now that we've finally
found a peaceful life in Xiang'an
as a family,
[why sacrifice the children's happiness]
for the sake of
our reputation?
A father doesn't control a grown daughter.
You decide for yourself
what to do with the future.
Thank you, Father.
[Jinzang, you're here!]
[Erudite Yan.]
[Please, come in!]
This is for you.
Erudite Yan.
Come in, come in.
Congratulations.
Come, let's go inside.
[Xing,]
[- your uncle is here.]
[- Hi, uncle.]
Lord Zhang.
Come in, please.
Lord Zhang, please take a seat.
That's not right.
Shiyuan,
I only came here to...
You should sit
on the groom's side.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The groom's side. The groom's side.
Yeah, yeah,
of course, the groom's side.
When does the wedding start?
Xing,
did your father really agree
to Yijiao's divorce?
It's rare for him to put his children's
affairs ahead of his reputation like this.
That's great!
This way,
when you get a divorce,
your father would be used to it.
Me?
Your three-month pact
with the White Death is almost up.
I told you to prepare in advance
but you wouldn't.
Do you think the White Death
will give you a hard time then?
The White Death is still not here?
Chancellor Lai,
[please come in. Come in.]
The guests have not all arrived yet,
[you're starting already?]
[They would never start]
without you, Chancellor Lai?
[What?]
You, Erudite Yan and I
are all court officials,
you can come to this wedding banquet,
but I can't?
Plus,
when Xing was
poisoned by Chen Huo'e,
it was me who gave her the antidote.
I basically saved Xing's life.
So why can't I come to this wedding
and have a toast?
Of course
you can have a toast.
[Lord Shen,]
Chancellor Lai,
I apologize for not greeting you earlier.
Today
is my brother's wedding day.
I'm truly grateful that you've
both come to offer your congratulations.
[Why don't we take our seats first,]
[and we can catch up once we're seated?]
[Is that okay?]
Okay now.
Now that I've given you my gift,
I won't impose on you any longer.
Lord Shen,
I bid you farewell.
It's a great honor
to have everyone here today
to celebrate my daughter's wedding.
Yeah.
Please take your seats.
Let's sit down.
Please.
[The ceremony starts!]
Good, good.
Lord Zhang
left my father alone
about the official's transfer,
was it your doing?
No.
Really?
Thank you.
[Urgent report from Gannan!]
Your Highness,
urgent report from Gannan.
Gannan?
[Mo Qianzhi, the magistrate of Yingzhou,]
[has reported that]
Ganna has suffered cases of
people being ate by half-faced ghost.
What?
It is said that the half-faced ghost
attacks while people are unconscious,
and it only
eats one part of the body at a time.
When the victims wake up,
they would find their limbs missing.
Ridiculous.
How can such a menace
be allowed in the daylight?
At first,
it seems truly terrifying.
But upon closer reflection,
I find it shares similarities with
[the Chen Huo'e case.]
Trickery
and fear-mongering.
Your Highness, you're as wise as ever.
Rumors spread when the truth is unclear.
[I believe the priority]
[is to send capable individuals]
to Gannan at once
to help Mo Qianzhi
find out the truth
and stop the rumors.
Wan,
then who do you think
would be most suitable?
Your Highness, perhaps
you have already decided.
You...
Your Highness,
they're here.
- Shen Du.
- Yan Xing.
- Greetings, Your Highness.
Mr Shen.
Mr Shen,
[did you see?]
Someone is trying to exploit
the panic in Gannan
to incite chaos again.
[I remember]
Mo Qianzhi, the magistrate of Yingzhou,
and you have a past.
[Therefore,]
[I'm sending the two of you]
to Gannan to investigate
the half-faced ghost eating people case.
I accept your order.
Clerk Yan, please wait a moment.
Bring the brocade jacket to Clerk Yan.
Bring it here.
Her Highness
knows that you're going to Ganna for cases
shortly after getting married,
has specially ordered me to prepare
some windproof brocade robes
for you to choose from.
This is?
This is a secret decree
from Her Highness.
Open it.
[Clerk Yan,]
do you remember when I asked you
what you wanted for a reward?
Your Highness, I only wish
to be addressed as Clerk Yan
instead of Lady Shen.
You wanna be known as a female clerk
of the Ministry of Justice,
instead of Lady Shen.
My request today is for you
to carry out your responsibilities,
[serving the Ministry,]
[and me.]
Clerk Yan,
do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
I accept your order.
[Supernatural occurrences]
[are bothering Gannan.]
I fear that Magistrate Mo of Yingzhou
might have treacherous intentions,
[thus command you to secretly investigate]
his actions and
see if he has any alliances in the court.
[You can send report when seeing the]
[red-feathered carrier pigeon.]
[Did Her Highness issue the secret decree]
['cause the accomplice she suspects]
[to be is none other]
[than Shen Du?]
[Did she give this order solely to me]
['cause she's figured out our marriage]
[is a sham or is she testing me?]
What are you laughing at?
The brocade robes from Shazhou
are known for the exquisite embroidery.
I wonder
why you took so long
to choose this one.
It's truly a waste
of Her Highness's generosity.
Such embroidery
is everywhere in Xiang'an.
Her Highness rewarded it to me.
As long as I like it.
In my opinion,
this design is simple and tasteful.
Overdecorating it with embroidery
would rather be tasteless.
Okay, fine.
Since it's a reward for you,
as you wish.
[If Mo Qianzhi truly had ill intentions,]
[what would Shen Du do then?]
I was just curious
why my apprentice
suddenly
invited me for tea.
I got it.
You wanna know
the story of Mo Qianzhi of Yingzhou.
You should ask your
husband about this.
That would be
easier to do than asking me.
Why's that?
Mo Qianzhi
was the most beloved student
of Shen Du's father,
Shen Bingzhu.
No wonder.
So they've known each other for long.
More than that.
Mo Qianzhi
had great potential
and a bright future
until the major scandal of the Shens.
He risked his life to plead for Lord Shen,
helping Shen Du outta being killed
but to the Custodial Ward.
But he himself was sent to the frontier
and lost any chance for promotion.
Such a pity.
Truly.
Are you here to see me
'cause he's involved
in some case?
You know,
even though I'm retired,
I still have a knack
for analysis.
You're worried that
in investigating one man,
another closer to you
might get involved.
Did I guess right?
Master,
I still have much to learn.
When uncovering the truth,
you'll inevitably go through
what you're experiencing now.
No matter how small the detail
or how close the person,
the first thing is not to fear suspicion
but to have the courage to verify it.
Trust,
can also be a driving force
in pursuing the truth.
Okay, okay.
Now you know all that you wanted to know,
why don't you pour me another cup of tea?
Okay, master.
That's more like it.
Thanks.
Shen Du is going to Gannan?
But the things there...
[My Lord, don't worry.]
They've already been cleared up.
Alright,
let him go.
He might just
cause his own downfall.
But the letter
from the Imperial Secretariat has gone.
What?
Gone?
I've checked,
it's truly missing.
[Moreover,]
[it vanished around the same time]
[as the Imperial Academy exams,]
right after Lord Shen
took over the Capital Guards.
Shen Du,
could it be
that you intend to
reopen and overturn
the case of your family?
[Quickly, quickly.]
[Be quick!]
I've almost prepared all
you asked for,
except for those
that I just couldn't find.
However,
I still managed to find them
from my father's pawn shop.
How could your father agree?
No worries.
I'm his precious daughter.
Of course he would agree.
Oh right,
Xiangren is unable to see you off
due to the task at hand.
He asked me to remind you
to keep the token
he gave you safe.
If anything happens,
you can ask
for help from the Delinquents there.
Gosh,
I almost forgot.
Your dear friend Chichi's letter
was delivered to the Ministry of Justice.
Let me see.
Chichi said
she's already on her way to Yingzhou.
[That's perfect.]
I can bring all the gifts
I've prepared for her.
[Master,]
all those rare items you wanted
are here.
[Am I good or what?]
Eh,
all good. We should leave now.
- Take care.
- Master...
Goodbye.
Have a safe journey.
What are these rare items
even for?
They are all from my friends.
Friends?
They're making such a fuss?
We're only traveling with one cart
and the space is limited.
Let's travel light
and leave behind anything
unnecessary.
[My Lord, don't worry]
[about the cart.]
I just arranged for two more.
No matter how much luggage Her Lady has,
there's enough space.
This is a business trip,
not a social gathering.
Bring only the essentials.
These are all!
[Xing.]
Lord Shen.
Xing,
[I brought you something.]
Medicine for injuries,
salted pork and fish,
[and something from Caiwei and your dad.]
C'mon, Mom.
We only have one cart this time.
The space is limited.
We can only bring the essentials.
You don't have enough carts?
You father has one.
We can bring it here right now.
No need for that.
Jing Lin.
Yes.
Where are the other carts you just said?
I...
Should be here soon.
I'll go check.
Let's go.
Didn't he just say no to any new carts?
As I said, he speaks his way
and thinks another.
[You know, this job]
[was not easy.]
Let's go.
[Xing,]
[the frontier is harsh.]
[And this is your first time]
[you've embarked on such a long trip.]
You must be careful.
Don't you ever
pull a stunt!
Safety first!
Mom,
I'm going there for a case,
not a war.
[Remember,]
you must
take care of yourself.
And
tell Father
to dodge court disputes.
The farther, the better.
No matter what,
wait till we get back.
If you need anything,
remember to send a letter.
I know.
You don't have to
worry about things at home.
[But you know,]
[Far water does not put out near fire.]
if got into any trouble,
you should help each other.
Don't worry, My Lady.
I will take care of Xing.
Good then.
You're awake.
You were sleeping
so deeply that I thought
you could sleep all the way to Yingzhou.
I...
I just didn't sleep well last night.
I'm not usually like this.
[The scenery outside the city]
[is indeed different from Xiang'an.]
My Lady, what do you need?
Nothing, nothing.
I was just looking at the views.
Can I read it?
Halt.
You stand guard.
All of you, turn around.
Yes.
If you don't feel well,
you need to tell me.
Thanks.
I'm just afraid that you would throw up
in my carriage.
I will be more careful.
But the IG's carriage
is truly poorly driven,
making constant turns.
Since leaving the city,
we've been closely watched.
[If we hadn't changed lanes quickly,]
[how could we've shaken off the spies?]
[Spies!]
Northwestern woods.
Switch lanes quickly.
Yes, sir!
[I didn't realize there're]
so many people watching us on this trip.
This trip to Yingzhou
probably won't be that easy.
Imperial guards, carriage team,
stick to the planned route.
Meet us at Shanyang
after you've shaken off all the spies.
Remember what I said,
no one is to
disturb their rest.
Don't worry.
My Lord, My Lady,
the room is ready.
After you finish your meal,
you can go to your rooms and rest.
Jing Lin,
the luggage is still not here?
My Lady...
the luggage cart is going to be late
for about half an hour.
My Lord,
Her Lady's luggage
is filled with medicinal ingredients
for you.
You mean,
all those large boxes are filled
with kinda medicinal material?
Yeah.
They're collected by her
from different regions.
She probably knew you wouldn't eat them
[and wouldn't agree to bring them, so she]
[didn't tell you on purpose.]
Who's there?
Come here.
Master.
Help!
Help me!
[Qi Yeyun?]
You finally arrived!
Or he would have
snapped my neck!
Let me see.
[Shen Du,]
doing that to a kid?
You are too harsh.
What kid sneaks around
in front of people's room
in the middle of the night?
He must be either a thief or a spy.
Weren't you pacing in front of
[a room in the dead of night,]
[making noise that bothered me?]
Are you a thief or a spy too?
I just ate too much at dinner
and needed to digest.
Jing Lin!
Is this how you got rid of the spies?
Even a child was able to follow us.
It's my fault.
I didn't follow you all the way here.
[I only followed you]
[out of the city]
[and sneaked in the carriage]
[while no one was watching.]
[I hid in the cabinet under]
[the carriage seat]
[and brought here.]
[Master,]
am I qualified
to be your apprentice now?
[I want to learn from you]
and become a great detective
like you.
Master,
please take me in.
[Stop, stop.]
Don't call me that.
Xing is okay.
[Learning skills takes time.]
Since you already followed us here,
just stay.
[Then go back]
[to Xiang'an together with us.]
Thank you, Xing.
Jing Lin,
are there any spare rooms?
Yes.
I'll go arrange it now.
Jing Lin,
who told you to do that?
You're right.
We're
both appointed
by Her Highness to this case.
[What?]
I don't even have the right
to arrange a room
for a companion?
Du,
[I don't have to have a room.]
As long as you let me stay with you,
I'll even sleep in a barn or on the floor.
What
did you just call me?
Du.
[I was asked]
[to call her]
[Xing.]
Such being the case,
shouldn't I call you Du?
Is that not true?
If you...
don't like it,
how about Mr Shen?
Or Lord Shen?
I don't like any of them.
This is an official mission.
We don't have room for idlers.
And your small frame
won't handle heavy work.
Jing Lin.
Yes.
I'll chase this idler
out of the inn now.
Who told you to do that?
From now on,
he'll live with you.
- I...
- This way you can also train him,
so he's not just idling around.
What?
Shut up.
Is it that hard for you to handle a kid?
I accept your order.
Boy,
please.
Du,
don't!
[I don't want to train!]
How come
the courthouse hall is empty
in the middle of the day?
Lord Shen is coming.
Is there no one stationed
at Yingshou Prefecture?
[Greetings from Bi Qiu]
[of the Bureau of Yingzhou.]
I didn't know you were coming.
I apologize.
Never mind.
Where is Magistrate Mo?
[Sir,]
Magistrate Mo is out working on a case.
I already sent someone for him.
[He'll be here soon.]
[Magistrate Mo is coming.]
I'm Mo Qianzhi.
I apologize for not greeting you properly.
Please forgive me.
[Magistrate Mo,]
were you on a case earlier
and have been in contact with corpses?
How did you know?
Those who deal with corpses frequently
tend to show it.
You
must be
the renowned Clerk Yan
from Xiang'an.
Clerk Yan, your keen observation
is very admirable.
Xiang'an is very far from Yingshou.
Clerk Yan, as a woman,
the trip must have been
hard on you.
Thank you for your concern.
The journey went well.
I'm fine.
Qianzhi,
how have you been?
Mr Shen,
you're too polite.
I apologize.
[Since cases piling up,]
I didn't have time
to prepare a welcome banquet for you.
[It's all for the people.]
[Why don't we work on the case first?]
The sooner we solve it,
the sooner the people will be reassured.
What do you think?
How can that be?
Lord Shen has traveled a long way.
Even if there's no welcome banquet,
[you should've at least]
[prepared some tea.]
[You didn't do neither of these.]
[Isn't that]
disrespectful to him?
It's okay.
We did come for the case,
not for pleasure.
The sooner we close it,
the sooner we can
return to Xiang'an to report.
[Jing Lin,]
take Yeyun to get something to eat first.
Clerk Yan and I will go work on the case.
[Yes, sir.]
Mr Jing,
please follow me.
[Mr Shen,]
these are the files.
It's a corpse without the head.
[Be cautious not to be scared.]
She's not easily scared.
Don't underestimate my wife.
The victim's name is Li Kaixiang.
The suspect is his brother, Li Kairui.
They got into an argument after drinking.
Li Kairui passed out
after drinking a lot.
[When he woke up,]
[he found his brother's]
[head missing.]
We still haven't found it.
Did you find anything?
Judging from
the coagulation of the blood,
he must have been alive when
his head was cut off.
Decapitated alive?
Currently,
there're only two possibilities.
The first is,
the victim was
passed out when killed
with a single fatal blow.
The other is that,
the killer is an expert.
The victim was
not a match for the killer
[and thus was decapitated.]
[However, I just checked]
his skin.
No bruises at all.
I also examined his abdomen
and found no internal injuries,
which largely
rules out the second possibility.
That is a remarkable analysis.
[Great minds think alike.]
The Ministry of Justice's top female
detective truly lives up to her name.
Chi,
why are you here?
Ms Yan,
long time no see.