English subtitles are available
Bright Time EP14
Go, go!
Come on!
Great job, Lan Jinghui!
Take it easy, don't rush!
Keep going!
Lan Jinghui, keep it up!
Lan Jinghui, go!
Lan Jinghui!
Come on!
Great job, everyone.
It's okay.
We're not far behind
Class 1,
so let's
keep pushing.
Good effort, everyone.
Wu Ge.
How's it going?
Not bad.
Number 10 is playing well.
All right, listen up.
Gather around.
We did well in the first half,
just a few points behind.
No worries.
In the second half,
we need to closely mark
number 35 and 28.
One is strong, and the other
can shoot threes.
Ma Yiming,
in the second half,
we'll support you with fast breaks.
Got it?
Jian Zhiqiang...
All right,
you go ahead.
Let's talk after the game.
Hey,
who's that over there?
An old friend,
just catching up.
Great effort.
Keep it up!
Class 5 will win! We will win!
Go, go!
The other team is bigger.
Be careful and don't go head-to-head.
Don't worry,
I got this.
Lan Jinghui, go!
Go, go!
What's wrong?
What happened?
Move, move!
Give him some air!
Are you okay?
Glasses broken, I can't see clearly.
What do we do?
We don't have a substitute.
This is unfortunate.
This guy is really causing trouble.
Lan Jinghui.
If it doesn't work,
should we forfeit?
No way,
we can't forfeit.
It's okay, I can still...
Are you sure?
Don't push yourself.
How are you feeling now?
Without a substitute,
do we have
to forfeit?
No, we'll switch players.
Switch players?
Rest for a bit
and find some glasses.
I'll play.
Ling Dong can play basketball?
Did I see that right?
He can play?
I've never seen him on the court before.
Could he be
our secret weapon?
Can Ling Dong do it?
I don't know.
People who step up in these situations
are either game-changers
or complete rookies.
Violation.
Rebound!
Move!
Nice shot!
Double dribble.
Kicking the ball.
Violation.
Traveling.
What are you doing?
Can you even
play basketball?
Go! Go! Go!
Come on!
Defense! Defense!
Go! Go! Go!
Hurry, defense!
Go! Go!
Go, Class 5! Go, Class 5!
Come on!
Go, Class 5!
Go!
Go, go!
Go, Class 5! Go, Class 5!
Go, Class 5!
Lan Jinghui, congrats!
You guys were awesome!
Absolutely amazing!
It's okay.
Let's talk later. Let's go.
Mengyu, how was I just now?
Not bad.
You guys were so cool
out there!
Yeah,
especially that shot you made,
and Ling Dong's
final three-pointer, it was awesome!
Keep the compliments coming!
But actually,
that was only fifty percent
of my skill.
I haven't
shown my full...
Hey! That's my water.
You've really changed.
What's the big deal?
Thanks for your hard work today.
Just doing our part.
Great.
Next,
keep up the effort.
Oh, come on.
Why is he so annoying?
Struggled just to play against Class 1?
No wonder you're a bottom-tier team,
bringing in random people to play.
How do you know
he's random?
Maybe he's
our secret weapon.
Fine,
see you in the finals.
We will easily win the championship.
Don't you know
villains always lose because
they talk too much?
Who are you calling a villain?
Lan Jinghui.
Go do your thing.
We'll see.
Don't you think
you owe me an explanation?
What explanation?
Do you actually know
how to play basketball?
No.
So
you might
be a
once-in-a-hundred-years genius,
though
a bit behind me,
who's a once-in-a-millennium talent.
I told you,
there's no
downside to joining,
am I right?
Listen to me,
basketball is great
when you're tired of studying,
you know?
It helps build your core muscles,
improves coordination,
and has countless benefits.
Trust me, it's something
that benefits you for lifetime.
I don't
get you.
You need to strike a balance
among physical education, arts, and labor.
Do you understand me?
You don't have the energy
someone at your age should have.
Wait, why don't you
listen to me?
Besides,
the most important thing
about basketball
is improving your body coordination.
Look at me, I'm agile
and I don't
bump into them.
Are you listening?
Hey!
Listen,
you can walk slower.
I'm holding food.
But I've been telling you
about basketball
until my mouth is dry.
You won't
understand its charm
unless you play it yourself.
This sport
is so great.
It's competitive and demanding.
Only basketball
can bring
a team together,
do you get it?
I've never seen you this hungry.
See?
No one who doesn't
play basketball has this kind of energy.
But seriously,
the charm
of basketball
is that...
Ling Dong, Ling Dong!
How long are you going to follow me?
Until you join
our basketball team.
Why do you
want me to join so badly?
I don't care.
You stole
my thunder that day,
and I've already announced you
as our secret weapon.
You have to join our team.
Then come with me.
Sure.
Wait,
are you agreeing?
Is that what this means?
Why did you bring me here?
Give me the ball.
The ball.
Your shooting accuracy
is impressive.
It's a shame if you don't
join the team.
But my dad only taught me how to shoot.
Dad, you're amazing!
I want to learn to shoot too.
You want to learn?
Then Dad will teach you now, okay?
When you grow up,
Dad will teach you how to shoot, layup,
dunk, and dribble.
Ready, aim,
shoot!
Ling Dong scores!
The most crucial point,
Ling Dong wins!
When I was little,
my dad used to
bring me to this court.
Then...
why did you stop?
I didn't get the chance.
He passed away.
I'm...
sorry.
I didn't know,
I hadn't heard.
I'm really sorry.
So every time I miss him,
I come to this court.
He taught me how to shoot.
So you only know how to shoot,
nothing else?
Dad, when can I shoot
at that big hoop?
When you
grow as tall
as Dad,
you can shoot at the big hoop.
Then show me first.
All right, Dad will show you.
In that case,
we're actually quite similar.
I saw your dad, that day.
That's not what I meant.
I started
playing basketball
because of my dad too.
He came to see me in Singapore
for the first time, and I happened
to be playing in a championship game.
I won the championship,
and since then,
I thought
he liked me and paid attention to me
because I played basketball.
So
I kept playing every day
and gradually developed a habit.
Out of 365 days a year,
you're home
so little I can count
on my fingers!
I can't live
like this anymore!
No!
I'm doing this
to earn money for us!
Stop talking about money!
Okay?
It never ends!
I just want you home
with me and our son.
Is that too much?
You're not a good father,
let alone a good husband.
And...
I'm taking our child.
I'm telling you, Yu Lihua,
don't even think about it!
He's my son.
No way I'm letting you
take him!
If you want to leave, go alone!
He's my son too!
I'm taking him!
He's my own flesh and blood!
I...
So your mom took you abroad?
And then?
Ling Dong,
are we here
for stories?
Isn't this
why we're here?
Didn't you say
no one
taught you after that?
I'll teach you.
You're pretty talented,
learning quickly.
I'm a fast learner.
Why not
stop studying so hard
and play
basketball with me?
We could achieve greatness together.
What do you think?
I have my own goals.
All right, tell me.
What do you want to do?
Study physics at Jing University.
Jing University?
The one in the Jing City?
What else?
Sometimes
I don't get
why you top students
always pick
the hardest paths.
Isn't it better to
live happily?
But dreams are important.
What if you achieve them,
right?
It's not my dream,
just my
next step.
True,
you top students
usually achieve what you
set your minds to.
So,
have you rested enough?
If you...
Stop,
isn't it rude
to complain like that?
I've been seriously
teaching you basketball.
Shouldn't you call me
Coach Lan out of respect?
Are you going to keep teaching or not?
Your dad taught you
when you were little,
now it's me.
I've roamed the world
for years,
and maybe I've picked up some
fatherly wisdom.
How about calling me...
Big Cousin.
Stop messing with family titles.
Come on, Big Cousin.
It's just our class and Class 8 left.
Rivals meet again.
They are tough.
They have good players
and work well together.
Plus, there's that tough guy, Bi Peng.
Feels like we can't win.
Why are you scared?
Don't undermine our morale?
Class 8 isn't that scary.
I watched them
play against Class 4 yesterday.
Their defense
has gaps.
Since we can't improve
our skills quickly,
let's come up
with a strategy to outsmart them.
Wow,
didn't know
you had a knack for strategy.
How about
spying on their
practice tomorrow?
I'm not going.
Why not?
Didn't you do great
in the talent show?
Despicable.
Ma Yiming!
If he won't go,
we will.
Is it safe?
Let's go.
Jinghui.
It's fine.
Jinghui, I've got all the details.
Listen,
Number 13,
the point guard,
is good at passing and ball control.
His speed,
especially on defense,
is impressive.
Leave him to Xu Chao.
And
number 9,
the shooting guard,
is a three-point specialist.
He rarely misses
from outside.
No worries,
Ling Dong can handle him.
And then there's Bi Peng.
No need to say more, right?
Old rival.
Jinghui, Bi Peng
will be your responsibility.
Can you handle it?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Trust me.
Jinghui,
Class 8's average height
is around 1.9 meters.
What do we do?
We're much shorter.
You two, what are you up to?
Retreat!
Come in.
Mr. Guo.
Ms. Chai.
Ms. Fang.
- Mr. Zhao. - Still working?
Let's grab a meal.
No, thanks.
I don't want people
saying the basketball coach
is giving special treatment
to our Class 5.
We wouldn't want that.
Come on, Ms. Fang, it's just a meal.
Even a meal isn't right.
Plus, my class
is still practicing.
I need to check on them.
About that hotpot last time...
Excuse me.
Let me, let me.
No need.
Ms. Fang,
let me help you.
Go!
Nice shot!
Hey, it's our ball.
Everyone.
Ms. Fang.
Take a break, have some water.
Let us help you.
Thanks, teacher.
Thanks a lot.
How's it going, Lan Jinghui?
How's practice?
It's...
okay, I guess.
Just okay?
Yeah, all right.
And you three, how's it going?
- We're good. - Just okay.
- Mr. Zhao. - Mr. Zhao.
Training, huh?
How's the training going?
The game against Class 8 is coming up.
It's... still the same.
Seeing these
worried faces
reminds me
of our old basketball days.
You played basketball?
I know what they're worried about.
What are they worried about?
First, strong scoring ability
and quick breakthroughs.
Who else at our school can do that?
Who?
Bi Peng from Class 8.
Bi Peng from Class 8, right?
I confronted opponents
like Bi Peng before.
They all have
a fatal flaw.
What flaw?
Their technique is rough,
you know?
They only dribble with their right hand,
so
they're strongest when
breaking through from the right.
So what did you do?
When I defended him,
I focused on his right side
and eased up on the left.
Eased up on the left.
Anything else, Mr. Zhao?
Do you have
any other stories
like that?
And
when he posted up,
our guard
would strip the ball.
I kept his scoring
under ten points that game.
Did your team...
sorry,
I mean, your opponent,
have a
particularly strong center?
Yes.
How did you handle that?
At that time, their center,
whenever he was on the court,
we couldn't score.
We couldn't even grab a rebound.
So what did you do?
Our coach
was out of ideas,
so he picked the most
physically fit player on our team.
Zhiqiang!
Yes, just like your class's
Jian Zhiqiang.
Right?
He told him,
just push him out of
the three-second area, no matter what!
Push him out, you know?
Push him out.
Mr. Zhao, any other stories?
Yeah, any more?
Yeah!
We want to hear more.
Mr. Zhao,
please share with us.
Sure, but my throat is getting dry.
I got it, I got it.
Here, Mr. Zhao,
have some water.
Drink it.
Any other stories?
Back to the center.
That center had good skills,
height,
and scoring ability.
But he had one fatal flaw.
What flaw?
A bad temper.
When he got mad,
he made more mistakes.
More mistakes,
more fouls.
Mr. Zhao,
did your opponents ever have
a shooter who never missed?
Yes.
We played against the top-ranked team
in the province,
and their shooting guard
was deadly.
Don't give him an open shot.
He'd hit every time.
So what did you do?
Well...
I can't really tell you.
Why not?
You can tell us, Mr. Zhao.
What's there to hide? Tell us.
Sure it's not...
Mr. Zhao, it's fine.
You can tell me.
What did you do?
I want to know.
How did you handle him?
Simple,
just block his view.
And if they don't let you block?
If they don't let you block, just...
If they don't let you block,
can I poke him
like this?
No,
you can't do that.
It's against sportsmanship.
Just block him naturally.