English subtitles are available
Fall in Love with a Fox EP24
Tonight, the Majesty
is busy at attacking the Tingqin Garden.
This should be your best chance.
Did you get it?
You got it as expected.
The Majesty got distracted,
so I sneaked in and transcribed a copy.
But I moved the gear,
maybe he will notice.
You don't have to worry.
If anyone found out,
I will take all the responsibilities for you.
Give it to me now.
What?
You have got the thing,
then you want to threaten me with that?
No!
It's only that the canon
isn't as immensely powerful
as what you imagined.
People who practice this canon will be easily possessed by the Devil.
Even the Majesty can't escape this destiny.
If you force yourself to practice this canon,
I'm afraid that you will...
I can't deal with that much.
This is the only chance
that I can defeat Qu Zheng.
Even if I get possessed by the Devil,
I have no other choice.
If you still try to prevent me from doing this,
I won't be gentle to you anymore.
But even if you mastered this demon skill,
what will change?
Chu won't
change for you.
How do you know she won't?
When I kill Qu Zheng,
she will definitely come back.
But what if in this re-match
you are the one who die?
Do you think she will care?
The only one who cares about your life
is me.
I'm only a few years late
than her to enter Nonuple Palace,
and a few years later than her to know you.
Without her,
our relationship won't be like this.
Right?
Give me the canon.
If that's what you want,
I will give it to you.
Stop.
I said that
if you could help me
get the Puyuan Canon,
I will satisfy all of
your requests.
Say it.
You knew
the thing I want.
But you can't give it to me.
Baiwan
Baiwan, wait for us!
Don't you know that the entrance of Tingqin Garden
is already surrounded by
a bunch of guys?
You are now considered as a female villain.
Are you gonna die there?
But Zheng is in danger right now!
I have to find him!
What are you doing here?
Qingyun
You recognized me.
Come with me.
Where is this place?
Why did you take me here?
Haven't you already
got the Lingyao Herb?
Why don't you remember me?
You can't leave.
Even without the Lingyao Herb,
I will make you remember me.
Let go of me!
How can I let you go?
You are Chu!
You are my Chu!
Not Jin Baiwan.
Chu
Are you alright, Chu?
My name is Chu.
My name is Qingyun.
One.
Two.
Three.
Chu
Do you remember now, Chu?
I am Qingyun.
Qingyun
That's right.
I am Qingyun.
That day in Taoyuan Valley
I didn't recognize you at first.
But I remembered your voice.
Did you remember now, Chu?
I don't know.
My mind is a mess right now.
Look at this place.
Look at this place carefully.
This place is
our favorite
when we went on missions before.
Only both of us
know this place.
Do you remember this place?
Chu
Come with me.
Do you remember this tree?
Every time we
finished our mission,
you would curve a mark
on the trunk of this tree.
What are these?
Don't you remember?
These are our tombstones.
What?
Field missions are extremely dangerous,
so you made tombstones for us
in advance.
Do you still remember?
There was one time I almost died here.
You promised me that
you would be with me forever.
Sister Chu
The clean tombstone you made
may be used this time.
Don't talk nonsense!
Didn't you say that when you cure your eyes,
I'm the first one you want to see?
You haven't seen me yet,
I won't let you die!
I will ask Master to save you!
Chu
Can I not call you sister
from now on?
Why do you say this
during this urgent time?
If I survive,
can you be with me
for the rest of my life?
Don't say this.
I'll call our Master to save you.
No!
If you don't agree,
I won't let you go.
Alright,
I will all agree with you, okay?
Cure yourself first.
Okay.
Chu
Do you remember now?
You promised me that
you would be with me for the rest of my life.
From now on,
don't leave me alone.
I only agreed for
that was an urgent situation
back then.
Qingyun
Don't get me wrong.
What?
We grow up together.
I always treat you
as my young brother.
No.
You only cared about me
back then.
The summoning.
The Majesty is summoning
all the disciples to go back.
Wait for me here, Chu.
Take a good rest.
Wait for me to come back.
I killed so many people
in my past.
I am the killer!
Why lie to me?
I already punished the thief
who offended you.
My name is Xu Yifei.
Fate brought us together.
May I have your name?
Chu
Let go of me!
Squeeze harder!
We've only known each other for a few days.
You don't have to do this.
What if I say
that I've already fallen love with you
during these few days?
Just let go of me!
You will fall down, too!
Even falling with you together
is better than losing my love.
That's because
ever since you entered the valley,
you never told me
who is your Master.
I can't defy my Master's orders.
But I can promise you that
I'm not a bad person.
All the missions the Master gave us
are about maintaining justice,
and fighting evil.
You?
Yifei
Why did you lie to me?
The person who slaughtered Xu's family
is you!
All the missions you gave us these years
are all excuses for
making us killing your enemies.
I raised you for these years,
and this is how you repay me?
You did raise me,
however,
I can't just stand here and look
you fool the whole world.
I'll let the world know that
it is you who's been fostering Heisha
and killing the innocent people.
You were poisoned by the Wangyou Poison.
Today
I won't let you walk out of here alive.
Zheng
Zheng knew
about these things all along!
He didn't want
my memory to recover.
That's because he didn't want me to know
that I am a killer
who killed so many people.
He's been protecting me,
but I have been misunderstanding him.
That's right.
Zheng leaving me at the Escort Agency
was to protect me.
He went back to Tingqin Garden to
distract everyone's
attention.
Zheng
Baiwan
Jin Baiwan Baiwan
We can't go like this.
That Qingyun
must have taken Baiwan away.
What should we do now?
Why hasn't Song Jianshan
shown up now?
Let's do this.
You go to the town first
and gather some people.
I will stay here and wait for him.
Okay!
Qu Zheng
isn't a good person as I expected.
Now the Nonuple Palace
is sending wanted orders
to the rest of the world.
Lord of Valley Junior
What about revenging
by this chance?
No.
Qu Zheng and Jin Baiwan are Qiu...
Muqiu's friends.
I don't want to give them a hard time.
Stop!
Isn't she the woman
who's always with Jin Baiwan
in the Battle of martial arts by the lake?
That's right.
If we abduct her,
maybe
we can draw Qu Zheng
and Jin Baiwan out.
Don't come near me!
Do you know who's my father?
Do you know who's my hus...
Don't come near me!
Help!
That's Qiuer's voice!
Lord of Valley Junior! Over there!
Help!
Stay away from me!
Lord of Valley Junior
Don't forget!
You can't meet with Mrs. Yu now.
It's an emergency.
I can't worry about that now.
-No, no, no!  -Stay away from me!
If you go there now,
Taoyuan Valley will take the fall.
Let go of me!
-Move! Don't struggle.  -Let go of me!
Stop!
You are?
Capturing this woman is
to draw out Qu Zheng
and Jin Baiwan.
We are doing this for justice!
Bullying a fragile woman
can't be justified by any excuse.
Get out of my sight!
You...
Let's go.
Miss, are you alright?
I'm alright.
Thank you for saving me, hero.
The disguise is so lame.
But she didn't even recognize our Lord of Valley Junior.
Are her eyes alright?
I'm no hero.
It's great to know Miss Jin is alright.
How do you know that my family name is Jin?
Also,
your voice sounds so familiar.
Did we meet somewhere else before?
Right.
We've met in
the novels' fan meeting.
I've read your
"Barefaced Yu Lingfeng".
You like that one, too?
I...
You are...
(He is Shu.)
He has the face covered
because of the Martial Arts Bet.
I remember now!
You are one of my book fans, right?
That's right.
I'm your book fan.
We've met before
in the fan meeting.
That's right.
May I ask you, hero,
how should I call you?
You can call me Nameless.
Hero Nameless.
There is a hero called Nameless
in my novel.
Thank you for saving me, Hero Nameless.
But I have some important business.
Maybe we'll meet again in the future.
Please stop, Miss.
The Nonuple Palace
already put out the wanted order
to the rest of the world.
All the people in the martial arts world
are going to the Tingqin Garden.
This path is the only passage to there.
I'm worried of your safety.
May I escort you?
You?
Your Majesty
All the schools already surrounded the
Tingqin Garden for a long time now.
But Qu Zheng never showed up.
Today,
let us kill
the villain Qu Zheng,
and the traitor Chu.
If they don't come out,
we will
attack the Tingqin Garden
directly!
Yes, your Majesty.
Host Jing Yuan
Today, all the heroes gathered here
to kill
the Lord of Tingqin Garden, Qu Zheng,
and the rouge disciple of Nonuple Palace,
Chu.
These two connived together.
Five years ago,
they killed Xu's family
and stole the Puyuan Canon.
Five years later,
they want to use this Canon
to bring the whole world into chaos.
They practiced the demon skill with Puyuan Canon
to absorb others' force,
and kill innocent people.
Kill them!
Swipe the evilness!
Zheng
There are more and more people
gathering outside.
Even...
Even Jing Yuan came.
Should we
take our disciples to battle them?
There's no need to panic.
I've already got a plan.
What plan?
You always tell me everything.
Also,
do you know that Miss Jin
is worried about you?
I know.
Villain Quzheng
Chu
Do you dare to come out and fight us?
Cowards.
If you choose to do so,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
Everyone, listen to my order!
Yes, your Majesty!
Follow me to attack in!
Let's kill these two
disloyal, unfilial,
merciless and unjust villains.
Yes, your Majesty!
Disloyal,
unfilial,
merciless and unjust villains
must be killed.
But the one you should kill
isn't Qu Zheng.
But the one who fooled the whole world,
yet act like a saint
whose heart are full with evilness.
Who are you?
Chu
The one you are looking for
is me, right?
Chu
No!
Traitor Chu
You conspired with Qu Zheng,
betrayed your school,
and hid the canon.
You are deemed to death.
But
if you are willing to repent,
call Qu Zheng out
and admit your crime,
I can
give you a chance.
The person who sinned
surely needs to be punished to death.
But we both know
who this person is.
I know,
everyone is here
to kill me today.
But I am the
only survivor in Nonuple Palace's mission
to get back the canon.
Don't you guys want to know
who has kept the real Puyuan Canon
today?
Villain!
How dare you lie to the whole crowd?
Capture her!
Who dare to touch me!
All you guys who gathered here today
are ones who
can see the truth for themselves.
Everyone will know whether I'm lying
when they hear my words.
You keep trying to shut me up.
Are you afraid of me to uncover the truth?
Nice speech.
Zheng
Since everyone's here
to be guest of my Tingqin Garden.
Then let me
uncover the truth for everyone.
Qu Zheng
You finally show up.
You slathered Xu's family,
stole the Puyuan Canon,
and practiced the demon skill.
Today,
I will represent the whole world
to punish you!
Wait!
These are not...
Yes,
I did all the things.
No!
Don't listen to him!
You already admitted all of your crimes.
What else do you want to say?
Host Jing Yuan
How long
do you want to play dramas
with your beloved disciple Chu
in front of me?
When you sent
your Envoy Xueyue Chu
pretending to get amnesia to approach me
and trying to get my trust,
your goal is to
collect all of the
evidence of my crime.
Then,
you claimed that
she's a rogue disciple
to continually deceive me.
That's the filthy method
a so-called decent school used.
Zheng
What are you talking about?
I never lied to you.
Even now
you are still acting to fool me.
You are under
Jingyuan's order in the first place
to deceive me with all the means.
I didn't!
Yes.
Like you wished,
I fell in love with you.
I plotted against the whole world,
but you are not in my plan.
However,
I've figured out the true form
of the decent schools.
Yet you are still trying to fool me.
I didn't.
That's right.
Chu did all of these things,
enduring the humiliation,
to fight against a villain like you!
Zheng
I,
I remembered everything now!
I know that
you are saying all of these just because of me.
Of course this is because of you!
If it's not because of you,
how would
I put myself in this kind of situation?
But I don't want you to do this.
I want the whole world to know.
Things happened five years ago
didn't go like this.
He is not Qu Zheng.
What?
He is Xu Yifei.
How dare you to hurt her?
Baiwan
Zheng
Be careful.
Don't pull the wound.
Where is Zheng?
What happened to Zheng?
He hurt you so bad.
Why are you still worrying
about his safety?
Please tell me now.
What happened to Zheng?
You...
Don't worry.
After he stabbed you,
Jing Yuan ordered everyone to attack.
It's a hard battle.
Both party suffered a lot.
However,
Song Jianshan protected Lord Qu,
and they retreated back to Tingqin Garden.
Many schools retreated
from Tingqin Garden
in the two days when you passed out.
So,
he is safe now.
Right?
He is alright.
But he hurt you so bad.
Qiuqiu
The stab wound looks dangerous,
but Lord Qu
avoided all the important parts
in Baiwan's body.
But Baiwan,
what's going on?
Yes,
why did Lord Qu
stab you that day?
Also, what did he mean
that day?
Besides,
why did they say that Lord Qu
is a villain who can not be forgiven,
but you are the one who exposed his crime?
Everything that he had done is
to take the fall for me.
Zheng
Is it worth for you
to do all these things for her?
As long as she's safe,
it's worth.
But even though you sacrificed yourself to this extent,
there's no guarantee
that Jing Yuan won't hurt her anymore.
He won't have the chance to do that.
Zheng
what exactly happened to you?
I'm fine!
You are not fine.
You always act like this lately.
What are you hiding
from me?
Please go out.
Zheng
Get out.
I want to eat this!
This?
Okay.
Slow down. Is this hot?
Husband Xu looks at
his Wife Zhang with deep affection.
On her cheery-like lips,
he lightly...
I can't read this to you anymore.
Baiwan
Your memory
have fully recovered.
I can't let Jingyuan
hurt you anymore.
Therefore, this battle between me and Jingyuan
has to be quick.