[English subtitles are available]
[Bright Time]
[EP22]
Any news on him?
Ms. Fang and Mr. Zhao
are out looking.
No,
I need to search too.
Ling Dong,
hold on.
No.
Ling Dong?
Why are you here?
Ms. Fang,
did you find Lan Jinghui?
Not yet.
Let's wait here.
If he's not back
by morning,
we'll call the police.
Lan Jinghui?
You're finally back.
Wait, what's going on?
You finally decided to show up?
Do you know how worried
Ms. Fang was?
Where were you?
Why was your phone off?
I was dealing with something.
Where's my phone?
Lan Jinghui!
Wait...
Ms. Fang, listen.
I really just
went for a walk.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Enough.
It's a misunderstanding.
Knees bent!
Hands up!
Misunderstanding?
What did I misunderstand?
This is unbelievable.
Look at
the time.
Do you know
how worried everyone was?
You're just wasting time.
I really...
I warned you repeatedly.
What if
something happened?
Huh?
I shouldn't have agreed
to bring you here.
I didn't do anything wrong, Ms. Fang.
Wrong?
What did I accuse you of, Lan Jinghui?
Listen,
stay squatting for 2 hours.
Don't get up until then.
You're driving me crazy.
Calm down.
It's okay now.
Lan Jinghui,
if you knew
this would happen,
why did you do it in the first place?
So, where did you go?
I...
I went to handle something important.
Jinghui!
Sis, why are you here?
Sis?
You were
into dancing that
you forgot your phone.
So, this is where you were.
You're so
forgetful.
Luckily, you told me
you were staying at this hotel
across from the square,
so I brought it
right over.
Ladies, dancing?
Sweet talker for your age.
Patience.
After this dance,
it's partner time.
Join in then.
No, wait.
Stop dancing.
There's a partner dance?
That's right.
Let me talk to you for a second.
Sis,
here's the thing.
My friend
has an
important exam tomorrow
and needs a
quiet place to study.
Can you
postpone the dancing
until tomorrow?
Sis, sis,
could you halt, please?
I bought some things for all of you.
Let them come over and get it.
Ladies, come here.
Ladies,
come over.
I bought something for you.
I got you
headphones.
Headphones for everyone.
That's high-tech. Do we need to pay?
No, it's free.
Everyone gets one.
How...
how can we dance with headphones on?
No problem.
Just dance as usual.
The music
will play through
the headphones.
Silent but effective,
right?
Come on.
Slow down.
Everyone will get one.
Okay.
Ladies, I have to go now.
No, you stay.
Ladies,
I can't dance today.
My friend
has something important tomorrow.
I really
have to go.
Okay, okay.
I was
looking for my phone
but I can't find it.
I realized
I must have left it at the square.
Your dancing was great.
Come back next time.
Thanks to you teaching me.
Sweet talker!
Lan Jinghui,
I didn't expect
you were dancing.
Just thinking...
just thinking about
you dancing
makes me laugh.
I... wait...
Why are you two laughing?
I'm a rising star
in the square dance scene.
All right,
stop laughing.
Sis, one question,
do you dance in the morning too?
Didn't you
give us headphones?
Don't worry,
your friend can study in peace
and do well on the exam.
Thank you!
I'm off.
Goodbye.
I'll walk you out.
We'll walk you out together.
[You dance really well.]
[Really?]
[Yeah.]
[All thanks to you ladies.]
Okay,
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood you.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Ms. Fang,
in that situation,
I find it hard to explain.
I probably
squatted too long.
My legs went numb,
and my brain got fuzzy.
Lan Jinghui,
I've seen you playing around
and not looking tired.
And squatting for me
made your leges numb
and stiff?
Mr. Zhao,
give him
a massage?
All right, I misunderstood you.
Let me help you stretch.
No, it's fine.
I'm fine, really.
It's getting late.
I'm tired and need rest.
I'll should get going.
I'll help you.
No need.
Let me stretch you out.
I'm fine now.
Then I'll head up too.
Ling Dong,
the hotel AC
is pretty cold.
Haven't you been sleeping well?
I'm ok.
Never been better.
Seriously?
No way.
Mr. Zhao said
he almost caught a cold this morning.
I'll ask
for more blankets
for you two.
Ms. Fang, you're so thoughtful.
Caring about us all the time.
Ms. Fang, I got
a blanket last night.
Wasn't that from you?
No, it wasn't me.
Did you ask for it?
No, not me.
Strange.
Snacks
and blankets.
Does it offer special treatment
for examinees?
Maybe.
Anyway, I'm heading upstairs.
All right, good luck tomorrow.
Thanks.
Bye.
Rest well.
Lan Jinghui
seems scatterbrained,
but
I really misjudged him this time.
Yeah,
he seems mischievous,
but now
I see him differently.
Oh,
by the way,
have you eaten?
I'm not hungry.
It's still early.
How about
get something to eat now?
Really?
You don't want to?
Then never mind.
I do.
Ms. Fang,
what do you want?
Anything.
What do you feel like?
How about spicy hot pot?
Sure, my treat.
Let's go.
Respect!
Well,
how was the exam?
Was it easy?
It was okay.
Hi.
Have a seat.
A mission impossible for me.
Class rep, did my sunny doll work?
It worked well.
Thanks, Qingtian.
No problem.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Ling Dong, this is for you.
It rehydrates you.
Xiaohua,
why didn't you
get me a drink?
I've been helpful.
Why don't I
get to rehydrate?
Ms. Fang.
There's a vending machine.
Get one yourself.
Well, well, Xiao Xiaohua,
you've gotten bold,
talking back
and making faces?
Enough.
Ms. Fang has something to say.
Exams are over,
so you have
free time now.
Go out and have fun.
But
be back by 8 PM,
understood?
Got it? 8 PM.
Isn't 8 PM early?
We can't enjoy much
by then.
So what?
8 PM is late.
How about 7 PM?
Or 6 PM?
Or
if you don't want to go out,
just tell me.
No, no,
that's not what I mean.
I mean,
8 PM is perfect.
Then...
Ms. Fang,
you're the best teacher
in the world.
We love you.
All right, enough flattery.
Now,
go have fun.
We're off then.
Goodbye.
Bye. Bye.
Have fun but stay safe.
Keep
your phones on
24 hours.
Yes, got it.
Goodbye, teacher.
Have fun!
Jing University?
Didn't you
want to see the physics lecture here?
Never mind,
it's too crowded.
And today's Open Day.
It's hard to get free tickets.
Knew you'd say that.
Tickets?
Master, you're amazing.
How'd you get them?
Well...
Why are there so many people
at this Open Day?
I have the same question.
They were all waiting their turns.
If my girlfriend didn't force me,
I wouldn't be here.
What about you?
My friend
wants to apply the university next year,
so we're checking it out.
Your friend?
It's super hard
to get in here.
Only a few
make it each year.
Totally.
I'm telling you,
my deskmate's here
for the
national physics exam.
National, you know?
Not everyone
can participate in this.
It adds points to
entrance exam scores.
Your girlfriend must be impressive.
It's a guy.
Ticket distribution starting now.
Don't crowd.
Register on the left, tickets on the right.
Next.
Okay.
Three tickets, please.
One per person.
You think
this small stuff
can stump me?
I got the tickets with different ID.
Master, you're amazing.
Without you
getting tickets early,
we wouldn't have
gotten into Jing.
It's nothing.
If you really
want to
thank me,
well...
my throat's dry.
How about a bottle of water?
Sure, on my tab.
What?
I'll buy it for you at school.
What about you?
Since you're aiming for Jing University,
I'll ramp up
your tutoring
when we're back.
What? No need, I think.
No room for discussion on this.
Why?
You're way off target.
[What? That's crazy!]
If I make it into this university,
my whole life's
gonna change.
Everyone here
just oozes energy and confidence.
You aiming for it too?
I'm not gonna make it.
But Ling's got it in the bag.
Come on, let's check the front.
If our school had this grass,
I'd be chillin' here all the time.
Take a photo of me.
You guys always
walk with all that jumping around?
Our version of life's journey.
Hey, time's ticking,
where's that
physics lecture?
Auditorium 2.
[I]
[scoped it out.]
It's over there.
But if we don't hustle,
we'll be
cutting it close.
I wanna check out
the Art Department.
We'll
regroup here in a bit.
Alright, so...
Sure.
See you later.
Yeah.
We're leaving then.
Let's go.
Hey, check it out.
If you order it with an iced lemon tea,
you can get 20% off.
Hi, there.
You can use
these coupons together.
Your friend gets half off.
Why giving it to me?
Toss them away.
These coupons are a mess,
I don't know how to use them,
so why keep them?
Yeah, it's
all tricks,
but if you play your cards right,
you can get the most bang
for your buck at restaurants.
Really?
Yeah.
Look.
This spot's
got its own deal,
but these two share
a discount.
And using
your phone to pay,
you can get
15 off 50.
How do you know all this?
They mentioned it,
plus it's right here on the flyer.
How come I missed it?
Basic stats,
that's all.
You're so good!
Craving some takoyaki?
How about that sushi joint?
They give us
a free serving of takoyaki
when we spend over 30.
So we should
be able to eat
all the food you want
for just
127.8 yuan.
You're really impressive!
Why're you staring at me?
I ain't no takoyaki.
No way,
you're my sidekick.
Today, you're officially
in the Rooftop Crew.
Rooftop Crew?
What's that?
Anyway,
you're in, like family now.
Let's go.
[Don't dirty up the darker parts.]
Keep the layers and depth going.
Nice job, Xingchen.
Is Professor Yang this popular?
Nice to meet you, guys.
You too.
[I'm delighted to]
[be here today, sharing and]
[discussing physics with all of you.]
I've noticed something interesting.
In a lot of
sci-fi stories,
when they're
stuck with
a tough logic problem,
they just
wave their
[magic wand of]
[quantum mechanics]
[and]
[everything's]
[good to go again.]
[It's almost]
[like a cheat code:]
quantum mechanics fixes everything.
[It speaks to]
[how complex]
[and elusive]
quantum mechanics
can be.
But don't worry,
I'll try to explain it
in a simple,
down-to-earth way
for us all to understand.
[About 1.3 billion years ago,]
two black holes
were merging,
[with masses of]
[36 and 29 times.]
[the mass of]
[our Sun respectively.]
[They were orbiting each other.]
The exciting news is that
China has designed and built
its very own FAST.
Its emergence
has directly usurped
the position of the Arecibo,
making it the world's largest
radio telescope by aperture size.
This marks a breakthrough
and rise of Chinese technology.
[It's a voyage]
[like no other,]
[one that will demonstrate to humanity]
[that our exploration can reach]
[beyond a hundred billion light-years.]
Xingchen.
I'm going out for a moment.
Will you monitor the class for me?
Right.
Remember everyone,
once you're done painting,
chill for a sec.
Step back, give it a good look,
and maybe squint a bit.
[That way, any out-of-tune spots]
[will pop right out at you.]
Hi.
What's your major?
I... I don't...
I'm just here for a visit.
An art student?
No...
I saw your painting,
your color sense is really good.
Not many
art students can pull that off.
Thank you.
Come with me.
About ten years ago,
humans observed the Higgs Boson
for the first time.
I'd like to
ask you,
what do you think
is the difference
between it and gravitational waves?
The student who's nodding off,
yes, you there.
You must think
my question is too easy
to pique your interest.
[Well, then,]
[I'll ask you to answer it for me.]
What were we talking about?
I lost track of it.
Einstein predicted the existence
of gravitational waves a century ago,
while Higgs predicted
the Higgs Boson half a century ago.
The Higgs Boson
is crucial
to the Standard Model,
but it also
comes with many
limitations and uncertainties.
[The discovery of gravitational waves,]
[on the other hand,]
[is like opening a telescope for us,]
[allowing us to use it]
as a cosmic probe
in the future
to explore even
more about the universe.
Are you from our physics department?
Not yet.
Alright.
I hope to
[see you again]
in my class someday.
You will, professor.
Okay.
Let's continue with the lecture.
I never knew we could paint like this.
Painting's all about
expressing yourself,
so go wild with it.
College is about
learning the rules
and then breaking them,
pushing past what's normal.
It's amazing to be in this space.
I bet the artists whose work
is displayed here are all super skilled.
You've got a natural gift.
Ever considered taking up art?
I...
I can't.
Why?
My mom doesn't want this.
so
I'll stick to it as a passion
project.
Let me ask you,
why do you enjoy painting?
When I was little,
my dad worked at an art museum,
and I'd always tag along
when he went to work.
While he was busy,
I'd roam around the galleries,
and those paintings
on the walls
became a part of my childhood memories.
That's how I fell in love with painting.
Whether I'm happy
or sad,
I use my pencil to capture it all.
You see,
every painting here
is a world
created by the artist.
Just like you,
they use painting to express
their understanding of this world.
Has anyone ever told you
that you're a talented painter?
Isn't Lan Jinghui here yet?
Yeah.
You have a great talent for painting.
But I think he's just
being nice.
And seeing
these paintings
just makes me feel
even more inadequate.
Someone once told me that
there's no such thing
as a genius,
most people are ordinary.
The difference between those
who seem like geniuses
and ordinary people
is that they strive
to do their best
in everything,
while the latter
often think they can't.
Nothing
in this world
comes easy.
And remember,
the brush of life
is in your own hands. Give it a shot
or you'll never know what you can do.
Come here.
This is for you.
I hope this comes in handy for you.
Thank you.
This
art gallery's
pretty well-known.
Need me to snap a pic of you
as a souvenir?
No need.
Why?
I think I'll be coming back here again.
Bye.
Looking forward to seeing you
as my classmate next time.
It's you.
It started raining all of a sudden.
What's this?
Admission info and
brochures for Jing University.
Put it in my bag.
Okay.
I've decided!
I'm aiming for Jing University.
Xiaohua.
Telling my dad
I wanna go to JU
was just a spur-of-the-moment thing.
It's not because of you.
I've discovered
my passion here at
Jing University.
I really hope you can
stand by me and support me.
Getting into
the Art Academy of JU is tough.
[Sure.]
Xiaohua, I'm on your side.
But
if you can dream it,
you can do it.
Yes.
The brush of life
is on my own hands.
Give it a shot.
Alright.
I'm in!
Let's all apply for JU.
Well, I...
Come on, don't deny it.
Your eyes lit up like Christmas trees
the moment you arrived at JU.
Yeah, Ling Dong.
You're destined for
JU's Physics Dept.
Who else could fill your shoes?
Hey, slow down!
You're leaving me with nothing to say,
huh?
So we've got a deal then?
Deal.
Yes, deal.
Jing University,
we're on our way!
[As I uttered those words,]
[it felt like I had sprouted wings.]
[I could hear them flapping.]
[Looking down at the campus,]
[I felt this rush of power.]
[The road's gonna be tough, but]
[I'm gonna keep going and make it big.]
[Lan, Ling,]
[let's go for it!]
I'm so full.
So full.
Bye.
Bye. Good night.
Good night.
Bye.
Hi.
Hey, I gotta say,
the AC in here
is blasting
and I'm freezing
at night.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
But the AC
is set to
a uniform temperature.
Let me see if I can
get you an extra blanket instead.
Yeah.
Could you please also
send one to room 2069?
Please make sure not to forget 2069.
Sure.
While you're at it,
could you add room 2070
to the list and
send a blanket there too?
Okay.
Thanks.
If Ling's cold, Chen must be too.
Let's go.