Hello Debate Opponent 2
EP19
Xiwang!
Let daddy kiss you.
You didn't stay up all night, did you?
I can think of nothing
but her eyes, her smile,
and my infinite devotion to her.
In the end,
she still chose to leave.
Let me ask you something.
His name is Gong Chen,
the Prince Charming of Xiaoyu in high school.
Fitness, swimming, or debates,
he excels in any of those.
Besides, he was the winner
of three consecutive debate tournaments,
and won the title of Best Debater for numerous times.
During high school,
he went to study abroad.
Look, he is capable, good at study,
handsome…
Wait, wait!
What? You don't want to hear it?
Did I ask you about that?
What are you talking about!
Then what do you want?
I mean, your chips have expired.
I just helped you eat more.
Expired?
I think this is a good argument.
Love is essentially a type of relationship.
And all relationships
require management.
Let me write it down.
It's not right.
For family members,
is management still required?
Isn't it?
No, it's not.
No matter how much I disobey,
my father and I, we are still like comrades in arms.
That's because your father
manages it well for you.
That's because blood is thicker than water.
It doesn't need management.
As for love,
if it requires no management,
it is true love.
What do you mean?
What I mean is,
that in love, we should let nature take its course.
Let nature take its course
and you just wait to die alone.
I am talking about the debate topic.
I'm talking about the debate topic, too
Love dies without management.
That states the topic.
But the topic limits it
to the love of college students.
More than 95%
of the campus romance
ended in failure.
Is there anything wrong?
Let nature take its course,
enjoy the beauty of pure love
and let it end without a cause.
That is the mission of a college relationship.
Is there anything wrong?
Yes, there is!
Xiaoyu!
Why are you here?
Why is he here?
Why are you shouting?
Who's shouting?
What's up?
I gave her the gift as you suggested.
She really liked it.
She liked it? Then that's good.
Right.
You all knew that, right?
Your opponent in the next match
will be our team.
Nan Bei!
The next competition
is a two-person competition.
Any volunteers?
Since the topic is about love,
of course,
a couple would be the best.
You and me, let's go?
Aren't you a dictator?
Just decide it by yourself.
Let's try it, OK?
Did you ask me for my opinion?
Ah, no, you don't have to.
Why are you talking in such a sarcastic way?
Why don't you give it a try?
OK, I'll be the first speaker.
But,
the rule in this game is the second speaker would do the rebuttal.
Aren't you good at rebuttals?
You'll be the second speaker, OK?
No!
What again?
How do you know what I'm good at?
Don't push it too far, Nan Bei!
I'm angry now.
Xiaoyu, he is waiting for you to say something sweet.
I'm not doing that!
What?
Groveling is love?
I'd better go broke.
How about you and me form a team?
You and me? I don't think it's good.
In terms of tacit cooperation,
Hao and I will make a better team. Don't you think so?
How long have you been in our group?
It's time for lunch.
How about I invite everyone to lunch?
No need, Hao.
I have painting class this afternoon.
I have to hurry up.
I'm leaving now, Xiaoyu. Bye.
As long as you are buying,
I will always be available.
Guys, no one wants to come?
Then we'll leave first.
Do you have time?
Have lunch with me, OK?
Hello!
What's going on?
I told you to wait for me.
Why do you come to school?
OK.
OK, then I'll come to you.
Who is that?
He said earlier in the dorm
that his childhood friend would come to visit.
Childhood friend?
The monitor of his class in primary school.
You know when he was a child,
Nan Bei was naughty.
The teacher then assigned him
to be the deskmate of the monitor.
That's how the story went.
The story about a naughty boy
and a straight-A girl
who helped tutor his homework.
An eye for an eye. A tooth for a tooth.
You think
why are those two making such a fuss.
They are just bored.
They have no better things to do.
Now you got angry, right?
Now you got upset, right?
Finally, you knew how I felt
when I hated Gong Chen, right?
Put yourself in my shoes for a moment!
I'm sorry, Nan Bei.
I know I did wrong.
I'll never do that again.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
Give me a feedback after you taste it.
Next weekend,
in the coffee bar near our school,
there will be a Hitchcock film exhibition.
Let's go together?
I'll think about it.
Thank you.
What?
I was thinking about Xiaoyu and Nan Bei.
Actually,
I quite understand Nan Bei's feelings.
You see, the two of them,
after all the ups and downs,
finally got together.
Suddenly appeared such a person
better than him
in every aspect,
an ex-Prince Charming.
It's quite normal to feel a little upset.
I think Nan Bei asked for it.
I thought
you would be on his side.
Both are young people.
It's quite normal to experience such a period.
Besides, Xiaoyu is a good girl.
That's true.
But I always feel like
Xiaoyu should
think more about
the feelings of Nan Bei.
Now you are doing it again.
You just want to make everyone happy.
Look, the noodle is clumped already.
But I think
if two people are together,
they should care more about
each other's feelings.
I think that no matter what,
it should be your own feelings
that are more important.
I think,
still, it's better
to put the other one's feelings first.
Do you think
that two people being together
see many things differently,
would it be a problem?
Not a problem.
Come on, take a break.
What are you guys doing here?
Ma Nan said,
sports
helped to forget sadness.
Hmm.
Then why don't you go out for a run?
Ma Nan said,
the lion dance
would stimulate the endorphin of the body.
What kind of nonsense are you spreading here again?
The endorphin is a hormone in the body,
also known as happiness factor.
When you exercise
to a certain amount,
the endorphin effect will be generated in the body,
people will feel happy,
and all the unhappiness and stress will be removed.
But
just this amount of exercise
is not enough.
You have already
implemented your plan, right?
Why are you like this again?
It does not work on that heartless Xiaoyu.
So what are you going to do?
For love and justice in the world,
I will do some real stuff.
You're not tired of hearing it?
I think this song
is about me.
I read it online before
that when people lose love,
they hear their own story
from every love song.
I used to feel that's melodramatic.
Now that I see you like this,
it seems to be true.
What are you going to do after this?
I don't know.
She blacklisted me on WeChat,
and also my phone number.
When I went to her dorm today,
I was stopped at the door by her roommates,
and was told
to stop wasting my time.
I can bear all these, really.
I just don't understand
why she did this to me.
I buy her drinks when she's thirsty.
I buy her food when she's hungry.
Even in the middle of the night when she said
she wanted to eat watermelon,
I ran ten kilometers
to some
24-hour fruit shop
to buy it for her.
But look at her.
She said no more contact, and she just cut all the connections.
She said she would leave, and she just left.
Was I not good enough for her?
Everyone would experience
their first relationship.
She will know how good you are.
And you, what about you?
What happened between Xiaoyu and you?
Had a quarrel?
Just need to put us into each other's shoes.
I thought it was normal.
But when Gong Chen
actually showed up in front of me,
I remembered
that Xiaoyu had a crush on him,
and
he was quite excellent,
then deep inside,
inexplicably, I felt irritated.
Look,
can we listen to another song?
Are you still bickering with Nan Bei?
I'll leave him rot.
Strictly speaking,
Nan Bei is your first love, right?
Not strictly speaking, he still is.
Then try to think like this,
he was unreasonable and jealous,
but it just proves that he cares about you.
There are so many ways to care.
Why he had to choose
such an annoying way?
You both are in love for the first time.
When expressing emotions,
you inevitably couldn't make it perfect.
Think about it, were there many times
that you clearly wanted to hug Nan Bei,
but in the end
you ended up beating him?
As a person who has been there before,
of course,
not quite a successful one,
I still think
that you should go and say something sweet to Nan Bei.
When he feels better,
and gets back his confidence,
and then you settle things with him.
What do you think?
He's not confident?
He has a low self-esteem now.
I don't think
he's any worse than Gong Chen.
But he doesn't know
that you think so.
When a person is facing
someone he likes,
it is normal to feel unconfident.
Hao,
if one's boyfriend is jealous and angry,
what sweet things one should say?
I don't have any experience.
Are you asking me?
But my experience
is not worthy of reference.
That's right.
What if we two break up?
Tell me, guys.
why didn't she have any reaction?
Look,
I won't say no to be an audience,
but I think
it's better the three of you
stop fooling around now.
Especially you,
beware of getting yourself into trouble.
Then what do you think?
Just tell her the truth.
I tell her the truth?
Yeah.
I say,
her Prince Charming is better than me in every aspect.
He is some kind of elite studying abroad,
while I am only here
being an ordinary student?
I say I'm envious and jealous?
Right.
Here's the thing.
If two people are together,
although it is said to let nature take its course,
you still have to manage it.
Right?
Look,
you've been together for quite long.
Being suspicious of each other,
don't you feel tired of that?
You do have a point.
But,
I think
about that "an eye for an eye, and a tooth for a tooth",
we need to talk more.
How about next time
you dress up as a girl again?
Why me again?
Or let me try it?
Why are you here again?
Nobody stopped you again?
Yeah.
Well, the practice will start soon.
Let's go see a movie before the practice, shall we?
I already bought the tickets.
What movie?
A meaningless
commercial film.
I remembered you said commercial films were cliché.
But you like them.
You two just go!
So, you just get prepared.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Yes!
Still there, still there.
What time is the movie?
In the afternoon. Why?
Eh…
Nothing.
My childhood friend will come to visit me this evening.
And then,
I have to
take a walk around here,
show her around,
and visit the campus, right?
What time did you say?
What time…
When we were kids, I always followed her lead.
So, whatever time she says.
My childhood friend could catch one for sure.
What do you think of this?
My childhood friend
likes this kind of flower skirt particularly.
Back then,
every day after school,
I took my childhood friend home by bike.
You know what?
When people are young, they weigh less.
She was riding just behind me.
And I just carried her
heading forward.
I was quite fast.
Besides, before…
Look,
it's working now.
Number four,
closing.
OK.
Then let's follow this framework
and sort out the offensive
and defensive points.
I think for every point
there should be at least two
examples and questions.
OK.
I have a dinner date with Weiwei today,
and I want to confess to her at dinner.
Expecting good news from you.
Look!
He is going to confess to Weiwei.
Now you have nothing to worry about, right?
I never worried about that.
What are you going to do later?
My childhood friend will come.
I have to have dinner with her.
Who is your childhood friend?
Yes!
Yeah.
You are here already?
You guys go ahead. I have to go now.
Just give me a second.
I'll pick you up right away.
Yes.
OK.
Let's continue.
Nan Bei, come here right now!
What do you want?
I'm catching up with my childhood friend.
Nonsense!
Are you angry?
Of course!
Now you know how I felt.
Let me tell you something, Nan Bei.
Back in high school, I was young and ignorant,
so I did think he was not bad.
But that was
before I met you.
This time he came back,
before dinner, when you were on your way,
I've already told him
that I had a boyfriend now.
Besides,
he just wanted to pursue
a girl he had liked for many years.
I was just helping with some ideas.
That's it.
I already have you
as my boyfriend.
I'm not the kind of
fickle girl.
Remove all your thoughts
about those dramas!
If only you had said so earlier.
Come on, give me a hug.
It's too hot.
In the end, I still didn't say it.
Maybe
I was afraid of failure.
Let's go!
Where to?
To meet your Prince Charming of high school.
Sorry.
It's so late.
And you guys
came here because of me.
Glad you know.
What is the real reason?
I'm leaving next week.
But I'm not sure
if she would be willing to wait for me.
After all, a long-distance relationship
would cause a lot of problems.
And I'm afraid
that all of these
are just my wishful thinking,
my fantasy.
Maybe Weiwei
does not have any feelings for me at all.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
But I think
it is precisely because of this
that you should tell her.
What if you regret it later?
In this era, long-distance relationships
should not be
a serious problem, right?
Even in a same city,
even in a same college,
like me and Nan Bei,
we have issues frequently.
Every day I have
a new reason to kill him for.
Hey!
Well,
don't listen to her nonsense.
We have a solid relationship.
But I think
as long as two people have feelings for each other,
even if he has so many problems,
even if he is childish, stingy,
bragging and jealous,
so what?
I wouldn't
stop liking him
just because
someone better than him appeared.
Don't think too much.
Even if all these craps add up,
I'm sure it's better than
that you can't be with her,
right?
Thank you, Xiaoyu.
Thank you, Nan Bei.
Send it!
Nan Bei and I,
can only help you to this point.
We are leaving now.
Let's go.
Wait, are we leaving now?
I haven't finished yet.
Come on, let's go!
See you then.
Don't be too cocky.
I just said that
purely to
make Gong Chen feel better.
I got it already.
Wow!
Weiwei
does not have a good taste.
I'm telling you,
I have the worst taste in the world.
Hey,
it seems that
we haven't posted an official announcement
on WeChat Moment.
Do you want to post it?
Do it, now.
Hmm.
Actually, it's not necessary.
No need for so many troubles.
My Nan Bei has grown up!
Nan Bei, stop right there!
Jingwen,
this is my first time in love.
I know there are many things
I didn't do well enough.
Can you give me another chance?
I promise I can change, everything.
I change it all.
OK?
This is also my first time in love.
But we're really not right for each other.
I'm sorry.
Both sides have rich and solid arguments.
Seems like it's a tie.
In the refutation and rebuttal,
Nan Bei and Xiaoyu
also did well.
Even better than the other.
Now it is the free debate.
It's probably again
the critical moment to create more advantages.
What do you think?
What's the matter?
Look at the state of Xiaoyu and the Prince Charming.
They seem casual.
Actually, there are frequent confrontations between them.
Look at Xiaoyu, her aura and her spirit.
It is obvious
that she has absolutely no intention
of showing his old lover any mercy.
But, when I look at
the eyes of the Prince Charming,
there is a touch of tenderness.
Could it be that he still
has feelings for her?
Or does he pity her?
It's so complicated. Wonderful!
You're absolutely focusing on the wrong place.
Look at Nan Bei.
He looks calm outside.
In fact, inside
there is already an undercurrent.
I think
his jealousy
has risen and transformed into a kind of
invincible super shock wave.
Nonsense.
In your argument, you said that
only hard management
will let us know how much
we are willing to devote for the other,
and let us know exactly
how much we love him or her, right?
Of course, it's true.
A relationship with no devotion
will you cherish it?
If I picked up a piece of gold on the road,
I would cherish it too.
Allow me to ask you,
when you have made the devotion
only to find that you don't love him or her that much,
what should you do?
Then just break up, make it clear.
So, to get the accurate judgment
of the relationship
also requires
hard work.
Then that is wrong again.
When you find that you don't love, make a clean break.
Isn't that letting nature take its course?
Letting nature take its course is passive.
Making a clean break is active.
In the way of letting nature take its course,
taking the initiative to break up,
that's not called
"letting nature take its course" at all.
Then please give an example,
what is "letting nature take its course"?
Blacklisting the other.
The act of blacklisting
is actually an active act, isn't it?
He said it wrong.
It's waiting to be blacklisted.
According to the data
from China Public Opinion Survey website,
relationships in college
that last for more than one year
only account for 26%,
more than five years,
less than 10%.
And those that actually lead to marriage
only account for 2%.
The success rate is so low.
What is the point of hard management?
It is precisely because everyone is holding
this thought of yours
and does not manage
that produces
such undesirable data.
Doesn't this prove
our argument,
a relationship in college
requires more effortful management?
For a relationship, is the process more important
or is the result more important?
What is the result of a relationship?
Getting married and having children.
Is love gone after marriage,
or does it disappear
after a baby is born?
Why getting married and having children
are the result?
After that, there is growing old together.
Growing old together should be
the process of maintaining a relationship until getting old?
Why does growing old together
become the result now?
Then in your opinion,
what is the result of love?
We believe that
love has no result.
Love in itself is a process.
So your question is not valid.
My fellow debater,
you misunderstood the meaning of the result.
When we say love blossoms and bears fruit,
the result does not mean that
love has come to an end.
It means that
love will enter a more advanced stage.
If defined in this way,
entering a more advanced level
is more important, of course.
Otherwise, is what we expect
the superficial love,
or superficial affection
and passion?
Or should we say,
my fellow debaters, are you planning to live a life
just holding hands with your lover
and doing nothing else?
In your opinion,
love is a relationship.
And all relationships need to be managed,
right?
That's right
Is unrequited love a relationship?
Is unrequited love real love?
Isn't unrequited love real love?
Love is the emotion and affection of love
between two people.
Unrequited love is a matter of one person.
Of course, it's not love.
From the Guan Ju of the Classic of Poetry
to the Qing Yu An of Xin Qiji,
are those works describing unrequited love
not masterpieces of love literature?
Of course, they are.
Unrequited love is not a love relationship.
But from the perspective of the types of emotion,
it can be classified into a type of love.
It's not a love relationship,
but it can be classified into love?
My fellow debater, may I ask you
how on earth do you define unrequited love?
My fellow debaters may think that
unrequited love is the sorrow of being along
in the moonlight,
a silent watch from far away,
or being careful to not approach.
I don't think so.
Unrequited love,
sometimes even
you are unaware of that by yourself.
You are unaware that
there is not a single moment
when your eyes
are not laid on her.
You are unaware that
no matter what she does,
you will find all kinds of reasons for her.
You are unaware that
every pen you have
remembers her name.
And you are unaware that
you seem to have set her chat box
on the top of the list
for a long, long time.
Of course, you are unaware that
even your favorite sneakers
are trampled by her or become dirty,
you won't be angry or sad.
Whenever she wants to hit you,
you might think that
you actually deserve that.
So unrequited love
shouldn't be
the mutual affection in love.
Unrequited love is supposed to be a love
waiting to be discovered.
I feel that
my goose bumps fell all over the floor.
Now it is the final round
of the tournament,
closing statement session.
First speaker of the affirmative side, please.
Hello, everyone.
What we're discussing about today
is how to maintain
a relationship in college.
My fellow debaters stated that
we should not maintain a relationship
just for the maintaining,
and we should let nature take its course
and enjoy it as it is.
It seems that
when we are managing
a relationship,
it will no longer be pure and beautiful.
It seems that effortful management
became a deliberate act
which makes love lose its essence.
But what kind of precious emotion
is not full of deliberate acts?
Effortful management is indeed a kind of deliberate act.
But whose love
is inadvertent?
The best of love
is exactly
the effortful management,
compromises and quarrels,
and entanglement and contradiction.
It's like,
one second you feel you could slap him,
but the next second it hurts
like your own heart
is being stabbed,
a split personality.
This
is the most charming part
of love.
If we can't learn
this point,
then maybe
we're losing
the most precious wealth in love.
Even I don't eat meat,
you still can eat it.
Lately your protein intake
has been so low.
Of course, the coach punished you.
No wonder you got cramps.
I volunteered.
Look,
I also like to eat green vegetables now.
So delicious!
A relationship in college,
maybe as my fellow debaters said,
has a lower success rate.
But when you are facing
every sincere emotion,
please cherish it and take care of it,
and devote our life
to maintain it
and manage it with great effort.
In this way,
every relationship with little hope
is possible to bear
the sweetest fruit.
Thank you.
Now I declare that
the winner of this tournament is
the affirmative side, Team 235.
Let's congratulate them.
Jingwen
I figured it out.
It was me who took it for granted.
I always thought
I followed your lead in everything
I thought
I was thinking of everything for you.
I thought I was
taking care of everything for you.
But I
ignored your actual feelings.
I was just living in a dream.
No wonder my name is You Mengyuan.
Jingwen
This time, I won't
apologize to you.
Thank you
for being a part of my life.
-Bye.  -Bye.
Bye.
Will you go to see
the Hitchcock movie tomorrow?
It's still early.
How about we walk a little longer?