English subtitles are available
Just in Time EP11
Morning, Wanzhen.
Morning, Mr. Sun.
You look great today.
Of course.
I want to bring in
more clients for the company.
I've checked the attendee list.
It consists entirely of premium clients.
As long as they show up,
in our past experience,
you'll make some big deals.
Really?
I hope you're right.
Keep in mind that
it's your first time bringing in clients,
and if you can close the deal,
you'll receive a commission.
Remember to ask Mr. Qian for it.
Really?
You bet.
Excellent!
Thank you so much.
I'll leave you to it.
Mrs. Chen, Mrs. Guo,
welcome.
Here's our brochure.
Please have a look.
Please step inside.
Wanzhen,
good for you.
Got a group of clients just by yourself.
I went to great lengths
to invite these esteemed guests.
Make sure they receive the utmost care.
Don't you worry.
I'll tend to them myself.
Thanks.
New guests have arrived.
Mr. Chen, Mrs. Chen,
welcome.
Take a look at our brochure, please.
The sand table models are inside,
please go in and have a look.
This way please.
Mrs. Mo,
Mr. Mo,
so glad you're here.
Welcome.
Here's the brochure for you,
please have a look.
Thank you.
This is our nephew.
He's a young man with refined taste,
so we brought him along
to offer us some advice.
Ms. Chen, nice to meet you.
Nice to see you.
The models are inside.
Feel free to take a look.
Chen Wanzhen,
what do you mean by this?
Nothing,
I just invited
our mutual friends
to my wine party and trade show.
You're also welcomed to join us.
What exactly are you going to do?
Thank you so much for
attending my internal house trade show.
What you have is the property brochure,
which contains details about the properties
Huaxing Real Estate
is set to launch soon.
Recently,
a lot of people have been asking me
about my move into sales
and the real estate industry.
Today,
I'd like to give my response
collectively.
It's because
I'm getting a divorce.
I've dedicated myself to being
a stay-at-home mom for the past 7 years,
which has resulted in a professional void,
leaving me
with no job prospects
outside of sales.
That's why this job
is valued by me,
because I have to earn money
to prove that
I'm capable of raising two daughters.
To put it plainly,
I need to close some deals,
so I'm asking for your help.
Thank you.
Today,
I saved the eight best houses
with the biggest discounts
for all of you here.
I also hope
that I can help all of you
find the most satisfying house.
Let's welcome Mr. Yu Hai,
the father of my daughters,
and my ex-husband.
Mr. Yu, nice to meet you.
We had settled all matters of
property division before our divorce,
and I gave up
all of my shares in Blue Ocean.
Should anyone here
still have business dealings
with Mr. Yu,
feel free to maintain your trust in him.
He is a trust-worthy businessman.
I'm also grateful to him
for fully supporting me
in making the decision
to start an independent life.
There's one more thing
I want to share with you all today,
about property.
Before Mr. Yu and I
made the decision to divorce,
he was generous enough
to transfer the ownership of an apartment
in the downtown area,
a property we had jointly invested in
after tying the knot.
This generous act provided
my daughter and me
with significant security for living.
That's why I am able to
begin a fresh chapter in life
with my children,
with the house serving as a foundation.
Being a beneficiary
of real estate investment myself,
I'd like to share this approach
with everyone.
Congratulations, Mr. Yu.
On what?
Career success and return to singlehood.
It's a double celebration.
Maybe
you can teach me a lesson.
Get out of here.
In tough times,
a house can offer your family
with the safeguard you need.
Of course,
that's only my personal advice.
I do hope, though, that everyone here
has a harmonious
and happy family life.
Thank you so much everyone
for showing up
and supporting me today.
I would like to thank you,
Mr. Yu.
Cheers, Mr. Yu.
Sounds good.
Let's go and make the payment.
Sure.
Yeah.
Ladies,
this way please.
Okay.
Mrs. Li,
I just found
a new Yanbang cuisine restaurant.
It's delicious.
Let's call and reserve a table.
It'll be on me,
alright?
See you next time.
See you.
Chen Wanzhen,
can you stop making this mess?
What's wrong?
Wasn't I behaving well?
You're clearly
using the divorce to play pitiful
and sell your houses,
you know?
My reputation
is completely ruined thanks to you.
I clarified for you
and thanked you for supporting me.
When did I seek pity?
Sure,
what you've said were all true.
But to them,
it all sounded
ironic.
Do you know that?
As a sales agent,
if playing pitiful can close some deals,
then I'll do it every day.
Sure, sure,
you're a good sales person,
alright?
But the houses you're selling,
you're selling them by ruining my image,
you know?
I am someone who values my reputation
above all else.
What about my reputation?
If it wasn't for you lawyer
fighting for custody,
I wouldn't be in a big rush
to prove my financial capability.
Wait,
my lawyer is fighting for custody?
No,
don't get this wrong.
I told him
to try our best to avoid the divorce,
even if it means making it difficult...
That idiot.
I'll fire him the moment I get back,
okay?
We're getting a divorce,
and you're keeping
the company, the stocks, and the villa.
All I'm asking for is custody of our kids.
If you're set on
taking that from me,
mark my words, Yu Hai,
I will ruin
your reputation.
Wanzhen,
you've exhausted
all the connections
we've accumulated
over the years
in just one day.
Who are you selling houses to after this?
You want to raise our children,
but what will you raise them with?
You feel that I don't respect you enough,
that I'm not good enough to you.
But in what way have I treated you poorly?
Emotionally,
I've never been unfaithful.
As for our special occasions,
I've always given gifts
and flowers
in all of our anniversaries, haven't I?
I wrote down all of them
clearly
in my work journal,
without missing a single thing.
And when it comes to money,
can any of the ladies present
claim their husbands
are as open
about their finances
with their wives
as I am?
No one could!
If you feel like you have nothing to do,
if you're really bored,
we can have another set of twins.
Between the two of us,
our...
our families,
we both have it in our family.
Maybe we
can even have triplets,
right?
Let's stop this mess.
Let's head back home together, okay?
Who's making the mess here?
We've come this far,
and you still think I'm playing around?
Yu Hai, I'm telling you,
there's really
nothing more to say between us.
Let's leave it to the lawyers.
No,
wait, Wanzhen,
wait, wait.
Do you really believe that
getting a divorce
means you've reached
the peak of your life?
Haven't you considered
how you, a middle-aged woman
with two kids,
are going to navigate your future?
How are you planning to live your life?
My future life is
none of your concern.
You're messing around here
at this hour.
And the kids,
who is looking after them now?
Ms. Chen.
Mr. Yu.
My uncle and aunt
are interested in a house.
They want to discuss it with you.
Of course.
What about the kids?
Who is looking after them now?
Hello.
Can you
do anything without me?
What investor?
Mr. Zhang.
Mr. Zhang? Is the gift for him
ready?
Okay, I'm on my way.
Mrs. Mo,
thank you so much today
for closing this deal with me.
No need for that.
We're such good friends.
I need a house
for my son anyway.
I'll leave
the rest to my nephew.
It's all on you.
That's it,
bye.
Goodbye.
Leave them to me, Mrs. Mo.
Sorry.
I actually
recognized you earlier.
Thank you for the other day, Dr. Yu.
You're welcome.
That is
simply my duty.
It's just you left without a word.
I was a little worried before.
But,
here you are today,
completely fine,
weren't losing at all in that argument.
That's embarrassing.
I'm so sorry.
I have to thank you today.
Because Mrs. Mo
trusts you,
she settled
on the house so quickly.
It's a house
for my cousin.
My aunt probably thinks
I know kids better.
You're not old yourself.
Pretty old,
30 something,
heading towards 40.
Dr. Yu,
you're still here?
Hi, Ms. Chen,
I had a drink and am waiting for the designated driver.
So do I.
Really?
Dr. Yu.
Just call me Yu Chen.
Thank you so much today.
Excuse me,
did you two call for drivers?
Yes.
Let's go.
"Do you really believe that
getting a divorce
means you've reached
the peak of your life?
How you, a middle-aged woman
with two kids,
are going to navigate your future?
How are you planning to live your life?"
Thank you, sir.
No problem.
You live here too?
What a coincidence.
Yeah.
Today...
No worries.
Chen Wanzhen.
I'll leave you to it.
I'll be heading up.
Goodbye.
Who is that?
You just met him.
Mr. Mo's nephew.
When did I meet him?
Wait,
why did he
come home with you?
You heard us.
He lives here too. He's a neighbor.
Neighbor? When have I...
I've never seen him.
Ridiculous.
How many times have you been here?
What are you doing?
I'm heading upstairs
to see my kids, okay?
I'm their father.
It's too late.
I'm worried about them.
What's wrong with that?
Now you're worried.
What were you doing before?
It's been seven years.
When have you ever thought about the kids
when you were out doing business?
When did you ever
worry about them
when you were out getting drunk?
Don't bring that up with me. It's useless.
I'm asking you, this late at night,
who's looking after the kids?
I hired a nanny.
Chen Wanzhen,
good for you.
You're fighting me for custody.
And now you have a nanny
look after them?
I can leave the kids
to a nanny too,
and I can look after them better.
I hired a nanny
so I
won't get distracted at work.
Yu Hai, I'm telling you,
my love for my children
won't lose to anyone.
These seven years,
I brought them up myself.
I will never let you have custody.
If you want to fight me for it,
fine,
I'll see you in court.
I'm telling you,
if I wasn't raising funds right now,
and I can't afford being sued...
I'd...
Is the apartment I bought
in this building?
Why take me out
for ice cream all of a sudden?
To treat you of course.
You can't have it anymore
after the surgery.
How many days off are you taking?
I applied for my annual leave.
Does Yunjie know about this?
Of course not.
I must not let her know this.
Okay,
that makes it easy.
I already cleared out
a room for you.
Stay at my place
after the surgery.
I'll prepare for you
the best recovering meals.
Don't worry about anything.
Take some time off.
Stay at your place?
What about your brother-in-law?
Who cares about him?
He's lucky I'm not giving him a hard time.
If it wasn't for him,
you wouldn't be like this.
I'm telling you,
all men are like that.
Look at me.
I wouldn't be
having a second child,
if Jia wouldn't let me have my way.
Stop saying that.
Jia Haowen lets you have your way
because he loves you a lot.
He's a man after all.
If he wants to lay a hand on you,
it'll be a piece of cake for him.
Parents still don't know?
Did you say anything?
I don't think so.
I told Haowen
to not flatter my mom.
Can he be trusted?
I think he can.
If he dares to say a word,
I'll make him pay.
Let's eat.
Today, enjoy your meal to the fullest,
and eat to your heart's content.
Once you're satisfied, we go shopping,
and you can buy whatever you desire.
It'll all be on Jia.
How come would Jia marry you...
What?
Good for him.
Exactly.
Our family is great.
I'm telling you
he's making his ancestors proud.
Transitioning from clerical work to sales,
and becoming the top seller upon arrival,
I thought
that only happens
in TVs.
Ex-husband,
and playing the sympathy card.
Wu,
what do you have?
You have your thick glasses.
I don't care
how you sell your houses,
but as long as you do,
you're the top agent.
Our top agent
for this week
is Chen Wanzhen.
Wanzhen,
welcome
to our sales department.
What you made before
is already the past.
I hope you can make it happen again,
got it?
Yes.
I'll keep working.
Let's all give it our best together.
Guys,
for the top agent's title and bonus,
let's keep working.
That's all.
Wu,
keep working.
She got the best houses.
Mr. Qian.
We'll work with what's left.
I've developed
a new media marketing strategy.
Please have a look.
If you think it's feasible,
we can work
with new media companies.
Expand our sales channels
by leveraging the private traffic
of online influencers.
Interesting,
good job, Wanzhen.
You've some great ideas.
This is exactly what I have in mind.
You know,
I've talked to Mr. Zhang of Xinmiao
about cooperating.
I'll show him
your plan as well.
Xinmiao Media?
Yeah.
Blue Ocean works too.
No,
Xinmiao is great.
Come on,
I'll introduce you to some
important clients.
Me?
Yeah.
You've brought our company
some important clients.
Now it's my turn.
But...
Don't worry about them.
This is a benefit of the top agent.
You said
you wanted to
make a difference in the sales department.
Then make it big.
Make a big difference.
Li Yunjie,
this drink is for you.
No,
no, thank you.
No.
Hurry up,
Yunjie,
get in the car.
Sir,
hurry,
let's go.
I'm here to help.
What's for dinner?
I bought a duck online yesterday,
and it arrived today.
So, Braised Ginger Duck for dinner.
Do you need any help?
Just leave it to me.
It's Jing.
Please help me take it.
Hello, Jing.
It's Meng'an.
Hi, I want to ask you,
do you remember your cousin,
Lanxiang?
Yeah.
She helped take care of Yunjie.
Yes.
She'd been in the city,
working as a nanny.
She came back a few years ago
when her son was taking the exam.
Now that he's at university,
she doesn't have much to do.
Your sister's
pregnant with a second child, right?
Ask her if she needs a nanny.
I'm telling you,
she's from our family.
There's nothing to worry about.
You're getting in other people's business.
Lanxiang asked me to help her find a job.
Jing,
Xin has already hired a nanny.
She doesn't need another.
Jing,
I'll check with her later.
Yeah, sure.
Meng'an is so nice.
Next time when something's up,
I'll talk to you.
Your son's at university too.
Why aren't you
working as a nanny?
Xu,
that's it,
we'll leave you to it.
Don't be bothered with what she said.
How ridiculous.
Don't call Xin.
It's a bad idea.
Thank you.
Here we go.
Stop drinking the juice.
Here you go,
now pick a milk tea.
Which one do you want?
This one.
Here.
Thank you.
Check this out.
Tonglu Music Festival!
Yep.
Our favorite band is coming
to perform here.
Am I your best friend?
You're the best.
But...
But what?
Don't tell me you don't want to go.
No, I want to.
But my parents
might not let me.
Okay...
then I'll give it to someone else.
No.
Can you keep it for me?
But it opens this Saturday.
I know.
There's still time.
I'll think of something.
Please, He, you're the best.
Fine, it's yours.
Xin,
Meng'an,
I was about to call you.
I've scheduled an appointment for you
with a top-rated doctor this Saturday.
Can you make it?
Is it possible to get a sooner one?
Two days won't make much difference.
This doctor is the best,
and is only available on Saturday.
Plus, I've already booked it for you.
Okay then,
Saturday it is.
Thanks.
By the way, I called to ask you
after you have the second kid,
do you need a nanny?
Of course I do.
I'm definitely finding
the best nanny.
I have a recommendation.
Li Lin, he...
Li Lin's distant relative,
his cousin Lanxiang,
you've met her.
She's helped with Yunjie.
Oh, Lanxiang.
Just keep her
for yourself.
She's too good for me.
Why are you like that?
Why the irony?
Meng'an,
you forgot
what she was like
with Yunjie?
What was she like?
She was good.
She cooked,
did the laundry, looked after the kid.
She was good.
She was good with her job.
Stop right there.
I remember it to this day.
She said,
educating Yunjie, a girl,
in so many subjects
is simply a waste of money.
When did she say that?
Why don't I remember?
Of course she said those things
behind your back.
I was still in school.
I remember it very clearly.
She was so sexist.
If I hire her, regardless of
whether I'm having a boy or a girl,
she'll lead the kid astray.
Okay, then don't hire her.
Forget about it.
Meng'an,
can you guess if
I'm carrying a boy or a girl?
How should I know?
You'll find out once the baby is born.
I'm going to hang up now.
You...
Only thinking of yourself.
Once you're done with your questions,
you no longer show concern for me!
Are you a boy or a girl?
I think you're a girl.
You can wear all of my purses,
all of my diamonds.
I told you,
Xin wouldn't hire Lanxiang.
Don't listen to Jing.
I think Lanxiang
is satisfactory.
After all, Yunjie was the first child
she looked after
upon her first arrival in the city.
And it's been so many years,
she's definitely different.
Besides,
she works with
great dedication and effort,
and she's a family.
Otherwise, when Yunjie was young,
we would not dare
entrust her to Lanxiang
and went off to work.
That's true.
Hey,
what are you saying about me?
She scared me.
Welcome back.
Nothing bad about you.
We're talking about
your nanny Lanxiang.
Do you remember her?
How ungrateful.
Um...
Xin said
she scheduled a doctor's appointment
for me on Saturday.
Okay.
Then I'll tell Yunjie
that we
are going to your hometown that day.
Okay.
Up to you.
Yunjie,
this Saturday, your dad and I
are going back hometown.
You can go stay with your grandma,
okay?
Yeah!
That's awesome.
Are you that happy?
It's been... so long since I visited there.
I miss grandma so much.
Then
your dad and I
will take you there first.
No, it's fine.
I'll go myself.
I want to hang out with He Lu first.
In the evening,
I'll go have dinner there myself.
Is that okay?
Sure.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay, mom.
Time to do the homework.
Yes, Madam.
Wanwan, Zhenzhen,
hurry up. Get up and have breakfast.
You lazy bums, time to get up.
Look, the sun is up.
Little lazy piggies,
come on, get up.
I feel so cold.
Here,
stay under the cover.
What's wrong with you?
Mom, I want to puke.
Puke?
You feel so hot.
Stay under the cover.
Let's take your temperature.
Come,
let's see.
38.5 degrees.
Here, Wanwan.
You'll be fine.
Let me give you an anti-fever sticker.
Good girl.
Wanwan,
You ok?
You feel so awful?
Mommy will
take you to the hospital,
okay?
Let's see what's wrong,
Let's get it checked out,
come on.
Be good.
Let's get up.
Put your clothes on.
Mommy, I don't want to go.
I don't want to get a shot.
Be good, sweetheart.
Be good, let's go to the hospital.
There won't be shots,
I promise.
Let's go for a check-up,
okay?
But I'm afraid of getting shots.
No shots,
only the check-up,
trust me.
What's wrong?
Are the kids sick?
Yeah,
they both have a fever.
I'm taking them to the hospital.
Mommy, I don't want to walk anymore.
Hold on.
Come on, get in my car.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Hold on, Zhenzhen.
Let's go.
Don't be afraid.
Be careful.
Get in the car.
You can get in the front.
Good girl.
Be careful.
Sit tight.
Please have a seat here,
and wait for me for a moment.
Give me the documents.
I'll go through the procedures.
I'll go.
It's fine.
Leave it to me.
Do you still feel bad?
Do you want some water?
I can't have any.
I don't want any.
Okay then.
Don't be afraid.
You'll be fine in just a moment.
I'm ready.
let's go, girls.
Who are you?
Forgot about me
already?
You're a doctor?
Yeah.
A real doctor or a fake one?
Have a guess.
Aren't you supposed to sleep in
on weekends?
He Lu and I
are having McDonald's
and then doing homework.
So early?
Breakfast has certain hours. Bye.
Lu.
Yunjie.
I'm here.
Let's go.
I'm free!
What're you looking at?
Your daughter.
Isn't she doing homework
with He Lu?
You saw how she was dressed.
Does it look like she's doing homework?
She's out having fun then.
You gave her money?
I gave her 300 yuan.
And she didn't tell you
what she's doing?
No.
She's not a kid anymore.
She can go wherever she wants.
If she doesn't want us to know,
we'll just act like
we don't know.
Even you won't tell me?
Don't start with me.
I'm not starting anything.
No,
don't get too fired up.
What I mean is
we should trust our child.
Of course,
you might think that because
your progesterone level is too high,
which makes you more sensitive.
I'll be fine after the surgery.
Excuse me.
My princesses,
you did so well.
Here are your rewards.
One for each of you, here you go.
From now on,
we're the bravest princesses,
and we'll fight the virus demon
till the end, right?
Yeah.
Sir,
you act like we're three or four.
You're really childish.
Aren't you a kid?
Of course not!
Right,
you're both little adults.
I'm the child here,
okay?
Keep your hands still.
Don't move them around.
I will go with your mom
to pay for the bills.
I can go myself.
I know where it is.
It's fine.
You see,
there aren't that many patients here.
You're my important guest.
Let's go.
Don't move around too much.
I'll be back in a minute.
Okay.
I'm sorry to bother you.
It's no big deal.
Wanzhen.
When you get back, make sure...
Where are the kids?
They are getting their infusion.
The fever is gone.
What happened?
Acute gastroenteritis.
What did you feed them?
You can't even look after
our children properly.
Sir,
please calm down.
Doctor.
Acute gastroenteritis
is a common illness.
Your children had cream and seafood
at school.
The fever is gone now.
Don't worry.
Thank you, doctor.
No problem,
it's my job.
Aren't you
her neighbor?
Now you're the pediatrician?
The doctor gave it to me.
Wanwan, Zhenzhen.
Dad.
How're you feeling?
Why did you just get here?
I felt so awful.
Dad,
why didn't you
come see us when we felt so terrible?
Yeah.
Dad is busy.
You've
made up your mind?
I've
already packed everything.
The suitcases...?
I think afterwards,
I'll stay a few days
at Mengxin's.
Who is it?
Mrs. He.
Mr. Li.
What's up?
Something's wrong.
Let's talk inside.
Mrs. He,
what's wrong?
Mrs. Xu, something's wrong.
I can't
get in touch with He Lu.
I can't reach her on the phone.
Can you
try contacting Yunjie?
Don't worry.
Take a seat here.
I saw them leaving together
this morning.
She said they were heading to McDonald's
for breakfast
They're probably fine.
Why's her phone turned off then?
They did it on purpose.
Let's talk to Liu Siming's dad
in the parents' group chat.
Okay.
Liu Siming?
Did they
go out with Liu Siming?
Mrs. Sun,
go ahead and take them upstairs.
Okay.
Goodbye, dad.
Bye.
Thank you.
Thank you for bringing them back.
Thank me? What's wrong with you?
I'm their father.
Well, speaking of...
The guy at the hospital,
why was he there?
It can't be a coincidence.
I've seen him
three times in the past couple of days.
He's the doctor, and he's the...
Let's stop this mess.
Let's stop, okay?
You see
how bad this is for the kids,
right?
Yes, I know.
I used to be busy with work,
right?
Didn't have the time for you and the kids.
But you see today,
when something's actually wrong,
I need to come and fix it.
I'm their father.
Right?
Lately, you've been
walking all over me,
and really gave me a hard time.
It's enough.
Let's call it a day,
and I forgive you, okay?
You can keep being Mrs. Yu,
okay?
Yu Hai, please stop.
I've made up my mind.
This isn't something you can change
just by saying some kind words.
No, look,
I've even put my ring back on.
One minute,
wait,
wait.
Hello,
the meeting, I know!
I went to the hospital
to see my kids.
Yeah?
Okay, I'm on my way back.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Liu Siming.
Just you wait.
Hello, the number you have dialed
cannot be reached at this time.
Come, this way.
Classical music is better after all.
No, it's got to be folk.
Li Yunjie,
Li Yunjie.
He's looking for us?
Quick, take cover!
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Mr. Li,
I found them.
I'll put her on the phone.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Doesn't matter.
Excuse me.
Liu Siming,
what do you want from us?
I'm keeping you safe.
I don't need you to.
My ice cream fell off.
Are you paying me back?
Li Yunjie,
your dad's looking for you.
He Lu,
and your mom.
Why did you turn your phone off
when you're out?
They'll be here soon.
Be prepared for what to tell them.
You, traitor!
They are here.
Be nice to Lu.
Rui just got back from home.
She's been upset about it.
He Lu, get up.
You truly drive me crazy.
Let go of me.
He Lu, come here.
Good luck.
Having the music festival here
is good,
just a bit too far.
If you'd told me earlier,
I would've wanted to see it too.
How much is a ticket?
Is it a lot?
Enough.
You've learned to lie now?
I... I didn't lie to you.
You didn't lie?
Didn't you say you were having breakfast
with He Lu at McDonald's?
Is this McDonald's?
And you're telling this isn't a lie?
If you didn't lie,
why won't you look at me?
Where's that usual defiance of yours?
If I look at you,
you'll say I'm being disrespectful.
And I did say
I wanted to hang out with He Lu in the day
and go back to grandma's for dinner.
What?
You're playing with words here?
Calm down.
Yunjie,
the music festival is pretty good,
and It's good that you like music.
Your mom is not against that.
What I'm saying is
if you told her about it,
no one would stop you from going,
right?
Your mom is worried about you,
two girls, so far from home.
You went out,
without taking your phone.
What if something goes wrong?
Mr. Li,
nothing would go wrong.
I'm here.
I'll keep them safe.
Liu Siming, thank you for that.
We're
having a conversation as a family,
okay?
Okay, Mr. Li.
Mom,
what happened today,
it's my fault.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you the truth,
but I heard you talking about
going back home to the hospital,
and having me go stay with grandma.
I, I...
You saw your chance, didn't you?
What's the point in that?
Tell me,
have we ever denied your request
to go out and have fun?
Didn't you go every time?
We understand that
you're under a lot of pressure
from your studies,
and want to go out and have a break.
We've always supported you.
Okay, that's it.
We're in public.
Is it your fault?
Mom, it's my fault.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have lied.
I'll never lie to you again,
mom.
Didn't you say
you were going to take mom
to the hospital back home?
Sorry, I upset your plan.
Yeah, that's right.