Hello Debate Opponent 2 EP25
Excuse me.
We have got the marriage certificate.
Why should we break up?
Your parents came here.
I have arranged everything, right?
Is that called arrangement?
I took my parents
all the way
to visit your parents.
What tickets did you buy
for my parents
and what seats did you book?
You said that your parents are not in good health
so I didn't
book air tickets for them.
I booked them
the high-speed rail business seats.
This high-speed rail business seat
is more expensive than an air ticket.
It's not bad, right?
Yeah.
Your house is decorated like a palace
but when my parents came
you booked them a hotel.
I booked
a five-star hotel.
A five-star hotel?
I have not even
stayed in a five-star hotel.
Am I right?
Yeah.
I married all the way here
and we already got the marriage certificate.
You didn't allow my parents to enter your house?
Don't you know
how many rooms are there in the house?
You can't let me sleep on the floor, right?
Besides
if business seats on high-speed trains replacing air tickets
is still considered bullying you
then you bully me!
Divorce.
When we were in love
you were always perfunctory to me.
You were late every time
and told me that you were late for work
or you played football the day before
or you would go to a party the day after tomorrow.
You gave me a variety of reasons.
I'm telling you, young lady.
You should be careful.
If he can be late today to perfuse you
he will be able to cheat tomorrow.
Don't worry, sister.
My boyfriend is timid.
He dare not.
Why are you aggrieved?
Why don't you talk about yourself?
Each time you were unhappy
you would break up with me.
Bossed me around
in front of others.
I'm a man.
Don't I want face?
Don't I want my face?
I don't need my face.
No, no, no. You need face.
But others' boyfriends
are all like this.
You always say that I'm not sensible.
If I'm not sensible
I would have bought
all the bags in the mall.
Well.
Let's sort out
what it means.
You two already
got your marriage license
but you two want to
break up.
According to what you said
and what you wrote
on this application form
Miss Chen felt that Mr. Gu
offered little bride price
and disrespected her and her family.
Mr. Gu
thought Miss Chen
was not reasonable
and her personality
is incompatible with yours.
Incompatible.
Incompatible with everything.
Even our horoscopes are incompatible.
Incompatible, right?
When you chased me
you said we were meant to be together.
Now you turn your back on me.
Okay, the house is mine.
How can you have the nerve to ask for the house?
Did you marry me
or marry my money?
Fine.
Return the 300 thousand yuan bride price to me.
Give it back.
Only 300 thousand yuan.
You still have the nerve to say.
Why can't I say?
Did the wind blow that money to me?
How can you mention that?
I married all the way here.
Hey.
She hits me.
No, no, no.
Hit me.
Don't.
Nan Bei, they made my ears ring.
Here, let me blow you some air.
Stop that now.
I originally thought that
if I found such a person
to like each other
it would be enough to be together.
I didn't expect it to be just the beginning.
In fact, there are
so many things to come.
We are in the passionate love period
so don't think about
unhappy things.
Have you ever thought about
the future of the two of us?
Of course I have.
Let's eat hot pot later.
I'm not talking about this.
What is that then?
Nan Bei, are you playing dumb with me?
If you are like this
we will break up sooner or later.
I'm not.
Don't think too much.
The future will always come.
Let's cherish the moment.
The main reason is that
too much thinking can't solve the problem.
Right?
Your attitude is so negative.
I'm not negative.
I'm very optimistic.
Break up.
Do you think girls
love to
talk about breakups?
I was just joking.
I didn't want to break up.
I said break up
just to
make him pay attention to me.
I knew it was a joke at first
but she can't keep saying it.
I know
it's not right to
keep saying those two words.
Now she said it
more and more often.
But I just want him to change.
You know that
we have known each other
for so long.
How can we break up so easily?
Even if I knew
it was a joke at first
she couldn't say it every day.
It was a slip of tongue again tonight.
She said it everyday, what should I do?
I said break up again.
He doesn't even coax me now.
But I also need someone to coax me.
What should I do?
Let me ask you.
If Xiaoyu chased you
in the same way
as Dango chasing Liu Yanze back then
would you be happy?
Then I'll transfer to another school.
Isn't it the same?
If Xiaoyu were not like this
would you like her?
Think about it the other way around.
Are you more handsome than Dandan?
Are you better at debating
than Liu Yanze?
Are you more mature than me
in handling problems?
Are you more masculine than Xiaoyu?
Why didn't she let you change?
What does this mean?
She didn't let you change.
What do you think it means?
I'm her true love.
It's only part of it.
Another part shows that
she's blind.
Does Hao have faults?
No.
But if I have to say, she also has faults.
She's too much of a planner.
She works too efficiently
and walks without looking at the road.
She thinks more but eats less
and likes to meddle in things
especially my business.
It is
the intermittent perfectionism
caused by years of OCD.
And she always let me drink milk.
I really can't drink milk.
I am lactose intolerant.
Then you really love her.
You can't say that.
Hey.
What do you think
she thinks of me?
Think in his position?
Yeah.
Imagine
if Nan Bei always
mentioned breakup in front of you
what would you do?
Kill him.
In fact, now
boys are much more
vulnerable than girls.
If he scolded you, you would get angry.
If you scolded him
he might
hide and cry somewhere.
The more the boy likes to
show off in front of the girl he loves
the more
inferior he is inside.
Really?
Hao
Do you and Ma Nan
have plans for after graduation?
He didn't really think about it.
I... I have quite a lot of plans.
He doesn't plan, and you're not angry about it?
No.
Anyway, I'm used to
like planning.
Our personalities complement each other.
Ma Nan
If I just recorded
what you said
and sold it to Hao
how much money would she give me?
Get away.
I'm going to your dormitory
to call you.
You are so active?
Just to let
my queen
see me
at the first ray of sunlight.
Let's go.
The secretary wants us to
go to their home
to understand the situation again.
Breakfast.
Let's go.
I have decided
to help you plan in the future.
Finish the paper first.
Then make up all your credits.
After breakfast in the morning
running and memorizing new words.
Go to the library in the afternoon
and in the evening.
-Evening.  -Wait.
Are you Mr. Li Possessed?
Ma Nan. I can ignore small things
but your graduation
can't be delayed any longer.
Otherwise, when I graduate
you would have not graduated yet.
My stomach hurts.
Stomach medicine, cold medicine
Huoxiang Zhengqi liquid
I have all prepared for you.
I will be with you.
You're late today.
We quarreled again yesterday
and are ready to get divorced.
Why don't you guys calm down for a while?
How difficult it is for you two
to be together and get married.
That's true
but not everyone
is reasonable to you.
Yesterday
our company held a financing meeting.
What an important meeting it was.
Just because I didn't
answer her call
she made the call from the front desk
to my assistant.
She also insisted that
they filmed me a video
to prove that I was in a meeting.
Do you think this is too much?
How did I know
what he was doing, right?
Eleven o'clock in the middle of the night
how did I know he was in a meeting
or in a hotel?
Besides
if he knew he'd be late
why didn't give me a call
in advance?
Right?
This showed that
he has no sense of family.
He didn't include me
in his life.
It was not over yet.
At twelve o'clock in the middle of the night
she unexpectedly
came to the company by herself.
She scolded me
in front of
so many colleagues.
This was so embarrassing.
When we got home
she had to check my phone.
What's wrong with checking his phone?
He can also
check mine.
It was okay for her
to check
my WeChat record.
But that was not enough.
She insisted that I post a WeChat moment
to say I love her.
If I didn't post on Moments
I just didn't love her.
I told her this is
a WeChat account for work
and suggested to post it on another account.
She didn't agree.
She said I'm a playboy
and keep many backups in my phone.
What does this mean?
Playboy.
It doesn't matter if he didn't want to post it.
I don't care.
Let's talk about
the bride price.
The decoration of this house
should cost a million, right?
He only gave 300 thousand yuan
to my parents.
The decoration of this house
costed more than one million yuan,
all of which was contributed by my family.
Of course, I don't care about this.
But she can't
go too far.
How can we live in the future?
My parents have
only one daughter
and I married from afar.
How distressed my parents are!
Now
when I think of these
my kidney hurts.
Can you understand?
Then
she talked about
the bride price.
Wait a minute.
I
came straight
from work
and haven't had any water.
Wait a minute.
I have some good tea.
Okay.
Here.
Thank you.
It's good.
Right? Drink more.
Your wedding photo
looks good.
Ugh.
This wedding photo
was taken last year.
At that time, one of her colleagues
showed her own wedding photos to her.
After she saw them, she was so excited
and insisted on taking them at the same place.
In the end
she chose a set
that was more expensive
than her colleague's in the store.
At that time, I thought that
it was enough
to take a cost-effective
wedding photo.
She didn't.
she had to do this fancy stuff.
Then you still agreed to her
didn't you?
I also want to
satisfy her as much as possible.
Hum.
Even at that moment...
Never mind.
Let's not talk about it.
Don't.
They're inside
and can't hear you.
We are both men.
I'm still unsophisticated in this kind of things.
I want to have a lesson.
Tell me something.
At that moment
I just paid
the decoration deposit for this house.
Originally, there was still a surplus of money.
I didn't expect that something went wrong
with the company at that time.
The compensation alone
was too much for me.
I really didn't have any money
in my pocket at that time.
Several credit cards were maxed out.
But I still had to take the wedding photo, right?
Twenty thousand yuan.
I couldn't even pay for the gas
for the car.
Where could I find
this twenty thousand yuan?
Then why didn't you tell her?
I couldn't tell her.
I'm a man.
I have to take the responsibility.
Yeah.
Maybe I am still too young.
I can't understand.
And then?
Later
I had to borrow money everywhere.
I always wanted to
give her what she wanted.
After that
the company slowly turned around.
I paid back the money I borrowed
and the final payment for the decoration of the house
was also settled.
Finally I scraped together
the cost of
the wedding and the bride price.
That's how I have come this far.
But I didn't expect that
she is now increasingly
unable to understand me.
How should I try to understand you?
You didn't say anything to me.
How could I understand you?
Why should I tell you this?
I'm a man.
You didn't say anything.
You shouldn't do that.
You were with me
when I had nothing.
Now that I am able to take care of you.
I don't want you to be aggravated.
Quite smart.
Of course. Two years of partnership.
Hey.
How did you know
their conflicts
could be resolved so easily?
I didn't.
I just think that
it's better for the doer to undo what he has done.
Sometimes persuasion is useless.
If the two of them really want to get divorced
they don't need to trouble us.
Asking us for help
means they still have each other in their hearts.
How do you look so...
Handsome, right?
Let's go back to report the work.
We don't have to come tomorrow.
Hey.
There is not even a hug?
Your mission is done
very well this time.
They have
solved the problem.
Do you have a sense of accomplishment?
Of course.
Thanks to your support
for our work.
This job
is dull
compared to your school life,
right?
It's not dull at all.
Okay. Then you can
get off work.
If you still want to come here after graduation
you will always be welcomed.
Okay. Thank you, secretary.
Where are we going?
Pack up and go back to school.
Get ready for training.
Let's stand our last shift.
Sit down, please.
Aren't you two going to say something?
There's nothing to say.
I will not waste our time.
And Mr.?
I also have nothing to say.
Let's move on to the next step.
My conclusion is correct.
If the fight is too fierce
they don't really want to divorce.
If they don't care about each other anymore
they want to end this relationship
peacefully.
I told you to break up before
but I didn't really want to
separate from you.
I...
I won't talk about that
in the future.
If I accidentally
talk about that again in the future
you beat me.
No, no, no.
I know you were joking.
I didn't take it seriously.
I
just think there are a lot of problems
when two people
are in a relationship.
I have no confidence in my heart.
Hmmm
I lose my temper when I am anxious.
I understand.
We don't know
what will happen
in the future.
No matter how many unknowns
there will be in the future
we can face it together
at that time.
I will never say
you are feminine anymore.
You are quite a man.
They've been holding us up for a long time.
Let's get back for training.
Don't be late.
Let me take a look.
I...
I forgot we are going to
invite them to have hot pot.
We're late.
Hurry up.
Come on
guys.
Enjoy.
I...
How much money do you have in Alipay?
Seventy.
How much more do we need?
One hundred and seventy-nine.
Come on.
Cheers.
Okay.
Do you have money in your card?
Not a single penny.
Cheers.
Let's go.
Go.
They pay for it themselves.
Waiter
one more plate of snow beef.
Two.
Three.
I don't remember
any funny content in this book.
I have read this sentence
no less than five or six times.
I finally understood the meaning.
So I'm happy.
By the way
didn't you say
you were going to train later?
Yeah, I'm running late.
How about going to our place?
I mean
come to our training room.
No need.
I invite you.
Our team invites your team.
It's not necessary.
Our place
is really romantic.
You can also look at the stars
and the moon.
It's quite good.
Then why don't you
take me with you?
Nan Bei will eat you. I'm leaving.
Wow.
So serious.
Studying the lottery?
Sa
I have to say
as a coach and teacher
can you follow
our pace
and make progress together?
The provincial competition will be held in three days.
Sa
If you say so
I'm a little unhappy inside.
It's like
we've never worked hard.
Yeah.
We have never been lazy.
Right.
Usually, it was me
who spent the whole night in the Internet cafe and didn't come to train,
and I took up the training time
to order takeaways.
It was me.
Only me.
Sa
has the provincial competition system
and roster been announced?
Yeah.
I came to
talk about this.
A total of 32 teams
participated in this provincial competition.
There will be two groups named A and B.
Sixteen teams in each group
will compete to win the group championship.
Finally, the group champions
will compete for the final championship.
We're in group A.
The good news is that
team one is in Group B.
Alas.
What a pity.
I wanted to take
this opportunity to take revenge
and teach them a lesson.
Right, Xiaoyu?
I don't think so.
I think it's nice
not to meet them for the time being.
The strongest team in Group A is...
Nanjiang Drama Academy.
Here.
Take a look.
You are mediocre.
Your life is mediocre.
If we admit
that life without dream
is not mediocre
then is it
a comfort to those
who do not have dreams?
Don't know why
we should study hard
when we go to school.
She's good.
Scared the hell out of me.
You were a ninja in your last life, right?
Scared me to death.
Mission accomplished.
Yesterday
I met a fortune teller
he said I was a sentry
in my previous life.
Fine.
You won't see me
these days.
Our school travel club
is going to Shennongjia.
They need a guide.
I'm going to be their tour guide.
I know what you are going to say.
Don't miss me.
Let me see.
Gu Bazi, Chen Buhe
Bazi Buhe (Horoscopes are incompatible).
The name is quite auspicious.
Don't use the allusion of name
to join in the fun.
Mr. Ma
What's your plan then?
I'll buy a dress in the afternoon.
Okay.
Then I'll ask
my Yanze to go with me.
Then let's...
Then let's go together.
It's been a long time since we went shopping.
Shopping...
Exquisite and elegant.
How about me?
Pure and cute.
Her face is seen in flowers and her dress in cloud.
A beauty by the rails caressed by vernal breeze.
Why do I feel that there is still something missing?
Hey.
Alas.
The twenty-sixth set.
I really can't think of any words
to continue to praise them.
Why is it more difficult
than a debate competition?
Alas.
Prince
We came to have a meal together
just don't pretend to be
a high level intellectual, okay?
Just experience
the public entertainment once in a while.
I also played the game
you are playing
but I didn't play well
so I got kicked out.
There are still things you can't do well?
The alarm set by Tao Hao.
Time to write my paper.
It doesn't matter. Hao is shopping.
When a woman is shopping
Godzilla can't hold her.
Not to mention your paper.
Do you know Tao Hao's plan
to divide the twenty-four hours
into forty-eight
blocks of time?
Then she wouldn't
apply this to you,
who has only one time block
in twenty-four hours
right?
You don't know Tao Hao.
You just called me?
Yes. We are talking about you.
I said I'm going back to write my paper.
They said that if I didn't go shopping with you
or eat with you
you would be angry.
I said how could you
influence my paper
because of these things, right?
Yes.
Hao
You obviously don't know much about Ma Nan.
When he goes back to bathe with burned incense
and power on the computer
it should be tomorrow.
Why don't
I send him back
and help you supervise him in the meantime.
I'll send them both back.
They have no sense of direction.
They might get lost.
Don't bother.
I got this.
Ah?
Then I'll go shopping with them.
Come on.
Tell me.
How do you feel
about having
such a sweet girlfriend?
Worse than death.
Isn't this analogy
a bit inappropriate?
Every day with her
is like a new life.
Good!
Hao
Do I have to cover my neck
with a necklace?
It's a bit thick.
My mother just gave me one
some time ago.
I will show it to you later.
Okay.
Well, Xiaoyu
You are already beautiful enough.
If you were more beautiful
you would steal
the bride's limelight tomorrow.
I'm covering up my shame, sis.
I do not care.
Anyway,
if I get married
with my Yanze
you two should
be my bridesmaids.
Then if I
get married with Nan Bei
you two as my confidants
should also be my bridesmaids.
I want both of you...
I want all the girls in the dormitory
to be my bridesmaids.
I have to say
It's only my own idea.
I have no intention to diss you guys.
If you reach such an
agreement
then the last person to get married
will not have a bridesmaid.
But it doesn't matter.
Whenever you
get married
I will definitely be your bridesmaid.
Fanfan, you don't want to get married?
No.
I won't.
Don't.
I'm very happy.
I have no character defects
or psychological shadows.
I think
the so-called marriage
means that you love someone very much
but
sometimes you want to shoot him.
On the way to buy a gun
you see his favorite food
so you buy the food instead of a gun.
Two days after
you still think
you should buy a gun.
This kind of repetitive thing
I find it very annoying.
It's suitable for you guys, not for me.
Fanfan
If you have no one
to support you in your old age
I will take you to my house
and we will spend time together.
I think it's good.
Xiaoyu
Are you going with Nan Bei tomorrow
to pick up the bride?
No.
I have to go to the hotel first
because I have a more important thing to do.
Chief planner of the wedding.
What?
Isn't that
how a gauzy dress turns?
Well.
Xiaoyu, let me tell you
if you and Nan Bei work together
there will be nothing wrong tomorrow.
Definitely not.
I guess this wedding
can not be done.
Hey.
You are an adult.
Don't be so impulsive, Okay?
It's just a marriage phobia.
Not a big deal. It's normal.
Right, Nan?
Let Nan tell you
about his mental journey.
I think
getting married
is a process of surrendering your freedom.
You will be fine if you work it out.
Bro
your thinking is very problematic.
Does Hao know?
You don't want to tattle on Xiaoyu
and take credit for it, right?
No.
Next time when Xiaoyu
points a finger
at me again
I have to break the news
and divert her attention.
Right?
But you really think so?
I actually don't resent
Tao Hao for controlling me.
On the contrary
because of her
my life is much more normal
than before.
But you know
I'm used to being alone
for so many years
so I still have to adapt to it.
Adapt for a few more decades.
Yeah, adapt to it.
Adapt to it. You are the same.
Enough for both of you.
Are you telling me cross talk here?
What you said is trivial.
I am troubled now
because of my mother-in-law.
She said that I should give a red envelope
to every relative at the wedding.
Is the amount of the red envelope large?
Are you... are you short of people? I'll sign up.
Fine, don't mess up.
It's quite large.
My mother-in-law said that
their family's
particularly distant relatives
will come tomorrow.
They take the effort
so I have to pay.
Wait, wait, wait.
You booked the banquet
and decorated the house.
They just attend the banquet.
They just come here.
Hey.
What are you going to do?
I can not tell my parents
about this matter.
I really can't
pay a penny anymore.
Forget it if I can't get married.
To be honest.
I think the situation tomorrow
is dangerous
but it's not a big deal.
You don't want to stop getting married
because of this money, do you?
Yeah.
Wait, I will bring your wife
to you
on that day.
Okay?
Okay. Cheers.
Dad, mom
I'm here to pick up He.
Don't rush to call us that.
Have you brought that red envelope?
Mom, dad, let me explain.
You just told me about this
yesterday.
I can't get the money
in one day.
What?
This wedding is not yet held
how dare you lie to us?
You are not sincere at all.
Yes, no sincerity.
I...
You are not sincere at all.
Come in, hurry up!
Wait.
You are not allowed to see others.
What are you doing down here?
Retain your composure.
Go back.
Mom and Dad
if I don't take Buhe now
it's really too late for the wedding.
Today there are so many people from our two families.
If something went wrong
it would be so embarrassing for us.
Don't get married.
Buhe, Buhe
Buhe, I'm here to pick you up.
Buhe
You can't come in.
I only need a word from you now.
No matter who is stopping me
I will take you away. Buhe.
Buhe
What are you talking about?
Aunt, don't worry.
Let me ask him.
Buhe
Come with me.
Why it's only you?
Xiaoyu, I'm sorry.
I really went to
get the bouquet on time
but I got stuck in traffic
for ten minutes on the way here.
I could have rolled here
but the driver just didn't let me get off.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. They haven't arrived yet.
Ah?
Hasn't Nan Bei arrived yet?
Didn't you give him an order
to arrive at half past nine?
If he couldn't make it before 9:58
you would kill him.
I think they should
have this awareness.
I already knew that
the bride's relatives
would not let them off easily.
Have you heard that?
The bridesmaids are very tough.
So I have counted the time
to pass this difficulty.
If they are not here at this time
he has no life
to attend the wedding.
I even doubled the time
in traffic jams
for them.
Even if they roll, they should have rolled here.
If he can not control the whole scene
as a best man
I don't know how bad
his own wedding will be.
Calm down.
Take a look.
This is their wedding.
No need to be angry.
When you get married in the future
I will be the chief planner for you.
Calm down, calm down.
Life is a drama.
This bastard
dares to call me.
Where are you?
Escaped the wedding, right?
You come to
the dressing room now.
Don't let others see you.
It's almost late.
What are you waiting for here?
Yeah, where's the bride?
I want to ask
who of you can do me a favor
to marry me for a while?
What?
I have paid for the wedding
and hotel.
My relatives and friends are here, too.
I have also took their red envelopes.
There is really
no other way.
I know
this is too much
but don't worry.
Later
you will wear the veil all the way
the relatives and friends will
definitely not be able to see you.
We will just go through
a procedure.
When the toast comes
I can come out by myself.
I really can't
let my parents
lose face
in such an important day.
Of course
if you refuse
I can understand.
After all, this matter
has nothing to do
with you.
I'll do it.
Really?
Dango
It's fine.
If this happens to me
I would even want to die.
I understand you.
Dango
If Liu Yanze
sees this
he would...
Dango, I support you.
It doesn't matter.
It's all fake anyway.
Just a procedure.
Liu Yanze is not here.
Even if he knew
I believe he would support me.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Well
I'm going to pick up my parents now.
Then I will communicate with the emcee
to simplify the procedures as much as possible.
Then
if you can call
some classmates here
it would be even better
because there are
still two or three empty tables on the bride's side.
Dango, thank you.
Xiaoyu, I have to trouble you
to pretend to be a bridesmaid.
I have no problem.
Thank you.
Fine.
Let's start our plan.
Get out.
Okay.
Get started.
Yeah.
Liu Yanze, come here.
You still remember me.
What's the matter?
There is a great thing.
Is the bride pretty?
Pretty or not?
Nan Bei
Go.
What's the situation here?
Situation... This is the situation.
Mainly because
it's too late now.
There is really nothing we can do.
Xianyu
What should we do?
This dress is too big for me.
I can't wear it.
Just changed like that?
Mainly because
you will support and understand me.
Just now you supported
and understood Dango.
I supported her
because she's...
Wait, wait.
Why haven't you changed yet?
I'm sorry.
The dress is too big.
I have nothing to do.
I can only be a bridesmaid.
Xiaoyu
Bro
you are a real friend.
In the future
if you encounter any trouble
tell me, I will be bound.
Wait, wait, wait.
She...
I just...
Time is running out.
Let's go.
This matter...
I didn't...