English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP06
A girl
shouldn't always expect
others to lend a hand.
When one is capable,
it's better to rely on oneself.
He is a servant of the Yan family!
My lady,
the lord asked me to remind you
that three days have already passed.
The day for you to return home
has been postponed repeatedly.
You mentioned you would return tomorrow,
please keep your promise.
Alright.
Got it.
Xing,
everyone in Xiang'an has been talking that
Commander Yan is deeply in love with you.
It brings great pride
to me.
So beautiful.
It looks good.
It's good, huh?
Truly beautiful.
Xing,
you've finally returned.
Why have you
been gone so long?
Where is your husband?
He...
has urgent matters at Imperial Guard.
The case is pressing.
Is it more important than
you returning home?
No lady returns home alone after a wedding
throughout the entire empire.
He'll be here once he wraps up his work.
Isn't that right?
Yijiao
what brings you back today?
You didn't come back just
to see me return home, did you?
Your brother-in-law ordered a bracelet
for me, and it was delivered here.
I thought I'd stop by to see you.
What about you all?
Take a look at this bracelet.
Isn't it stunning?
I fell in love with it the moment I saw it.
No matter what unkind remarks she makes,
just ignore her.
What's so special about it anyway?
What a show off!
Why isn't your husband here?
Well,
your brother-in-law asked her
to bring a variety of snacks and fruits.
Everyone, please help yourselves.
Here, dear husband.
My lord,
Xing
lives a miserable life.
The others marry well and live happily,
but my Xing
had to save someone else's skin.
Hey,
where did that come from?
So you were saying it's
all my fault?
Look at me,
I'm only good at
making myself look pretty.
I don't lift a finger around the house.
My husband still calls me his lucky charm.
I had always hoped to have a daughter,
someone who'd be a little sweetheart.
But who would have thought,
I ended up with a pair of twins!
Mom, you wouldn't believe
how mischievous the little ones are.
Xing, you really
should spend more time with Yijiao.
So you could partake in her good fortune.
Don't just bury yourself in official duties.
Settle down now that you're married.
Exactly!
My sweet little sister,
you should quit
the clerk job.
Listen to me,
as a woman,
what's the best way to
change your fate?
It's to manage the household well.
My dear brother,
I heard from my colleagues
that last time when
they were patrolling the stew streets,
they saw you partaking in courtesan entertainment.
You were even chasing after the girls,
running all over the place.
That's a lie!
You have the nerve to criticize me.
The most disappointing one in the family
is you!
Look how sharp-tongued you are.
Tell me,
where's your femininity?
I am sharp-tongued, huh?
If I were your husband,
I'd be visiting the stew streets every day
and wouldn't want to see you at all.
Say that again? I dare you!
That's enough!
Commander Yan has arrived!
Welcome, Commander!
I do believe
my wife is wonderful.
Apologies, I was caught up with work.
Father-in-law, Mother-in-law,
please forgive me.
Well, well,
The timing is just perfect.
Yes, indeed.
Today, as Xing returns home, I'd like to
express my heartfelt gratitude to the Yans
for raising such a remarkable daughter.
It's truly a blessing
to have such a wise and exceptional girl.
Bring them in.
Lord Yan,
Xing told me
that you have a passion for tea.
These are glazed sunflower-patterned cups,
from the Yue kiln.
This is the imperial gift of zisun tea.
It's far too precious!
I'm truly humbled!
I was incredibly fortunate to marry Xing.
Even Princess Ying remarked
that I married an exceptional wife.
Her Highness, Princess Ying?
Pan Yanzhi?
Hasn't his calligraphy
already become extinct?
It's a copy.
A few years back, I happened
to come across a rubbing of his work.
On a whim, I decided to study it.
Even you find it look authentic,
it truly is remarkably lifelike.
It seems your talent for imitation
comes from my father-in-law.
I merely
knows the basics.
However,
there's no calligraphy
that my father
can't replicate.
It's just practice.
Nothing to boast about.
Come, dear son-in-law.
Let's have lunch.
Come here.
Time for lunch.
Father,
we need to head back;
there are still some issues...
Since it's an invitation from Lord Yan,
we should definitely
stay for lunch.
But we need to leave early,
as there are
pressing issues to handle.
Understood.
We got it.
Xing,
seeing you thrive now
fills my heart with joy.
However...
Has Lord Zhang reached out to you?
He has brought it up multiple times.
The message is quite clear.
The allotment for the post in Xichen
remains to be settled.
Should the task he entrusted
be poorly executed...
Regarding Lord Zhang,
I'll provide him with an explanation.
The pigeons' feathers are soft and fluffy.
Quite a few have fallen.
Hmm...
Ya, be quiet!
Commander.
Commander?
Commander,
someone went to the pigeon coop.
Who was it?
It's...
the lady.
She has made her choice after all.
My lord,
the curtain
you asked me to prepare
is ready.
This is a special fabric
from Xichen
that effectively blocks out light.
My lord specifically
asked me to...
It's just perfect
for sword practicing.
What a waste!
Your unpredictable temper
really needs to change.
Otherwise, who would want to serve you?
I remember back at the Yan residence,
you swore an oath
to serve me faithfully, right?
How could a lady serve
if she avoids her husband?
Do you truly want me to serve you?
We are husband and wife, after all.
Even if something happens,
no one will gossip about it.
I don't really care about gossips.
It's only natural for a wife
to serve her husband.
If serving is what you ask for,
fine!
You smell wonderful, my lord.
Would you like to take a whiff?
See if I smell good.
Challenge me huh, boy?
Guards,
light up the lamps
over by the lady!
Commander.
Something happened at Ximing Temple.
Imperial Guard has sufficient manpower.
Commander just
reassigned you back to Ministry of Justice.
Hey...
Who would want to follow you around?
Don't you come begging me to
assist you in the investigation!
The handwriting is neat,
and the brushwork is impressive.
These blood characters
suddenly appeared on the wall.
It's not blood;
it's a special stone material
mixed with vermilion to create ink.
Once applied, it won't show immediately.
It will only reveal its blood-like hue
after being washed by the rain.
The murderer had written it long ago,
just waiting for last night's rain.
There are also blood tears
on the statue in the main hall.
What could be the motive behind this?
He is clearly taunting us.
The gods are enraged,
which is why there's blood.
I've heard it said
that when a statue weeps blood,
it signifies the gods mourning the world.
This serves as a warning to us.
Apologies.
I didn't notice you were here.
I didn't see you cleaning the floor.
Hey, Xing girl,
you know, our Ministry of Justice
really can't function without you.
You have no idea,
not long ago,
the floor of our office
wasn't even this shinny.
My lord, my lord.
Good morning, my lord.
Isn't this Lady Yan, Commander's wife?
Why are you mopping our floor?
Yeah!
I am unworthy of your effort, my lady!
Here, here!
This area still needs some attention.
Wash that cloth.
Then continue mopping.
My lord, your belt has slipped!
Your belt.
Here.
Did you two have a quarrel?
No.
No?
If that's the case, then why did you
suddenly come back?
Go on,
what trouble have you stirred up?
My waist seems to gain weight again.
I need to work on it.
I've taken on the role of a spy.
You were putting...
You're truly playing with fire!
I've heard that someone once
snuck into the Shen residence at night
because he was a spy.
In one night,
not only did he vanish without a trace,
but his entire family...
His whole family was gone.
Moreover,
at midnight,
someone even saw
them being dragged into hell
by a demon.
Your entire family would be wiped out!
You were really bold!
This whole thing
is quite complicated.
By the way,
how's going with that thing
I asked Mr. Xu to do?
Don't worry,
he has already dispatched inspectors
to investigate.
My lord,
Excuse me for the moment.
Don't worry.
Yan Xing,
I forgot to mention something important.
Someone spotted
your master.
He has returned from his journey.
However, as soon as he entered the city,
he was captured by
by the Imperial Guard.
What?
Where's your Commander?
Shen Du!
Shen Du...
Commander is busy
and cannot see anyone.
I am his wife!
How dare you stop me?
Shen Du!
Get your arse out here!
Get her out of my face!
Shen Du,
come at me if you have a problem!
Why did you arrest my master?
Don't think too highly of yourself.
You're overestimating your importance.
Let my master go!
Shen Du!
Release my master!
- Let my master go! - Xing?
Master?
My girl,
you're already a married woman,
yet you're still so impulsive.
Master!
You really should cut down on alcohol.
Especially avoid drinking
anything offered by weirdos!
This disciple of mine
is a very straightforward girl.
Commander, please forgive her.
I understand.
What do you understand?
I...
Let's stop the game for now.
Go ahead,
what would you like to know?
I've heard Master Chen has developed a
unique type of vermilion.
It doesn't show when applied,
but reveals itself with water contact.
That's right.
It was originally created
to prevent corpses from decaying.
I wonder if this special vermilion
is exclusive to Master Chen?
Before I retired,
I shared this formula
with a few friends' servants
for pest control purposes.
The results were outstanding.
Please let me know who they were.
I see now.
That explains why the time of the victim's
disappearance and the time of death
were so far apart.
It delays decay
and repels pests.
Right, it's vermilion!
The corpses were surrounded by herbs.
Initially, I thought
it was to mask the odor of decay.
In reality, it was mixed with a
special preservative vermilion.
That was why the coroner
couldn't accurately determine
the time of death.
Master, stop drinking!
I wonder if Master Chen
could deduce the
actual time of death.
Come on, my girl, you don't
seem to worry about tiring your master.
Master,
there's a case to solve.
Please bear with it a bit.
Show us your skills!
Master has won
this round.
I did?
I did!
let's go then.
- Take me to the morgue. - Let's go!
- The morgue. - Master, watch your step.
Master estimated the
actual time of death
based on the degree of preservation.
Early spring of the fourth year of Shengli.
Summer of the fourth year of Shengli.
February or March of the fifth year of Shengli.
June of the sixth year of Shengli.
Mid-August of the sixth year of Shengli.
Can't we narrow it down any further?
The way I see it,
there's no need for that.
Male victims' stomachs contained these.
Based on the decay of the corpses,
I thought that even if the victims
had eaten before they were murdered,
the contents of their stomachs
should have decayed
along with the bodies.
I was too quick to judge.
Avoid premature conclusions in forensics.
The more bizarre and shocking the scene,
the more one must follow a systematic approach.
The key
often lies in seemingly
insignificant details.
Melon seeds?
Exactly.
Melon seeds can only be
digested and expelled
through bowel movement
while a person is alive,
and they are typically expelled
within a day.
They all had seeds in their stomachs,
which suggests they ate them shortly
before they were killed.
What seems logical
is not always the truth.
Even what you see with your own eyes,
may not reflect reality.
Someone may use tricks
to make you believe that is the truth.
I've learned a lot, master.
What a coincidence!
These male victims
all ate melon seeds before they died.
When too many coincidences come together,
they are no longer coincidences.
These seeds
are not just any ordinary seeds,
but the barbarian melon seeds from Xichen.
Barbarian melons, the tribute?
Aren't they exclusive to the palace?
No,
there's another occasion.
Those gentry males
had the chance to enjoy barbarian melons.
Kaiyang Festival!
The date of the Kaiyang Festival is
determined by the Imperial Astrology Bureau(IAB).
based on celestial observations,
and is funded by the government.
Her Royal Highness will also
bestow rare treasures from the palace.
However, the date changes each year.
The next Kaiyang Festival is...
Three days later.
Commander,
Her Royal Highness is still in a meeting.
Please be patient and wait here.
The statue of Buddha wept blood,
and rumors are spreading wildly.
She has been suffering from migraine,
and even Princess Ying
has been implicated and grounded.
Her Royal Highness' oral edict!
The current situation is dire.
If the case is not resolved
within five days, it will be
handed over to the Imperial Inspectorate.
I, your humble servant,
accept the edict with gratitude.
Lord Zhang, if you'd like to meet me,
there's no need for you
to send so many escorts.
Mysterious events were unfolding at Temple
Someone is behind them.
This nursery rhyme is just the beginning.
Things are escalating.
Prince Xian's situation is concerning.
I heard Princess Ying was grounded too.
Her Highness
has reprimanded
all her children.
Please forgive my audacity.
Is the weeping blood of the statue
related to you, my lord?
How dare you!
My question may be abrupt,
but I only wish to clarify
the truth of the matter
so I could be of help.
This has nothing to do with me.
Also,
how's the investigation that
I tasked you with going?
I haven't found anything yet.
Are you playing tricks with me, girl?
Aren't you afraid I'll
ruin your family's prospects?
Please allow me to explain, my lord.
You asked me to investigate the pigeons,
which was merely to find out
Her Royal Highness'
attitude towards Prince Xian.
But based on my investigation,
you could rest easy.
How can you be so sure?
Besides the pigeons,
the communication routes of IG
have suddenly increased.
Most of these are merely
decoys of turning back midway.
This is intended to conceal
the real route.
Moreover,
a significant number of guardsmen from IG
have been dispatched out of the city.
This is likely to ensure
Prince Xian's safety along the way.
If they intend to harm him,
why go through all this trouble?
That said,
this is merely your personal
speculation.
Isn't it also your speculation
that Prince Xian is in danger?
I'll take your word for it for now.
However,
I'd like to wrap up the whole thing soon.
Rest assured, my lord,
I will soon uncover
the true mastermind behind all this.
Good.
The transferring order for the position
at the border will be issued shortly.
The time for you and your father
is running out.
Your Royal Highness,
if you don't make a move,
I
will win this round.
Fine.
If Your Highness is fine with this,
I will ask for a reward.
Sure, tell me,
what do you want?
Regarding this year's Kaiyang Festival,
thanks to Your Highness' gracious favor,
the celebration is being prepared by me.
So, can I also
have a say in who to invite?
In past celebrations,
guests would recite poetry
and sing melodious songs.
This time,
can we invite some
real talented scholars and fair ladies?
Invite whoever you wish.
Is there a fair maiden
who has caught your eye?
Gratitude,
Your Royal Highness.
Lady Xu,
this is the list you provided.
I have included all of them
on the guest list.
Gratitude, Lord Zhang.
Don't mention it.
In the future, I hope you
will extend me a bit more favor.
So,
those who know the vermilion formula
are already on the guest list
for the Kaiyang Festival celebration.
The murderer is among them.
Finding the murderer among these people
is certainly not an easy task.
It would be better to
let the murderer come to us.
This way, we can save ourselves
a lot of trouble.
The female victims share striking
similarities in their appearances.
Moreover, they are all skilled
pipa performers.
If I disguise myself like them,
I can attract the murderer's attention.
This way, the murderer will take action.
At that point,
you can capture him on the spot.
No.
This is far too risky.
It can't be you.
I...
Go find someone from Tongming Pavilion.
And have her disguise as the target.
Understood.
No.
The musicians at Tongming Pavilion
are just civilians.
How can we risk
the lives of civilians?
Besides,
the murderer's methods
are extremely cruel.
What if something goes wrong?
How will you explain to their families?
So you are aware of the risk involved.
If something happens to you...
how will I explain to Her Highness,
Lord Zhang, and your father?
I'm the one who
insisted on investigating this case.
If I hadn't intervened,
it would have been closed long ago.
Now, we are getting so close.
I should see it through to the end.
This is official business,
so lady officials should take the risk.
You expect me to endanger
the lives of civilian girls?
I simply can't.
If you wish to participate,
you need to assess your qualifications.
You need to be skilled at playing pipa.
Can you do that?
My lady's abilities
caught me off guard.
How was it?
Do you consider me "skilled?"
My lady, you truly have exquisite skills.
Play another piece for us.
I'm tired.
Let's call it a day.
Are you tired, or just not good enough?
When the time comes,
are you planning
to only play these few lines
at the Kaiyang celebration?
I
haven't really prepared for this.
I'll just speak off the cuff.
Let me give you
a few key points.
First, when you play,
this outfit won't be suitable.
You should wear something
appealing.
That is... unnecessary, right?
How well you play
doesn't really matter.
The key relies on your vibe.
Look carefully.
You know the poses, right?
Let's start with the...
Extend your leg.
Cross your legs.
Exactly.
Take it slow.
Now spin.
Spin around.
Twirl, twirl.
Look at the skirt twirling.
That's it!
So graceful.
Mom, mom!
Could you sit back here and play?
You keep spinning,
and I can't see your fingerings clearly.
Fingerings don't matter.
What comes next matters the most.
Watch closely.
Raise your pipa above your head.
Bring it down from behind your head.
Your posture should be enchanting.
Show your face.
Eyes are the key. Watch me in the eyes.
The charm of a woman.
Eyes, remember?
Look into my eyes.
That's right.
Pay attention to this part.
Now spin again.
Then shake it!
Normally,
your dress should be
already off on the floor.
Mom, please.
You can dance later.
You should sit down for now.
I just want to focus on learning a piece.
It's not about how many pieces you know,
but about mastering one well.
Back then,
I only played one piece.
A true master
doesn't need a second piece at all.
And your dad,
he never managed to get through
the first one.
No, mom.
What are you talking about?
Just now, what I taught you,
that one...
After the spinning,
a man
couldn't hold himself back at all.
Mother.
I just want to
really learn a piece.
It's for my investigation.
What do you think it is for?
I thought
you wanted me to teach you some skills
for the joy between men and women.
The pipa ignites fires of passion.
That's not what I want!
Uncle.
Exactly what's going on
in my mother's mind all day?
Just because I got married,
does that mean everything I think and do
has to be related to
how to please my husband?
Your mother was sent to the music hall
since she was little.
Back in the day, the impresario
taught us to be
extremely tolerant.
To humble ourselves.
To entertain others with our charm.
Fortunately, your father showed her
kindness, which provided her with a
place to call home.
So in your mother's eyes,
the best fate
for her daughter would be to find
a good husband to share her life with.
Based on that standards,
I certainly don't have
a good fate.
The man I married is not a good one.
Your mother has repeatedly sent word to me
to ensure I navigate things
for you in the palace.
So you will not be harmed by White...
Your husband,
to bring you harm.
Now that you are
safe and sound,
so she can ease her mind.
Yet she spends her days worrying about
how to secure your position
as the primary wife.
She is overly concerned about me.
As for the primary wife,
whoever wants it can have it.
I don't need a man's protection.
I just hope
I could become
a strong and capable woman
to protect myself
and my family.
I, Yan Xing, am fortunate
to have been born in a dynasty
where women can hold positions of power,
and don't need to leverage beauty for others' sake.
However, at this moment,
I truly need
a pipa performance that can captivate
all the spectators.
You mentioned earlier
that it's for your investigation.
I need to perform a pipa piece
on the stage of
the Liushang Theater
Draw out the fox from its den.