Hello Debate Opponent 2
EP20
Considering our current situation,
we must win eight competitions
within two weeks
to enter
the provincial competition.
The first problem is
the games are all
held in the suburbs.
We can't even get there easily.
Maybe,
we can train to be ninja
and teleport ourselves.
Or maybe we can look into
lotteries
and win a car.
There are ways.
Look at the game held on the day after tomorrow
in the east of the city.
We have
85 minutes
until the next one.
We can take the crowded
Bus No. 621.
After 28 stops,
run across
complex Yingli Park.
Next, get on Line Alpha
which is overcrowded.
Hurry up, Hao.
Finally,
scuttle to the hall
in five minutes.
You're 20 minutes late
and disqualified.
Let's worry
about that
when we get there.
Our mission today
is not finished.
I'm sorry
we have to stay up.
I'm so sleepy.
Take a break.
Jeez, what is that?
Come down.
Sa.
Where did you
find this piece of trash?
How much is it?
Less than 20 yuan?
Let's take the subway.
This thing will be
a cultural relic soon.
This
is old, I know.
But at least it has four wheels.
Right?
Our schedule
is getting tighter.
We can't waste our time on the road,
right?
Yeah, it looks cool to me.
At least we can sleep a bit
on the way.
Yeah.
we can also get
takeaways
to eat normally.
That's right.
Sa,
where did you
get the car, and how much was it?
There's a used car market
nearby.
You can get a car right away.
And I
have a little deposit.
And,
I asked for three months' salary
in advance to buy it.
It's burning.
Get in now.
We're getting late. Hurry.
Go.
Let's go!
Sa,
l, I'd like to know
if you have a driver's license.
Of course, I do.
Don't worry.
It, it's new.
I need to get used to it first.
New?
What's new?
Sa, I can drive, too.
Why don't you let me drive?
Sa, is the fuel nearly used up?
Mother Earth, nice to see you again.
Jeez.
Hold on.
The winner is
team 235.
The winner of this competition is
Let's congratulate
team 235 on their victory.
It's impossible.
Even 5G has been
popularized.
I don't need five.
Just give me one.
Hey.
There're single people here.
Keep it to yourselves.
I'm just
trying to be a good boyfriend.
Okay?
Great progress!
Do you feel hot?
No, I'm actually a bit cold.
Why do I feel somewhat sweaty?
Do me a favor.
Put it on.
Xiaoyu, Xiaoyu.
Well,
aren't you tired like this?
No. I don't want to get off.
Just try it.
Nan Bei!
None of your phones have service?
We are three points away
from the admission.
The game is approaching.
The upcoming contests
are crucial to us.
There are three games left.
Two of them are overlapping.
The other one
is a tripartite debate.
But our opponent is team one.
Not them again.
Hao, what is a tripartite debate?
I'm new to it.
It's a debate held
between Party A, B, and C.
The process
is similar to that of an ordinary debate.
But two of the parties
can join hands against the third one.
I'm not working with team one.
In the end,
if the third party
finds some loopholes,
things can be tricky.
There're only three points to go.
Let's not risk it.
Just avoid them.
Fight them later.
You've finally grown.
That's right.
One of the two overlapping games
is called the Edge Cup
The topic is
"Should we do something not encouraged?"
It's a B-class game
we signed up for.
Even if we win,
we get only two points.
Only two points?
That does not make a big difference.
Should we drop out?
What about the other one?
It's held by Luojia College
on "Should the debate topic
be made into films and TV dramas?"
It offers three points.
- That's it. - That's it.
Also,
I like this topic.
Under the present world view,
such topic is like
a destiny.
Then let's get ready.
I know
that we've been working hard recently.
Go back and rest well tonight.
It's a deal then.
Let's rest like we mean it.
No one thinks about debating today.
Don't worry, Hao.
I'm tired enough
to pass out right away.
Dango.
You're awake, too?
Yeah.
At least Qing is not here,
so I can sleep in your room.
Our room
is probably having a tea party.
Hao, are you asleep?
No.
Hao,
I gave the topic
some thought.
This topic sounds
interesting
in the first place.
But if you think about it,
there is a problem.
The debate topic
should not be made into films and dramas.
Why not?
Theoretically, any topic
can become literary and artistic works.
One just needs to dig into it.
What?
Then there's nothing to argue about.
It's not like that.
The other party will not
hold onto this point.
After all, debate
should bear a meaning.
We should find
specific examples.
What did the old coach say?
All debates
must have specific scenarios
as examples.
That's right.
For film and drama shooting,
what's the goal?
It's a commercial operation.
So the goal should be to make money.
It's against the rule to not make money.
Debate topics are enjoyed by few
and may not have commercial value
or offer
great commercial profit.
So it's against the rule.
The idea is right.
But the argument is too rudimentary.
Girls, aren't you sleepy?
I have a class at eight tomorrow morning.
Sorry.
Let's sleep.
I'm sorry.
I don't think it's a problem.
Most people wouldn't think so.
Who would film something
that nobody watches?
If no one is going to watch it,
then it's against the rule to make it.
It sounds correct at first.
But there's still something wrong about it.
Does the amount of audience
determine
the commercial value?
The potential
development and expansion
of the audience
requires testing.
Then it involves
the cost of business decision-making.
Making a TV drama
is so costly.
If one needs to try it out
to know
whether the decision
is correct,
then it's too risky
and too costly.
For decision-makers,
it's against the rules.
It makes sense.
Girls.
Sleep!
Alright.
For real!
But high risk
is associated with high returns.
Besides,
films and dramas
are making money in various ways.
Will they stick to this argument
as a breakthrough?
You lost me again.
And me.
I'm not very bright.
Now, it's even worse.
I'm sure I can't sleep now.
I finally understand
why I'm losing so much hair.
Why don't we go run on the playground?
Let's go!
Go!
Jeez, I'm getting more awake
thanks to the debate.
Help me.
Where are you going?
We talked about the debate
and got stuck.
It's the same here.
So where are you going?
Shui said that
he's got Killer's Game.
We're going for a break.
You going?
Sure. Let's go.
Go.
What's wrong with you?
You have plenty of space
there.
Why do you have to squeeze here?
Why didn't you go there?
Why should I?
Cut it out!
Let him go. Come.
Excuse us.
That girl's got
her guy under control.
Mind your own business.
It's so weird.
Yeah.
Hello, everyone. I'm Dango.
Hello, everyone. I'm Mu Xiaoyu.
I am Nan Bei.
You can call me Ma Nan.
Hello, everyone. I'm Yuan.
Yun.
I'm Jingwei.
Call me Wu Shan.
Are you having
raw Pu'er tea here?
It seems that
you know about tea.
Just a bit. Not much.
Here you are.
Good tea.
Hello, my name is Tao Hao.
Hello, I'm Xia.
You go first.
What would you like to have?
-Barbecue. -Iced lemon tea.
I want something spicy.
Anything spicy will do.
OK, I'll be right back.
Okay.
Alright.
Now, please
confirm your identity.
Done?
Okay.
The night falls. Close your eyes.
The killers, please open your eyes.
Please confirm the identity of your companions.
Please choose the person you want to kill.
Please make a decision.
It'll be day time if you don't make a decision.
Okay.
Please close your eyes.
Police, please open your eyes.
Please confirm your companions.
Please choose one person to verify the identity.
Please make a decision.
Are you sure?
This means "good".
This mean "bad".
This person is...
Okay.
Close your eyes. It's day.
It's day.
Last night,
player no. 3 Xiaoyu died.
Last words.
Nan Bei,
you killed me in the first round
of the first game!
Thankfully,
I checked your identity.
You're a killer.
What the hell?
I am the killer?
Wait, wait.
Did you ask him to check me?
Did you check me first?
No conversing!
What's wrong again?
The gift?
I spent all my money this month.
Next month,
I'll give you two gifts.
Are they a couple?
You sense it, too.
Actually, they like each other.
They just need to
tell each other.
What's wrong?
We're holding a debate contest,
and one team is dropping out.
It's getting tough.
You hold debates?
What is it called?
It's a small game,
the Edge Cup.
I don't think you've heard of it.
The team that dropped out
was called team 235, right?
Can you guys
stay in the game?
Let's talk
about it.
Maybe
you can find
other debaters?
We don't offer many points.
There aren't many players.
Now,
you're the only team left.
We
chose to drop out because
there's another game
at the same time.
They offer three points.
We're exactly three points short.
Otherwise, we wouldn't.
In fact, we've been
struggling to hold
the game for years.
It's not a top competition,
and we offer only two points.
Nothing has been easy
but we managed until today.
If it is cancelled this year,
Next year, I'm afraid...
I hope
you can attend
the Edge Cup.
I'm really sorry.
We
have no other options.
Oh.
It's okay.
You did well today.
I just thought...
It's like how we turned against team one
to win the game back then.
I sympathize with them, too.
But
every team has its own problems
to be solved by themselves.
Listen to that!
You've grown up.
Treat me to bubble tea.
Shouldn't it be the other way around?
I should be rewarded
for helping you recover.
But
considering your good performance,
I'll treat you.
Coming.
Guys,
here's the takeout.
How did you find this place?
I asked around
and nobody knew.
Finally,
a delivery man
showed me the way.
Hello, Killer.
You've got quite some
hobbies.
To train for the debate in such an environment
is very
luxurious for me.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
You're not here
just for a visit, are you?
Tao Hao,
I know your team
is having a hard time.
But I really need help.
Can you help me?
We
will think about it.
You will?
That's great.
Think about it.
Please think about it.
Enjoy your food.
We're just going to think about it.
I didn't promise him anything.
Yeah.
It's even worse.
You're giving him
false hope.
Is it really that bad?
We'll see.
Got it.
I'll get dinner and come over.
Xia?
Don't worry.
He won't come again.
Okay.
Tao Hao.
I'm leaving.
I cleaned the car twice.
Rest assured.
Tao Hao,
may the sunflowers bring you sunshine.
Thank you.
Give me that.
Sunflower.
Hey, do you want some sunflower seeds?
It's yours.
Those who skipped the class
yesterday
had to copy short essays.
I did it until midnight.
I'm so sleepy.
Why
did you skip the lesson?
Madam,
please dive into
your memory.
Wasn't I sitting
next to you
yesterday?
I forgot.
What's wrong
between you and Liu Yanze?
He took your girlfriend?
I don't mind
telling you this.
You
are my first love.
Then what's the problem?
Please, it hurts.
Just tell me.
When did you become so gossipy?
I'm not gossiping.
It's for Dango.
What if he's a scum?
We should stop her.
Dango has
no taste.
What's so great about Liu Yanze?
Everything.
He's good at debating.
He's quite handsome.
He's president of the student union.
And he has good grades.
What?
Oh my,
you're angry.
What's wrong?
I'm afraid Xia
would come out of nowhere.
You're being dramatic.
He's not a ninja.
Me?
Come.
Come on, buddy.
Dude,
you go around here all day.
You've improved a lot
in pestering people
instead of debating.
Why don't you
split your team
in two to debate by yourselves?
You're wasting
your time and energy here.
Visit a nursing home.
Even the earthworms
can entertain themselves.
You can learn from them.
Then you won't have to ask for help,
right?
Why would a debate organizer
hang around here all the time?
Hey, hey.
Don't do this, man.
Hey.
Don't cry.
Let's go. I'll buy you a drink.
Stop crying.
Who is this?
See for yourself.
Man,
are you planning to...?
Don't be impulsive.
Listen,
Hao has no interest
in him.
Write a novel, alright?
Then what's going on?
He has been pestering Hao.
I roasted him.
That's it.
How did you
get him so drunk?
What to do now?
He's wasted.
What to do?
Let's call his friends first.
Sure.
Hey,
this dude has a girlfriend.
I'm his ex-girlfriend.
Do you know where he lives?
In the debate classroom.
Huh?
He's drunk
because of debating, huh?
How do you know?
It happens every time.
I thought he was on the debate team.
Why is he hosting games?
Fill it up.
He was the leader
of the debate team
back at the university.
Maybe the university wasn't great,
or maybe they weren't talented.
They were never invited to big games
and were often told to drop out.
It doesn't
have much to do with the university.
The good universities are the same.
Right, Ma Nan?
Yeah, it's about the debaters.
But he just wants to debate.
So he started the Edge Cup.
But of course,
they couldn't even attract
enough debaters.
In the first year,
some people
just like him were coming
to the game.
But since last year,
their games have been degrading
and losing participants.
So this year,
there is no financial support.
Will you do this for
your hobby?
That's not the right question.
For him,
it's not a hobby anymore.
But,
it was hard
for us to get so far.
Tao Hao,
let's go to the Edge Cup.
I've never done a tripartite debate.
It'd be interesting, right?
That's right.
I've long wanted
to battle team one.
Why is it feeling
so exciting?
So,
it's a deal.
Time is up.
Okay, thank you.
This is what debate means to me
and
to all the debaters
here on the spot.
No matter
how difficult it is,
we should just
do it.
Captain,
we're going to face team two.
Next, let's welcome Nanxiang Technical School,
DUFE,
and Team 235
to draw
the argument for the upcoming match.
Party A,
one must learn to take on burdens.
Party C,
one must learn to accept the fate.
What a loser's motion!
It suits you.
Accept the fate with the game.
Not everyone can take on burdens.
Let's see.
I...
Should I draw?
What a bad draw!
What's wrong with your luck?
Why can't you
be like team one
and draw a better motion?
Ouch.
Coach,
their argument
is that one should accept the fate.
It's not easy, right?
Jeez,
the orange is so sour.
No, it's not.
I'm peeling it for you
and feeding it to you.
What's your problem?
Your students are here.
I'll give you some respect.
Don't push it.
I have ulcer.
I don't want oranges.
Can you
get me a dragon fruit or something
from downstairs.
Maybe it helps.
I've been treating you too well.
You're so spoiled.
Kids,
I'll leave your coach to you.
Don't let him out of bed.
Don't worry, Madam.
Alright.
She's watching me
like I'm a prisoner.
I'm done.
I'm eating like a monk these days.
Now I don't
taste anything
and I'm bored to do anything.
Coach,
aren't you
eating light these days?
How did you get the ulcer?
Wait.
That's why the bag
is so hot.
Oh.
Chen's Sauce Pork.
What is this?
Why didn't you take it out earlier?
Give it here.
Maybe you should...
Give me that,
and I'll lecture you.
My brain is not working properly.
Why didn't you bring it earlier?
Nice.
Not bad. Thank you.
Coach, let's make it fast.
There's a tripartite debate tomorrow.
Our opponent
is the annoying team one.
We've never done it.
Tell us about
the tactics and rules.
The key points
are summarized into a poem.
A poem?
Take advantage of your opponent's arguments.
Seek the origin of the argument.
Attack the opponents on the key points.
Use their contradiction to set them up.
Substitute one thing for another to buy some time.
Oh no.
My brain is not working.
Get me
some spiced peanuts.
Go ahead.
Oh my,
Madam,
the coach just...
Shut up!
Hurry up and learn.
Time is running out.
About the tripartite competition,
we have to make arrangements
and find their
potential loopholes.
Do you understand?
That's what the old coach said?
Well,
I'm wondering if it's possible...
I mean maybe
team one wins and we rank second.
Will we share
the points in the end?
For the tripartite debate,
only the first place has points.
None for the others.
So...
So,
you should
shift your focus
from romance.
This is not a drill.
I repeat.
This is the final showdown
against team one.
Why are you yelling?
I said "maybe".
I, I just thought
there is the possibility.
If that happens,
we won't go to the provincial level.
All right.
We'll crush them!
Let's assign tasks.
I'll make the argument as usual.
Nan Bei and Xiaoyu, main debaters.
Ma Nan, closing argument.
Dango, information collector.
Any questions?
No.
Have you checked the rules?
It's a three-person competition.
Only three debaters are allowed.
What?
Then I'm not going.
That'd be a good idea.
Then I won't go either.
Ma Nan,
you can't
keep a low profile now.
You are a fine debater.
I agree.
That's it, then.
That's it for today.
Well,
do you have any plans this evening?
No, why?
Nothing.
See you then.
Bye.
Hao, bye.
Bye, Hao.
See you.
Stop.
What's wrong?
Dango.
Why do I feel
that I won't like
this conversation?
Ma Nan,
we always respect you
as our senior...
predecessor...
and a guide on debate.
Even though you're
passive, procrastinating, lazy,
bad at personal hygiene,
indecisive when something happens...
sometimes arrogant...
and occasionally
belittle others
to praise yourself,
we generally
think pretty highly
of you.
Hmm.
Thank you?
So we feel the need
to give you a push
in some things.
What is it?
When exactly are you going to
ask Hao out?
See you around.
Sit down.
Come on.
Don't mess things up.
Tao Hao and I are...
Shut up!
Come on!
Are we blind?
Don't move.
Thank you.
Well,
that's all for today.
Go back to rest.
Ma Nan.
Do you have any plans later?
No. You?
Me neither.
Oh.
See you, then.
See you tomorrow.
Hey.
Well,
"Three Hundred Days of First Love" will be on.
Shall we watch it together?
Sure.
OK, then.
Nan Bei, Xiaoyu, and Dango,
are you going?
I have plans. I'm busy.
I'm busy. I have plans.
None of us has time.
All right then.
I'll ask Meng Yuan and Dandan.
Then let's go together.
Great. The more the merrier, right?
See?
You're so sweet together.
You've made it
to the ninth sweetest
couple-to-be.
It's still getting updated?
Stop trying. You have no argument.
Even if you're right
that there's chemistry between us,
we can't rush
with those things, OK?
I have my own tempo.
Show some respect!
I had concerns before.
Do you want me to witness
Meng Yuan's tragedy again?
No!
You can't let it happen!
You know better than that!
So there's
one possibility left.
You
chickened out!
You couldn't make the final move.
You can't even win a sure game.
You're a tank
hiding behind a mage.
You're a disgrace!
Stop, stop.
You guys
have made your points
quite clear.
You got me, okay?
I swear
I'll make the move
at the right moment.
Okay?
Come on.
What's that look?
Do you want me to go now?
That's right!
If not now, when?
After graduation?
After retirement?
We've
prepared two movie tickets
for you.
"Godzilla vs. Kong"?
Sorry, those are mine.
These are yours.
"We'll Get Better"?
Yeah.
You will
get better together.
How nice.