I won't work overtime today
Episode 6
Director Wu
I'm sorry
I'm late
He Jiaojiao
How did you arrive
But everyone doesn't want it either
Blame her too much
After all, she just became a full-time
Late
And it's not what
An unforgivable thing
As long as next time
Just don't do it again
Director Wu
I know today is a seminar
So I just follow
All the information of the company in previous years
I made a copy for everyone
But the printer is broken
So I'm late
This is your information
It's okay
You are very thoughtful
Very good
Thank you
Just come
Why is there one missing
I'm sorry
Everyone
I copied it per head
Maybe it was careless
I'm sorry, Sister Ting
Without yours
Why is there one missing
I obviously bought it according to the head
I may have forgotten about you
It's okay
You two read a copy together
Come
Let's start the discussion now
So hungry
Bingbing
Didn't you have breakfast
Would you like to try two pieces
I made my own Poria cocos cake
Do the math
You can eat when you are asked to eat
Don't talk nonsense
How about it
This dish is really delicious
You did it
It's really delicious
As long as it tastes good
What about me
Learned before
A little bit of traditional Chinese medicine
Know a little about acupuncture points
Do you want me to press it for you
Real or false
Xu Chao, sit down, sit down
It won't work if you click it lightly
Switch sides, switch sides
Little Master
Whether it is massage technique
Or is it the art of documents?
Not in the palace
Are there imperial doctors and cooks
If you have too many skills, you don't weigh yourself
Learning more is never a bad thing
Sister Li
I'll give it to you again
Recommend cosmetics
How about it
Good
-What lipstick number -What lipstick number
I bought milk tea for everyone
Give him back in his way
How about this trick
Five women, eight groups
This is really an unspoken rule in the workplace
He Jiaojiao, stop
What is it
Are you spreading rumors about me
I warn you
Show some respect to your seniors
How
Stop pretending
Want respect, don't you
Do you think about your usual
All the things you did, all the things you did
What is the matter
Is worthy of my respect
Respect is about ability
Not seniority
He Jiaojiao
I'm going to educate you today
Tell you what a junior is
Let me educate you
What do you usually do
Forget it
But because of this
Delay my work
Don't blame me for being rude
You
You just became a full-time
You're doing this to me
You've gone too far
Get up
Mr. Li
You can go back first
It's working hours now
Thank you, Mr. Li
He Jiaojiao
You stay
The little beauty fainted
Is the ceremony more important or human life more important?
Empress
I didn't expect
You are a self-serving person
How can you be like this? How can you be so impressed with the world
I'm so disappointed by this
Is there anything else going on, Mr. Li
Did you just
How
Blame me again
I'm not
I just saw
I feel sorry for her again
Our President
It's really fraternity
What the hell are you talking about
I just saw her
Yeah, what you saw was right
I am
A person who likes to bully others
A self-serving person
If you don't think you can
You can fire me
He Jiaojiao, what are you doing
If you don't want to fire me
Then I'll go back to work first
What are you doing
So unaware of what's good or what's bad
Sooner or later I'll take you
You feel free to
This woman
Why don't you listen to me
Mr. Li
Why is it so slow
Just a sound
Don't make excuses at work
I was wrong, Mr. Li
Mr. Li, what are your orders
You go and arrange for Ho Jiaokjiao from the personnel department
Send me the information
Now
Immediately
What what what information
Casually
What's wrong with him
Personnel Department He Jiaojiao
Jiaojiao
Put this
Send it to General Manager Li's office
That
Brother Kai
My recruitment plan
Not finished yet
I just got some idea
Otherwise I
What thinking is not thinking
The leader will arrange some work for you
Why are you so picky
Leadership's instructions
Is your highest order
Go ahead
Good
Du Xiaosong
I finally found you
Do me a favor
Put this
Send it to the president's office
Why don't you send it yourself
If you ask you to send it, you will send it
Where's so much nonsense
Are you worried
I'm afraid of meeting Mr. Li changing clothes
Go quickly
Let me see
What happened to the promise
Ask He Jiaojiao to send a document
It's gonna take so long
Still
He Jiaojiao doesn't want to come
Go ahead
All right
Then you help me
Make a copy of this
OK
And this
Come on in
Do you know it's wrong
Yes Yes Yes
Mr. Li
It's all my fault
Who are you
Why are you here
I am
Intern at the Human Resources Center
I came to bring you the documents
He Jiaojiao
Didn't I ask her to come
Sister Jiaojiao
She's not feeling well
Uncomfortable
What's wrong with her
Mr. Li
Not
Mr. Li, where are you going
Mr. Li
What's wrong with you
Why are you uncomfortable
Or I'll take you to the hospital
I have a bit of a headache
But it's okay
I'm almost done
Headache
Do you have a fever
Mr. Li
This is in the company
You come with me
What's the situation
Am I going to be silenced
Mr. Li, can you let me go
I won't let go
What are you gonna do
Don't stare at me
You glared at me and wouldn't let go
Why don't you listen to me every time
Finish your words
It's always I haven't spoken yet
You're impatient
Then tell me
What are you gonna say
I'm sorry
He Jiaojiao
Today I was in the hallway
It's all angry words
I've never had
Want to fire you
I've never felt
You are a self-serving person
People who like to bully others
And
Why did you treat me
Hot and cold
What exactly am I doing wrong
Mr. Li, it's not your fault
I'm wrong
I also think
Mainly your problem
But I can forgive you
Please correct it
What I made
Here's your apology
Whether you like to eat or not
I eat
Who said they wouldn't eat?
You really did it
It's delicious
That's nice
Mr. Li
If you don't have anything else to do
I'm leaving first
Don't be angry anymore
Okay, then I'll forgive you, too
Then you can go and do your job first
Actually
You can stay a little longer
He Jiaojiao
Sister Jiaojiao
Are you still not leaving
Let's go
I'll do it tomorrow
Waiting for you
Forget it, you go first
I finished the plan
Could it be that you and Li
Don't talk nonsense
I promise I won't give it away
Your adultery
I'm leaving first
Why are you here
Wait for me
I'll be fine in a minute
Who's waiting for you
I'm leaving
Childish
Aren't you leaving
Why are you back again
It's too dark
I'm afraid of the dark
I need someone down with me
Can you find some
A more careful reason
Here is my company
I can be where I want to be
More childish
You give me that cake today
Is there any more