English subtitles are available
Bright Time EP18
Folks at the frontline, and friends,
at this moment, we express our gratitude
to those still committed to their jobs
across all sectors.
Friends...
Dong, you're back.
Good evening, ma'am.
Happy
New Year!
Madam,
you look very familiar,
and seem amiable.
Thanks, you're so sweet.
It must be destiny.
I feel like I've seen you before.
Oh, really?
Well, Dong,
there are fruits and snacks.
Have a sit.
I'll go make dumplings for you.
Don't bother,
we just had dinner.
You did?
We had dumplings.
Mom, please. I'm hungry.
Help yourself.
Okay.
Make yourself at home.
Thank you.
Change your shoes.
Nothing beats your mom's dumplings.
They taste completely
different from
what I made.
Dong,
you guys eat.
After that, go take a shower.
Tomorrow is the first day
of the New Year,
you should start it fresh and clean.
Madam, I'd rather not shower.
I didn't bring pajamas.
What's there to worry about?
You can wear Dong's.
No, Mom. No way.
Come on,
isn't Jinghui
your good friend?
Be kind.
Thanks, Madam.
Mom,
wait a sec, let me finish eating.
I'll make the bed.
No, I'll do it.
I'll sleep on the couch tonight.
No way!
How could you,
as a guest, do this?
It's fine.
How about
you two boys share the bed?
It's quite big.
Can we?
Sure, it's settled.
Forget the couch.
Eat more, Jinghui.
Okay.
You don't hog the bed, do you?
Of course not,
I never do that.
And do you snore?
No.
Never!
It's so cold.
Jinghui,
come on,
eat now
before the food gets cold.
Thank you.
This is for you.
What a feast!
This fish,
Dong made it.
His cooking is better than mine.
Try it.
You made this?
How's it?
It's pretty good.
Of course.
At least you won't starve
as a cook.
Absolutely.
Madam,
since you and Ling Dong cook,
I can't just eat for free.
I'll wash the dishes later.
No, you're our guest.
Eat more fish,
it's good for the brain.
You
need nutrition for school.
Eat more.
You too.
Right, not only is your brain slow,
but your feet stink.
Rumors,
complete nonsense!
You can say my brain is slow,
but stinky feet are just your nose
being too sensitive.
I'm just being honest.
Ignore him, ma'am, have more food.
Jinghui,
is there a tear
under the sleeve
of your elbow?
Where?
Pull it back, see?
Look, isn't it?
Oh, yes.
It's okay,
might've ripped it
playing basketball.
I didn't notice.
I'll just throw this away
and get a new one.
Don't.
I can
sew it up later.
Let's eat.
Have more.
Enjoy it.
Dong, you eat more too.
Okay.
Jinghui, if you like it,
come over more often.
That's cool.
Hold on,
don't move.
Can you hear the ocean?
Yes, I hear the echo of wisdom.
Shouldn't it all be water?
How could it be?
I know what you mean by water.
The sea of knowledge.
Can't tell at all.
Mom, here you are.
Jinghui,
I don't think your shirt
can keep you warm.
It may just look good.
No, ma'am...
it can.
I didn't feel cold.
That's right,
you young boys
are full of energy.
Dong sometimes doesn't wear the clothes
I bought him 'cause he feels hot.
When did this happen?
Remember
the thermal underwear
I bought you?
You never wore it.
I was worried you'd be cold,
even got you
the thick kind.
Are you asleep?
I can't sleep.
Counting sheep then.
My grandma's coming back tomorrow.
Thank God.
You're finally leaving.
I'm gonna
have a nervous breakdown.
Would you stop saying that?
Exaggerating.
Didn't you complain about the hot water
and hard bed?
Hurry up and leave.
But, to be honest,
I really like
staying at your place.
It feels just like home.
Goodnight.
Sweetheart,
did you miss me?
Of course,
I missed you so much.
Your dad had to
go abroad for work,
left early this morning.
Who cares about him?
Let's go inside.
Come on, Grandma.
I'll carry that.
It's okay.
Let's go.
You look like you've lost weight.
No,
I've been well taken care of by my friend.
You definitely haven't eaten properly.
No! I have!
My friend cooked for me.
Look at you...
Jinghui!
Jinghui.
Hi, Ma Yiming.
Did you miss me?
Disgusting.
Jinghui,
you've changed.
What's wrong?
You don't love me anymore.
Get away.
Jinghui.
Ling Dong,
here's the breakfast I brought you.
Have a try.
Thanks.
How is it? Good?
Yeah.
What would you like
for tomorrow?
Thanks, but I can buy it myself.
No worries, there are
many breakfast stores around my home.
I see,
well, thanks then.
By the way,
have you finished your homework?
Yes.
There are 2 questions
that are easy to get wrong.
I can
help you have a check.
Okay.
Sometimes,
making sacrifices
for others is a virtue, right?
What are you talking about?
I didn't get it.
You'll understand when you're older.
Why are you
picking on your apprentice again?
How is this picking on her?
If she wasn't apprenticed to me,
would I do this to her?
Let's go play basketball.
Go ahead.
Keke,
have you seen the new movie?
No, is it good?
It's fantastic.
I'm telling you,
it's definitely the best one
I've seen this year.
Who did you go with?
My mom.
It was so awkward.
Oh my gosh,
shouldn't it
be watched with someone you like?
Exactly.
I'm so jealous of those
who went to see it together.
Lan Jinghui, what are you doing?
Today's sunlight is so nice,
isn't it?
I'm serious,
that movie is amazing.
A Must-Watch for Couples!
This one?
Saturday night at 7:30 p.m.,
two tickets side by side.
Done.
Good morning, Xiaohua.
Your breakfast.
Since you bring me
good food every morning,
as your master,
I want to tell you
some good news.
I don't care
about which team won
or who was the
MVP.
Not about basketball!
It's about Ling Dong.
What's wrong with him?
He...
wants to invite you to a movie.
But he's too shy to say so.
So he asked me to do it.
I had to
help him out.
Good news, right?
Anyway, the ticket code
has been sent to you.
Don't be late!
Beauty in common things.
Each different part of China.
Let's go watch a movie this weekend.
Why?
The latest release. Don't miss it.
Tell me the reason.
Just a regular
team-building activity.
Why so many questions?
Will you join me?
I've bought tickets.
Will you finish your homework?
Yes, I promise.
Okay, send me the ticket code.
Got it.
The most common things.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Hi, Ling Dong.
Xiaohua?
You...
Sorry, bro,
I was caught up
in an unexpected situation.
So I gave the ticket to Xiao Xiaohua.
Tell me the plots later, okay?
The movie's on.
Such a good movie,
I can't miss it.
Hi, Luyang.
Qingtian, you're here.
When you invited me out today,
I thought you wanted
to help me with my studies.
I didn't expect a movie.
I'm gonna go get popcorn.
It's still early,
let's go somewhere first.
Let's go!
Okay.
Ready for my show?
One more time.
You can do it.
You can do it!
Forget it.
I just don't have luck with it.
Let's go back for the movie.
Wait,
I'll help you.
That one, the panda.
It's normal not to catch it.
That's how they make money.
Let's go watch the movie.
No, today I'll get you one.
I must!
Wait for me.
Lan Jinghui!
Don't think we don't know
what you're thinking.
How can you do this?
To get what you want,
you'll do anything!
You dare to call yourself
"Captain Chenjun"?
a student from Class 5?
You dare to
let me call you master?
You're despicable, shameless!
Despicable!
Shameless!
May I ask
when can we leave?
I must do
what I promised you.
You spent enough
to buy twenty dolls.
We've been at it all night.
I got it!
It's so ugly!
No, no.
I want to get your favorite one.
No need!
One more time.
This one is good enough.
Really?
But...
Stop it. This is good.
We spent all night,
even missed the movie.
I've always been asked
to do my best.
And then,
I got used to it.
Just be yourself, don't force it.
Be carefree, like me.
I'll get another ticket.
I just said,
be carefree
like me.
Okay.
What do we do next?
Tired. Let's go home.
Morning, Xiaohua.
Where's my breakfast?
Xiaohua,
where's my breakfast?
Ling Dong,
how was the movie?
Good, right?
Do you like it?
Wait,
why are you ignoring me?
Hello?
Hi?
C'mon!
Xiaohua.
Xiaohua?
Xiao Xiaohua!
It was my bad.
I was wrong.
I really had something to do yesterday.
That's why I didn't show up.
Okay?
Childish.
Xiaohua...
Don't do this again!
You made me...
Made you what?
Nothing!
Then where's my breakfast?
Depends on you.
Wait,
Xiaohua...
save me an egg white,
or you can leave me the yolk.
You aren't taking your bags.
Where are you going?
No one's grateful.
Good intentions wasted!
Hmph!
Grandma, I'm back.
Finally, you're back!
Wash your hands for dinner.
Tired from studying?
Why do you look so down?
Nothing.
Maybe because I'm hungry.
Grandma, what's for dinner?
All your favorite dishes.
Your dad's back too.
He's in the study.
Go call him down for dinner.
My good boy.
Go now.
Remember
to transfer money to the school today.
Ling Dong
is a good kid.
He's been doing his best
to help Jinghui with
with his studies.
So make sure the money
is transferred on time.
I shouldn't have to
remind you.
Don't forget it.
Okay.
Morning, Jinghui.
You're here.
Do these first.
I'll explain if you get them wrong.
Don't wanna do it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Do I need a reason?
You have to do...
I'm out.
Ma Yiming, let's go for a walk.
It's too stuffy here.
Can't stay another minute.
Wait!
Do I need a reason?
Leave me alone.
Let's go.
Jinghui.
Jinghui!
What's up? Are you arguing?
What's wrong with Lan Jinghui?
No idea.
Why did you...
Are you here?
Morning.
I've marked the
key points.
Check them out.
It's upside down.
You just asked me to read,
but didn't mention how to hold it.
Do this worksheet today.
See you in the study room after school.
On purpose?
Nope.
You told me to do it, so I did.
I don't know why you're
suddenly acting like a kid.
I don't have to
help you if you
don't want.
This attitude helps no one.
Lan Jinghui,
you finally made
some progress.
Giving up now?
I'm telling you,
studying is
your responsibility.
If you don't want to learn,
no one can help you!
Listen!
This is
my own business!
It has nothing to do with you!
Okay, I'll leave you to it.
Ling Dong!
What's up?
It's getting cold!
Just wait for a few seconds.
It's okay.
Ling Dong!
What again?
Towel!
Don't use mine.
I'll give you another one.
Which one is yours?
Are they all yours?
I told you not to use mine!
I'll give you another one.
What's the big deal?
I'm so handsome.