[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP28]
Lady Yan,
Is there truly no
way to bring someone back to life?
This world is rife with injustice,
especially towards women.
[At home, one must obey the father,]
[and upon marriage, the husband,]
As for all the so called women's virtues,
If one makes even the slightest misstep,
we will face scorn.
The constant barrage of
criticism will be overwhelming.
Just think about it,
how ironic is this?
But if one only clings to these notions,
how can they ever seek
true fairness?
Xiu,
how did you come to know Lord. Mo?
And why do you refer to him as Qianzhi?
[He once saved my life.]
[However,]
perhaps at that time,
he had already
selected me as a sacrifice.
You do bear some
resemblance to Mo Xiuxiu.
[But Xiu]
is not Mo Xiuxiu after all.
Halt!
Stay where you are!
Jing Lin, stay alert.
What is the meaning of this?
Release Lord Mo, now!
He's conspired with the Fire Moth Sect,
exploiting his power and slaughtering innocents.
The IG has been ordered to apprehend him.
This is sheer nonsense!
Lord Mo is a guardian of the people,
[fighting valiantly against the spectres.]
[When the criminal Ji Dafu was executed,]
Lord Shen intervened multiple times,
clearly with ulterior motives.
Lord Mo instructed us
to remain vigilant.
And indeed,
we uncovered that you
[were secretly colluding with the spectres.]
[Now,]
[you're caught abducting Lord Mo]
[and turn the tables on us?]
You are framing us!
Since Lord Shen's arrival,
[the masked spectres have emerged]
[like mushrooms after a rainstorm.]
Is this merely a coincidence?
[This is utterly foolish.]
You have all been
deceived by Mo Qianzhi's facade!
Exactly who abducted you all?
Xiu,
you must reveal the truth.
Mo is the one colluding with the spectres,
planning to use you
as sacrifices.
Shen Du,
[we haven't met in years.]
[I never imagined you'd]
[end up to be such a corrupted official.]
Surrender yourselves!
Corrupt officials!
Release Lord Mo at once!
Mo Qianzhi is the true culprit behind the
masked spectres' atrocities in the city.
He has exploited
the trust of all of you!
The White Death!
Release Lord Mo immediately!
[Lord Mo is a compassionate official]
[who genuinely cares for the people!]
[He is always concerned about us.]
Don't you frame him!
Release Lord Mo!
What are you trying to do?
Step back! Back!
Don't harm the civilians!
Neither violence nor reasoning
will resolve this situation.
[These people]
[have lost their minds!]
Shen Du,
[guise or genuine,]
[they've figured it out,]
have you?
So this is your true scheme.
Hold on!
Stop!
Sun Tan!
Are you delinquents revolting?
Apologies, Lord Mo.
You all know
how difficult we are to deal with!
Everyone, step back! Step back!
Let them go!
Come on. Move!
We're grateful for your aid earlier.
Lord Shen, I'm truly humbled.
Chief has sent a letter instructing me
to assist Lady Yan with the investigation.
This is indeed our duty.
If it weren't for your aid earlier,
the citizens in the city
would have surely
drowned us with their spittle.
To the people of Yingzhou,
Lord Mo is a
rare and exemplary official.
In disasters, he opens soup kitchens,
offering free porridge to those in need.
On normal days, he leads the constables
to repair houses for the citizens
[without any charge.]
[With his exceptional behavior,]
[how could the people]
ever perceive him as a villain?
On one hand, he's cherished by the people,
and respected by his peers as a virtuous man,
while on the other, he is a madman who
disregards life and follows a cult.
It's hard to see through
these two personas.
For now, we can only stay outside the city
and observe how things unfold.
I truly appreciate
the delinquents, our brothers-in-arms,
who have stood by us in this situation.
I, the head of the Delinquents
in Gannan,
place my trust in those
acknowledged by our chief.
Lord Shen,
we've just received a classified message
from Xiang'an.
Her Majesty has issued a decree to mobilize
the troops of the neighboring counties.
She orders me and General Zhenyuan
to capture Mo Qianzhi alive.
But Mo Qianzhi just drove us
out of the city.
The message came with unexpected haste!
Prior to our arrival,
Her Majesty summoned me and
[ordered me to keep an eye on Mo Qianzhi.]
Upon my arrival in Yingzhou,
an agent reached me through covert means.
That must be Biqiu
who was murdered not long ago.
It's very likely that Mo
sensed something amiss and reported
the news to Xiang'an early this morning.
So it appears,
the entire world,
inside and outside the imperial realm,
is under Her Majesty's
watchful eye.
Based on this, it is evident
that sending me to Gannan region
to handle the case of the masked spectre
was also part of Her Majesty's
calculations.
Her Majesty
has ordered you to seize Yingzhou.
If a war breaks out,
what will happen to the citizens within?
I pray for a turn in our fortunes
before General Zhenyuan's arrival.
Who is it?
Show yourself!
Qi Yeyun?
Sneaking around,
you want us to catch you or something?
Sis taught me to act this way.
Always observe carefully first,
Caution ensures lasting safety!
[I, Shen Du, am here.]
[I need to have a word with Mo Qianzhi!]
If you want to talk,
come up and talk!
You really dare to come alone,
aren't you afraid I could end you?
I'm here to deliver
the ultimatum.
Xiang'an's aware of your suspicious activities.
Her Majesty has dispatched troops
to Yingzhou.
It's not too late to back down now.
They planned to launch an attack?
It won't be as simple
as they think.
You believe that the
tens of thousands of citizens in the city,
along with those few masked spectres,
are enough to challenge
the imperial army?
The will of the masses
can stand against legions.
Do you recall the vow you made
when you became my father's disciple?
To serve the empire with loyalty
without disappointing the populace.
Shen Du,
I honestly never imagined
that one day you would say this to me.
Can't you see
that the current empire
is already infested with corruption?
Its downfall is just a matter of time.
Then eliminate these corrupt elements
instead of toppling the entire empire.
The Fire Moth Sect
has always been ruthless,
ready to betray anyone at any moment.
Are you really willing to gamble
with the lives of
these innocent citizens?
If you want to negotiate,
I'm open to it,
but you must agree to one condition.
What condition?
Bring me
the head of Lady Yan.
Then there's nothing to discuss.
My dear Du,
she is the Queen's pawn,
[a mere tool used by her]
[to manipulate you!]
Without her,
you will finally see clearly
the true state of devastation
that has befallen the empire!
The one blinded by hatred
is you.
This time,
you've truly made a mistake.
I made a mistake?
You're treating your foe like a father.
No,
like a mother, I suppose.
What she consumes daily
is the delicacies stained with
the blood of your kin!
[What she revels in]
is the wealth and luxury built upon
the bones of your kin!
I made a mistake?
Aren't you even more absurdly wrong!
Don't you yearn to uncover the truth?
This is a sack used for storing supplies.
Why does it bear the mark
of the granary from back then,
and why is it found
in Gannan, a thousand miles away?
Shouldn't these
have been destroyed
in the fire back then?
Have you ever considered
that my master,
your father
was actually guarding
a treasury
that had already been emptied!
I will uncover the truth myself.
But you want to gamble
the lives of all the citizens in this city
and risk a massacre
to secure your own future.
I'm afraid I must disagree!
Just stop.
I have very few
loved ones left in this world.
I don't need your approval.
There's no turning back now.
I have planned and endured for so long,
I won't let it all go to waste.
I remember
you said you wanted revenge, right?
Of course I want revenge,
but I
and my father
would never risk
the lives of the citizens for revenge!
Lord Shen.
Shen Du,
how did it go?
There's no room for negotiation.
Jing Lin, where is
General Zhenyuan's current location?
We've received word from Mengzhou that
reinforcements should arrive in three days.
As for Mo Qianzhi,
who knows how many troops he has amassed?
If by then all the able-bodied
men in the city come to defend,
it will surely be a fierce battle.
Not necessarily!
Mr. Pan, your efficiency is remarkable.
Lord Shen,
we've brought the things
that you requested.
What are these...
What do you need these bamboo poles for?
Employing a daring strategy.
Success or failure, it's all on this!
You're not planning to
capture the city before
General Zhenyuan arrives, are you?
Qianzhi,
people often say
let the past
be the past.
But some pains
aren't just memories; they are
deeply embedded in our flesh and blood.
They resonate with
every breath,
[It constantly destroys,]
[curses,]
asking why I haven't ended my life yet.
For those
who have never truly experienced it,
how could they possibly know
and on what grounds can they teach others
how to live?
Xiu,
do you think
I am wrong?
You are a good official,
a great brother.
[You are the]
[kindest soul I know.]
You rescued me
from the piles of corpses.
[You saved my life]
[and helped countless others in the city.]
You have never wronged anyone.
It is this world
that has failed you far too much.
You are just like her,
always trusting me without hesitation,
while I have let you both down.
If one day,
she truly returns to life,
I fear she may not recognize
the man her brother
have turned into now.
If it were possible,
I would genuinely like to know
what the original you
was truly like.
People above, heed my words!
General Zhenyuan commands a hundred thousand strong,
and has reached the outskirts.
[Safeguard the citizens]
[and crush the rebels!]
This would be your last chance.
Surrender, and you will not be harmed!
[If you remain obstinate,]
we will wipe out the traitors
to safeguard our people!
[Lord Mo!]
Lord Mo!
If this battle can be averted,
please spare the people in this city
a chance to survive.
[The current situation]
[far exceeds our expectations.]
I have heard that General Zhenyuan
is known for his blood-thirst nature.
[With a hundred thousand troops,]
[the city will surely]
face destruction today.
Great suffering awaits the people!
[Greatness never]
comes from indecision!
Lord Mo, Master
sent me to deliver a message to you.
This is the crucial moment
for our great cause.
Do not let mercy
cloud your judgment.
[The Fire Moth Sect]
[has always been ruthless,]
[ready to betray anyone at any moment.]
[Are you really willing to gamble]
[with the lives of]
[these innocent citizens?]
[Lord Mo has dedicated himself]
[to Yingzhou and its people,]
yet he's been framed by the treacherous.
We must stand by Lord Mo!
Defend the city!
Stand by Lord Mo!
[You are a good official,]
[a great brother.]
[You are the]
[kindest soul I know.]
In the end,
it is I who have failed Yingzhou...
[Stand by Lord Mo!]
[Defend the city!]
Shen Du!
[I, Mo Qianzhi,]
challenge you to a duel!
[You and I have finally come to this.]
The martial arts you mastered as a child
were taught by me.
In the past,
you have never bested me.
You picked up this technique
with surprising speed!
With dedication and practice,
one can achieve remarkable progress.
One day,
I will defeat you!
Then you better catch up,
for I am determined to become
the greatest general of the empire,
to charge across the battlefield and serve
my country with unwavering loyalty.
This time,
I will emerge victorious!
What should we do?
Qianzhi...
It seems I have indeed aged,
my reflexes can't keep up with yours.
Protect Lord Mo!
You challenged me to a duel
because you can't stand to see
the people of Yingzhou suffer, correct?
Open the gate!
No need for war, wonderful!
What a clever ruse!
Du,
you have truly made
great strides over the years.
[You have won!]
If you had observed with a clear mind,
you might have seen through this trick.
What I wagered on
was your reluctance to risk
the lives of all the citizens of Yingzhou.
Thus,
you have not truly lost.
When will the reinforcements arrive?
Tomorrow.
Then how will you
explain everything?
Mo Qianzhi's been manipulated by the cult,
overestimating his own strength.
Yingzhou's military strength
is severely lacking.
There are still many citizens in the city
who believe you are being used
and manipulated by the Fire Moth Sect.
They are still pleading for you.
[Tell me,]
how do you contact with the leader
of the Fire Moth Sect?
All that laugh, like moths drawn to the flame.
Moths that brave the fire do not perish,
[but are reborn anew.]
The notion of resurrection is a fallacy.
[God cherishes all lives.]
Even mayflies that live for a day
have their place
in the cycle of reincarnation.
How could they not enter the cycle?
Moths into the fire will turn to ashes,
unable to enter the cycle,
how could they ever be reborn?
The one you contacted,
was it Chen Huo'e?
I warned you long ago
not to get involved.
You didn't realize the depth of the
situation and insisted on forging ahead.
[In truth, I never reported the]
[chaos caused by the masked spectres;]
someone was posing as me.
From the very start,
you were ensnared in someone else's plot.
What is this man's true intention?
Until I meet the Queen
in Xiang'an,
I will remain silent.
Regardless of what happened,
you are always like a brother to me.
Lady Yan!
Xiu.
Why are you here?
Does Mo Qianzhi have to die?
Once we arrive in Xiang'an,
Her Majesty will make the decision.
It's a long journey ahead;
would it be OK if I gave him some food?
Rest assured,
we will take good care of him
along the way.
No matter what,
[it was Qianzhi]
[who named me.]
You didn't come
here just for this, right?
I'm begging you,
please help me.
I'm sorry about all this.
Jing Lin!
I must see Mo Qianzhi!
I'm not like those girls
who were meant to be sacrificed.
[I've known for a long time]
[what Qianzhi planned to do.]
I did it of my own accord.
Xiu,
please stop.
You shouldn't be here.
Leave.
Xing.
Don't come any closer!
I just wanted to see you
and have a few words with you.
[Speaking of which,]
the days when Qianzhi was with me
were the happiest
and most fulfilling days of my life.
Without you,
I would have perished long ago.
[Thank you for giving me a name.]
[Xiu,]
what a lovely name!
Xiu...
But I know
that every time you call
her name,
it feels so profoundly different.
[I understand]
that deep down,
what you truly desire
has always been one thing:
to bring
Xiuxiu back to life.
Qianzhi,
farewell.
Xiu!
[Xiu!]
Qianzhi,
[Xiuxiu is here for me.]
Xiu!
Why are you so impulsive?
Du!
Have everyone else step back.
Come here,
I need to talk to you.
Du,
I knew you got out of the Custodial Ward,
[and I've heard you've become]
[the commander of the Imperial Guard.]
[I've also heard you've become]
[cold-hearted and ruthless.]
But I'm genuinely happy for you.
You're the last survivor of the Shens.
If you were still gentle and naive,
how could you possibly avenge master
and the rest of the Shen Family?
After establishing the Imperial Guard,
I have been diligently investigating.
On the surface,
the evidence in the Shens' case
appears irrefutable.
Yet I still uncovered
some suspicious details.
The events could not possibly have been
orchestrated by a single person.
Master was inherently modest,
always seeking to avoid court intrigues.
[His only concern was for the people.]
Regardless of who it was in power,
he simply did what he believed was right.
Peace for the people was his only wish.
[His very wish]
[offended the interests of many.]
The Majesty,
to whom you are devoted,
desired nothing less than his submission.
The ones responsible for the Shens' demise
were the Zhou Family.
I will definitely get to the bottom
of what happened back then.
No matter how many years it takes,
no matter who I will cross,
I will seek justice
from them one by one.
To bring peace to the souls
of the dozens who died unjustly.
Du,
I never thought
that you and I would find ourselves
at odds due to the same hatred.
Should you ever have your revenge,
remember to light an incense in my memory.
When I journey to the afterlife,
I will finally find peace...
Qianzhi!
[Qianzhi!]
I left something
for you in
Xiu's portrait.
Qianzhi...
Gosh!
Retribution has arrived!
Right after Lord Mo's departure,
this bizarre incident occurred.
This is divine retribution!
It's poisoning.
Move aside!
Lord Shen,
there have been several reports
of this strange phenomenon in the city.
It's truly alarming.
Over thirty citizens have been affected.
If this continues,
we're bound to face chaos.
This is the work of the Fire Moth Sect.
[If we can't find a solution...]
Then
the Fire Moth Sect could use this poison
to take down the entire city
without a single drop of bloodshed.
Although this poison is potent,
its effects are slow to manifest.
For now,
they are not in immediate danger.
I will find a way
to obtain the antidote.
Understood!
You take over.
[I left something]
[for you in Xiu's portrait.]