Hello Debate Opponent 2 EP11
-I'm sorry.  -Stop.
Hao
Why should you apologize to us?
You don't know
how cool you were just now.
After you left,
the students here were blue in the face.
I'm so scared just now
that my heart virtually burst out of my chest.
Hao
You know what,
Mr. Li
at that time
was blue in the face for a while
and then was black in the face.
This is the effect of rehabilitation training.
But the question is
how they know
we were in the competition.
They must have noticed
the league.
I still can't believe that
the senior is such a person.
I don't think he did that.
Why can't you see through him?
He's just a polished scoundrel, okay?
That's enough.
Don't listen to his nonsense, Dango.
I think it's a thing about the whole team.
It's not up to one person to decide.
It's useless
if he opposes it alone.
Right?
Besides,
now that they
already have this idea,
even if we
report it to the school at that time,
they'll still compete with us anyway.
Right.
Just now
I left on an impulse.
Now
we need to be calm and rational.
Because we certainly
won't give the league to others.
We've been preparing for this for a long time.
How can we
just give it to others?
Now let's figure out
how to enter the league.
Hao
You send me a copy of
competition system and schedule.
I'll see what loopholes
I can find.
Hao
It is OK.
We'll go through
the difficulties together.
Look, this is...
Your transformation plan worked.
In fact, it's not
your job.
You still said no.
It's not just the effect of the transformation plan.
I didn't think so much at that time.
I just couldn't stand the fact that
we all worked so hard,
but they still
thought nothing of us.
So
I can give you an
extra reward.
What?
You don't have to serve team one anymore.
So you must have plenty of time for yourself.
You can spend it on yourself.
Are there any places you want to go
that you haven't yet been able to visit?
Aquarium,
Botanical Garden,
Zoo,
Museum,
and several shopping malls.
Enough, enough.
Although it is an extra reward,
I can only accompany you to one place.
You think about it carefully.
The old coach says that
he supports our decision.
I told you.
He must be on our side.
Oh.
Hey.
Discount.
It's great.
Let's have a talk.
I have a competition tomorrow.
It won't take you long.
You go ahead.
I've been thinking a lot these days.
I think
we'd better calm down
for a while.
Just hear me out.
I didn't mean to break up.
I just think
we've had a lot things
going on these days.
You and I both need some time
to think it over, right?
I agree.
Well, I'll go first.
Well, I...
We are just...
friends.
He's here to see what you mean, right?
Yeah.
Have you decided yet?
At the beginning,
we were really together
because we liked each other.
But it wasn't long
before we realized that
we weren't really right for each other.
But you know how I am.
I've been trying to
cater to him
and adapt to him.
After all, it's
not hard for me.
He also had a lot of complaints.
But because I've been catering to him
and humouring him,
so
He may not bear to say goodbye.
Are you tired?
A little.
But
there is a run-in period
when two people get together.
After all, no two people
are born right to each other.
Your words
are no different than
saying the earth is round.
It's basically nonsense.
Remember
what we told you before?
It doesn't matter what his ups and downs are.
What matters is how you feel.
It's how you feel that matters.
Understand?
Okay.
Thank you for walking me home.
Bye bye.
Senior Ma Nan
Do you also want to read it?
I remember
one episode of Conan
where a team
kidnapped
the younger brother of the opposing ace player
in order to win.
You see, why don't we also...
It's not a good idea.
I major in law.
That will be sentenced.
There is also a theatrical version
where a singer
drank a special drug
and couldn't speak for three days.
Why don't we
sneak into their dormitory?
And then...
Did you hear
what you said?
Oops.
There's nothing I can do.
What can you do?
There is one actually.
Stop bragging.
What will you do
if I get this done?
Oh.
If you really get this done,
I'll call you Dad for a week.
Okay.
You can count on me.
You just have to prepare for the competition.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Background music for the entrance.
Why are they here?
They are just envious.
Later the captain
will show them
what is self-limitation.
Let them know what their limitations are.
Chief judge
We find that
the players of DUFE
don't match the registration list.
The registration list is
Tao Hao, Ma Nan,
Mu Xiaoyu and Nan Bei,
which doesn't match the current players here.
According to regulations,
we have the right to suspend the competition.
Oops.
Coach Wang, long time no see.
I heard that
Fulin is determined to
win the championship this time.
You are...
Yeah, Yeah.
But I heard that the requirements for the Points Race
are particularly strict.
Fortunately,
we compete with team two.
I heard that their team one
hasn't lost a competition in several years
in a row.
If Fulin
loses in Points Match,
it would be too demoralizing.
Hmm.
Coach Wang
If it wasn't for my stomach
at the time of recruitment,
I would have won honor for Fuling now.
Although
the strength of our team
is quite strong,
will exposing
all the strength
so early affect our chance of winning this year?
Maybe
we should save our strength.
What the hell?
How could the opponent know
our internal affairs?
It has been confirmed that
the participants of Team NEG
don't match the registration list.
According to the rules of the Match,
both sides should
strictly abide by the rules.
But because they are from the same school.
So if the original team members
have special reasons,
they can report to the organizer.
And the live debate team can replace them.
May I ask the original debate team members
have any questions?
Chief judge
Our debate team
has no special reason.
Coincidentally,
we even bring our clothes.
Background music of leaving.
You also don't leave.
Since I'm here,
just stay and have a look.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to
final eight of
the Qiyi Cup College Students Debate Tournament.
This match
will be broadcasted live
on the city's educational channel.
Now I declare that
the match officially starts.
Yanze
You will preside over the replay.
Okay.
Let's talk about the angle first.
Team two has an advantage in this topic.
Setting public image
is a typical marketing.
And people
naturally have
negative feelings about marketing.
Not necessarily.
Don't you like watching Li Jiaqi
who sells goods through livestreaming?
There has been
a similar debate before
about whether the entertainment stars
should be criticized for setting public image.
But if we apply
this phenomenon
to
the average people,
people will talk more about
the kind of behaviors
we use to label ourselves
on our moments
and social media platforms.
And people will unconsciously
try to rationalize
their various actions.
So team two is easy to lose advantage.
Most people will instead
support the public image
and think it's
a harmless thing.
Yes.
I think this point is really well
in argument of Team AFF.
We will begin with the opening argument
of the first debater from Team AFF
which will last three minutes.
Please.
Thank you, chief judge.
Hello, everyone.
Our view is that the advantages of
setting public image outweigh its disadvantages.
We often see the news in our lives
that the public image of some entertainment stars
are ruined,
and often
set some public images
for ourselves
in our circle of friends.
What exactly is setting public image?
We believe that
setting public image
is a kind of image management
in the era of social network.
It's not that different from
how we express ourselves
through dressing and speaking,
or making
a well-crafted resume
to apply for a job.
They are all managing our image
in the eyes of others
to present a better version
of ourselves.
This point is down to earth.
It is quite normal to dress appropriately
or embellish the resume,
thus leading the audience to agree with
setting public image.
In today's complex
social division of labor,
a marketer
may be exposed to more people
and information in a day
than throughout a lifetime
in an agricultural society.
And the phenomenon of public image
in social networks
greatly solves
the problem.
It uses simple settings
to outline our image,
so that the cognition between people
is fast and concrete.
By checking your Weibo
and updating your WeChat Moments,
I'll know roughly
a lot of information about you.
Setting public image has virtually improved
the social efficiency of the whole society.
This is another benefit.
To sum up,
we firmly believe that
the advantages of setting public image outweigh its disadvantages.
Thank you.
The definition of image management
confuses the purpose of setting public image.
And then they put the public image
equal to the goal.
I'm afraid it will keep our arguments
from hitting the nail on the head.
The two arguments of the opponent are profound.
Let's start by the wrong relation between public image and goals.
Argue image management first.
Thanks for the wonderful argument
of the first debater from Team AFF.
Now let's welcome the first debater from Team NEG
to make an opening argument,
also with a time limit of three minutes.
Welcome.
Thank you, chief judge.
Hello, everyone.
Just now, my fellow debater told us
that setting public image
improves our social efficiency
and reduces our communication cost,
which seems right at first glance.
So we met for the first time,
you added my WeChat
to check my Moments
and found I am a Taurus with type A blood
and like eating Italian food,
literature and art, and painting.
You seemed to
know me very well immediately
with a swipe of your fingers,
which is really efficient.
So you excitedly
took me to see
the Banksy's exhibition
and to eat expensive Italian food.
You arranged everything strongly
because I'm a Taurus,
who is indecisive
likes to let others make the decisions.
But that's not
who I really am.
That's just the shadow
of my public image,
the way
I want to be seen by everyone.
Under this condition,
I'm not happy.
But I can't show my true self
in front of you,
because I have to maintain my public image
and I'm afraid to let you down.
Eventually we all get tired of
this social way in exhaustion.
At this time, you will find that
public image
is not just a label.
Its purpose is to
let us imagine
what kind of person you are
through the label.
But are you really such a person?
Each of us
is aware of the gap in it.
So
public image
won't make me know you
but
only let me have prejudice against you.
And experience tells us
how hard it is
to reverse a prejudice.
So now I want to ask you
whether setting public image improves
or decreases
our social efficiency.
The first negative speaker directly refuted
the last point of the Team AFF,
and drew the audience over their side.
A direct refutation
can be powerful
when the Team AFF has just finished.
That's right.
The rhythm of the debate lies in
the guidance of the audience's thinking.
But the second half of her argument
is common.
Especially compared with
the preceding spot,
there are some contradictions.
The Team AFF still has its advantage
in the argument.
So they took advantages to attack
and cut the battlefield.
Since the Team AFF suggested that
there were many drawbacks of the image
imposed by others.
So the first round of debate
focused on
whether the public image should be projected by ourselves.
My fellow debater,
you took an example
that a star's agency team
projected him as a foodie,
and ended up with stomach perforation.
Is the image projected by others
also a public image?
The first speaker.
Yes.
So when I was a child,
my mom always pulled me out
to perform,
giving me an image
as a genius child.
Is it
my public image?
The second speaker.
Yes, it is.
And I can see that
this has caused a lot of trouble
for you.
Isn't it
the disadvantage of setting public image?
It is the drawback
caused by the improper way of education.
Well, according to your side,
is it that
the label others give me
is my public image?
The fourth speaker.
It is right in many times.
For example, the label your parents gave you.
The third affirmative speaker is experienced.
He first felt the basic condition of each person,
and then break down one by one.
Not bad.
When I was at school,
my classmates always had a nickname for me
and called me a cheapskate secretly.
Is the cheapskate my public image?
The second speaker.
That's called gossip.
What's the difference?
Gossip is
other people's prejudice against you,
not what you say.
I'm careless.
After a round,
the answer of Nan Bei
contradicted
Tao Hao's argument.
But the star's public image
is not projected by themselves.
Why can the agency team
set a public image for others?
The first debater.
Because the agency team
represents the star
when managing the public image.
So the star
empowered his agent to represent him.
As a result, the star suffered
for the public image.
The image that you choose,
even with tears, should be insisted on.
What's wrong with this?
Is that a disadvantage?
The second speaker.
Is the decision we make by ourselves
always the right one?
When I was a kid, I wanted to
practice the sunflower bible from a gentleman to a lady.
It was only when I grew up
that I realized
what the Invincible Asia had lost.
All right.
At least we have reached
a consensus,
that is, people must set their own image
and it is an autonomous and spontaneous behavior.
Right?
The fourth speaker.
Autonomy is not necessarily spontaneous.
Anyway, others can't
really force us.
Therefore, the second point of your argument
that the involuntary image
will cause great disadvantages
cannot be established.
We screw up.
It's okay. This point has to be given away sooner or later.
Let's work on image management later.
It is easier.
No.
Aren't they trying to define it?
I beat them to death.
Thank you, chief judge.
My fellow debater,
you said that public image
is a perfect model of a person,
and also a goal
that one strives for.
Right?
The first speaker.
Yes.
Is it true that all public image
is a goal?
The fourth speaker.
Yes.
This is the typical case
of making trouble out of nothing.
But she asked the fourth speaker.
The fourth speaker are generally
very familiar with the theoretical framework.
Is this a mistake?
No.
This is the answer she wants.
To complete her later reduction to absurdity.
A journalist, in order to obtain the trust of
the underground casino through unannounced investigations,
sets himself as
a person who loves gambling and money.
Is the lust for gambling and money
his goal?
The second debater.
No.
His goal is
to gain trust.
And setting public image help him
accomplish this goal well.
That's right.
But your argument
tells us
that public image is a goal in itself.
Why does it become
a means
to achieve the goal?
The second speaker.
It's wrong, my fellow debater.
In your context,
his so-called public image
is not what he really wants.
It's just a disguise,
instead of setting public image.
So the impure goal
is not public image
but disguise.
So all the public images
are all goals.
My fellow debater,
do you think
it is a circular argument?
The first speaker.
But what we want to emphasize is that
some public images themselves
are inconsistent with ourselves.
I don't like sports,
but pretend to exercise every day.
I'm a layman
but share museum photos every day.
These are just to
satisfy my false vanity.
We think these are called disguise
not public image.
If all the public images
are true,
why would
public image be ruined?
The second speaker.
Because...
Because people will change.
So we can't deny the behavior
of those who are around us
every day
for vanity
or other purposes
to set public image.
The image that does not match ourselves
also called public image.
Right?
The fourth speaker.
No, because...
Great.
Here,
Team NEG is catching up with the Team AFF.
In rebuttal,
the debate would be more in-depth.
The ruin of public image
must mean the image doesn't match me?
Is it possible that I have changed?
But the ruin of public image will bring people
great pain and stress.
Do you deny this?
I don't deny it.
But is this a drawback of public image?
Isn't this the drawback
of losing public image?
Is the disadvantage of losing public image
the drawback of public image?
Of course not.
The disadvantage of losing one's life
is the drawback of life?
Isn't the pain of a drug addict
losing drugs
the downside of drugs?
My fellow debater,
that's a bad analogy.
Setting public image is neutral.
It's just a way
of image management.
So, my fellow debater,
do you think that
the process of maintaining public image
is a kind of consumption to oneself?
That's right.
I project myself as a tourist talent
in my Moments.
I also like to travel in my daily life,
take some photos,
and share them in my Moments.
I'm very happy.
Where is the consumption for me?
Do you need
extra energy
to manage this public image?
No.
Because this is who I am.
You just said
projecting public image is a kind of image management.
Now it doesn't need management.
Don't you want your image?
We emphasize that
setting public image is
a way of image management.
It's like when you're going to an interview,
don't you have to dress properly
and prepare carefully?
Isn't this
who you are?
I'm not questioning image management.
What I question is that you confuse the concept
of public image and image management.
What is image management?
Image management is about
presenting a better version of ourselves.
The point is ourselves.
Instead of those who
looks good on Moments and Weibo
but looks floppy
in life.
Are they presenting themselves?
They just
want friends in their Moments
to monitor them
and to become a better version of themselves.
Wrong.
They're just trying to
attract more attention.
Likes in the Moments,
the comparison between girlfriends,
or the cater to
to join a certain circle
are essentially the same thing,
that is, to attract more attention.
Even if they are to attract attention,
what's wrong with that,
my fellow debater?
Team AFF retreats again
in the essence of the resolution.
I'm afraid they're going to lose this round.
They have lost it.
One should not live with others attention and feedback.
and should not
live to please others.
Is attracting attention
about living for others?
Do you know
who wants to attract people's attention most
in the world?
Internet celebrities and stars.
But they are very happy
to post Weibo every day.
But they...
The rhetoric is too intense.
I can hardly breathe.
Who will make the summary?
I'll do it.
I will make the summary later.
Let's welcome any debater in the Team NEG
to make a summary
in two minutes.
Please.
Let Hao make the summary.
Hello, everyone.
My fellow debater just admitted that
the purpose of projecting public image
is to attract attention.
And they said it's good.
Stars set public image to get attention
and become more popular.
Ordinary people set public image to get attention
and make themselves more visible.
My fellow debater asked us
what are the disadvantages?
We acknowledge that
setting public image can help us
get these.
But what is there in this world
that is
completely without gain?
So please remember that
when we look at
the advantages and disadvantages of one thing,
don't just look at what you get,
but also think deeply
the cost of it.
At this time, I wonder
why the trend of setting public image
sweeps the society.
Maybe
it's because the shortcut to attract attention
is too tempting.
Just like when I was a child,
I am called a sensible child.
As long as I studied hard and did housework frequently,
as long as I was never naughty not coquetry,
and took care of my sister,
I can get everyone's recognition.
So I should be more sensible
to
make everyone around me
to be happy.
And maybe
they would love me more.
Gradually I got used to
bringing the public image
into my whole life.
People think I'm a nice and warm-hearted person.
So I naturally thought
that people really like
this kind of me, right?
So what does it matter
if I give myself up?
Every time I wronged myself
to make people around me happy.
Isn't that good?
So I worked harder
to get close to my public image.
I paid infinite care to others.
I pleased them,
threw away
all my temper and dignity.
Do you notice that
the most terrible thing
of setting public image
is that your image will in turn affect
and shape your life.
Your public image
will make you lose yourself
between standing and collapsing,
thus making you forget
who you really are.
I don't think that's a good thing.
Thank you.
This part really attracts my attention.
It's really emotional.
And she emphasized
the most important argument of Team NEG
that public image will in turn affect ourselves.
But it would confuse the adjudicators.
The point that
public image will in turn affect our personality
is equivalent to
be suddenly thrown out in the middle of the competition.
I think
Team NEG has begun to lose
the advantage
they won so hard.
But is the debate there
to convince the adjudicators
or the audience?
I'm a pragmatist.
It's the adjudicators who grade me.
Generally speaking, free debate is that
Team AFF says public image is good
and Team AFF says public image is bad.
Battlefield begins with
our familiar gossip.
Last month,
The shocking news occupied headlines.
I wonder if my fellow debater noticed that.
The public image of loving celebrity couple
was ruined overnight.
They were both revealed
to have cheated on each other.
Does their public image
do more harm than good?
My fellow debater,
You can't just watch the bad effect
without seeing the good effect.
They relied on the public image of loving couple
to participate in many shows,
receive a lot of endorsements
and earn plenty of money.
Aren't these advantages enough?
It turns out that the advantages you refer to
is money.
The ruin of their public image
caused adverse social impact.
Why don't you talk about it?
So from a social point of view,
does project public image
actually
improve our social efficiency
in some way?
Improving efficiency is a false proposition.
We have already refuted it.
Is it the pursuit of vanity
to beautify a picture
and share it on our Moments
to get 100 likes?
Vanity is common to all.
I want to ask
whether a clear public image
can help others quickly
establish a
basic cognition of myself.
But this cognition
is vague and one-sided,
isn't it?
All cognition
is from vague to clear,
from one-sided to comprehensive.
Isn't the information on the business card
also a one-sided introduction?
Then may I ask you
whether the business card improves
or reduces social efficiency?
Improve.
But it
only works on shallow social contact,
and it will hinder deep social contact.
Very good.
We have reached a consensus.
There are different degrees of social contact.
So at the shallow social level,
setting public image
helps to improve social efficiency.
Right?
Team AFF indeed has strong strength.
At the beginning,
they resized
the argument of social efficiency
by three logical leaps.
More importantly,
They upset the rhythm of Team NEG.
Then they keep cutting the battlefield
in favor of their side.
At this time,
What should we do?
Recognize the point,
grasp the core argument,
and wait for an opportunity to fight back.
We have to admit that
public image has good effect
in some times.
But if we have set a public image,
in order to protect it,
we will be bound by it.
Are we in bondage
as long as
we care about how others see us?
Then we should not
leave any impression on others,
and do not have any social networks
and Moments.
How is such a requirement
not a form of bondage?
Today, I set myself
as a computer talent.
Will many friends
come to me to repair the computers?
Is this a kind of
consumption and burden?
My fellow debater,
I think you can
set yourself as
someone who doesn't like to be bothered.
Your trouble will be solved.
Well said, my fellow debater.
For the sake of one public image,
I need to set another one.
Eventually numerous images erode
the truest self.
One public image
need countless images to cover up.
Isn't it like a lie?
Do lies
do more good than harm?
Team NEG won a little advantage.
But the advantage of Team AFF
is still not reversed.
Does my fellow debaters agree that
the public image is based on
people's stereotypes?
We believe that
the understanding of my fellow debater
is the stereotype of public image.
Is public image
a kind of label?
Setting public image
is a kind of labeled behavior.
But is label
necessarily bad?
In fact, setting public image existed since ancient times.
Cao Cao was evaluated by YueDanPing
as a capable minister at peaceful time
and a cunning chief at a war time.
Liu Bei spent his whole life
to keep his public image
as a righteous person.
All these have promoted the
their hegemony.
What are the drawbacks?
Putting ancient stories
in today's view
seems lofty.
But please think about it carefully.
Are you willing to follow
a true leader
or a public image?
The essence of public image
is not a natural person.
My fellow debater,
how can we follow it?
May I ask my fellow debater
what the essence of
public image is?
We believe that
setting public image
is an autonomous and selective process
to present ourselves.
In today's time,
that's not wrong.
On the contrary,
this is exactly a way
that will allow us
to live better with the world.
All arguments in the free debate
are fifty-fifty.
But...
At this time,
the closing argument
becomes the key point of winning.
In the past, closing arguments on this type of resolution
are usually about value.
But the audience have just accepted
a lot of confusing information.
Under such condition,
blindly talking about value
will only make
audience is more confused.
Closing argument.
In the original closing argument,
value sublimation accounts for half.
This won't work.
If I were here,
I would return to the definition
and lead the audience to
sort out the logic of the whole competition.
This is the
the final part of the competition.
Closing arguments.
Four minutes for each side.
Let's first welcome
the fourth debater from Team NEG.
Thank you, chief judge.
Hello, everyone.
Team AFF said that setting public image
is to present ourselves better.
I don't think it's right.
Some people will set themselves
as people who are naturally cool and thin.
Some people will project themselves
as people who have allodoxaphobia
or who are depressed.
But all these public images
don't match what the Team AFF said
about presenting themselves
or improving social efficiency.
They have only one thing in common,
that is,
attracting attention.
We believe that
the essence of setting public image
is a kind of communication behavior.
It seems that more people today
want to be seen,
and want to be noticed.
So we will have all kinds of
public image.
For example, happy or sad one,
friendly or unkind one.
All of these
are guiding us
to attach one label after another
to ourselves.
We hope to fit in the circle,
hope to gain recognition,
hope to receive praise and jealousy.
But as information
increasingly explodes,
people's attention
seems to get more and more distracted.
How can I
get more attention?
Communication tells us
the simpler, the more efficient.
So our public image
is getting simpler,
from loving life at the beginning
to loving food.
In the end, it becomes one word,
foodie.
Do you remember
what our first debater said?
Your public image
will also in turn shape
and affect your life.
So your life and goals
also begin to become so simple and extreme
that we all forget
why we set the public image
at the beginning.
Instead, we just care about
how much attention we get.
Public image is in essence
a tool for screenwriters.
Its principle is that
a few simple words
can be used to
describe a
complete character.
But when we spit out
the thin and rigid characters
in movies and TV shows,
when we talk about
the gossip that
stars are ruined by fans and public images,
whether
do we also become shallow
because of the ruin of public images?
I hope our debate
will be a wake-up call and reflection
for all of you.
Thank you.
After the deliberation of adjudicators,
the result of this competition
is in my hands.
The best debater in this competition
is the third debater from Team NEG.
The winner of this competition is
Team NEG,
Dongzhou University of Finance and Economics Debate Team
Congratulations.
OK. That's all for today.
Study it carefully.
Train on time tomorrow.
Did you win?
Well, congratulations.
Thank you.
Let's make peace.
Let's break up.
Thank you for taking care of me
over the past two years.
I wish you happiness.
We can break up.
But we should
talk about it clearly.
I have tried hard
for the relationship.
Even if I knew that
there was serious problem
between us,
I'm still trying to fix it.
Now we break up.
Don't you think it has a lot to do
with your personality?
Yes.
There is something wrong with my personality.
But I'm not
entirely responsible
for our breakup.
As my boyfriend,
you were supposed to
accept all of me.
But you didn't.
You always
ran away my weakness.
You only accepted
the part you could accept.
But it doesn't matter.
I believe
there will be someone who can do it.
When things go wrong
in a relationship,
you shouldn't
blames others first.
Think about your own problems.
I hope you can
be more mature in the future.
I asked you out today
to explain
why
I ran away from the debate classroom that day.
I know that's very impolite.
So
I want to
tell you my story.
In fact,
when I was in junior high school,
I put on a lot of weight
because I was addicted to sweets.
I became the laughing stock of the whole class.
Round ball
I'm sorry.
There's no way I'm in relationship with you.
At that time,
they gave me a nickname,
round ball.
It was the darkest time
of my life.
After that,
I don't even have the courage
to eat sweets again.
Until that day
I ate the cookies you made for me.
So
I didn't run that day
because I hate you
or other reasons.
It's because your dessert
is so delicious.
Okay.
Is it?
Yes.
Well, senior.
I'll make you some
low-sugar and low-calorie cookies later.
This provincial league
will adopt a free point system.
All teams that
score 50 points by March 21
will qualify for
the final.
Teams
that register as
university team
will have five basic points.
And the social team formed by individuals
don't have the basic points.
After the free points competition,
the Provincial Competition Committee
will make the final system
of the next stage
according to the number of teams
entering the finals.
The competition champion will
be known a week later.
See you in the final.
With the way
we're winning points,
there's no problem
accumulating enough points in short time.
Hao
How many points does our team have now?
Since we
signed up
as the social team,
all the points of the team two
are cleared.
So now the point is
zero.
What about the zero?
With our strength,
we can get enough points quickly.
Do you forget the days
when we were beaten by team one?
Don't you
want revenge on Liu Yanze?
This is our momentum.
Yeah.
What about the zero?
Look at the strength
of the members in our team.
We.
Our team.
What's the name?
Right.
We need a team name.
It is best to be able to
reflect our mental journey.
That's right.
Hmm.
After all the humiliations we've endured,
there's nothing we want more than to turn around.
That's right.
Okay.
Our name is
Turnaround Team.
Right.
That sounds kind of depressing.
Naming
is very important.
It's better to
be catchy
after we're popular.
It's better to highlight our
vigorous youth,
hard work,
strong strength
and determination
to become popular in cities and villages.
Okay.
Then our name is Cities and Villages Team.
It's not good.
Justice League Team.
That has the copyright.
I'm the Champion Team.
Superficial.
I'm the Veteran Team.
This won't pass the review.
It's too troublesome to think of a name. Oh, my God.
Let's play cards for a while.
Ten.
K.
Two.
Take it back.
Above k are jokers.
Two is the smallest one.
Who taught you the rules?
Two, three, five are the biggest cards.
JQK comes after that.
Don't play tricks.
Two, three, five are the smallest.
Yeah.
No.
In my hometown,
two, three, five are really the biggest cards.
I don't care.
I only have one card left.
Our name may be
Team 235.
What do you mean?
It's too casual.
235 means that you're sophomores,
I'm a junior,
and you are the senior?
No personal attacks, OK?
No.
Take playing cards as an example.
In some places,
two, three, five are the smallest cards.
But there are places
where two, three, five are the biggest cards
and can defeat JQK.
Just like our team.
That's interesting.
Okay.
Defeat team one.
It's time to show
our real strength.
Good.
Hurry up to study the competition system.
Let's see
what other games we can play next.
OK?
I and Sa
had studied the competition system.
We've signed up
for every competition we can.
So as long as
we play all our games on time and on schedule,
we should have no problem in qualifying.
I've made a list of the competitions.
Let's have a look together.
Sorry, it's closing time.
Oh,
sorry, sorry.
Dango
Do you think
there's anything going on
with those two?
From the horse's mouth.
Their relationship is simpler than that of you and Ma Nan.
But you're right.
They've gotten to this point in their relationship.
What are they waiting for?
Do you think
they don't want to make progress,
or they haven't made progress yet?
Nan Bei said that
his mother had absolute sovereignty
since he was a child.
He and his father are both afraid of his mother.
So Nan Bei wants to find
a gentle woman like water.
Do you think Xiaoyu is like that kind of girl?
Not necessarily.
Doesn't Nan Bei
always contradict himself?
Right.
Maybe he's used to
such a way of getting along
and feel it is the most comfortable and convenient way
to get along with others.
Yo yo.
Rise to the theoretical level.
I'm thirty years old.
I don't see any of you
bothering about me.
Go back to sleep tonight.
Begin to fight tomorrow morning.
All right.
Okay.
The original team two of our school
has officially left the school team.
As a social team,
they signed up for
preliminary stage of provincial league.
In the next three days,
they will fight against the tigers in the development zone,
Huarong Vocational College,
Xinxing Hotel Management College
Huang Zhizhong from Yau Ma Tei.
and
Linhai University of Chemical Technology
with the title of "a gun in a village".
Today
they will fight against
Ruihong Vocational and Technical College
with the title of
Ma Weiwei in Shanzhai Zhenhong Street.
Let's wait and see.
Pain is a kind of consciousness.
If you can't sleep, you are awake.
So you are conscious.
You're asleep
and can't get up, so you don't even have consciousness.
You know nothing about pain.
How can this be more painful than sleeplessness?
According to your statement,
you can't get up, so you're unconscious.
You are forced to get up and have consciousness,
which is a forcible strike.
The comparison shows that
it is more painful not to get up.
My fellow debater,
today we discuss
whether niche hobbies should become widely known.
Does it mean that
the development of niche hobbies
is limited?
When it comes to limitation,
it refers that my fellow debater
force them to be widely known.
Forced love does not last.
My fellow debater
Becoming a household name will be more beneficial
to the development of niche culture.
Is that right?
I would like to hear the details.
If an activity become widely known,
it will have more audience,
more practitioners,
more sponsors and so on.
So these more resources
can promote better development.
Right?
Not necessarily.
What hobby do you have
that doesn't work that way?
My hobby
is to be a niche enthusiast.
If it is widely known, I need a new one.
For the group of niche enthusiasts
like me,
the ideal situation
is to entertain ourselves in niches.
The help of my dad
reduced my struggle of twenty years.
Did my dad's help
get in the way
of my struggle?
Quite reverse.
Your dad helped you
to a higher platform,
thus helping you
struggle better.
Struggle for what?
Struggle to better collect rent?
Okay, even if we don't mention anything else,
we just focus on the face score.
What if the opposite one
is tofu beauty?
Isn't it the same?
My fellow debater
Tofu beauty
originated from Mrs. Yang
in Lu Xun's "Hometown".
I suggest you
check the source first
to prevent
the stupid mistake.
My fellow debater
I'm afraid you just read superficial meanings.
You don't criticize bystanders' humiliation
but blame Mrs. Yang's beauty.
My fellow debater
You are
sour grapes.
The winner is
Team 235.
Shui
What's the name
of your lead singer?
Xiaoyang
There is really a band.
It's been three years.
I work in the bar
to support this band.
Wow.
Why don't you sing?
I'm tone-deaf.
My sketch homework is due tonight.
I'm gonna be a little late.
You guys practice first.
I also need to do my work
in the student union.
What are you reading?
WeChat group. Phone.
No hurry. We haven't
find a place to train.
I have a suggestion.
You and Nan Bei can take seats first.
We used to train there.
Right here?