English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP38
I won't make things too hard for them,
out of consideration for you.
I'll give you three days
to think it over.
I bid you farewell, Chancellor Lai.
Poker face!
Poker face...
Stop crying, Chui.
I'm fine.
Really, I'm fine.
My dearest Xing,
you can't keep skipping meals.
Open the door.
I have a bowl of soup for you.
If you have any grievances,
just wait until you're fed,
and let's barge in the Shen residence!
I've also
been at death's door before.
It doesn't matter if he's The White Death
or the King of Hell;
your mother will
definitely make him cry out for mercy!
Darling,
I know you hurt inside.
But as a woman,
you need love and appreciation
to truly flourish.
Why keep someone
who doesn't appreciate you?
You can't let a little setback
bring you down, can you?
I promise you,
I will find you a caring and
handsome young man who will always
cherish you and listen to you.
How does that sound?
Hello there, handsome young man!
I came to check on Yan Xing.
Xing,
It's me,
Pan Chi!
Xing!
She locks herself inside,
and refuses to comes out.
Come in.
So she actually heeded my words?
My lady?
Madam Jin.
Did a strange man just
enter Xing's room?
My lady, what are you talking about?
What strange man?
Xing is an official of the Ministry of Justice.
She is not a typical house wife.
Of course, she needs to people
to hand official business.
Xing is indeed a capable lady.
Though she is not my biological daughter,
I have watched her grow up.
Everyone knows!
When she married Shen Du,
I was quite concerned for her.
I hoped she would
find a good match.
But now, having divorced
and returned to the Yan residence,
she should consider
the reputation of the Yan Family.
What do you mean by that?
Don't you know?
The entire Yan residence is now under the
watchful eye of the Imperial Inspectorate.
There are rumors circulating
that a daughter of the Yan Family
has become a discarded woman.
If strange men enter freely,
I fear people would think
that our Yan family lacks proper manner.
My lady!
It's clear that Xing
discarded that
heartless Shen Du.
How dare you label her
as a discarded woman?!
For your information,
I've put up with you for far too long.
I'm done with this!
I was only trying to help...
What do you mean by "trying to help?"
Stop it! Please, stop!
Enough already!
Just stop!
Such a misfortune for the family!
You two, please stop!
Xing...
I was only trying to help, you...
You all, hush...
Mother, My lady,
please stop fighting.
Father.
We need to step out for a moment.
Ru,
-stop your nonsense! -Look,
isn't that a stranger?
Stop it!
You sure like to talk, huh?
My lord!
Why did you slap me?
Look at her!
Do something about her!
Easy, you just hit my face!
You are...
You are from Tongming Pavilion.
You are Yan Xing, right?
Just turn left up ahead.
There's an alley.
You can exit from there.
No one will notice.
Why are you helping us?
For the bond of sisterhood.
For the women's virtue .
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Just hurry.
They're coming!
Sis!
Come on!
Xing.
Chui.
Hurry.
You finally made it!
I was worried you wouldn't make it here.
Fortunately,
it was a close call.
Has The White Death
truly joined forces with Lai Luozhi?
From this moment on,
I won't have anything to do with him!
How did you manage to evade
the men from Imperial Inspectorate?
You've been cooped up at home for days,
which has likely made them
let their guard down a bit.
It seems Chui
has grasped the meaning of my message.
Salt (Yan) has ears and eyes.
At the pool (Pawn, Chi) in three days.
It means there are Lai Luozhi's
eyes all around the Yan residence.
In three days,
we will meet at the pawnshop.
Lu Chuichui
is already waiting for us at the pawnshop.
We need to find a way
to bypass those lookouts.
For Zhanxin?
So she is a friend of
Kuang Zhanxin from Tongming Pavilion.
Then her assistance today
was because she believes
I cleared Kuang Zhanxin's name?
Conducting investigations
are not for the sake of reward.
What we got in return today
is all due to kindness and goodwill,
helping one another.
Chui, now that
Lai Luozhi has the empire at his feet.
I've thought of a plan.
Why don't you and Jiang Langxing
just leave Xiang'an for now
to lay low until things calm down?
I played dumb with him yesterday,
so he will let his guard down for a while.
We can take this opportunity
to escape.
Xing,
why don't you come with us?
I still need to stay here.
Why?
You're not still hung up on
that The White Death, are you?
Take care of yourself!
Chui.
Chui!
Father.
This is your first time traveling far.
Remember,
nothing surpasses the value of gold.
I have prepared
plenty of gold for you,
to ensure your journey is smooth.
Here, take it with you!
Stay safe on the road!
Be good!
Father...
Alright, just be good.
Chui!
It's all good now!
Poker face,
you're leaving Xiang'an
for my sake,
and giving up your job as a delinquent.
Are there any regrets on your mind?
Do you wish things had been different?
As long as you are by my side,
wherever we go,
there will always be a place
for me to showcase my talents.
Exactly.
Then from this moment on,
we shall be a pair of
heroes, fighting against evil!
Wonderful!
Thank you so much!
Take care of yourself.
Farewell!
Let me carry it.
What do you mean they disappeared?
I've failed in my duties.
Lady Lu and Jiang Langxing
have truly vanished without a trace.
I'm afraid they've already left Xiang'an.
Then head out of the city
and search the entire empire.
Leave no stone unturned
until you bring her to me!
Understood!
She was just deceiving you.
A woman like that,
why do you still hold onto her?
Get lost!
All of you, get out!
The commander of Dongzhou garrison
has come to pay respects to Chancellor Lai!
The governor of Yangyue requests an audience!
Legatus legionis from Yuan Legion greets Chancellor Lai!
My lord,
the road outside the residence
is packed with carriages of
civil and military officials
coming to pledge their allegiance,
and they refuse to budge.
Now,
seventy percent of the officials have
already pledged their allegiance to you.
We can't get things done with solely civil officials.
Any news from the regional commanders?
Various commanders of regional garrisons
have sent tokens of allegiance.
They all express the desire
to come to Xiang'an to pay their respects
to Chancellor Lai during the grand assembly.
Excellent!
Four Imperial Legates from the six field
armies have already pledged their allegiance.
The remaining two are hardly a threat!
The second day of the second month...
It seems that
this specific date
is indeed a fortuitous day.
Moths drawn to the flame.
fleeting in life,
they do not enter the cycle of reincarnation.
But are reborn anew.
The violet star rises,
heralding the empire's prosperity;
divine benevolence prevails,
uniting(Luozhi) the realm.
Divine benevolence prevails,
Xing.
Pan.
The Imperial Inspectorate
has not yet lifted
its watch over the Yan residence.
Aren't you worried about being implicated
by showing up like this?
If he wished me harm,
he would have done it earlier.
I'm simply accompanying you to unwind,
what's wrong with that?
I've heard that now the Imperial Guard
and the Imperial Inspectorate
are colluding.
Peaceful days in Xiang'an
may be lost forever now.
Listening to too many rumors
can be detrimental.
It's better to seek some fun.
My lady!
Chief Clerk, Lady...Yan...
Chief Clerk, Lady Yan,
you claim to be
dedicated to your duties,
yet here you are,
not in the Ministry of Justice,
but engaging in idle chatter
with a nobody?
Lord Shen,
she has finished her shift.
Though she's an official,
who she chats with and associates with
is probably none of your concern, right?
Among all civil and military officials,
except for the Imperial Inspectorate,
who dares to defy
the orders from the Imperial Guard?
Shen Du,
look at yourself.
People are talking that The White Death
and Dark Demon walk hand in hand,
so the realm is now a living hell.
Are you under the impression
that being shunned like a pariah
is a badge of honor?
Do you still remember
the promises you once made,
the oaths you swore?
People
will change.
Xing, don't
waste your breath on someone like him.
Let's go.
Xing,
just sit here for a short while.
I'll be right back.
Xing,
do you remember
this is where we
first met?
"The view manifests,"
"come noon it takes shape"
"and extends;"
"the essence rests in its form."
This is what you taught me.
From the moment we met,
I envisioned
what your future would hold.
You would become a
female official who serves the public,
leaving a legacy for generations to come.
Now, you are the only one
who still believes in my dreams.
In my eyes,
you have been more than someone's daughter
or wife.
You are Yan Xing, a female official
of the Ministry of Justice,
the most skilled detective in the empire,
and my soulmate.
I only wish
for you to pursue your ambitions freely
within the Ministry of Justice.
I will always be there,
silently supporting you.
But sadly,
everything has changed now.
The court is filled with hidden agendas.
There's no sense of fairness or justice.
You are caught in the crossfire,
suffering the consequences.
In this vast world,
being an official is not the
sole path to fulfill your dream.
Perhaps you are right.
With our combined strength,
we can travel the world,
righting wrongs and
clearing the names of the wronged.
Yan Xing,
would you like to join me
in escaping this place of turmoil
and journeying together across the world?
Should you desire it,
I can take the lives
of these adulterous wretches
this instant.
If you let them go now,
you may never see them again.
That might be for the best,
to avoid the sight of them.
Rest assured, I will ensure the
Ministry of Justice clears the Shens' name.
It's just a matter of issuing a decree.
Anything else you need to inform your family?
I've already told my family
that I'm going out to travel for a while,
and they are very supportive.
With the vastness of the world,
one can cultivate an open mind
and not be burdened by trivial matters.
Once we leave the city,
all the conflicts and struggles
will no longer concern us.
With sky and earth as our shelter,
we will ride with the clouds and winds.
Your Royal Highness.
Ease your mind.
I'm fine.
Your Royal Highness...
Some...
Your Royal Highness,
please take your herbal medication.
News has arrived from the palace that the
Empress Dowager's condition has worsened.
It seems her time is running out.
In that case,
I should personally go to visit her.
Who is it?
Hearing Your Highness' health has declined,
I am deeply concerned.
I have come to check on you.
I am quite well,
just need to rest for a few days.
Ease your mind, Chancellor Lai.
Just focus on
your duties.
Be more mindful of your conduct,
to avoid being accused of lacking decorum.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
It seems that
the news of the Empress Dowager
being gravely ill
is indeed true.
Insolence!
How dare you show
such disrespect in my presence?
Calm your anger,
for life is fragile.
Guards! Guards!
Have you come to assassinate me?
Your Royal Highness,
how could I have such wicked intentions?
I have always been
loyal and devoted.
Lai Luozhi,
you were born into humble beginnings.
If it weren't for me,
how would you have attained today's
wealth and status?
Yet you dare to harbor treasonous thoughts.
You are worse than an animal!
Had you not been so
suspicious and jealous,
unable to tolerate others,
this fate could have been avoided.
I believe I have acted justly before God,
with a clear conscience,
and have not failed the empire.
You, a lowlife, have no right to judge me!
What a fine statement about conscience.
But do you still remember
Consort Shu you framed, who was
driven to her death by your actions?
Consort Shu?
Who exactly are you?
What's your relationship with her?
That's right.
Within these imperial walls,
who would recall a woman presented
by a neighboring tribe,
a consort
forced to
her demise,
much less
her offspring?
Zhi,
you must keep in mind
that it's Zhou Xu who caused my death!
Once your father passes away,
there will be no way for us
to survive
in the palace.
The queen and her supporters,
the Zhou Family,
hold all the power.
They will not allow
you to live.
But don't be afraid,
I will protect you.
Even if it costs me my life,
I will ensure your survival.
I will trade my life
for your chance at life!
Zhi,
you must live.
You must survive.
Go and reclaim what is rightfully yours.
Do you understand?
Did you keep that in mind?
Zhi...
My nanny switched
her son with me.
From that moment on, I became Lai Luozhi,
and nanny's twin daughters
became my sisters.
Mother!
All that laugh, like moths drawn to the flame.
But they do not realize that like mayflies...
Mother!
After my mother passed away,
the high and mighty
Empress Dowager thought
this was merely
a scandal in the harem.
She decreed that no one
should discuss the matter in the palace.
Because of this,
the maid who came to the empire
with my mother,
my nanny,
managed to keep it a secret from everyone
and snuck me out of the palace...
So...
back then,
in the ruins...
the charred body of that boy...
That was my nanny's son,
who was about my age.
He willingly
walked into the fire for me!
Insane...
Truly insane!
All of this
is thanks to you!
You are the cause of this,
so I must
return this favor to you!
What do you want?
Your time is running out,
and the young emperor has yet to mature.
I believe it would be best
for this empire to be handed over to me,
his uncle.
This throne should have been mine.
Only by ascending can I better continue
the bloodline of the Xiao Family.
My father in heaven
would also feel comforted
for our ancestors!
I ask the Your Highness
to issue the abdication decree now.
Abdication decree?
What a delusion.
Come to think of it,
my sister, Princess Ying,
is still confined to her residence.
Also, the Prince Xian,
Perhaps I should begin
to plan for his future as well.
How dare you!
Now that I am the acting regent,
and you were the one
who brought me all the way up here.
Princess Ying conspired to rebel,
with irrefutable evidence.
It would be easy to dig up
some dirt on Lord Zhang,
so I could
frame Prince Xian.
You can't possibly be at a loss
for what to do next,
Your Highness.
I
entered the palace at fourteen,
and my whole life
has been spent in political struggle.
But ultimately,
I was still caught off guard.
You can wait until I die,
and then you can fabricate
all sorts of decrees as you wish.
You are nothing more than
a man hungry for power and fame,
aiming to
ascend to the throne with legitimacy.
The day of the grand assembly will also
mark the anniversary of my mother's death,
and it will be
your deadline.
By then,
my mother will see her son
returning with honor!
Her death anniversary will also
be the day her son ascends the throne!
Shen Du,
I understand what you intend to do.
Counting the days,
they should have arrived by now.
This is the boundary stone of Nanlang.
We have finally arrived.
Master!
Lord Chen?
Xing girl,
I received your message.
I thought you'd arrive soon,
but I didn't expect you to be this fast!
Master,
Lai Luozhi's men are everywhere
in Xiang'an City now.
To ensure our safety,
we didn't stop at all during the journey.
The truth you want to uncover
is indeed quite complicated!
It turns out that Xing
had already contacted Lord Chen
to secretly investigate
Lai Luozhi's background in Nanlang.
I heard from Chui that
on Lai Luozhi's mother's tombstone,
there's only the name "Biluo"
with no family surname attached.
So I had Ye Yun look into it.
He found that on the paper offerings,
there were drawings of conch shells (Luo),
which are rarely seen on
the ancestor worship paper in the empire.
However, I've heard that in Nanlang,
there're people who worship conch shells.
Ye Yun also discovered traces
of spilled cow's blood on the ground.
Using cow's blood as an offering
is indeed a custom of Nanlang.
Master,
could it be that Biluo was the consort
offered to the late emperor?
That's correct.
But this Biluo
has a hidden past
that few know about,
and perhaps even her own son
is unaware of it.
After tomorrow's grand assembly,
everything will be settled.
After all these years,
if she obediently
hands over the throne tomorrow...
It still feels a bit anticlimactic.
Long live the emperor!
The Xichen envoy offers tribute!
The Nanlang envoy offers tribute!
Today,
nations gather to celebrate,
joining in this grand occasion.
May we strengthen our diplomatic ties
and bring peace to the world!
With a solid foundation, the nation will thrive.
We must renew our commitment to the people,
so that all subjects unite as one.
Only then can we
shine for eternity.
By selecting only the virtuous,
we can surely stabilize the realm!
To maintain peace
is the responsibility
of a great nation!
Greetings, Your Royal Highness!
Love live the Empress Dowager!
The grand assembly
is a celebration for all.
Her Royal Highness is delighted,
so she even have recovered
and will grant a banquet for you all.
Gratitude, Your Royal Highness!
Now that Your Highness has recovered,
it's best not to overexert yourself.
If the illness relapses,
that would be unfortunate.
Do Your Highness have an edict
to announce to the officials
during the assembly?
Chancellor Lai, you really are
becoming more and more disrespectful!
Thanks to your reminder,
I do have an important announcement.
I fell seriously ill not long ago, which
left me unable to attend to court matters.
Many affairs were temporarily
entrusted to the Imperial Inspectorate.
Chancellor Lai has worked diligently.
Now,
I have fully recovered, and His Majesty
is also studying the principles
of governance with the Grand Tutor.
From today onward,
Chancellor Lai will no longer need to
serve as regent.
You have fulfilled your role at the II.
Go and enjoy a tranquil respite.