[English subtitles are available]
[Bright Time]
[EP28]
[I give up.]
Please tell me
what do you want from me.
I'll buy you
anything you want.
Skins for games, clothes,
skincare, luxury items,
or makeup. Anything.
Please tell me.
Okay. Wait and see.
Don't push me
to my last resort.
I don't have a weak spot.
Except for my susceptibility to handsome guys.
So that's why you sold me out?
No other way out,
so I had to do this.
It won't work, I won't give in,
no matter how cute he is.
Got any other ideas?
Don't you wanna join us
for stargazing?
Spill the beans,
and you're in.
Really?
No lying?
Nah,
we don't do that.
You just lied to me.
What? We'd
never lie...
Trust me.
I wouldn't lie to you.
The handsome guy doesn't lie.
It's auntie.
She asked me to take your passport.
Your auntie?
Passport?
So that's my mom.
Here's the thing.
Auntie
was gonna come back with me,
but on the way,
she got
a call and bailed.
She whispered to me to
grab your passport,
get you a visa,
and keep it on the DL.
But I already have
a Singapore visa.
Your visa's from way back
when auntie took you outta here,
like a decade ago.
She thinks
it's probably
outta date by now.
Why didn't you
just ask me for it?
All the
sneakiness, huh?
She probably wanted to
take you on
a surprise trip abroad.
Mystery solved.
Why
didn't you tell me earlier?
If you had shared
the secret with me sooner,
I could've just given it to you.
Why keep it
bottled up?
So, my mom's got
a surprise for me.
Should I play
dumb?
Right.
Pretend you don't know.
Problem solved.
Auntie's happy.
And I'm
off the hook as a spy.
We're gonna go
stargazing later, right?
I gotta get ready for that.
When's mom
gonna drop the bomb on me?
How long since you saw her last time?
A few years, I think.
And do you think I should
get her a gift too?
You said you two
went overseas.
And?
And
we lived together,
and then she remarried
and brought little Will
into the world.
William.
My half-brother.
At that time,
mom had to juggle
taking care of me
and little Will,
and her work.
It was
a lot
for her.
I felt bad,
so I
offered to come back here
to help ease her burden.
I didn't know
you're
actually pretty thoughtful.
Of course.
But a bit impulsive.
Back home,
I missed her a lot
but I had to hold back
from calling her.
I knew
she was
swamped with
Will and work,
and didn't
have the time for me.
But
she's got the surprise
for me this time,
so she must be
doing well over there.
Right?
It's nice.
So,
you're a momma's
pet, huh?
So are you.
[Now.]
[News about astronomy.]
[According to the forecast,]
[there'll be a very rare]
[astronomical event]
[of Jupiter and Saturn conjunction]
[on the 22nd.]
[The angular distance between them]
[will reach 6.19 minutes arc.]
[From the perspective of the earth,]
[Jupiter and Saturn]
[will be extremely close.]
[Experts said that]
[the best time to observe]
[in China is one hour after dark]
[on the evening of the 21st.]
[Jupiter and Saturn,]
[two giant planets,]
[will be practically]
[hugging each other.]
[It'll be stunning.]
Qingtian.
Are you feeling down?
You haven't replied
to my messages.
Nah.
Wafer, haw flakes, egg tart.
Which one's your pick?
I'm not in the mood.
You're gonna love this.
They're not stuck anymore,
all broken up.
Don't cry.
I...
There's a place I wanna go.
Yeah, let's go.
Here.
No.
I've got more
for you.
This.
More of that wafer.
Your favorite dried yellow peaches.
And there's more.
Let's take a break.
Yeah, need a break.
Go.
You're getting pretty pro.
Not bad.
Another
text from the cutie?
For a lakeside hangout.
She wanna talk about
her new writing piece.
Her writing's
childish and mawkish,
but I gotta praise her
for her mom's sake.
What?
Dude, you promised
to win her over,
and now you're already
acting like you've got her on a leash?
Yeah.
I'm serious,
I'm over her.
[It's her who's now clingy.]
[Really?]
[Full of hot air.]
[Yeah.]
[It's not.]
[Alright, let's make a bet.]
Let's see
whether she'll wait for me
at the lake for 3 hours or not.
[Okay.]
Let's bet on a pair of sneakers.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll text her now.
Do it.
For real?
Really?
[Impressive.]
[The lakeside.]
[I'm gonna send it.]
[Watch this.]
[Alright.]
[Back to the game.]
[Yeah.]
[I got it.]
Block! Block!
Rebound! Good shot!
Pass, pass, pass!
Again, again, again!
Qingtian.
So it's the fun park you wanna go.
This is great.
It stays the same
no matter how time
passes.
Yeah.
A dream factory
for all ages.
Two fluffy cotton candies.
Qingtian, here.
Chow down and ride up.
What's your pick for fun?
Wanna spin on the carousel?
Alright, let's go.
So, Saturn and Jupiter
meeting up?
Is it worth
the long trip?
That rare?
This is their closest
meet-up in ages.
In astrology,
[they have totally]
[different vibes.]
Jupiter's all about seriousness,
calmness, and detachment,
while Saturn brings the luck,
optimism, and enthusiasm.
Opposite planets
[hugging?]
This rare
astronomical event
is a must-see.
Sit.
Here.
Curious why I'm
obsessed with
the carousel?
Yeah.
But I'm hesitant to ask,
in case you don't wanna share.
But no matter what,
if it makes you happy,
I'll be there for you.
Don't be sad.
You still wanna
ride the carousel?
I'll go get the tickets.
Be right back.
No.
I don't wanna ride it anymore.
When I was a kid,
I loved riding the carousel.
My parents and I rode it
every visit
to this park.
So it's
because of your parents.
No one will ever
ride the carousel with me again.
They're working hard
to earn money,
so they can buy you more
delicious snacks, right?
I overheard them arguing.
My parents argue a lot too,
it's pretty normal.
They've divorced,
but they kept it from me
because of Gaokao exam.
Hey, where's my
happy-go-lucky Qingtian?
I'm just down in the dumps.
I bet that optimistic Qingtian
would think that
"even if they aren't together"
"I gotta look at the bright side."
"Like,"
"double the allowance,"
"double the red envelopes"
"during the holidays,"
"I can buy so much"
"treats."
Hey, stop it.
Qingtian.
They kept it from you
because they
love you deeply.
And that love
will never fade.
And besides,
you have your favorite lollipops.
And I
will always by your side.
[Look, look!]
Stars are about to align.
What are they looking at?
Saturn and Jupiter.
They're at their closest point
in 400 years.
Which one is Saturn,
and which one is Jupiter?
It's actually quite easy.
Jupiter's brighter than the others.
Saturn's a bit dimmer,
but it's got
this cool golden ring
around it.
See?
When'd you get into stargazing?
You know,
I'm class monitor,
student union prez,
and top student in Xiangbei.
Why
do them get so close?
Some say
every star in the universe
will eventually meet.
Jupiter and Saturn
[took 400 years]
[to make it.]
It's like people in this world.
You will
find your someone special.
Just like...
Silly.
Thanks for riding
[the carousel with me for so long.]
You said that
two opposite stars
can take centuries to meet?
It's rare, so it's extra special
when it does happen.
Why do they
meet up?
Because
everything
in this world
has an attractive force.
Just like between stars,
between the moon and the Earth,
and even
between people.
That reminds me
of when I was a kid,
I made a promise with a bud
to go to space and see the stars
together when we grow up.
The one
who betrayed you?
Wonder
where he is now
and if he's doing well.
Maybe
he's looking at
the starry sky as you,
who knows?
[Sorry, Mengyu.]
[Gotta deal with some team stuff.]
[Let's catch up later.]
You saw, right?
[I waited here like a fool]
[for three hours.]
Thought he'd
love my writing,
but he doesn't care at all.
Maybe no one
cares, huh?
That's not true.
I love your writing.
I've read all your essays.
You're just like them.
Xu Mengyu!
November 20th:
Starting from tomorrow,
from the dawn of the very next day,
you will throw yourself
into the journey
with all your might,
you'll find that all you seek is won.
January 1st:
Never have I felt life's
generous gifts,
until I saw my mother's face
has wrinkles,
until each grain
whispered tales
of seasons' toil,
until every meeting with you
brought smiles.
March 14th:
As the guardian
lamp dims,
I realize that
nothing
stands eternal.
[White sneakers,]
[now yellow with disuse,]
[and aged houses,]
[now cloaked in moss's hue.]
[Could there be]
[one who loves you?]
[A love that lasts,]
[until the end of life's night.]
Xu Mengyu!
I know it was your birthday,
and I know you love stars,
for you shine as brightly
as they do.
It's okay if you don't see me.
But I'll always be here for you,
to protect and support you.
I don't need your support,
[I don't need your protection.]
I don't want your pity.
Xu Mengyu!
I'll always be here for you.
Look.
They're aligning.
Hey, Xia Qingtian!
Hey, Chen Luyang.
Going for JU!
Me too!
I'll be with you.
I'll always be with you.
I'll always
always always be with you.
Stars, you hear me?
You know,
when they seem to
meet up in the sky?
That's just an illusion from down here.
They're still way,
way far apart.
You nerds're good
at killing the mood.
I was feeling
all romantic about this.
Yeah. It's romantic.
Been over 400 years
since they've
got this close.
After 400 years,
right?
And we're here to see it.
Every star
has its own path.
They get close, then they split up.
The farthest distance between them
can reach over 810 million kilometers.
And it'll take another 60 years
before they get this close again.
Don't get all mushy.
When you're old,
I'll still be here.
Lan Jinghui.
You ever think
your mom's surprise might be
sending you off to study overseas?
I hadn't
really thought about it.
But if that's really
the case,
should I go or not?
It's up to you.
Your opinion matters.
I said, it's up to you.
Alright.
Gotta give it some serious thought.
What are you looking at?
Stars.
What's so fun about looking at stars?
Mom said that
when you
miss someone,
you look up at the stars.
Stars will tell us
where that person is?
They will.