English subtitles are available
Bright Time EP29
Xiaohua!
Hi, Xiaohua!
You're back.
Yes.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I feel like you're a little unhappy.
Actually, I'm not happy either.
School starts too early.
I haven't had enough vacation.
How could I be happy?
Did someone bully you
at the art studio?
Who dared to bully
my disciple?
Tell me.
No.
Why do you like a frost-eaten plant?
A frost-beaten plant.
I've learned
there's always
a bigger fish.
They're more gifted,
yet more hard-working.
That's all?
Doesn't it matter?
I don't think I can get into Jing University.
Disciple.
Good luck always favors
those who work hard.
You didn't have such calluses
before you went to intensive training.
I'm not as talented
as the others.
If I don't try harder--
You've worked very hard.
Wasn't it after 3:00 a.m.
the last time you posted a Moment?
You can't be in the studio
24 hours a day.
How long till the exam?
It's over four months away.
There's nothing else
I can do but work.
You've got 4 months before exam.
Don't worry!
You have to have faith in yourself.
Come on, you're the best.
But I--
Who said the brush of life
should be in her own hands?
What?
You're going to give up
after such a tiny setback?
No!
Then don't worry.
Remember, don't be influenced by others.
Just be yourself.
We are behind you.
That's right!
Even if you don't believe me,
what about Ling Dong?
He's the versatile god of our school.
With his support,
You can win the envy
of those students in studio.
You're right. Nobody knows
who's going to win until the very end.
Nobody knows!
Let's go!
You two
are keeping me worried.
Captain Chenjun
is almost an agony aunt.
Why are you riding so fast?
Is that a challenge?
I won't allow anyone
to ride faster than me!
Look how fast those boys are riding!
Naive.
Jiang Jing, did you miss me?
How was your vacation?
It went too fast.
It's over before I even feel it.
Yeah.
It went too fast.
What did you do on vacation?
I've been busy.
Welcome back to school,
Luyang.
Welcome back.
But don't forget
to turn in your
summer homework.
Okay.
This is mine.
And this is for you.
Look at me.
What's the most important for a man?
It's confidence.
Only if you're confident--
Jinghui, Jinghui!
Jinghui!
Did you watch the game last night?
Yeah.
Off the glass! Tomahawk dunk!
Amazing!
I've never seen
such a good game.
I tell you,
James almost had a
a triple-double last night.
Ling Dong.
These are letters for you.
I brought them for you.
Thank you.
It's okay.
You got so many letters.
Xu Mengyu,
Don't you have anyone write to you?
Ma Yiming.
Once in a
blue moon, eh?
Eat your egg!
If you keep bullying me,
I'll tell Mengyu.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I thought you
never read letters.
You've changed?
Who's that unlucky girl?
Su Xi.
Li'l Su.
Why didn't she write me a postcard?
Maybe she's not close to you.
I'm her brother, not you!
Heartless girl.
She went home without telling me.
I've even prepared so many
specialties for her.
Ungrateful.
Good to see you again, class.
How's your vacation?
Did you have fun?
Yeah!
Okay, so before we get to the lesson,
let me give you a few words.
Time flies.
You're going into
your senior year.
We all know
the senior year is critical.
But actually,
it's only as special as you imagine.
It's just a small part
of your life.
In this year,
you don't have to exhaust yourself,
but you should do your best.
You don't have to give up your rest,
but you should grit your teeth.
Of course,
some of you may choose to give up.
Like most people said,
like they don't care,
"Whatever.
Work hard or not,
life continues anyway."
Sweat
or tears,
you have to choose one.
Whether to choose temporary happiness,
or the bright future.
It's up to you.
Okay.
The class has begun.
Stand up!
Good morning, Ms. Fang.
Okay, everyone.
Another thing before I let you go.
According to Chenjun's tradition,
to improve the efficiency
of senior students,
weekly practice tests
will be held,
starting from next week.
Then, based on
your scores in each subject, you will
be divided into classes for tutoring.
Everybody,
I hope you can study well
before the tests
to get high scores.
Cheer up!
Okay. Class is over.
Stand up.
Good bye, Ms. Fang.
Good bye.
Why are you so quiet today?
Not even a sound?
Did you feel a bit of pressure
on college entrance exam
after hearing
Mr. Fong's words?
Do you feel a sense of
"the serenity
before the storm" right now?
Everybody's ready to sprint.
It's thrilling
and tantalizing.
Are you a normal human?
I don't understand
the straight-As.
Don't you think
a little pressure
is good for us?
No!
Mom.
Mom, you don't know
that Li'l Su is too hammy
to finish the task
you gave her.
I knew it right away.
You know it already?
Yeah, of course.
Next time, find someone
more reliable,
or your surprises will be wasted.
I know you're taking me covertly
to travel to Singapore.
If you want my passport,
she's not the master thief
you are looking for.
Besides,
aren't you a little
too late?
I'm already in school.
I'm glad you're here, though.
Yes.
I should've come back earlier.
William was young,
and in need of care.
I've been busy at work.
That's why I'm late.
Right, Jinghui.
Do you remember William?
He's six years old now.
And he's been looking forward
to seeing his brother.
Yeah, uh, I remember.
He was a baby
when I left.
Can't believe
he remembers me.
Of course he remembers me.
You both are my sons.
Blood is thicker than water.
Of course, he remembers
he has a brother.
By the way,
mom,
why don't you stay a few more
days this time?
I can
show you around.
Xiangbei
has changed a lot.
I think you're the one
who's changed the most.
Am I?
I remember when you left me
and went back,
you were only a tiny boy.
Suddenly you're a young man now.
Mom.
How about I take tomorrow off
and keep you company, okay?
It's okay.
I'm going back my hometown tomorrow
to see your uncles.
Then,
when are you coming back
to see me and Grandma?
I'll visit your Grandma
after I come back.
Is that okay?
Right.
Then,
I'll take you to your
favorite restaurant.
Is it still there?
Mom.
You still remember it!
Silly boy, of course I remember.
Okay.
Alright.
It's a deal.
I'll take you home now, okay?
Okay!
Let's go.
Go!
Oh, my bike.
Okay.
I heard it announced the list of
candidates for Jing University's
independent enrollment today.
Ling Dong and Chen Luyang are on the list.
Why are you so listless?
I'm worried about the practice tests.
We could be separated afterwards.
If we can
do justice to ourselves in tests,
we're unlikely to be separated.
But Ling Dong is going to the Top Class.
Yeah.
Then
Chen Luyang will leave us too.
What is this school doing
by setting this kinda
tests?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Since when do you
care so much about Chen Luyang?
No.
This is just
friendship between classmates.
Really?
Yeah.
Again?
Yes! Have a sweet to keep your mouth shut.
No, I won't.
Xiaohua!
Have you
prepared a speech
for your interview?
Why?
How can you be so casual about this?
Here, I'll help with it.
After all, I won first place
in the speech contest.
Really?
Of course!
We're friends.
You've been
helping me with study before.
I'm going to help you this time.
Okay.
Ling Dong.
How about your speech?
It's almost done.
Uh, Ling Dong.
Do you need slides
for your interview?
If you need,
I can help you with slides design.
Though I haven't
won first place in it.
Okay.
I'll let you know if I need it.
Okay, okay.
You've got a big job ahead of you.
Let's go over there and work on it.
Don't let them hear you.
We wouldn't copy anyway,
okay?
Help me translate these.
That's too many!
Think of it
as practicing your translating skill.
Don't you know
translators charge a lot?
tutoring also charges a lot?
I'll get started.
Help yourself, mom.
Jinghui,
are you tired
after school?
No.
Mom,
did you rest well?
I just didn't sleep well in a new place.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Jinghui, have some tomatoes.
I remember
you love tomatoes.
Mom, I don't like tomatoes.
Have you forgotten?
I may get it wrong.
Alright.
Have something else.
Here, take some croquettes.
Kids love them.
Okay.
Mom, mom.
Look, Look.
Hasn't Xiangbei
changed a lot now?
The tower
didn't got this light before.
It did change.
I used to
bring you here when you were little.
Yeah.
Maybe I ran
too much at the place
in those days.
That's why they put up railings,
keeping me from running.
Jinghui.
You've been with me for the past days,
will it delay your studies?
No.
I know I was
a bit behind
in my studies,
but now things are different.
I've got a desk mate.
He's been improving me
on my study.
I've made a little progress, I guess.
And I'm on the
basketball team at school.
I'm exceptionally fit.
What's wrong, mom?
It's okay.
Jinghui.
You're about to go to college.
You know,
there are a lot of
good universities in Singapore.
Have you thought about--
Mom.
I seem to know what you mean.
But,
I can always go to Singapore
to visit you, right?
I'm doing
pretty well here now.
The most important thing is
I have a group of friends here.
The desk mate I mentioned,
Ling Dong.
He is
one of the top students
in our school.
And he's a good guy.
I also know
a girl
named Xiao Xiaohua.
She's a bit silly,
but she's...
Well, she is silly.
How can I put it?
Excuse me.
I have to take this.
Okay.
Hello.
What?
How's William now?
Okay, I'll be there as soon as I can.
Mom.
Speaking of the contest earlier,
let me show you
the video from the Talent Show.
This is our show
in the talent contest
I told you before.
The Talent Show
is a citywide
competition.
I was here.
The others were my classmates.
We had a band.
We played the instruments.
And
the band was called
"Rooftop Crew".
The things is,
I was not
at the center.
But as a bass player,
I played a central role.
Sory I'm late.
It's fine.
I'm used to it anyway.
Well...
What do you mean?
I didn't wanna be late either.
I'm really busy at work.
Enough, Lan Shangjin.
I didn't wanna
argue with you.
How have you been?
I'm here
to ask you for a favor.
What is it?
I want you to talk to Jinghui for me.
I have to say,
I'm
good enough that I'm not stopping you
from going to him.
You want me to persuade him?
Not a chance.
I've already been to
my brothers.
None of them
were matched.
Now, Jinghui
is the only hope I have.
Haven't you met him already?
What's his opinion?
I didn't dare to say.
Yu Lihua.
I'm telling you.
Neither of us
are good parents.
I'm his father after all.
I have to look out for him.
He has his own dreams now.
I've seen a change
and hard work in him
lately.
Every second
of the senior year
is so important to him,
you know?
Of course I know!
But now I have
no other choice.
That's why you need to
talk to him in person.
The decision is his.
No one has a right to interfere.
When I came over here,
I saw the candidate of Class 1
wearing a suit.
It looks decent.
Ling Dong, you need to be in suit, too.
Can't lose them on suits.
I think so, too.
Yes.
As the saying goes,
"Clothes make the man."
If you wear a suit,
you'll get into Jing University.
I'll pass.
School uniform works fine.
School uniforms are similar
with suits.
No. if they have it, you must have it too.
Yeah.
Forget it. I'm not wearing a suit.
What?
My dad bought me a lot of suits,
but I never wore them.
I always thought suits
were for good students like you.
How about this,
I'll take care of the suit.
I'll bring you one.
But his size
may be different from yours.
Are you sure he'll fit?
Not that far off.
You'll fit.
Look.
Tomorrow's the weekend.
I'll drop it off at your home.
You try it on.
No. It's too much trouble.
What's the trouble?
It's a deal.
I've got something to do. I'm off.
Jinghui, you're leaving now?
What about your study in the evening?
My mom came back.
I'm going to
take her for hot pot.
I'll leave you guys.
I don't need a suit.
I won't wear it.
Who cares?
I'm off. Bye.
Bye. Bye.
I won't wear it.
Hi, do you have a suit?
Yes.
But
I don't think
they fit me anymore.
If you're free,
can you go with me to buy another one?
Okay.
Tomorrow's the weekend.
We'll meet tomorrow.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're all helping Ling Dong.
If you wanna play fair,
Luyang needs a suit, too.
Don't follow us tomorrow.
She cares him so much, and she said
there's nothing between them?
She doesn't even want a third wheel.
As the saying goes,
"Always be on guard against your bestie."
I mean Xiao Xiaohua.
What are you talking about?
Do your homework.
Let's go back to the book.
This can also be seen
in the third question we met before.
Hello.
Mom, it's me.
Yes.
You can wait me
at the restaurant.
Okay.
Alright, alright.
I'm going now.
I'll be right there.
I disagree!
If he goes with her
because of that,
he won't be back!
I'm his grandma.
How can I see
my grandson suffering?
Mom, it's not as bad as you said.
I don't want him to go, either.
But that's a boy's life.
Look,
Jinghui and William
are half-brothers.
Jinghui is very likely to be
a perfect donor match.
It's bone marrow
we're talking about!
It's hard for me to think about
he'll have surgery.
If there's aftereffects,
how am I supposed to take it?
He's not even there yet.
Besides,
he may not have to have surgery.
Since Yu Lihua came back,
look at Jinghui,
he's so happy to see his mother!
Every time I remember
she had promised to
take Jinghui
abroad with her,
but then sent him back
alone,
I'm heart-broken for
his suffering when he's abroad.
In all these years,
she hasn't come back to see him.
When she has trouble,
when she has trouble,
she'd like to turn to him?
The senior year
is very critical to him.
Shangjin.
I don't care about your opinion.
I won't let him go anyway.
Your brother William
was diagnosed with leukemia.
He needs a bone marrow transplant.
They've checked all of his relatives.
None of them
is a match.
Now you're your mother's
only hope left.
Jinghui, I'm sorry.
I know I'm being selfish.
Mom.
I know what you're going to say.
I'll go with you to see if I'm a match.
Jinghui.
If you don't wanna go,
no one will force you.
It's a surgery you'll go through.
It's okay, Grandma.
William is my brother.
I would have helped even if
my mom hadn't begged me.
So don't worry.
Mom, when are we leaving?
I need to pack.
William is not well.
We should leave as soon as possible.
Okay.
We'll leave the day after tomorrow.
I have
things to do tomorrow.
Because I know Jing University...
Hello. What's the matter?
Well,
I'm downstairs.
Are you at home?
I'm here to bring you the suit.
I said I don't need it.
I really don't need it.
Besides, I'm not at home right now.
I'm waiting for Mr. Zhang
for interview practicing.
I'll be busy on Monday.
Your mom's home, isn't she?
She...
Alright. Fine.
How's this?
I'll just send it in.
Is that okay?
I have another thing to tell you.
What is it?
Ling Dong, your turn.
I'll see you later.
You can tell me then.
It's my turn now.
Okay.
Then,
I'll see you and tell you face-to-face.
Face-to-face?
What happened?
You'll see when you come back.
See you.
Who is it?
Jinghui!
Come on in!
Thanks.
Weirdie,
aren't you just like this?
You look like this!
Let's go on a space trip together
when we grow up, okay?
I promise
to be your friend forever.
You need to promise, too.
Why does Ling Dong have this painting?
My mom and dad are arguing again.
Mom said she'll take me away.
Does it mean we'll never see
each other again?
I don't wanna go.
What would you do if your mom
insisted on taking you away?
I could hide.
Hide? Where to hide?
Here.
This is our secret base.
No one can find me here.
I'll come out after my mom leaves.
Okay!
You must keep my secret.
You can't tell anyone.
Pinkie promise!
Jinghui!
Jinghui! Jinghui!
Liar!
Okay.
Stabilize.
Don't get nervous.
Lower your chin.
Smooth your shirt.
Smooth it.
Okay, okay.
Just a bit. Just a bit.
It's alright.
Get ready.
Three, two, one.
Your name?
I don't think
this is necessary.
Why isn't it necessary?
You're going to have an interview.
So you need to practice.
Am I right, disciple?
He got points.
Your name?
Ling Dong.
Any strengths?
I have no flaws.
You wanna be funny?
Alright.
Try to compliment your desk mate
in a glamorous way.
Stop it, Lan Jinghui.
I'm just kidding.
Give it to me.
I've collected the interview questions
of independent enrollment
in previous years and
corresponding answers for you.
Now,
I'm going to pick
some tough ones
to test you.
Ready?