[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP10]
Halt.
Chief Shen,
Lady Shen has instructed that
once we're here,
all the lights should be put out.
What's your order?
Kill the lights.
Chief Shen,
watch the stairs.
Chief Shen.
[Clerk Yan]
[brought a strange man]
to my bedroom
[and has asked me to wait here.]
[Lord Han,]
where have you been hiding
these days?
[Why are you leaving already?]
Han Shiyuan?
Shiyuan ran away!
Are you sure that was Han Shiyuan?
Yes, it's him.
[He ran away like this the other day too.]
[And he was wearing]
[the exact same clothes.]
Yes,
the exact same clothes.
That day, you were startled
by the fire at Ming Hall, which brought
[bright in the east and dark in the west.]
[People were walking toward the west.]
[That day,]
[you didn't get a clear look]
[at his face that day at all.]
It wasn't him?
But it was definitely him just now.
[It was him too that day.]
It wasn't him in the room just now.
[It wasn't him either that day.]
It was his shadow.
[That day,]
[Lan Guizhou used shadows]
[to create the illusion that Han Shiyuan]
[was still inside the room.]
[He then disguised himself as Han Shiyuan]
[and went out towards the west.]
[That's when the fire]
[from Ming Hall happened in the east,]
[which produced a strong blaze]
[and distracted people,]
[causing the witnesses]
[to mistake him]
as Han Shiyuan.
You are merely speculating.
On the seventh of May,
it was definitely Shiyuan in the room.
[Then he went out and headed to the West.]
The problem is,
both you
and the scholar
who had witnessed it outside the room
[have said that]
[only Han Shiyuan]
[came outside.]
[You were indoors]
[with the lights on.]
[It was bright inside and dark outside,]
how could you have seen
Han Shiyuan was heading west?
[Clerk Yan has a point.]
[When the lights are on inside,]
[you couldn't see outside.]
[As for why someone faked]
Han Shiyuan was still in Imperial Academy
on the night of May 7th,
we'll have to ask
his good roommate.
Take him back.
[You're now dismissed.]
Apan,
thank you for today.
It was really nothing.
Don't mention it.
Who is this Apan?
Lady Shen is very
cheerful with him.
Looks like they're old friends.
Clerk Yan,
I have other matters to attend to today,
so I'll be leaving then.
Are you leaving so soon?
I haven't had a proper chance
to thank you yet.
[We will meet again.]
If you need anything in the future,
come find me at Gui Market anytime.
Deal.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Lady Shen has
never been this joyful in the residence.
It's all thanks to Apan
that I can solve this case today.
You're not taking me to the Imperial
Guard(IG) with you?
There's still the interrogation to do.
[Figure out a way yourself.]
What's with him now?
[Chief Shen, I found it.]
[Apan's real name is Pan Chi.]
[He has solved a few cases in Jiangnan.]
Chief Shen,
do we start the interrogation now?
Interrogate me
however you want!
Shut up.
[Lady Shen.]
How's the interrogation going?
Lady Shen, you're finally here.
We were waiting for you.
[You could've crawled here by now.]
What are you waiting for then?
You thought
after Shiyuan had eloped,
he wouldn't come back again.
[So you faked his presence]
to frame him for the murder.
Yes.
Yeah.
Shiyuan said that he would
elope with his lover the night of May 6th.
I didn't harm Shiyuan.
I knew he was leaving.
I only wanted to use his name.
But that wasn't
why you killed, was it?
You keep talking about Han Shiyuan,
but never a word
[about the scholar you killed.]
You haven't told me
why you killed yet.
Him?
What's there to say about him?
He ruined my poetry anthology.
Didn't he deserve to die?
Just because
he ruined your poetry anthology,
you killed your classmate?
That poetry anthology meant a lot to me.
Shiyuan
was my only friend.
[Ever since Shiyuan got together]
[with Caiwei,]
[I stayed up countless nights]
[copying that poetry anthology]
[as a gift for Shiyuan.]
My poetry anthology!
It's just some worthless copied poems.
Who do you think you are, Pan Yanzhi?
Do you really think
someone would cherish
this foolish poetry anthology as treasure?
[A pile of useless paper.]
My poetry anthology.
How dare he ruin it!
And he dared to mock me?
You killed someone and
deliberately framed Han Shiyuan for it.
Are you
secretly hoping
he'll hear about it and come back?
[Han Shiyuan went missing as soon as he]
[came back to Xiang'an.]
You've seen him, haven't you?
[Where are you hiding Han Shiyuan?]
At Xi market.
In an abandoned distillery warehouse.
[So Lan Guizhou]
has been abusing and killing animals
in this place all along.
His heart is truly twisted.
No wonder he killed someone
for just a poetry anthology.
Someone took Han Shiyuan
before us again.
That's the IG's signal.
[It's coming from the Furong Theater.]
[Shen Du,]
can't you just let me
sit on the horse properly?
Your hand.
Jinglin,
my legs are a bit numb.
Can you help me?
You're so stubborn.
Stop trying to be tough from now on.
Jinglin.
Go save them.
[My...]
My sister is in there.
Tell the guards to put out the fire now!
Something's not right.
Stay put.
Maybe you can ignore them like this,
but I can't.
If you won't go, I will.
Don't go over there.
Watch out!
It's the cold flame.
She's here.
Like a moth to a flame,
here today and gone tomorrow,
escaping the cycle of reincarnation,
neither dying nor being reborn.
I announce to the world,
[I, Chen Huo'e,]
am back.
Chen Huo'e?
The serial murderer from five years ago?
Didn't she kill herself in public
five years ago?
People can't come back from the dead.
Such deliberate secrecy,
must be to mislead others.
To think that someone
could remain so calm and composed
in front of my Nirvana Rebirth Formation.
[You're truly worthy of your name.]
Unfortunately,
even if
you are the White Death,
[you still won't be able to stop me]
from rising from the ashes.
Then I'll just send you
back to hell.
Caiwei.
Shiyuan.
Xing.
Chief Shen.
Since Ms. Yang is here,
I assume
Princess Yong'an
will be in charge here tonight.
But Great Grandmother's bodyguards
are also present.
I'm truly
a bit confused.
Er..
Prince Ying
only asked me to save Han Shiyuan.
[I don't know]
about the rest either.
Chief Shen, Ms. Yang,
[I apologize for being too hasty earlier.]
[I hope I didn't get in your way.]
I was wondering
who could call upon
[Great Grandmother's bodyguards,]
[turns out it was]
[someone favored by Her Majesty herself,]
Lord Zhang.
[Shiyuan,]
you...
How did this happen?
Are you hurt?
[Are you okay?]
It's okay, it's okay.
As long as you're okay.
You must remember
to be more careful in the future.
[Don't let yourself]
[get caught in such situations again.]
Chief Shen,
today's event was very unusual.
Thank heavens you're here.
You must tell the Imperial Guards
to be more vigilant in the future.
You must catch
the one behind all this,
to prevent further problems.
The IG was already
in charge of this matter.
If it weren't for you two's hasty actions,
the culprit would've already been caught.
I was in a rush
and have offended you.
Please accept my apologies.
[The reappearance of Chen Huo'e]
[is quite suspicious.]
We'll have to rely on you,
Chief Shen. to capture the culprit.
I need to return to the palace now,
so I must take my leave.
Han Shiyuan, Her Majesty
[has asked me to deliver a message:]
[as long as you are still willing,]
[Her Highness hasn't changed her mind.]
Han Shiyuan,
do you have anything to say
about tonight's matter?
I know nothing.
Xing has already cleared you of suspicion
for the murder
at Imperial Academy.
[Tonight,]
[Yan Caiwei and you are victims.]
If you don't have anything to say,
you should take her back
to Yan residence to rest now.
How is this Han Shiyuan
deeply connected
with both Princess Yong'an
and Zhang Baohuan?
[It's truly surprising.]
Yeah.
Han Shiyuan obviously had known
Zhang Baohuan for a long time and
had had a history with Princess Yong'an.
But after they saved him,
he showed no gratitude
and almost pretended not to know them.
There must be a reason behind this.
But it looks like
my sister really
doesn't know anything.
I know.
I never
meant to make things hard
for your sister.
I was too reckless
before.
I'm going to the Ministry of Justice
to check the records later.
Would you
like to come with me?
Yes.
Yes!
C'mon, brothers.
Put two over here.
And put two over there.
At the door.
Put also two at the door.
Make sure that the lanterns are aligned
and well-lit for Chief Shen.
Let's leave.
Aren't you exaggerating a bit?
This is too much.
It's not like the candles are free.
I found it.
Five years ago,
the notorious Chen Huo'e committed
multiple murders in various places,
[killing over fifty women.]
[A large moth mark,]
[burned into the skin,]
[was found on the back]
[of each of the victims.]
This has caused nationwide panic.
Families with daughters
[all kept their doors shut.]
[Finally, Chen Huo'e was]
[caught by the Imperial Inspectorate(II)]
[for her countless crimes.]
[She turned out]
[to be a hideous-looking woman.]
[She arrogantly declared that]
she knew the secret of resurrection
and would ultimately return.
At the scene of her capture,
Chen Huo'e killed herself with her sword.
[Before dying,]
[she left behind one final statement.]
Like a moth flying into a flame,
here today and gone tomorrow.
[Escaping the cycle of reincarnation,]
[neither dying nor being reborn.]
Like a moth flying into a flame,
here today and gone tomorrow.
Escaping the cycle of reincarnation,
neither dying nor being reborn.
Lady Tang?
These two cases
have no similarity
in their motives or methods.
But judging by the details alone,
neither of these two cases
could have been done by one person.
There must be a group behind.
Whether it's
Lady Tang murdering and burying bodies,
Chen Huo'e's series of killings
five years ago,
[or]
[tonight's elaborately mysterious]
[Nirvana formation,]
none of these can be done
by one person alone.
It's not simply a group crime.
Judging from tonight's situation,
the connections behind are very complex.
It's likely that this Chen Huo'e
is just a scapegoat.
So, is the Chen Huo'e tonight
the same person as the one
who was caught five years ago?
Whether it's the same person or not,
Chen Huo'e disappeared after the crimes
five years ago,
which meant the person behind her
no longer needed her.
[But now, Chen Huo'e]
[showed up again after five years,]
suggesting that this person behind her
has a need for her again.
Yeah.
What is he really after for?
This situation is very complex.
Even the slightest mistake
could result in great calamity.
Mother,
the jasmine in the backyard has blossomed.
So I picked a bunch
and brought it to you.
[You must feel very alone]
[on the other side.]
Why don't I
sing a song to you?
Do you still remember
the lullaby you used to sing to me
when I was little?
♪Don't speak nonsense.♪
♪Grandma will scold you.♪
♪Mother picks endless flowers.♪
♪Father's always happy when he hears music.♪
[Who's there?]
This is the first time that I've heard
someone singing a lullaby in a cemetery.
It's dark and windy here,
it actually has a unique charm.
It's you.
Lord Ghost, I've seen you.
When I was visiting
my mother here,
I often saw you nearby.
Do you have a loved one here too?
Yeah.
My mother
is buried here nearby.
I didn't know
there were
other family tombs nearby.
The prime Feng Shui locations
near Xiang'an are naturally bought
by prominent and wealthy families
to use as ancestral graves.
[Nameless ghosts]
can only curl up
in the corners of the graveyard,
seeking a humble
refuge.
My dad
indeed had bought this tomb
with a lot of money.
And it's indeed big and grand.
But I know,
my mother
wouldn't want to be here
all by herself.
[She must wish]
[to make more friends.]
So I guess
my mother and your mother
must have already become
good neighbors and friends.
Good friends?
You
are quite different.
Why are you wearing a mask?
Is it because your face is hurt?
I've had a
hideous birthmark on my face since birth.
It's terrifying.
People who have seen my face
would all have nightmares about it.
Do you want to see it?
Wait a second.
Let me mentally prepare myself.
Can you wait for me to count to five?
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Lord ghost?
He left?
Your hand hasn't been treated yet.
[ I asked the butler]
[to bring all the ointments]
[from the residence]
to see which one is best for treating
this bite.
How is this so grave?
It was from a small dog.
It's not serious.
The butler said that
there was a red ointment
that Yaya has used before.
Bitten by Yaya
and bitten by me
should be the same.
Yeah.
Yaya was bitten
by a mad dog.
It's indeed the same.
Is this how you apologize?
Why do I need to apologize?
You didn't explain yourself clearly
and made me misunderstand.
Besides,
you've been injured all night.
Didn't you think to
have Jinglin treat it?
You had to wait for me to do it?
I...
[Let go of me!]
[Walk!]
Let go!
Walk!
Let go of me!
Du,
even though you were saving someone,
you still need to pace yourself.
If the arrow had been
even slightly more off,
that man would have surely died.
Father,
I wouldn't have missed.
I intended to leave him alive
for interrogation.
I'm Shen Du.
Are you okay?
[Are you]
[still the boy who saved me]
[that I remembered?]
Who's there?
Yan Xing!
How... How did this happen?
Did you do it on purpose?
Of course not.
I'm sorry, I took the wrong one.
You...
I'll wash it off right away.
Be good.
Stay still.
You did do it on purpose.
My lord.
Come, come, Xing.
Have a seat. Have some tea.
[Let's chat.]
Is there any new rumors about me?
[No, no. There isn't.]
No rumors.
[Right, my lord?]
[However,]
[all of us]
[agree that we have]
a she-demon in the Ministry of Justice.
And this she-demon
is truly very impressive.
She dares to yell at the White Death.
[But such a pity.]
[In the end,]
she was still hang on the horse
by the White Death
[and paraded through the streets.]
A woman
should be
gentle,
gentle, virtuous,
gentle, virtuous, respectful,
gentle, virtuous, respectful, thrifty,
gentle, virtuous, respectful, thrifty, and considerate.
It's best for their own good.
Lu Chuichui!
You're late again.
[Why the gloomy look]
[when you're late?]
What were you doing yesterday?
Nothing.
Look at you!
Feng Gui.
My lord.
Last night Chen Huo'e came back from the
dead.
The chief of IG
[had someone send over]
[the records early this morning,]
meaning that this case...
When I came in,
[Ji Fangming, the one in charge of]
[reviewing case files gave this to me.]
Give me, give me.
It's a case
from Wannian County.
[There was a murder]
[at Xuanpin Theater, Wannian County.]
The victim
was the wife of Chen Shoujie,
a retired court official.
Such a fuss over the death of a woman?
Chief Clerk Wu, so you mean
only the death of men
matters.
Is a woman's life
not worth taking seriously?
What did I tell you.
She's grown bolder now that
she's married into the Shen residence.
Fine.
Forget I said anything.
Feng Gui,
tell the Delinquents to go investigate.
My lord.
[The case file says that]
[the victim died last night.]
There was a huge, fire-drenched moth
on her shoulder.
Exactly...
Exactly the same as the one
[on the victims of Chen Huo'e]
[from five years ago.]
Chen Huo'e again?
Chief Clerk Wu,
please allow me to investigate this case.
Since this case is connected to
Chen Huo'e coming back from the dead,
we should turn it over to the IG
[for them to handle together.]
[That's right.]
It's not appropriate for the
[Ministry of Justice to get involved.]
That's right. It's not appropriate.
Even though Chief Shen is your husband,
you have no significance
at the Shen residence.
[The White Death wouldn't]
bring you to solve cases together.
He wouldn't.
[Vice-Chancellor Lai is here.]
[Greetings to Chancellor Lai.]
Chancellor Lai.
If the White Death wouldn't take her,
the Dark Demon
would gladly invite Clerk Yan
[to assist with the investigation.]
Chief Clerk Wu,
five years ago,
it was me who was in charge of
the Chen Huo'e case.
I've long heard of Yan's skills
in investigations.
Since you're also
interested in the Chen Huo'e case,
why don't you
come work at the II
and help me catch the culprit?
Thank you for your appropriation.
I'm just a small clerk in this Ministry.
I only hope
to take the female official's exam
and become a ninth clerk.
[I have no intention to change ministry.]
Since you've refused the easy way,
then,
until next time.
Chancellor Lai, take care.
[Halt.]
Greetings to Prince Ying.
Shiyuan,
[we haven't seen each other in a while.]
We met by chance today,
yet you still plan to avoid me?
[I wouldn't dare.]
Shiyuan, what do you mean by that?
Get up.
Your Majesty,
I am just a commoner.
I don't want to offend Your Majesty.
Shiyuan, no need to say such things.
[Matters of the heart]
[cannot be forced.]
Since you already
have someone in your heart,
I will naturally support your happiness.
I appreciate Your Majesty's kindness.
Let's go.
Your Majesty.