English subtitles are available
Bright Time EP30
Mom.
You're back.
Where's Lan?
He went home.
And, he hung the clothes
in your room.
Whatcha doing in the kitchen?
Making your
breakfast for tomorrow.
You're gonna have that
JU exam, right?
Rest up and get ready.
Alright, good night.
Oh, he's quite slim.
Dad.
What's up?
Changing the SIM card?
Chill out.
Just change it when you get there.
What if
someone tries to reach you?
Nah.
I've hit up everyone
who needs to know.
Okay.
Just be safe
when you get there,
and let me know if you
need anything.
Got it.
Alright.
Dad.
Good night.
Don't be tardy for the interview.
And put on that suit
Jinghui gave you.
Yeah, mom.
Mom.
You moved my painting?
No.
What's up?
Nothing.
Sorry.
The number you dialed is powered off.
Chen Luyang,
a senior from Chenjun.
It's your turn.
Good day, esteemed teachers.
Thanks, school, for this chance
to share my dreams.
Let's start with my intro.
My name is Chen Luyang,
and I'm from Xingsha.
How's the interview?
Not bad.
Good then.
You ate that lucky candy
I gave you?
Of course.
It helped.
I was less tense.
Ling Dong.
How's your interview?
It should be okay.
Where's Lan?
He'll go overseas.
He texted me
last night,
his plane leaves at 3 pm today.
Right, I got it too.
Strange,
he's gonna leave like that?
I told you his mom
was taking him to Singapore,
but no one believed me.
Is he coming back for gaokao?
Why would he?
He'll probably just stay there.
He didn't tell you?
Ling Dong.
He probably didn't
want to distract you.
Ling Dong.
It's time for the written exam.
You've got this!
Go!
Go for it!
Let's go.
Lan Jinghui.
You liar,
liar!
Huge liar!
Clownfish.
Lan Jinghui.
Chen Luyang really pulled it off.
Yeah.
He topped the exam.
Incredible!
He surpassed
Ling Dong this time.
After Lan left,
everything seemed
to be the same as before,
but I felt
something changed.
We humans
always miss what's gone.
We only realize
how much we need someone
once he's gone.
Hey, slowpoke.
Finally!
I held this spot for you.
Ling Dong.
I wish I had realized sooner
how you felt about me.
Lan Jinghui.
I'm gonna be your uncle for life,
for real.
Wanna get a free ride for life, huh?
Good luck with that!
Trust me?
Nah.
This is the first
simulated exam,
so I hope you all bring
your best game.
It's not just a review
of all the knowledge,
but also a mock exam for gaokao.
It'll give you a clear picture
of your current standing.
Class's over.
Stand up.
Thank you, Ma'am.
See you, guys.
He's been gone ages,
and no word from him.
Is he never coming back?
Who knows?
Parents nowadays,
they think sending kids
abroad fixes everything.
I knew his mom
was taking him
overseas.
Nonsense.
That can't be true.
Did he reach out to you?
Nope.
If we had known
he wasn't coming back,
we should've
thrown him a farewell party.
Now he's gone.
And we'll be reassigned.
It's sad.
Class begins.
Stand up.
Good morning, Ma'am.
Morning, sit down please.
Please
turn to page 39.
We're
gonna do a quick review.
Last time,
we dug into Du Fu's
poem "A Night in Chamber".
Now, let's
go over the main idea
and how the poem's
put together.
Ling Dong.
Ma'am's got your name.
Stay focused.
The first round of review
is important.
Put your hearts into it.
Stay focused.
Alright, we studied
Du Fu's poem.
Ling Dong, check this out.
B's the answer.
B?
Why?
B's the one.
B?
Exhausted.
All we do is study and study.
The vibe's so heavy.
I miss Class 5,
where Lan Jinghui
would crack jokes
whenever we got tired.
He kept
things lively.
Remember that
hilarious one he told?
Which one?
Kid's been busy with
his high school studies, and his
parents care deeply about his grades.
One noon, he's shampooing up,
and Dad walks in,
"Whatcha washing there?"
Kid says, "I'm washing my hair."
Dad's like,
"Don't waste your time."
"Go take a nap."
"Put your head down, I'll wash it."
Can you keep it down?
I've been busting my butt
teaching you ball,
shouldn't you
address me as...
Cuz.
I'm your uncle.
Come on, cuz.
One hand on the ball,
cut to the side,
three steps.
Shoot!
Try it.
I told you.
For the three-step shot,
if you squat too low,
you won't get that jump.
You're back?
What's up?
Weirdie. Don't you wanna see me?
Sorry.
I actually recognized you
as Clownfish way back,
but I couldn't bring up
our childhood stuff.
I didn't mean to
betray you.
And it's been
weighing on me
for years.
When I realized it was you,
I wanted to tell you.
But
I was all tongue-tied.
I was afraid you'd...
Dude, what's up?
Come on, let's ball out!
I'm good.
Mom.
Jinghui.
How do you feel?
Much better.
Jinghui.
I made chicken soup.
Load up
on the good stuff,
so you get better soon.
How's William doing?
He's fine.
The docs are on it.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Here, sip some soup,
take it slow.
Tastes good?
Yeah.
Mom.
Your cooking's still top-notch
after all these years.
If you like it,
I'll cook soup for you every day.
Yeah.
Jinghui.
I wanna talk to you about something.
Yeah.
You know,
your dad's got a demanding job,
and grandma's health
isn't what it used to be.
Would you stay and
study in Singapore?
I'd love to have you around.
I know I wasn't there
for you.
But I wanna make it up
to you both.
Will you give me
a chance?
Everyone.
Today is the first day
of the 2nd semester,
which means that
all of you here are
entering the final sprint
of gaokao.
What is gaokao?
Gaokao's a mountain
we gotta conquer.
Only by
reaching the top
can we see the view.
Brave hearts
never shy away from challenges,
they keep pushing limits
and making history.
I believe that you
will be the creators
of Chenjun's glorious history.
Today, you honor your school,
tomorrow,
your school will honor you.
Now, I hereby announce that this year,
a total of 519 warriors
will rock
the exam!
No. It's 520.
Surprise!
Jinghui, you're back!
Jinghui.
Alright, settle down.
Sit down.
Especially you, Ma Yiming.
Calm down.
Jinghui.
Chill out, sit.
Sit, sit, sit.
Sit.
Lan Jinghui.
Yes.
What's the fuss?
Late on the first day?
Be seated.
Yes, sir.
Sit here.
Jinghui.
Long time no see.
After you.
Take it easy.
My back.
I missed you.
We missed you a lot.
Just had surgery.
Alright, enough.
Man, don't be like that.
Okay. Now.
Correction.
I hereby announce that
this year, a total of
520 warriors will
take the exam.
Yeah!
Now, let's do this.
I'll say one, two, three,
and we all yell "Go Team!"
Yeah.
One, two, three.
Go Team!
Mom.
I wanna go back.
Why?
Wouldn't you like to stay
and be with me?
Mom.
I left to give you
a better life,
and I'm back
for the same reason.
Please. Don't feel
guilty, it's what I
wanted to do.
You know.
You have your own life to live,
and I have mine.
Plus, I have
my buds and
grandma back in China.
The thing is,
I gotta be there
for my dad,
he might get a bit lonely
sometimes.
You can always
visit them often.
Mom.
I haven't told you
that I wanna apply to JU.
I know
I slacked off
before,
but now I
have a clear goal
and I wanna fight
for it.
So, mom.
I wanna go back.
Looks like
you've made your choice.
I won't force you.
Just promise to
visit me whenever
you can, alright?
I promise.
Alright, have some soup.
Take it slow.
Did you miss me
when I wasn't around?
Feel like a ship without a rudder
when I'm unreachable?
Feel lost without
your deskmate?
Not really.
New class,
new deskmate.
No distractions.
I was over the moon.
Just me and my books.
Plus, I get to help out
my classmates.
Yeah?
If that's the case,
why
all the texts
and calls?
Ling Dong, no offense.
But you're always like this.
So reserved.
So petty.
You think I'm like you,
right?
I'm not.
I'm not gonna
flip out just because you didn't
tell me about childhood stuff.
I have never been
a petty person
like that.
You saw my text?
You saw my text.
Why no reply?
And you say you're
not mad,
but why did you
run off to another country
without a word?
Why hold out on me?
Why?
Yeah.
I know it was my fault
when we were kids,
but bailing on me
without saying a word
like that?
You have no idea
how much I've been
worrying and missing you.
Alright.
We're even.
You kept your identity
a secret too.
Why'd you leave
and come back?
I had to go overseas
because I'm the only one
who can save my little bro
with
a bone marrow match.
A bone marrow match?
So...
Did you end up being a match?
I...
You been stuck in the hospital?
Are you okay?
So many questions.
Where do I even
begin?
Now's not the time for humor.
Hey, take it easy.
I'm cool.
Take your time.
Really?
I'm fine.
I'm buzzing with life.
You're not still pouting, are you?
Lan Jinghui.
I'll be honest
with you from now on.
Me too.
I promise I'll never lie to you again.
I'll support you in your studies.
Me too.
Let's go for JU together.
Go for JU together.
You're back.
You scared me.
You're still up? It's late.
It's half past eleven.
You're pretty tipsy.
Leave me be, I'm good.
I'll grab you some water.
I'm fine.
Just go to bed.
Senior year
is crucial.
I know.
Finish this.
What's this?
Why is it sweet?
It's honey water.
Tea's the cure.
That's not true.
Tea at this time
can worsen
your drunk state
and is not good
for your health.
Yeah?
Tea's always been my go-to.
Just because you do it all the time
doesn't make it right.
Change can be good.
You're not
pulling my leg because
I'm buzzed, are you?
If you're not too drunk,
let me ask you a question.
What?
Did you know
my mom
asked about staying in
Singapore?
Yeah.
So, you wanted me
to stay there, huh?
Son, you're grown up.
You gotta
make your own decision.
And besides,
Singapore's pretty great.
Alright, I know.
Another question.
After the divorce,
did you ever wanna
get me a new mom?
You little rascal.
You...
Mind your own business.
I don't want you to
be alone when you're old.
Right?
With your looks and charm,
if you find someone special,
just go for it.
And
when I'm off
to college, you can
do whatever floats your boat.
Are you kidding?
I'm a catch!
And hey,
let's get you into
that university first.
Staying up late just to
give me
a hard time, huh?
And, you know...
I...
I'm just curious,
where do you go
so late every day?
It seems like you're
never home at night.
Just out networking.
What else would I be up to?
Finish your water and
hit the hay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Also,
stop
sneaking in
like a burglar.
I'm dead to the world up there,
won't even notice.
Got it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Last but not least,
don't burn yourself out
chasing after money.
You know?
I'll be bringing in
the bacon soon.
Right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And besides...
I wanna say...
I know, I know.
You know.
You...
Easy on
the criticism.
That was
too much
for me.
Please, go to sleep.
Okay.
We'll chat about it later.
What now?
Don't forget.
What?
About finding someone new.
Little rascal.
Good night, dad.
Prove that A2, A5,
and A8 form an arithmetic sequence.
Given that S3, S6, and S9
form an arithmetic sequence,
we have S3 + S6
= 2Sq,
and q does not equal 1.
1 - q/A1
x (1-q^3)
+ 1 - q/A1
x 1-q^6
= 1 - q/2A1.
Therefore, A2, A5,
and A8 form an arithmetic sequence.
There's another
formula to solve this
which is
a bit more difficult.
I'll write it on the blackboard.
Try to keep it in mind.
This is the
formula.
Give it
a shot
-Ms. Fang. -after class.
Ms. Fang.
It's break time.
I know.
Class's over.
Stand up.
Thank you, Ma'am.
See you, guys.
Ling Dong.
Listen,
you've got
quite some
catching up to do.
I've got some practices
for you.
Okay.
This.
Focus on lines and
hyperbolas'
interactions.
Key section.
Page 73, huh?
Yeah. Page 73.
And this.
Two defs of hyperbola...
See you after school?
Sure.
But I'll be a bit late.
Okay.
I'll be waiting for you.
Yeah.
See you.
I'll be there.
See you, bye.