Does the boss need coffee
Do you hate me so much
Sure
In this case
We
Terminate the contract
Hi
Would you like to wipe that
You can't see, can't you
I didn't think you were selling badly.
You won't have to come again
Go to the finance department to sign and claim the compensation
Contact the public relations department and the legal department immediately
I don't want this man
To reappear in this city in the future
And I don't want this picture
Any more proliferation
Why are you up so early today
Because I have to accompany you to work
You can't get up two hours early, can you
It can't be
I'm just giving you a video
Oh, that's right
By the way, your brother's atmosphere was a little wrong yesterday
Is he okay
You can rest assured of this
He has a lot of nerves
Lin Yulu, I'm sorry
I shouldn't have taken a sneak shot
It should not spread maliciously
You did it
Your best friend did it
All right
Thank you for helping me
But in the future this kind of thing
Never mind