English subtitles are available
Melody of Golden Age EP12
Princess Ying has arrived!
Your Majesty.
I seek to bring charges against Lord Zhang
of using the exams to recruit
students from humble origins, and
plotting to kill them when they refused.
Today,
several of them have already gone missing.
Your Majesty!
I am being unjustly accused!
I merely sympathized with the hard journey
of the students from humble origins.
I was afraid they wouldn't be
well taken care of before the exam,
so I instructed the gentry to treat them.
How can such false accusations
be unleashed on me?
Then tell me,
what happened to those students
who left the banquet early?
Where are they now?
Your Majesty,
I believe that
Lord Zhang is the head of the civil officials
and has always valued talent.
To say he'd win over them is convincing,
but to say he would resort to violence
is probably
beyond one man's capability.
Lord Lai,
What do you mean by that?
Cease your nonsense!
Yongan,
such a significant matter must not be
subjected to careless debate.
Do you have any evidence?
I...
I have it!
Last night, several students were attacked,
and were rescued by the Imperial Guard.
These are the weapons we seized.
All of them are standard issue
from the Prince Xian's residence.
Your Majesty!
I have nothing
to do with this!
I request a thorough investigation.
The assassins confessed before they died
that they were instructed by His Highness.
Lord Commander,
you...
End your baseless slander!
I
didn't know that
you pledged allegiance to the princess!
Lord Zhang, cease your cunning arguments!
There are both witnesses and evidence.
What right do you and Prince Xian have to
continue to oversee
the examinations?
Confess your crimes at once!
Violence-doers must face justice,
but they are not among them.
Lord Shen,
the people were saved by you,
and the evidence was brought by you,
why do you now claim
that the mastermind is someone else?
There were three groups of assailants.
The first was for abduction and intimidation.
It was for establishing authority
among the students from humble origins.
These individuals
were subordinates of Lord Zhang.
I...
The second group was ruthless,
but they used weapons standard
to the Prince Xian's residence.
They frequently brought up
Prince Xian,
as if afraid others wouldn't know.
Who are you people?
His Highness is wise.
Threats and temptations won't work
on you stupid scholars.
It'd be better to eliminate all of you!
The third group
were hidden assailants
who used vicious methods just to silence them.
They used the standard
weapons of the Prince Xian's residence.
This doesn't make sense!
If His Highness is truly behind this,
how could it be so obvious?
Your Majesty,
this doesn't make sense at all!
It seems there are
a bunch of people out there
eager to convict me,
Your Majesty.
I implore Your Highness to see the truth.
Since the evidence is questionable,
then let the
Imperial Guard continue the investigation.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Thanks to Lord Shen,
the students
turned out to be safe.
From now on, we must ensure
that no further troubles arise.
Prince Xian,
Lord Zhang,
the safety of these students
is in your hands.
If anything happens again,
you will be held accountable.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please rest easy.
Even at the cost of my own life,
I'll ensure the safety of the students.
Commander!
Thanks for your help earlier.
I was just conducting the investigation
without favoritism;
no need for gratitude, Lord Zhang.
Lord Zhang.
Gratitude for him is unnecessary.
He
was merely
showing off
in front of Her Royal Highness.
Apparently, Lord Lai
prefers to keep a low profile,
but remember, lurking in the shadows
can sometimes backfire.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Xing girl, the lunch is on your for sure!
Let me tell you something.
You didn't witness the spectacle.
Today, when Lord Wu
heard that Xing was given the authority
to investigate the Chen Huo'e case,
his face was something else...
It turned purple, paling pig liver.
Lord Wu
even insisted that we sit
separately from her.
Sure, he is in charge at the ministry,
but can he really dictate
who I drink with?
Xing,
if this case requires
any assistance from the Delinquent,
don't hesitate to reach out to me.
Come on,
Let me raise a glass to you!
Me too.
Me too, me too!
Come on, cheers!
Alright.
By the way, Xing,
I'd like to ask you something.
Do you know of any
methods to remove birthmarks?
Birthmarks?
How come I didn't know you have them?
I...
I have a friend.
He asked me about
how to remove birthmarks.
I've been exploring medical texts lately.
but I haven't found anything useful.
So I thought I'd come and ask you.
Birthmarks are something we're born with.
Birthmarks are not disease and
herbs alone can't remove them.
I've heard from some friends
about a method
for removing birthmarks.
What is it, Lord Xu?
This method sounds a bit unusual.
It involves using a ring made of pure gold
to continuously rub the birthmark.
That sounds pretty straightforward!
I have plenty of gold to spare.
Thank you, Lord Xu.
Don't mention it.
Barman!
There's no one around. I'll go get it.
Barman! More wine, please!
Chui...
Has she recently made any
friends with birthmarks?
Xing!
You know,
there are a few drunks next door,
and one of them
is gorgeous.
He came to the office seeking you.
Looking for me?
That one, that one!
Here!
The one in the middle.
Pan?
Pan.
Mr. Pan.
The examination is just around the corner.
Didn't you mention, you wanted to
bring honor to the humble families?
Why aren't you focusing on your studies?
Instead, you're here drinking?
Disregarding social status?
It's clear my effort can't overcome fate.
They are all from Prince Xian's residence.
He has dispatched three groups of people
to silence us, insignificant scholars
of humble origins.
This is just the beginning.
This examination
is not as straightforward as you think.
I advise you all not to naively
try to cling to a powerful figure.
Don't even think about wading into
the chaos of Xiang'an City.
The chaos of Xiang'an City
are but a reflection of the sullied hands
of those in power,
such as someone like you.
Is it wrong to seek power?
The issue isn't with power itself.
It's about how that power is wielded.
With power,
one can protect those they care about
and pursue what they believe is right.
Being self-righteous,
having nothing but a proud spirit,
what can you achieve with those
other than showing off your eloquence?
With this energy,
you'd be better off using it
in truly meaningful ways.
I might as well drink.
Drinking is more meaningful.
Please send them back to the Guishi
Thanks.
Clerk Yan.
Live life to the fullest.
Don't let the drinks stop flowing.
Keep the drinks coming!
Easy, easy.
The examination is just around the corner.
How come he acts like
he is drowning his sorrows in alcohol?
Xing, haven't you heard?
Last night, three groups of thugs tried to
kill the students of humble origins.
Is that true?
Yes, it is.
What happened to the students?
Didn't the Commander tell you?
He single-handedly turned the tide
and saved them all.
Otherwise, it would have been a disaster.
Shen Du saved them?
Deliver this to the Ministry of Justice.
Gratitude.
Excuse me, my lady,
I'm looking for
a female official, Clerk Yan.
She's not here.
She's out investigating with White Death.
White Death?
The commander of Imperial Guard, Shen Du.
He is Xing's husband.
Husband?
I heard the wife of IG Commander
got beat up again today.
She left with a limp.
Yeah,
her forehead is
swollen quite a bit.
Can she truly find happiness
by marrying White Death?
Xing,
we have shared much,
and your wedding
should bring me joy.
But the thought of you marrying
the notorious White Death
troubles me deeply.
My lady.
Zhong.
Greetings.
What's the matter?
Since my lord returned, he's been
in the training of martial arts,
and hasn't had dinner yet.
My lady, you're finally back.
You should head to the backyard.
For the past few days,
the Commander has been at home,
preparing tea and snacks for you.
But you've either been out on cases
or drinking with
a bunch of strangers.
Now that the Commander
has been waiting for you all night.
So...
He's been waiting for me?
I thought
you were busy with investigations.
Now start serving the dishes.
Nice punches!
So you do realize you have a home.
Me?
I reported for duty to the Imperial Guard.
I also investigated
Chen Shoujie's residence
and went out for drinks
with Chui and Chief Xu.
I even ran into the merchant, Pan.
So I came back a bit late.
Did you need something from me?
I'm hungry.
If you're hungry, you should eat!
By the way,
I came back to let you know.
I promised my mother that
I'd return to the Yan residence tonight.
You go ahead and eat.
I'm leaving now.
You little...
I've already prepared dinner for you.
Forget dinner.
This family will fall apart without me!
Zhong, you go ahead.
We will join you shortly.
My lord,
my lady is not just some
illiterate village girl.
She is a respected female official
in the Ministry of Justice.
She holds a public position.
During the day, she handles serious matters,
and at night, it's normal that
she shares a drink with her colleagues.
On the other hand,
you might be overreacting a bit.
So what I mean is,
you might as well take this opportunity...
Mother!
I really can't take anymore.
This is the finest tonic
that I chose for you.
I made it just for you.
It's a shame your husband isn't with you,
or you two could have enjoyed it together.
I promise you'd have two kids in three years!
Mother.
Stop your wild imagination, please.
Did you put anything
weird in it?
No, not at all.
I wish there was something special.
I wish I had the power
that Chen Huo'e possesses.
Otherwise, I'd get you some
elixir for immortality
and resurrection.
Come again, mother?
How do you know about Chen Huo'e?
Are you kidding?
Is there anyone in all of Xiang'an
who doesn't know about her?
Five years ago,
Chen Huo'e committed suicide in public.
She died and came back to life,
reborn from the ashes.
She fought her way back
from the underworld,
overcoming countless obstacles.
Her power is
incredible!
Mother, where did you hear
about all these nonsense?
I heard it from the
primary wife.
You don't believe me, fine,
but you can't doubt her words.
Everyone in Xiang'an's noble circles
is talking about this Chen Huo'e.
She has the power to cross the gates of hell.
Even Death himself
can't do anything to her.
Mother, you smell amazing!
What perfume are you wearing today?
Curious to know?
Want some?
Then you should eat a bit more.
Xing,
I heard that thanks to you, Caiwei
and Mr. Han were able to return safely.
You rarely come back,
so my lord instructed the kitchen
to prepare some late-night snacks.
Help yourself.
Dig in.
Xing,
there're rumors circling about
you and the Commander.
If you ever feel mistreated,
you need to let us know.
Right.
Commander Shen has arrived.
Who is he going to catch this time?
Commander, this way please.
Come on,
go hide in the back room!
Hurry!
Don't act like you're seeing the King of Hell.
He won't eat you.
Mojie.
Ever since the last time
you were taken by White Death,
you seem like a completely different man.
Why are you speaking highly of him?
Of course!
I'm now...
now...
I can't reveal that.
Greetings, Lord Commander.
Looks like I arrived just in time.
I could join my lady
and all of you
for a late-night snack.
Yes, indeed.
What brings you here?
Lord Commander, please take a seat.
In the absence of my beloved,
even the finest cuisine loses its savor.
Lord Yan, please.
Gratitude, Lord Commander.
Gratitude.
My lady.
Here.
Thanks.
That's enough, enough!
There you go!
Please, savor this dish slowly, my lady.
Though it may not match the fine taste
of your own cooking,
it offers the solace of a familiar taste.
Don't just stand there.
Everyone, dig in.
Alright, alright.
I still want to
chat with my sister a bit more.
Why don't you head back first,
darling?
Alright.
Take your time.
I'll wait for you.
No need to rush.
Shen Du, what exactly are you planning?
Lord Commander,
the information I provided recently
was quite timely, right?
As soon as I saw those students of
humble origins, not knowing their place,
I figured that Lord Zhang would
definitely take action against them.
As expected of Xing's brother,
your intelligence is remarkable.
Gratitude, my lord.
Once I pass this examination,
my lord, please promote...
Lord Commander,
apologies for my son's nonsense.
Please don't take offense.
It was indeed him who saved the students.
Please come in, Lord Commander.
With nothing else to attend to,
I am eager for you to take a look at the
calligraphy I have spent years perfecting.
I have long heard that Lord Yan
is a master of calligraphy in the empire.
Today, to be able to see your works,
is truly a stroke of luck.
I didn't expect that the Yan residence
would actually collect
so many calligraphy works.
About this piece of calligraphy...
Isn't the original in the palace?
I didn't expect
that I couldn't hide it
from Lord Commander's discerning eye.
The original of this calligraphy
is indeed in the palace.
This piece of calligraphy
is but an imitation
by me.
To be honest,
Lord Commander,
all the famous works in this room
are merely imitations of mine.
They look very authentic.
I didn't expect that Lord Yan
would be so adept at imitating
the calligraphy of various masters.
You flattered me.
I have no other talents,
only this skill in copying.
I can barely manage to stand out.
I heard that my lord and son...
Lord Commander
are enjoying calligraphy,
which reminded me that my lord once copied
Lord Shen's calligraphy.
I dug it out.
My father's?
Apologies, Lord Commander.
I...
I wasn't planning anything harmful.
It's just that...
It's fine.
My father being a condemned official,
people shied away from associating with him.
Actually,
I did put in some effort
to study Lord Shen's brushwork
back then.
When Lord Shen was young,
his brush strokes were like swords,
powerful and grand.
But later on,
his strokes became more subtle,
ancient and smooth.
I also practiced for a long time
to achieve
this level of similarity.
Could it be...
I haven't seen
such a striking resemblance
to my father's handwriting in a long time.
I was momentarily lost in thought
and lost my manners.
Not at all.
I have business back in the IG.
I must take my leave.
Alright, alright.
Lord Commander, you're a busy man.
No need to walk me out.
Take care, Lord Commander.
Sigh...
Lord Zhang has mentioned that
Shen Du confessed on his father's behalf
so he could get out of jail.
Why did you bring up
this topic again?
How...
How would I know?
Father, your handwriting is excellent.
Please give me a piece.
Since my arm
was injured a few years ago,
my brushwork is not as strong as before.
I will give you a
fan I wrote on before.
The strokes are smooth, and
the brush strokes were like swords.
Indeed, they are the same style.
The forger of the letters
incriminating my father for treason...
Could it be
Xing's father?
Why isn't he here yet?
Maskman!
Maskman,
You're finally here.
Are you here to see your mother?
I'm here for you.
For me?
This is for you.
What is this?
I found out about a folk remedy
that can remove birthmarks.
It's said that by using this
to rub on the birthmark back and forth,
it can lighten and eliminate it.
You should give it a try.
You specifically came to give me this?
Then if I don't show up today...
I'll just come tomorrow.
Anyway, I'll come to keep my mother company.
She'll be happy to see me.
Let me teach you.
Stretch out your hand.
Just like this.
Rub back and forth on the birthmark.
It shouldn't be too gentle,
or overly firm.
Got it?
Here you go.
Keep it.
Anyway,
you must persist
for it to be effective.
We are not related by blood,
so why would you
give me such a valuable thing?
It's alright.
I, Lu Chuichui,
have plenty of gold.
As long as your birthmark can be removed,
in the future,
you will be able to take off the mask
and face the
world with honesty.
That is worth more than
any amount of gold.
Thank you.
I seek justice, my lord.
I come to plead my case.
I implore my lord to intervene.
To have someone appeal to me for justice,
this is truly unprecedented.
What injustice are you seeking to rectify?
In the case of Jinxiu Workshop years ago,
many died by injustice.
My lord, please investigate thoroughly.
Boring.
Be gone.
Lord Commander.
I heard that you are known as White Death,
an honorable man who catches evil doers,
and you won't ignore the injustice.
If Lord Commander
won't right the Jinxiu Workshop wrongs,
I am willing to die to prove my point.
Madwoman.
She's probably an assassin.
My lord,
please right the Jinxiu Workshop wrongs.
Stop it.
Lord Lai.
What crime has this woman committed?
Burning someone on the street?
This is the Zhuque Street of Xiang'an,
right under the emperor's gaze.
People are all watching.
You wouldn't take a life recklessly, right?
I'm just dealing with an assassin.
Do you want to intervene, Commander Shen?
Commander Shen?
So you are
the White Death, Commander Shen.
I am not an assassin.
I am seeking justice.
I implore my lord to act.
Reopen the case; it was wrongfully decided.
Lord Lai,
Since this girl
has been looking for me.
I will take her with me.
Since Lord Commander has requested,
this girl will be handed over to you.
Lord Commander,
Yunque has long known of your
strict and impartial nature,
the very image of integrity.
My family in Jiangnan
supplies silks for the Jinxiu Workshop.
This is the record of the orders
that Jinxiu Workshop placed.
This was the order placed
by the princess's husband back then.
The one that exceeded regulations.
However, this order paper
is thinner than usual.
If it can be proven that this order
has been tampered with,
it could clear the name for us,
Is that right?
I'm taking the evidence.
You should go home now.
If necessary, the Imperial Guard
will reach out to your parents.
The owners of the workshop
are truly good people.
They must have been wronged.
Jinglin.
Escort her out of the city.
Help!
Sir,
please go after him.
Don't let him escape!
He's far gone.
Miss, are you alright?
You don't need to worry about me.
You should go after him!
He must be connected to
the case of the Jinxiu Workshop.
Otherwise, he wouldn't want to silence me.
Mr. Xu.
Xing.
Lord Commander.
Miss Yunque,
was attacked at the inn last night.
If I hadn't happened to patrol by,
she would have been harmed.
Is this how your Imperial Guard
protects witnesses?
I sent her out of the city yesterday.
How did she sneak back in?
Lord Commander,
Yunque almost
couldn't see you again.
That man in black
definitely wanted to silence me.
Lord Commander,
you've taken my evidence,
which means you need to keep me safe.
That order from the Jinxiu Workshop
is crucial evidence
for their case.
I am a key witness.
You can't leave me unprotected.
I mentioned it to you yesterday.
That case
cannot be overturned
based solely on this
order from six years ago.
You made a scene in Xiang'an City,
and it almost made the whole world
to know you are involved in this case.
Do you find it
exciting and fun?
Do you know that
this case is complex and far-reaching?
Last night, you attracted assassins,
and tomorrow you could bring
disaster to your family.
You are so
passionate about solving the case,
but what about your family?
I didn't think that far.
I was wrong.
Now that it has come to this,
the Imperial Guard will enhance
protection for your safety.
As for your parents,
I'll deploy guardsmen to watch over them.
The case will be investigated by us.
Until the truth is revealed,
you'd better stay put.
Thanks, Lord Commander, I knew you
wouldn't leave me to fend for myself.
You have the order
from six years ago.
So what's your connection
to them?
So that everything I just said
was pointless, huh?
I'm just curious, you know.
Who are you, anyway?
That evidence was given to Lord Commander,
so why should I share it with you?
Show respect to my lord's wife!
Lord Commander,
you...
You're married?
Isn't it said that
all the women
who tried to marry him
would meet with misfortune?
How could this be?
Yunque always believed
that somehow,
he was waiting for me to marry him.
So all these years,
I've been diligently learning
how to manage household affairs,
how to be a good primary wife,
how to cook, keep accounts, and make beds.
Even in my dreams,
I've been thinking about marrying him.
You, you must be out of your mind!
My lady,
this has nothing to do with us!
It's...
It's this woman.
She cried out for justice on the street.
That's why my lord
brought her back.
What's there to misunderstand?
There are at least thousands of women
in Xiang'an
who admire Lord Commander.
That's quite normal.
Besides,
we are fa...
If you happen to find your ideal partner,
that's a good thing.
It seems you've made your decision.
So what are you
planning to do next?
At Chen Shoujie's residence,
I've only found
a piece of fabric from the workshop.
I still need to confirm
which year's pattern it was.
Changing the subject.
Very well.