[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP17]
Just sit back and listen quietly.
Don't create any disturbances.
Or, you'll face charges of
disrupting the proceedings.
That's quite a chilling warning.
But let's be honest here,
[although Ji Fangming]
[is minor in his position,]
he's still an appointed official by
the emperor's decree.
If you intend to coerce a confession,
I certainly won't turn a blind eye.
Ji Fangming!
No matter how many
elaborate tricks you have,
they can't
change the truth.
You've been scheming for years,
isn't it all just to uncover
the truth behind the
Jinxiu Shop incident?
[Regrettably,]
you ended up killing the wrong person
and seeking revenge on the wrong target.
You're manipulated without knowing it.
Ma'am, spare me your theatrics.
Trying to trick a suspect into confessing,
[that tactic is]
[hardly groundbreaking.]
Since you're all eager,
I'll lay out the truth for you.
Chen Shoujie and his wife
[were the true instigators behind it all.]
Everything that has unfolded recently
is entirely my doing.
To seek vengeance for the lives
unjustly lost in the
Jinxiu Shop incident.
What makes you so sure
that your knowledge
encompasses the entire truth?
Lady Chen was originally
an embroiderer at the Shop.
To shield her, Chen Shoujie
manipulated the investigation
to erase her origins.
[He altered the testimonies of others.]
[Kong Xianrong]
[personally inspected the summer garments]
before they were delivered to
the princess' residence.
[He verified them against the work]
[before sealing them away.]
Thus,
the swap could only have happened
during the interaction
with the embroiderers.
[Following the incident,]
everyone at the Shop
was detained and interrogated,
yet only his wife
[managed to evade capture.]
Once I uncovered the truth,
I approached him to test his reactions.
Shoujie,
do you recall this item?
Jinxiu Shop...
No...
You must not...
To live...
I was wrong.
We were wrong...
We're completely unaware.
Revenge has its source...
Please, don't
come after us!
My love,
we can't say a word.
[So,]
you're absolutely convinced
that Chen Shoujie is the murderer.
Do you understand why
he's so fearful of these illusions?
[Because he knew]
[that many lives were unjustly taken.]
He feared vengeful spirits!
He carried
guilt!
In this world, there are no ghosts.
If there are indeed ghosts,
they exist solely within the hearts.
If your conscience is clear,
why should you fear
the arrival of these spirits?
[Lord Shen is indeed honorable.]
But not everyone is the same
as you describe.
Someone,
even after committing heinous acts,
will still don a facade
of righteousness,
[blending in with the masses.]
[Then,]
we can't discern evil from good.
So,
you took the step to kill Lady Chen.
That's true.
She deserved her fate!
[She was the true mastermind.]
[She's the one]
who tampered with the summer
designs.
This is for Jinxiu Shop!
I knew this day would come.
Any last words?
Time to repay my debt.
I killed her.
It was merely to bring solace
to my friend's spirit in the afterlife.
What's wrong with that?
Even the most unforgivable individuals
should face the law's judgment.
If necessary, you can call
for seeking justice.
But unauthorized killing
is fundamentally wrong!
That's easy for you to say.
[What?]
[Seeking justice?]
Who doesn't know
that this is a wrong trial?
But who is willing
to speak the truth in so many years?
Let's focus on...
you!
[You hold a crucial position,]
[trusted by the Great Grandmother.]
[You've allowed this case]
to be buried for so long
and have never taken a stand.
In that case,
I might as well
take care of them myself.
After you killed Lady Chen,
[you deliberately left]
[the mentally disturbed Chen Shoujie alive,]
not out of friendship,
but to torment him.
Is that correct?
Yes.
His wife is indeed the true culprit.
She's doomed.
[As for Chen Shoujie,]
[I don't kill him]
not because I lack the desire.
He sheltered the real murderer.
He's culpable!
Killing him
would be far too merciful.
[I just had a thought]
to use a different method
to torment him to death.
Let him truly experience
the helplessness and
despair of losing loved ones
and friends
in a wrongful conviction!
[Xianrong,]
[I have finally]
[brought justice for you all.]
These individuals
should suffer for all eternity,
with no chance of rebirth.
[But now,]
he has lost his sanity,
and you still
choose to believe
that he is innocent.
You simply refuse to accept the truth
that it was a wrongful conviction.
Thus,
you are also guilty!
You all
should pay for your sins!
[What fire moth?]
[Fire moth, fire moth!]
This was discovered at
Chen Shoujie's residence,
belonging to Jinxiu Shop.
If they truly are
the instigators you speak of,
then why
have the kept the very item that
reminds them
of their crimes?
This isn't right.
Perhaps those who feel
helpless and tormented by the events
of that year are not limited to you.
This isn't right.
I am absolutely certain of it.
Perhaps you were solely seeking revenge,
but you haven't realized that
what Lady Chen gazed upon until her
last breath was that hidden compartment
in the beam where the cloth was concealed.
[Perhaps she wanted to speak,]
but she never had the chance.
It was all my fault.
It was entirely my fault.
I shouldn't have kept
the truth hidden for so many years.
I was scared to death.
[In my attempt to protect my family,]
I ended up causing harm to so many.
I deserve to pay for this!
The truth can't be concealed forever.
The truth will soon be laid bare
for all to see.
Mr. Kong,
I owe you an apology.
It was my fear of death
that led me to be coerced
into hastily closing the case.
[I never anticipated,]
[I never anticipate...]
Coerced?
Who was it that coerced you?
You must tell me!
What good is it to admit your mistakes?
So many innocent lives were lost.
Many wronged souls
are unable to find peace.
[As a public official,]
[you feared the true culprit]
[and chose to cover up the truth.]
Even if you admit your mistakes now,
can those people
ever return to life?
Who was it that coerced you?
Fire moth, fire moth!
[Chen Huo'e, Chen Huo'e!]
Chen Huo'e, Chen Huo'e!
Chen Huo'e again?
[This is impossible!]
I didn't kill the wrong person.
She was the true murderer.
She wouldn't trick me.
Then who instructed you
to lure Yan Xing to Mingsheng Temple?
I was truly manipulated...
I was being used...
All that laugh,
like moths drawn to the flame.
But they do not realize
that like mayflies, fleeting in life,
they do not enter the cycle of reincarnation.
Moths that brave the fire do not perish,
but are reborn anew.
Ji Fangming, get a hold of yourself!
Kong Xianrong cried for justice till his last gasp.
He sought innocence,
a revelation of truth.
Yet you've been blinded by hatred,
[manipulated by others to commit murder.]
How is this any different from
those who framed
the Jinxiu Shop?
[Now that the evidence is irrefutable,]
you still stand here spreading falsehoods.
Lord Shen,
Chen Huo has returned from the dead,
and exposed the other perpetrators
in the case to me.
Don't you want to know who they are?
The true perpetrator is
Princess Ying!
[She's envious of the capable,]
[and has long harbored resentment]
[towards Princess Runing.]
[She exploited the Jinxiu Shop]
[to frame Princess Runing for treason.]
Be quiet!
Not just her,
but also Prince Xian!
He refuses to be subservient to
[Princess Ying, plotting to seize power]
[and eliminate rivals!]
And also,
the Great Grandmother!
They are all murderers!
Each one of you
[is culpable in this crime!]
You are slandering the royal family,
defaming Her Royal Highness.
You simply want to create a scene
to reopen this case.
Lord Shen!
this matter is serious, indeed!
Reopening the case involves many parties.
Do not bring trouble upon yourself.
Just disregard this madman's rants.
Ignore them,
ignore them!
Wu Taiming,
you wretched dog!
I am not insane.
I am
perfectly lucid.
[Every word I speak comes from the heart.]
I wonder if Lord Shen
dares to report my words
exactly as I said
to the Great Grandmother!
You truly seem to wish
for a quick death.
If my death
could appease those spirits
in heaven,
then it's worth it.
If so,
I will do as you wish.
Regarding today's interrogation,
I will report truthfully to
Her Royal Highness.
Lord Lai,
what are your thoughts?
Lord Shen is the presiding judge,
the Imperial Inspectorate
is merely here to observe
the case of the murder.
[How the Imperial Guard decides]
is entirely up to you.
One stays detached,
the other is crafty.
[Each of them keeps their hands clean.]
I, Ji Fangming, expresses gratitude to
Lord Shen for the unjustly slain people
from the Jinxiu Incident.
Today, I have witnessed
the cleverness and courage of
Secretary Yan.
I wonder if you'd be interested in working
with me at the Imperial Inspectorate.
I am in need of
capable minds like you.
Lord Wu
wouldn't be so petty
[as to hold onto talent, would you?]
Lord Lai, you are just making fun of me.
[Though]
[Yan Xing works for Ministry of Justice,]
she is also the wife of
Lord Shen of the Imperial Guard.
Lord Lai,
you're not planning to recruit my wife
right in front of me, are you?
Apologies, Lord Shen.
I seem to be
a bit abrupt and inconsiderate.
I merely wanted
to recruit some talent for my own office.
You seem to be overly concerned.
Overly concerned?
After all these years,
Lord Lai,
your ability to retaliate
hasn't changed at all.
In official matters,
family should remain separate.
With Lord Shen's approach,
I'm afraid that Secretary Yan
spends every day with you solving cases,
and it wouldn't be pleasant for her.
Moreover,
[allow the best to be chosen,]
[and don't block their way to success,]
She has great prospects ahead.
You shouldn't stand in her way.
I'm quite comfortable
where I am now.
[I'm the kind of girl]
[who enjoys comfort and laziness,]
and I'm not quite ready to change places.
Gratitude, Lord Lai
for your concern.
If so,
I will wait and see.
Let's see how good
your choice is.
It's said that husband and wife are birds
of the same woods, yet when the storm comes,
each takes to the wing alone.
Lord Wu,
what are your thoughts?
Er...
I must admit, I'm rather dull-witted,
[and I struggle to grasp]
[the intricacies of love.]
[I truly cannot comprehend.]
What a fitting phrase.
Quite intriguing.
[this matter is serious, indeed serious.]
[Reopening the case involves many parties.]
[Do not bring trouble upon yourself.]
[How the Imperial Guard decides]
[is entirely up to you.]
What's on your mind?
You seem lost in thought.
I'm feeling quite exhausted.
I really need to take a proper rest.
Is something amiss?
Yun Que seems particularly
invested in this interrogation.
The case of the Jinxiu Shop,
she came here specifically for this.
Now,
she can no longer contain herself.
So,
you intentionally kept her in here
to determine
whether her presence was mere coincidence
or if someone was manipulating
events from behind the scenes.
Jing Lin has looked into her,
and she genuinely doesn't
know much.
However...
What?
Well, her parents
had significant business dealings
with the Jinxiu Shop back in the day.
Yet they were not implicated.
If they hid evidence for
self-preservation,
then why,
after Chen Huo'e appeared,
did she steal evidence to seek justice?
Isn't that a bit too coincidental?
If so,
why don't you just
ask them directly?
It's not a good time.
And it wouldn't be easy to
ensure their safety to testify.
Our actions are visible, but
our enemies operate from the obscurity.
Just leave it
all to me.
However,
it involves many parties.
Even Wu Taiming and Lai Luozhi
are eager to distance themselves.
It seems the truth
is far beyond my expectations.
It might be even more complicated.
I didn't expect
that the fearless Yan Xing
to have her fair share of fear.
Do you truly
intend to report
Ji Fangming's
heretical words?
Regarding the case,
I made a promise to someone
to investigate it personally.
Someone?
Would that be Princess Runing?
Ignorance brings no fear,
but knowledge brings deep fear.
I've come to understand
the difference in our courage.
You anticipated this day long ago,
yet you remain so calm.
This doesn't sound like
the usual you.
If you had heard of
a wrongful conviction,
you would have jumped up to investigate.
No one could stop you.
That's for sure.
Injustice must be addressed.
Grievance must be voiced.
That's what it means to be an official.
That's how we live up to our wage.
However,
I also understand
what it means to
reopen the case.
By his testimonies alone,
I'm afraid...
You are becoming wiser.
This wrongful case
caused quite a stir.
It continues to haunt
numerous people.
[With the reopening of the case,]
the shadows of the past
will inevitably resurface.
And then,
no one will be able to escape its grasp.
That's absolutely true.
They intend to use him
to draw public attention to
the Jinxiu Shop case, thereby
casting suspicion on the royal family
and inciting unrest.
Ultimately,
he should come to realize
that he was being manipulated.
Yet he had no other options.
How tragic.
And pathetic.
What's your level of confidence
in the Jinxiu Shop case?
That's precisely why I'm concerned.
It has been closed for years.
If you bring it up to Her Royal Highness,
and she refuses to reopen it,
that's just one issue.
If she were to take her anger out on you,
that would be...
So after leaving the Ministry of Justice,
you've been anxious all along.
You're worried about me.
I didn't!
[I'm worried you'll involve me in this.]
After all,
I currently hold
the title of primary wife
in Shen residence.
I have to take the safety
of everyone in Shen residence
into account.
[Every party's position is quite difficult.]
The wronged wish to reopen the case,
while Her Royal Highness seeks only
peace in the realm
and the well-being of the people.
What about you?
Don't worry about me.
Just leave it
to me.
No, I didn't.
Then I'll leave her
to you, my dear.
Since you know she's trouble,
why do you still keep her around?
She might possess
another crucial evidence.
So that is your reasoning, huh?
White Death truly is cold-hearted,
only bringing more trouble.
So,
Jing Lin,
you should keep tabs on Yun Que.
If the opportunity arises,
you should
see if she is still concealing anything
about the Jinxiu Shop case.
Understood.
Could you abduct someone for me?
Not actually abducting someone.
I just need you
to make a trip to Jiangnan
and safely escort him to Xiang'an.
Jiangnan?
Isn't Yun Que, who is currently living in
your residence and competing with you
for the title of wife, also from Jiangnan?
Are you a bit jealous?
And...
Pretty, please!
C'mon, please!
Chichi...
it's something only you can help me with.
I'm counting on you!
It's not a huge deal,
just a bit
of legwork.
You can count on me.
When you return,
I'll definitely treat you to a lavish meal
and offer you some fine brews.
And I can tell that
you're not just an ordinary merchant.
But I assure you, I won't expose you
or cause you any trouble.
Are you trying to threaten me?
Absolutely not!
How could I dare?
After all, we
are friends who support each other.
Just friends, huh?
What did you say?
Nothing.
Then I'll be waiting for your treat.
By the way.
Here.
Take this with you
along the way.
What's this?
These are the names of the victims
that Chen Huo'e murdered back then.
This is...
About those that have been crossed out
the crime scenes are all located near
Xiang'an, or in close proximity.
There are a few places you'll pass by,
so you might as well investigate
the circumstances of the deceased.
Trying to snag a free meal from you
is quite the challenge.
By the way,
here,
take this with you.
I just acquired it.
What do I need a fan for?
Are there some hidden tricks?
You should be cautious.
This has a mechanism.
The handle is hollow,
and it can hold powder inside.
Just a gentle sprinkle,
and you can discreetly
disperse the powder.
The handle is hollow...
Is this for poisoning?
Not quite.
The so-called hidden weapons
depend on the user
and the context of its use.
You're giving me such a unique item?
Are you...
Are you planning to use it to extort me?
Just hold onto it for now.
If you find it useful,
you can always pay me later.
Isn't that still a form of extortion?
Does it contain poison?
Not that it would be lethal,
but it could easily
put a cow to sleep.
[Have you all heard?]
[The ruins of the Jinxiu Shop]
[have shown miracles again.]
[Really?]
[A swarm of moths is flying into the walls,]
[their blood forming characters.]
[These flying insects]
[are crying out for justice.]
The resurrected Chen Huo'e...
So eerie.
Is seeking revenge on the true culprit.
[That incident]
[happened years ago.]
[Why is it suddenly like this?]
[Haven't you heard?]
Someone died because of the
[Jinxiu Shop incident again.]
[This has caused unrest among the people.]
This must be a wrongful conviction.
So many died tragically back then,
and they haven't been vindicated.
[That's why they linger in this world.]
These vengeful spirits
won't just randomly take a life, right?
We are all innocent, after all.
I've heard
[that only by reopening this case]
[and delivering justice to the deceased]
[can these vengeful spirits]
[finally find peace.]
Why aren't you eating?
Dig in, or the noodles will clump.
You came back so late.
You ate outside, right?
Of course.
No matter how tough or tiring it gets,
I won't let my belly suffer.
I've been quite busy
these past few days,
and it's really worn me out.
Eat!
Let me tell you,
I investigated the workshop tonight,
and I saw what looked like ghostly lights
floating in the air.
There was something drifting around,
but I couldn't see them clearly.
This must be
what the common people refer to as
ghostly shadows.
On my way back,
I noticed that
that every household along the street
near the Jinxiu Shop
had hung these fire moth jades
at their doors.
Investigating alone at night,
don't you find it eerie?
Those are all mere illusions.
It must be that so-called
reborn Chen Huo'e
causing all this stir.
As for ghostly lights,
I often
see them in graveyards during summer.
My master once told me
that they appear after a body decays,
due to some
undetectable substance
being ignited
in the dry air.
The method of ghostly shadows
should be quite similar.
It's just a quick-moving
shadow of a black bird.
I knew it.
You seem to know all this.
Were you doing this on purpose?
The Jinxiu Shop
should have been guarded by
the guardsmen from the Imperial Guard.
But this afternoon,
when the moths flew into the walls,
showing what they call a miracle,
they didn't drive the people away.
Jing Lin was clearly nearby,
but he just watched from a distance.
So?
The IG has a lot on the plate.
Ji Fangming has already been apprehended.
There's no need to worry about those.
Aren't you the one waiting?
Waiting for what?
Waiting for some
wind that could help reopen
the Jinxiu Shop case.
You only went out for a bit,
and ended up with an extra item.
Be careful with it.
Don't fool around with it.
Careful.
Why so tense?
Who gave it to you?
I still haven't paid
for this fan yet.
Don't break it.
Is that so?
Why have you been
acting so strangely lately?
Really?
Yes.
If the medicinal dishes
are not prepared in the future,
you must eat on time.
Don't skip meals.
And also,
you must not say
something weird all of a sudden,
and then
act all scary.
And you must not suddenly...
Suddenly what?
Just suddenly...
No wasting food.
Alright.
Deal.
But in the future,
you must not engage in
dangerous activities like
investigating at night.
Fortunately, tonight I had people arranged
to keep watch around.
Or else...
You really don't take your life seriously.
Just this time, I'll let you off the hook.
I won't allow it in the future.
[What's going on?]
[I feel so dizzy.]
[No way.]
[Pan Chi!]
[I'm totally screwed because of you.]
Yan Xing!
Put a cow to sleep...
What the...
Smells so good.
You got all the good deals...
I'm not allowed to...
Not allowed to...
It seems I should be the one
to pay for this fan.
Let her sleep peacefully,
no need to wake her.
Yes, my lord.
[Ji Fangming is quite the character.]
Not only has he shown disrespect
by lacking the manners of a subject,
but he also dared to use the case
to frame Prince Xian and
Princess Ying.
[His crimes are unforgivable.]
Your Royal Highness,
[Ji Fangming's numerous evil deeds]
[make his death not worth mourning,]
yet there are puppeteers
in the shadows,
exploiting his fixations
to sow fear.
Who is behind this?
It's precisely the one who was arrested
and committed suicide five years ago,
the serial killer,
Chen Huo'e.
What?
A dead person
can still stir up trouble
in Xiang'an City?
I remember back then,
this case was investigated
by you personally, Lai Luozhi.
What on earth is going on?
Your Royal Highness,
back then, the case of Chen Huo'e
caused great panic among the people.
So I
publicly executed Chen Huo'e
after capturing her.
At that time,
half of the citizens of Xiang'an City
saw Chen Huoe
commit suicide in public.
In front of everyone,
her body was thrown into a mass grave.
It's just...
What?
It's just that Chen Huoe publicly stated
that she would come back to life.
So you mean
that she really has come back to life?
Recently,
there have indeed been rumors
saying that Chen Huoe has appeared,
[and there is a group of followers]
[who believe this one is the Chen Huoe]
[who committed suicide five years ago.]
But I believe
it's just that some people
are using this to create trouble
and incite the public.
My trusted officials,
Chen Huo'e has fabricated a divine sign,
[leading the populace to doubt]
[the fairness of a past case.]
The Imperial Guard has requested
that Chen Huoe and
the  Jinxiu Shop cases
should be combined and re-examined.
What are your thoughts on this?
Your Highness cares for the people deeply.
Now, Lord Shen
intends to re-examine this case.
I believe there's nothing wrong with that.
Lord Lai,
do you have any insights?
I believe that
the past case being suddenly brought up
may have hidden motives.
However,
whether the case will disturb
the peace of Xiang'an City
I dare not speculate.
Your Royal Highness,
I just pulled out the previous records
and after careful examination, I found
that there are still unresolved doubts.
Your Royal Highness has always been
perceptive and cares for the people.
I know this matter is difficult,
but I wouldn't dare to hold any details.
Your Royal Highness,
I believe
what Lord Shen stated makes sense.
If we can get to the bottom of this
and bring peace and comfort to the people,
it'd surely be in line with mother's wishes.
Moreover, it would reveal to the world
Your Highness' genuine concern for
easing the people's burdens.
What a "easing the people's burdens."
Lord Shen,
I will entrust this case
to you completely.
You must thoroughly investigate it.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
I'll not disappoint your expectations
and will capture the perpetrator soon.
What's your thought on Lord Shen
reinvestigating this case?
The incident back then
caused great panic among the people.
I shall take my leave.
Your Highness have never
interfered too much in court affairs.
This time, you might
have attracted attention.
Sir,
I didn't think too much this time.
I just wanted to see how Shen Du
would handle this case.
Back then, Princess Runing was
implicated in the Jinxiu Shop case.
There were already voices suspecting
that it was the work of Princess Ying
who was at odds with her.
Should this reexamination of the past case
genuinely uncover
a link to Princess Ying,
it would be a tremendous
advantage for us.
We can leverage their actions
to help us root out our enemy.
Sir, that's actually unnecessary.
I merely wish to
uncover the truth.