I won't work overtime today
Episode 7
Bright moon
Are you willing to stay with me for the rest of my life
If you live up to it
I will never give up
Bright moon
Didn't you always want to
Do you want me to accompany you to enjoy the moon
This evening
I'll accompany you, okay?
Really
Your Majesty, Your Majesty
Something went wrong
My concubine Zhao
Be uncomfortable
You are noisy and refusing to eat
Your Majesty
Stop making a fuss
I
I'm going to have a look
Emperor
Your Majesty, Your Majesty, please take a look
They exactly
Is it the same person
Empress
I didn't expect
You are a self-serving person
How can you be like this? How can you be so impressed with the world
I'm so disappointed by this
I've never felt
You are a self-serving person
People who like to bully others
Men or something
Everyone step aside
Getting into a career is the right way
Sister Jiao, you're here
I heard that Sister Zhao Ting resigned
It's okay to resign
Is it you
I don't bother to do this to her
I should be embarrassed
Have you stayed
Come on, everyone, please stop for a moment
Where's Director Wu
There is a very important thing
To announce
Team battle recruitment plan
Is it from your group
Which one of you brought it up
Director Wu, what do you mean
Mr. Li felt
This scheme is very creative
Very cost-effective and feasible
Sister Jiaojiao
Is it your plan
Sure enough
Li Su or
More inclined to go on dangerous roads
Director Wu actually
Director Wu
What about this idea
It was originally put forward by me
Then I'll write it for everyone
What about this project
Can it be approved by Mr. Li
It's really a great honor
Everyone's recent efforts
It's not in vain
Is it right
OK
Then you continue to lead them
Refine this scheme
Do a good job
You obviously wrote it
Why in his mouth
Become what he put forward
I asked you to write it
That scheme
Has nothing to do with him
Isn't this grabbing credit
It's too bullying
No way
I'm gonna fight for you
Go ahead
What do you do
Say it well if you have something to say
You shameless thing
Take the credit of my boss
If you don't talk nicely
What are you doing
-You piece of trash -You piece of trash
You piece of trash, I'll beat you to death
Beat you to death Beat you to death
All right, all right
What are you giggling at
Aren't you going to fight your life
A gentleman talks but doesn't do anything
Let me change the way
I'm going to find Director Wu
Don't worry about it. It's useless
In the workplace
The boss bullying the subordinate
There are plenty of them
That
Then let him
Steal the fruits of other people's labor
Keep squeezing you
Pattern determines the upper limit
The more short-sighted he is
The more you will suffer the consequences
My company
There's no room for such a person
YOUR COMPANY
How did this become
Your company
Sooner or later it will be mine
Not to mention
Who says I'm gonna put up with him
Last time you dared to do this
Someone who bullies me
Still kneeling in the cold palace
Sister, I found out
Every time you do this
When talking nonsense
That's when you're ready to make an enlarged move
Okay, Komatsu
Getting smarter
Fuck him
Let's go, Brother Kai
What time will I get off work
Let's go first
Chief inspector
Don't worry
I will definitely tomorrow
Send you the plan
No, isn't this working overtime
You can rest assured that I will do things
Okay, please go to bed early
Jiaojiao is still busy
Get things done tonight
Send it to me
Come on
I have something to do now. I'll leave first
That brother Kai
I keep having a problem that I don't quite understand
Can you
You have to learn if you have a problem
Solve it yourself first
If it doesn't work, Baidu first
Right
OK
You see how much I trust you
Such an important job
I'll leave it to you
You have to seize the opportunity
You get down a little bit
Go down
Shh
Such a huge office
I'm the only one working overtime
Come on, Brother Kai, work hard
That tonight
Be sure to get things done
Then send it to me first
No problem
Refuel
Bye
Bye bye bye bye
Walk slowly without sending off
Refuel
Finally finished writing
Just print it out
Come on, Brother Kai, work hard
Hello
Mr. Li
I don't drink porridge
Must drink
I know you don't like it
Something bland and tasteless
And always eat spicy and exciting food
Sometimes busy with work
Don't even eat a meal
This is too bad for your stomach
Must drink porridge
If you don't like it, you have to drink it quickly
Are you concerned about me
There is still time for stomach pain
Say so much
Drink quickly, I'm leaving
Get up quickly
Get up
Open your mouth
Hot
Are you feeling better
Does your stomach still hurt
You rub it yourself
No, I'm in too much pain
I can't rub it myself
It's all in the play
It looks good
Drink it yourself and drink two more sips
I'm leaving
Can
Will you stay with me a little longer
Forget it, it's getting late
You can go back first
Okay, I'll go back to the office and get my stuff
Can I work overtime in your office
Can
What are you busy with again
Work overtime so late
Make a plan How about you
The company is not now
Is it expanding
A lot of things
I need to handle it myself
Some are very urgent
Then remember to eat well
Listen to you
What's wrong
It's okay. Work hard
Yao shang me Yao shang me
Fuck me fuck me
Come
Fuck me
Come on, come on
What are you doing? Run away
Brother Kai
Brother Kai, please also have a look
Give me some guidance
Good
Wait till I'm done
Not finished
I'll watch it when I'm done
Go ahead
Thank you, Brother Kai
Does it look good
I think you could change the color
Change the color
Little plum to Concubine He
Please say hello
Xiao Li's father-in-law came this time
Is there anything to do
Return to the Empress's words
My lady heard that you
Written a good handwriting
So I'd like to ask you to help her
Copy a Buddhist scripture
Why didn't Concubine Zhao copy it herself?
Bold
Where did the dog minion come from
How dare you call out
My Empress's name is taboo
After all, he is from the inferior class
Just don't understand the rules
Father-in-law Xiao Li, please calm down
It's Little Songzi who's ignorant
Remove small pine nuts
Take over the Buddhist scriptures
You
Mother, please copy it quickly
My mother
But I want it tomorrow
Tomorrow
If you don't get it tomorrow
My empress may be angry
Then while waiting on the emperor
What did you say to the emperor
It's you who suffer
Thank you, Father-in-law Xiao Li
Walk slowly and don't send it off
Brother Kai, you have to report the plan
Use me to come with you
Your plan
There are still many problems
I'll have to help you later
Do it all over again
Where's the director's side
If there's anything I can do for you
Thank you, Brother Kai
Go ahead
I'm leaving first
The little girl is still too young
Li Jiakai
You really did this
Yes
Director Wu
Do you see what's wrong
I'm gonna take it right away and modify it
Well done, very thoughtful
I underestimated you before
No No No
Or thanks to
Director Wu's care and cultivation
I'll make you
Tell Mr. Li everything
This project
If it is officially implemented
Nine times out of ten
Will leave it to you
Seize the opportunity
Director Wu, don't worry
This time I
I promise to complete the task successfully
Don't worry
Director that
My relatives gave me
Two cans of tea were mailed
It tastes particularly good
I'll send it to you later
Don't do this
As long as you have the strength
The opportunity is yours
Okay, Director Wu
Then I will withdraw the director first
Go back and get busy
Good
Zhao Bin, did you copy all this
Return to the Queen Mother's words
These are all concubines
Personally copied
It's a good handwriting
Thank you Queen Mother for your praise
Why is the last sentence missing
Return to the Queen Mother's words
I think this should
It was when my sister was copying the scriptures
I think this last sentence
Is that the finishing touch of the whole story?
I want to paint this dragon with a bright stroke
I'll leave it to you to make up for it
Is Zhao Bin like this
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's how it works
Good
When I read Buddhist scriptures
I love this sentence best
Zhao Bin
You have a bit of wisdom
Inappropriate inappropriate
Queen Mother
Excuse me, what do you think
What's wrong with it
Your handwriting is beautiful
In one go
If I am rash
Plus the last stroke
That's not beautiful
Concubine Zhao, it's better for you to do it
Why haven't you started writing yet
I
Queen Mother
You must decide for me
What else do you have to say
Empress, it's her
She set me up on purpose
The Buddhist scripture is covered in her handwriting
She must have dropped the bag on purpose
Empress
You must decide for me
Concubine He has this matter
Please learn from the Queen Mother
The lettering on this Buddhist scripture
Not a concubine's font
I don't know why
My sister wants to say that about me
He Mingyue, you
This is clearly
Font for two people
You messed up the Ai family's birthday party
There is no sincerity in copying the scriptures
And slandered others and fooled the mourning family
Who gave you the courage
Someone drag her out
In limbo
Kaige Kaige
How about it? What did Director Wu say
Jiaojiao
You're still inexperienced
After Director Wu read it
Not quite satisfied
But it's okay
I turned back
Help you make another one
Let Director Wu again
Take another look
Thank you, Brother Kai
But
I'm pretty optimistic about you
Wait until I get promoted and raise
My position
Maybe it's you
Thank you, Brother Kai, come on
Refuel
Go ahead
Bye
After receiving credit, you still want to pretend to be a good person
That's all you want to get promoted
I hope Li Su won't disappoint me