[English subtitles are available]
[Melody of Golden Age]
[EP34]
Watch me.
Like this.
A little pinch.
It doesn't work, why?
Here.
Shen Du, look! It's snowing!
Come here.
Look.
It's finally
snowing.
Did I go too far
with Lord Zhang today?
You can't possibly
keep pretending forever,
acting like a spy for him.
Eventually, this will come to an end.
But today,
you brought up the Shens' case.
Did you uncover
anything new?
I did it on purpose,
just to test his reaction.
Now it seems
Lord Zhang definitely knows something.
These days,
all the clues are tangled and confusing,
and we still can't be entirely sure.
But one thing is clear,
that long before the Shens' incident,
there were multiple forces
beginning to plot behind the scenes.
I have a feeling.
What is it?
I was thinking,
the situation your father was in back then
is not too different from yours now.
I mean,
navigating among various fractions,
to stay impartial while keeping
dignity is no easy task.
A small misstep could lead to...
A fallen tree attracts many axes.
Staying true to yourself is right.
And it's also not wrong to avoid
bowing down to the powerful.
Shen Du.
Please keep doing what you do,
and pursue what you desire.
I will do my utmost
to help you uncover the truth,
and clear the name of the Shen Family.
Snow on the winter solstice
is a sign of a fruitful year ahead.
Lord Commander is nothing special.
Let's see
if you can catch me.
Poker face, poker face!
Come on!
Chui!
Hurry!
How are you? Are you cold?
Absolutely freezing!
Feeling any better?
What were you doing?
I went to buy you some treat.
[Try it.]
It's good.
Slow down.
Your cheeks are all puffed up.
It's good!
Let's build a snowman!
Does it look like you?
Not even close.
This one looks like you!
Not at all.
Yours doesn't look like me at all!
Mine looks like you!
Yours is so chubby!
Easy.
Chui!
Catch me if you can!
It's snowing, take this!
[My beloved,]
you've always loved the winter snow.
You once said,
that snow is the purest,
capable of covering all the
filth and ugliness.
My beloved,
how have I conducted
myself in your stead?
[Are you content?]
I am unaware of
any mistakes I may have made.
[When we]
reunite in
the netherworld,
will you blame me?
Your Highness!
The incense smoke
stung my eyes.
Why are you back?
Didn't I ask you to
take a break for the festival?
Wan is already
accustomed to handling daily affairs.
Now that I have time off,
[I find it quite boring.]
Wan finds this snowy night
to be quite dull and lonely,
so I invited Mr. Jin to join me,
[hoping to entertain]
[Your Highness.]
Girl...
I know
you must feel that I
am solitary and heartbroken,
so you intentionally find
comforting words to console me.
Your Highness,
I have just composed a new melody
[titled "Melancholy and Mirth."]
I wonder if Your Highness
would care to hear it?
Prepare a feast.
For today we shall
eat and drink heartily,
just like the ordinary households,
and celebrate the Winter Solstice
with warmth and joy!
Don't melt! Don't melt!
You are not allowed to melt!
No!
You are meant to be mine.
Mine!
I will not allow anyone
to snatch away what's meant for me!
Never!
Good.
Please.
Your Royal Highness,
Chancellor Lai requests an audience.
Summon him!
What brings him here
on such a snowy night?
Chancellor Lai,
[what could be so urgent]
that you've ventured out
on this snowy holiday eve?
Your Royal Highness,
I have just received an anonymous tip-off
stating that Yan Xing
was specifically arranged by Lord Zhang
to marry Lord Shen
[with the intention of winning him over.]
On the day of the winter solstice,
Lord Zhang even used the safety of the Yans
to coerce Yan Xing into compliance.
This is someone
trying to create trouble for no reason!
Does Yan Xing truly belong
to Prince Xian's faction?
[Your Highness,]
I'm afraid that
there may be some misunderstanding.
The tip-off also mentioned
[that originally, Your Highness]
[granted a marriage decree]
[to the third daughter of the Yan Family,]
[but the Yan Family, with ulterior motives,]
[switched her with Xing.]
Now this Yan Xing has been promoted
to Chief Clerk of the Ministry of Justice.
[It is evident that the Yans' intentions]
[in this are treacherous!]
[Could Yan Xing's allegiance]
truly lie with Prince Xian?
Your Highness,
[Jin Zang humbly speaks.]
The sixth daughter, Yan Xing
is my niece.
[She has always dreamed of dedicating]
[herself to the imperial court]
[as a female detective.]
[Despite an unexpected marriage]
to the Shen Family,
her loyalty and sincerity
remain untainted.
[Please see her true nature, Your Highness.]
Jin Zang,
you have been permitted to perform in
my chamber for many years.
Meddling in state affairs, a new boldness!
I wouldn't dare, Your Highness.
Lord Lai,
regarding Yan Xing,
is it worth your late-night visit?
If you have any more urgent matters,
speak them all out at once.
I have just learned that
in Xiang'an City,
a nursery rhyme has suddenly spread,
[and it sounds quite inappropriate.]
A nursery rhyme?
Red porridge and dates,
five feet from the heaven.
[Citruses and loquats,]
[hard for lad to grasp.]
[Do not speak recklessly.]
[Who says,]
[granny is angry,]
[salt rises.]
Lady Xu is clever and graceful,
and she has clearly identified
the issues within.
[It directly targets Your Highness,]
["five feet from the heaven."]
"Hard for lad to grasp."
This is a blatant disrespect
to both Your Highness and His Majesty!
Insolence!
Such a rhyme
could not have appeared without reason.
[There must be wicked schemers]
plotting behind the scenes.
I urge Your Highness to take action!
Can we uncover
who is spreading such slander?
It's challenging to trace the source,
as it circulates among the children.
After all these years...
I have dedicated myself
wholeheartedly to the Xiao Family's reign,
[yet there are always those who suspect]
I act out of selfish motives.
To exploit a nursery rhyme
to manipulate public sentiment
is truly despicable!
We'll launch a full-scale investigation
immediately to ensure that we
take down the mastermind!
But...
What?
However, the melody used in this rhyme
was composed by Mr. Jin
[for the winter solstice banquet]
[at Prince Xian's residence.]
This melody is
titled "Melancholy and Mirth."
Your Royal Highness,
this piece was created by me
to honor the Winter Solstice.
[It was indeed performed for the first time]
[during the feast at the prince's residence.]
[However, this piece has no lyrics,]
and certainly no disloyal intentions.
But if the player
[is unintentional,]
[what if the listener has ulterior motives?]
[That last line of the rhyme,]
"granny is angry,"
"salt rises."
the "salt (xian)" in this line
likely refers to Prince Xian!
Summon Prince Xian!
Mother!
I am unaware!
I am being wronged!
[Regarding "Melancholy and Mirth,"]
I first heard it
during the banquet.
I didn't pay much attention at the time,
and I had no idea
that someone would seize this opportunity
to add lyrics that allude to Your Highness!
I firmly believe
this is not the doing of Mr. Jin,
nor is it instigated by His Highness.
[However, this piece was]
[just performed at the prince's residence]
and immediately had rebellious lyrics
added, spreading through the streets.
Moreover,
the ending of this rhyme clearly implies
that His Highness seeks advancement.
I urge you, mother, to see clearly
that someone is trying to use this rhyme
to sow discord between us,
to undermine our mother-son bond,
and even to threaten my life!
Mother!
Your Royal Highness,
Wicked words poison the public.
[If we don't make a decisive action,]
[and it continues to spread,]
[it will at least tarnish the reputations]
[of His Highness and Mr. Jin.]
At worst, it could be interpreted by those
with ill intentions that His Highness
truly has disloyal intentions!
Please issue an immediate decree to
[allow me to arrest all those who attended]
[the banquet at the prince's residence]
for a thorough investigation!
This incident
was caused during the banquet
hosted by Prince Xian.
[Effective immediately,]
Xiao Zhong, the Prince Xian
is to be confined to the residence.
Jin Zang, who composed the music,
is to be detained by II for questioning.
The other musicians who performed
at the banquet, are to be thoroughly
[investigated by II!]
Understood!
My lord, my lady,
Lady Xu has sent a secret message.
What happened?
["The wind direction changed last night."]
["Be extremely cautious."]
["Do not let the Shen and Yan Families"]
["repeat the mistakes of the past."]
Help!
-Move!
-Help me!
My lord, save me!
Help me, my lord!
Hurry!
Find Xing, hurry!
And Lord Shen!
Go tell Xing
and Lord Shen!
-Hurry!
-You need to see them now!
[Go inform them!]
[Ask them to save me!]
Go tell Xing!
Hurry, hurry!
Shut the gate!
Get in!
Zang!
What happened?
Sister...
Zang,
exactly what is happening?
Move!
Zang!
Now!
No...
Don't resist!
-No...
-Go!
-Zang!
-Move!
Father!
What's happening?
How could mother be taken away?
Xing,
your mother has been taken by the
Imperial Inspectorate!
They claim your uncle, Jin Zang, is
involved in Prince Xian's conspiracy,
which endangers the entire family!
How could my uncle, a mere musician,
get involved in a conspiracy?
This is impossible!
This is a frame-up!
Xing,
calm down.
Although Madame Jin has been taken away,
the Yan Family
has not yet been implicated.
[For now, the Imperial Inspectorate]
[should not be giving you]
[any hard time.]
The Yan Family hasn't been implicated?
Father.
Even though mother's surname is Jin,
she has married into the Yan Family,
making her a Yan.
Even if it implicates
the Jins, it shouldn't involve her.
The Imperial Inspectorate has no reason
to take her away!
Those men from the Imperial Inspectorate
are just like demons from the underworld.
There's no reasoning with them.
If they want to arrest someone,
they just do it!
Wait!
It's not that they don't reason,
it's that you all
are simply too afraid to reason, right?
Father, my lady,
you let the Imperial Inspectorate
take mother away,
and you didn't even step up
to question
or intervene,
did you?
Fine!
You all fear the Dark Demon,
but I do not!
I will save her then!
Xing!
[Xing!]
Chui?
I finally found you!
Your Lord Shen
sent a message from the palace
through Jing Lin, saying he will
meet with Her Highness
to plead for the Jin Family.
I split up with poker face to find you.
I knew you must
have returned to the Yan residence.
Chui,
thank you!
But this involves Prince Xian,
so the future is uncertain.
Shen Du's help may not be enough.
You should go back,
and I will go talk to Lord Zhang.
Alright.
Be careful!
Poker face, is that you?
[Lai Luozhi...]
Seeing that it's me,
are you disappointed?
I...
I'm expecting Jiang Langxing;
and he will be here shortly.
Jiang Langxing.
Has he become the sole
focus of your attention?
How good it is when
you're so obedient!
Chief Clerk of the Ministry of Justice,
Yan Xing, requests to see Lord Zhang!
Lady Yan,
Lord Zhang is not in the residence today.
After asking around, I've learned
that Lord Zhang has been avoiding visitors
ever since the Prince Xian incident.
He didn't attend the assembly today.
Chief Clerk of the Ministry of Justice,
Primary wife of Lord Shen,
the sixth daughter of Erudite, Yan Xing,
requests to see Lord Zhang!
Lady Yan,
please don't make it difficult for us.
I'm not making it difficult for you.
I'll just stand here and wait.
I can stand here for a day or two.
He will eventually come out, right?
He wouldn't
avoid me, a woman,
by sneaking out the back door, or even
crawling through a dog hole, would he?
I knew it.
You, Yan Xing,
are not easy to deal with.
If I don't come out,
are you really going to turn
my residence upside down?
I plead with Lord Zhang to save the Jins!
You don't need to plead with me.
As for this matter,
I cannot help you with it.
Lord Zhang,
you are the Prime Minister,
the head of the state.
The Jins have clearly been wronged;
you cannot ignore this!
Since you have
Her Royal Highness' token,
why did you come to me
instead of going directly to her?
In front of Her Royal Highness,
I am merely an insignificant official
who can chat about trivial matters.
If I mistakenly believe
I can meddle in state affairs,
that would be overestimating myself.
Since you understand this,
why can't you see the reason
Lai Luozhi is using
Mr. Jin as a scapegoat?
Because of me?
The cause of all this
is that you are Shen Du's wife,
[and you are also the one]
[who stirs up trouble everywhere,]
Chief Clerk, Yan Xing.
Of course,
it's not just that.
It is said that
on the night of the winter solstice,
[Lai Luozhi]
[reported to Her Royal Highness, saying]
you were sent to the Shen residence by me
with the intention of winning over Shen Du
and forming factions for personal gain.
[Mr. Jin had the audacity to]
speak out in court, even challenging
the authority of Her Highness!
My uncle
argued with Her Highness
for my sake?
According to our imperial laws,
royal servants and musicians are strictly
forbidden from meddling in state affairs.
[Those who defy face the death penalty.]
Jin Zang
relying on his favor, has become arrogant
and overestimates himself.
My uncle wasn't being arrogant.
nor was he overestimating himself.
He acts out of genuine concern for me,
seeing me as his own flesh and blood.
Even at the risk of his own life,
he wouldn't want to see me suffer!
Xing,
I have often relied on the Yan Family
more than I have cared
for you over the years.
Regarding this matter,
this is about all that I can offer.
When it comes to protecting Prince Xian
and the Jin Family,
I find myself with no choice.
Back then,
regarding the case of the Shen Family,
was it the same kind of choice
you were presented with?
My lord.
Prince Xian has been confined this time,
yet I have chosen to remain silent.
Do you know why?
I don't know.
Prince Xian has grown up under my care.
My feelings for him
are akin to Jin Zang's
for Yan Xing.
How could I not wish to dedicate every
last bit of my strength for his sake?
As for this nursery rhyme calamity,
I am fully aware of the situation.
He does not
harbor any intentions of usurpation.
Her Highness is also aware of it for sure.
But Her Highness
is not merely a mother.
She is also the
Empress Dowager of our empire.
If I were to intervene,
my students and colleagues
would all follow suit,
petitioning Her Highness
to release Prince Xian.
The chorus of voices only
pushes Prince Xian closer to ruin.
Chui!
What's wrong? Why the urgency?
Has Chui returned?
Didn't she go out
with you earlier?
I split up with her to look for Yan Xing.
Has she not come back yet?
It's possible that after
finding Lady Yan,
they went off to have some fun elsewhere.
Here,
just ask Lady Yan
and you'll find out!
Alright!
You go ask...
What are you talking about?
Stop bothering her!
What do you mean, my lord?
Lady Yan...
Something serious happened to her family.
You didn't know?
The Jins have been suspected
of inciting Prince Xian to rebel,
and the II has rounded them all up.
By the way,
even if something major happens,
don't bother Lady Yan.
You're right, Lord Wu.
I'll go find her myself.
Farewell!
Watch your step!
What is this place?
Everyone calls me the Dark Demon.
So perhaps,
this is the underworld.
What do you want?
Are you going to kill me?
The eighteen layers of hell
are reserved for others.
As for you,
even if one day
you truly end up in the underworld,
I'll use the bones as the lamp,
and offer evil spirits as sacrifice,
to illuminate the King Hall of Hell
and transform it into
a paradise for you.
There's no way to escape.
What's got you so scared?
I...
will not hurt you at all.
Chui.
Raise your head.
Look around you.
What do you think?
Do you like these?
What... is...
Word has it that you're
quite content with the wedding gifts
Jiang Langxing sent.
So these are the things you like.
I bought everything that girls adore
from the market in Xiang'an,
[as well as all the wedding gifts]
[that wealthy families]
use for betrothal.
What do you think?
What exactly do you want?
I'm here to propose!
Propose?
I'm asking for your hand in marriage.
May you agree to be my wife.
What are you talking about?
I'm already engaged to Jiang Langxing!
I'm going to marry him!
That rigid delinquent,
what's so special about him?
What he offers,
I can give you ten times more.
[This isn't about that.]
I've already promised to marry him.
What's so significant about a promise?
Even if you are wed, you can still divorce.
If you feel guilty towards him,
I can make it up to him for you.
As long as he likes,
I could take out Xu Xiangren
and make him the Chief Inspector.
Don't pull any mad stunts!
Alright.
I'll do as you say.
Why can't you see?
Jiang Langxing and I
have genuine feelings for each other.
We have feelings for each other too!
I like you a lot!
I've never cared for a woman
as deeply as I care for you!
But I don't like you!
That's a lie!
You clearly have feelings for me too!
Didn't you call me maskman
and treat me like a close friend?
Also...
Our mothers
are buried in the same spot.
This is destiny for sure!
The affection between friends
is different from
that of lovers.
I have no such feelings for you!
That's not possible!
It won't be long before
you realize I'm right.
Let go of me!
It's alright.
I'm willing to wait;
eventually,
you'll fall in love with me.
Stop right there!
[The case of Jin Family's usurpation is]
entirely under the jurisdiction of Il.
The Ministry of Justice can't interfere.
[Lady Yan,]
[please leave.]
Hold on.
Greetings, my lord.
[Lady Yan,]
[if you want to save your family,]
[it's actually quite simple.]
You just need to submit a petition
[stating that the Jin Family]
was falsely accused by Shen Du.
Then I can help you overturn the case
and rescue your family.
Lord Lai,
you're deliberately teasing me.
I won't betray my husband
with false charges.
I didn't realize
that the former spy
who married into the Shen Family
[would now be so deeply]
in love with Shen Du.
Lord Lai,
there's no need to
use my past as leverage.
[Regarding this,]
[I have already explained everything to]
[my husband and Lord Zhang.]
My conscience is clear
and have not
wronged anyone.
[I have been diligent in my duties]
[at the Ministry of Justice,]
committed to uncovering the truth
and clearing the names of the wronged.
Not to mention that Shen Du is my husband,
even if it were anyone else,
I, Yan Xing,
would never do anything
to tarnish my reputation
as a Ministry of Justice official!
Lady Yan, there's no need to be stubborn.
[One day,]
you will yield to me.
Lady Yan,
please leave.
Please!
Xing.
Welcome back.
Xing,
Her Royal Highness hasn't budged.
I will think of another way.
I already foresaw it.
I went to see Lord Zhang today
and gained some insight
into Her Royal Highness' difficulties.
Even though I don't attend the assembly,
I could envision the situation back then.
If Lai Luozhi succeeds
in framing Prince Xian
with these accusations,
it wouldn't just mean
the annihilation of the Jin Family,
but a complete upheaval in the court.
There would be fierce power struggles.
I can't imagine how many families
would face destruction...
I will find another way.
Tomorrow, the Jin Family
will be put on public display
by the Imperial Inspectorate.
After that, there may still be hope.