[English subtitles are available]
[Just in Time]
[EP02]
Have you decided to confess to me?
About what?
So you know all this?
I was planning to confess everything.
You'd receive a lighter sentence.
I see.
Actually,
I was planning to be honest,
but I didn't find a chance.
Until this morning
when I heard that career course,
I was very touched,
and they were quite right.
The competition within the industry
is too fierce now,
so I plan to
go on a business trip to Beijing.
Who will you meet with?
Just a conference within the industry.
I'm not going to see someone.
It's beneficial for me
to expand my network
by meeting
more people, right?
Just a conference?
This is the invitation letter.
Take a look.
[You were right.]
I'm not trying hard enough.
I'm in my forties now,
and I can't go on like this anymore.
At this moment,
I should roll up my sleeves
and work hard.
Why didn't I hear that
you were going to attend
a conference before?
I just
didn't understand this before
and wasn't proactive about it.
I mean...
It's okay not to go to this conference.
There are many other ways.
Let me think about it.
I'll come up with a plan.
Oh, you have to think carefully.
Deliberately concealing
and refusing to confess
can have serious consequences.
Darling,
as for my job...
What's wrong with your job?
Is there a problem?
Did you fight with a colleague?
No.
Have you been criticized by your boss?
Not at all.
Really?
Yeah.
The job's going well.
What are you worried about?
Yeah,
I don't need to worry.
Nothing.
It's okay.
Go to sleep.
Well,
okay,
it's time for bed.
Good night.
This week,
[the Career Promotion Course]
produced by Content Department,
led by Professor Shang,
has been officially launched.
It is worth celebrating that
we sold over 7000 classes
within 48 hours of our launch,
and the development costs
have been recouped.
This afternoon,
we will have a live broadcast
with Professor Shang
to sell courses online
and strive to achieve
our profit goals.
Guys,
you should learn from Meng'an.
We all know
the current situation of the company,
so I won't say much about it.
Projects like this,
with low investment
and short monetization cycle,
are worth promoting.
I think this kind of project
is worth continuing.
So we have started preparing for
the online teaching content
for the next quarter.
I'll make appropriate arrangements
regarding manpower.
Let's call it a day.
Li Yunjie!
What?
Excuse me.
Stop!
[You are the best]
[in my heart!]
[Stop! I am not!]
She's running away.
Hello, Ms. Xue?
Ms. Xu,
are you free now?
Can you come to school?
Now?
Is it about the advances to her?
Yunjie's father is responsible for
her daily affairs.
But I think
we still need to
communicate with you about this.
After all, she's a girl.
Oh, I see.
I'll go over now.
What's the fuss for?
Mu?
I have something to go out for.
Please pay attention to
Professor Shang's live lecture
this afternoon.
Sure.
Li Yunjie?
I'm sorry,
I'm just too excited to win.
I'm sorry to
have implicated you.
Can you not show off?
OK.
Since you don't like this way,
next time
I'll try a different way.
Save it.
Can you stop doing stupid things?
No wonder people say
you have more brawn than brain.
They were jealous of me!
I won the championship this time,
and I can choose
any high school in the city.
Which one you want to go to?
I want...
I would choose the same one as you.
Why on earth do you like me?
I can make changes.
How can you say that?
Sorry,
please go on.
I've figured out the situation.
[Liu Siming just]
[transferred here not long ago]
[and hasn't adapted to]
[our learning pace yet.]
But
as a student
still in junior high school,
he shouldn't do this
in public.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Please tell me it's an emergency.
[Indeed!]
Professor Shang's company has closed
and the phone cannot be answered.
Where is he?
Professor Shang?
[OK, listen,]
[I'm talking to Ms. Xue now,]
and I'll call you back later.
Sorry for that.
As elementary school classmates,
Liu Siming and Li Yunjie
have been close,
and Li Yunjie is quite helpful
and caring
to Liu Siming.
I'm not!
I didn't care about him,
nor did I help him.
Yunjie,
it's normal for classmates
to care about each other.
I really don't.
Mind your manners.
Ms. Xu,
Ms. Xue,
this is all my fault
[and has nothing to do with her.]
She bothers me,
really.
Maybe it's not true.
Ms. Xu,
are you busy now?
Now it's in silent mode.
Liu Siming,
you don't have to
[blame yourself for everything.]
The children in our class
are quite simple and positive.
[Siming and Yunjie]
[are both]
[good children,]
[however,]
[as students,]
[your only task at this stage]
is to study for the
high school entrance examination.
Right?
[Ms. Xu?]
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Right.
Yeah.
It's actually not a big deal.
Because of this incident,
the school asked me to
explain the situation to you.
You don't need to
care about that video either.
[Just]
[adjust your mindset,]
[focus on studying,]
and not be distracted
by other opinions.
We can rest assured that
the school is so strict
and responsible.
We are very assured.
Right.
Not quite.
Education requires
joint efforts
from parents and schools.
[In case of an accident,]
the school will be
held responsible.
Got an emergency.
One minute, please.
OK.
One minute.
Hello?
If you can't find him,
just withdraw the plan first.
[Wait until I go back]
and don't call me again,
okay?
OK.
Well,
since both of you
are aware of the situation,
I won't
take up your time.
Alright.
The examination is approaching,
and studying is not
solely the responsibility of the child.
Parents should put in more effort
at home,
okay?
Sure.
Alright.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Is there a teacher
surnamed Shang here?
I have no idea.
I just praised you in the morning,
and in the afternoon came the seizure!
More than 7000 classes
worth over 2 million yuan,
what about the after-sales services?
What about compensation?
Who conducted the risk assessment?
Xu Meng'an!
Where is she?
Tell me!
She went to see Ms. Xue.
Who is this again?
It must be a substitute.
No wonder she is the director.
She must have anticipated that,
so she found a substitute in advance,
right, Mu?
Yes.
Don't cover for her.
Tell her to see me later.
Who is Ms. Xue?
[Your act today is not appropriate.]
[After all, the teacher is talking to you.]
It's inappropriate.
There is an emergency situation
at work.
Is that serious?
Nothing.
Well,
what did you think about
the teacher's conversation today?
It's not a big deal.
Someone likes my daughter,
which is good.
It shows that my daughter is excellent.
But puppy love is not allowed.
That's for sure.
I don't like him anyway.
He's not that outstanding.
Mainly because you're too young.
Yes.
I can't go home
for dinner tonight.
Why don't you go out with your dad?
My dad?
Didn't he go to Beijing?
When?
Don't you know?
Oh, maybe I forgot.
I'll go to my grandmother's house.
Sure.
OK.
I won't be going home tonight.
It's okay.
Send me a message
when you arrive.
OK.
I have to go.
Go ahead.
Bye, mom.
He Lu!
My mom didn't criticize me.
See?
Look how fast my mom runs.
Her physical fitness is good.
What did your mom say?
She told me
puppy love is not allowed.
Especially He Lu,
no puppy love!
Nonsense.
Yiduo,
it's been a long time.
Let's gather together
this time
and catch up.
Give me a chance.
Too straightforward
and impolite.
Yiduo.
No need to bow.
Whatever.
It's been a while.
Yeah.
The last time we met
was at the decade alumni association.
Oh, yeah.
It's been ten years.
Time flies.
How are you doing?
Everything's fine with me.
It's great that
we can meet together
and recall
the past.
Besides,
I actually want to...
How to put it?
Well,
let me see,
if you are...
I want to...
Mei Yiduo?
Do you remember me?
I'm Zhao.
Mr. Zhao, Mr. Jia.
Sure.
We met at a conference
in the US.
Yes.
That's right.
Yeah.
Please sit down.
OK.
Professor Mei,
with the current favorable
research environment at home,
have you ever considered
returning to your home country
for development?
[Oh, sure.]
Especially when I came back this time,
I found that
the research environment
is really good.
It seems that I really need to
plan carefully.
Let me introduce to you,
my senior schoolmate, Li Lin,
of the same industry.
I will have to rely on his care
if I want to return.
Nice to meet you.
Are you Li Lin?
The top student!
Yes.
I admired you very much
when I was in school.
Oh, I'm too flattered.
Li Lin,
you must attend
tonight's party.
Oh, I don't...
Lin.
Come together.
Come with us.
Let's exchange business cards.
Professor Mei,
the meeting is about to begin.
OK. Let's go.
Alright.
Come on, Lin.
OK.
Let's go.
Okay.
Ms. Mei,
nice to see you again.
It's really unlucky.
Many days of overtime have been in vain.
Stop complaining.
Lin,
have you finished the poster?
Why? It won't go online anyway.
Whatever. I won't do that.
I heard that our company
has recently laid off employees.
Since this project fails,
won't we all be laid off?
Mu?
Director Xu, you're back now.
Contact Mr. Zhang
from the plan B immediately.
If conditions permit,
please contact the legal department.
OK.
Liu,
I want to re-shoot
online paid content.
Put it online within 48 hours.
Communicate well with the lecturer.
In terms of content,
I want methods, not preaching.
OK.
Yu,
rewrite the promotion plan
and visual poster.
Just stick the face
of the teacher who is suitable.
Jiaojiao,
contact the after-sales services
and ask them to inform the customer,
our content needs to be
fully upgraded this time,
for free! Remember that!
OK.
Good.
Director Xu?
Mr. Zhang is
looking for you.
Mr. Zhang,
are you looking for me?
Can you still laugh?
Of course, I have to question you!
How's your conversation with Ms. Xue?
Oh, not bad.
Did she agree to be a substitute?
Substitute?
Rachel said you were
inviting her as a substitute!
Yes.
The conversation was good,
but it's not possible,
it's expensive.
You get what you pay for,
okay?
Cheapest is the dearest.
Isn't something wrong
with Professor Shang?
Is there a remedial plan?
It has already been arranged.
They are already on it
and put it online within 48 hours.
Listen,
keep the losses to a minimum!
Besides,
can we sue Shang
for compensation?
We need to consult to determine
if it is due to force majeure.
You don't need to do this!
I will go. Get out.
Then I'll go out.
Dad! Dad!
Hey, Dad!
Hello, my boy.
How are you doing today?
Are you happy?
He's my dad.
He came to pick me up.
Hello, I'm Xiongxiong's father.
We just moved here.
Your help would be appreciated.
My wife is Xu Mengxin.
Our family makes clothing.
This is a gift.
Here you are.
Don't mind.
I hope you will like it.
I'll treat you to dinner next time,
and let my wife treat you to tea.
Keep in touch and appreciate your help.
You just moved here?
Yes.
Baby,
are you happy spending alone outside
for the first time?
Yes!
But I'm a little worried.
Mom, don't worry.
We'll be as brave as
Elsa and Anna.
Great.
But at the training camp,
you have to listen to the teacher
and take care of each other.
Do you hear me?
♪Let it go, let it go.♪
♪Can't hold it back anymore.♪
Nice.
Dad is calling.
[Dad?]
[We're going to the training camp.]
We don't have to
stay at home tonight,
just like you.
[Enjoy yourselves.]
Take care.
Dad has work to do,
otherwise I would
go with you.
Tell mom to
bring me some
clean clothes later.
I have no clean clothes here,
and I have a dinner party tonight.
[Wanzhen, are you there?]
I heard you.
I will send you clothes
after sending them to the training camp.
[Enjoy yourselves.]
OK. Goodbye.
Bye.
I'll take a shower.
Baby?
Stay away!
Get out.
Hey, baby.
Leave me alone.
Babe.
I was wrong.
My baby is angry.
I'm sorry.
Baby, I shouldn't have scared you.
Sorry, baby.
Baby?
Don't be angry.
It's not worth getting angry.
Really.
Being angry is not good for your health.
I've taken care of everything.
I've taken care of all those moms.
They were shocked to hear about
the Mengxin brand.
Don't be angry,
I love you!
Don't be angry.
Don't touch me!
Baby.
I bought seafood
from Linhai.
Let's take Xiongxiong to
my parents' house
and enjoy it together,
especially you,
baby.
Look, look,
you look so beautiful wearing this.
Go get it.
Get ready to go.
Okay, okay,
I'll go take it, baby.
Visiting parents with seafood.
I'm so happy.
Let's go.
I'll do it.
Hold on.
It's okay.
Yu Hai?
Why so long for the clothes?
Well,
there's a traffic jam.
I brought them for you, hurry up.
It's too late.
Huang just
bought me a shirt,
otherwise I'll be late.
Go.
Your skirt is wrinkled.
I forgot the files.
Do you wanna cooperate with Yaohui Co.?
Yes.
I heard the manager
is quite impressive.
Zhou Yao from Yaohui Investments
is my former colleague,
him.
Really?
You've been at home for long,
and he may not even recognize you.
Help me
tidy up my things.
My underwear and panties
are all in the bathtub.
Sorry for that.
Nothing.
Thank you.
Wanzhen?
Zhou Yao?
Long time no see.
Exactly.
You...
Let me introduce,
Ms. Chen Wanzhen,
an outstanding financial talent
from my investment bank before.
Oh, please.
I've been out of this industry for long.
It's been seven or eight years.
I remember you quitted your job
as soon as you got married.
It's been eight years.
Look, I've become
a housewife.
Yeah, you chose family.
you were better than me
in projects before.
If you hadn't resigned,
you would have been my boss.
Oh, you are flattering me.
Wanzhen,
my business card.
I am starting my own business,
Yaohui Investments,
keep in touch with me.
I'm going to a meeting.
Nice to
meet you again.
See you.
Are you still angry?
Don't be angry.
You are so excellent,
you should get used to
others' pursuit of you.
I'm so annoyed.
It's embarrassing.
Don't be.
Just because of that video?
I think it's pretty good.
[Let me tell you,]
[if you have any troubles like this,]
[you can come to me.]
I used to be the school belle,
and I have
a lot of experience.
I know how to deal with it.
Auntie,
what was your attitude
towards being pursued?
I will thank him.
This is a recognition of me,
indicating that I am excellent enough
and worthy of being liked.
But
it's others' business
whether they like me
or pursue me.
I know in my heart
whether I like him or not,
and I won't force myself.
Look, in your case,
when others pursue you,
you accept it in your heart,
right?
But I believe
you would never
start a puppy love,
would you?
You know me the most.
I'm better than your mom, right?
Exactly!
My mom doesn't stay with me at all.
It's all my dad who does housework,
sends me to school,
cooks, and cleans.
When my mom comes back,
she thinks that she did everything,
and she works very hard.
Yes.
It's so typical of Xu Meng'an,
I told you.
Right?
She just
has an inexplicable desire
to control the people
around her.
Yes.
It's like the world
would collapse
without her.
Totally!
She's that kind of person.
Sister!
I bought delicious cakes.
They can bless you with a perfect score.
Thanks.
Come on.
Yunjie.
Grandpa, Grandma.
OK.
Eat slowly. Don't choke.
Sit down.
Take a rest.
Try it.
It can bless you with your grades.
Too much sugar.
Shall we go play for a while?
Cool.
We go out and play.
OK.
Go.
Help me open it.
Mom,
as you see,
can the baby
gets along well with Xiongxiong
like Xiongxiong
with Yunjie
after it's born?
Sure.
What are you thinking about?
Why worry about this?
I'm afraid that
what if it frequently
fights with Xiongxiong
after giving birth?
You and your sister
are still arguing at this age.
That's true.
Yours is not sweet.
Well,
try mine.
Just eat.
Try mine.
Your ice cream has filling.
I even bit it.
My dad is biased.
Totally.
Mine has no filling.
Do you feel hot?
Too hot.
Has Haowen not returned?
He's busy.
Don't worry about him.
We'll eat together.
Always so busy.
Every time...
He brought seafood.
It's hard to have a meal together.
This is the first payment
for the substitute lecturer.
The finance department need your signature.
It's really expensive.
He is considered
the most cost-effective candidate.
And the dropout rate
may be very low.
Are you sure it's all good?
I think so.
Why are you hesitating?
Yes,
absolutely no problem.
Thank you.
Hold on.
Rachel told me that
the layoff lists for each department
have been submitted.
What about your department?
Mr. Zhang,
in the current situation,
my department is
really not suitable for layoffs.
Then you should have me fired.
Li Lin,
I'm preparing to return to China.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I've been thinking for long.
Would your husband
also be willing to come back with you?
I used to have to
worry about his feelings,
but now that I'm divorced,
I don't have any worries anymore.
I can do whatever I want.
Just live my life.
Are you divorced?
Is there anything wrong with that?
It's nothing.
Divorce may not be
a bad thing for me.
You know,
foreigners seem very open,
but in fact,
for a Chinese woman like me,
my ex-husband especially
minded my
being better than him
academically,
so we
got divorced.
I see.
I always thought
you were doing well
abroad.
Maybe everyone thinks
I'm quite glamorous
on the surface.
But to be honest...
It's actually quite difficult.
But this time when I came back,
I was quite happy
to see you.
I still feel
so familiar
with you.
I can express myself without restraint.
To be honest,
I haven't told anyone about this,
including my family.
Li Lin,
you are still the man
I trust the most.
Thanks.
Don't just talk about me.
How are you?
I...
Why are you so nervous?
I'm...
I'm not nervous,
not at all.
What am I nervous about?
[I'll do it myself.]
[Hold on.]
[It's okay.]
Hands off.
Yu Hai?
It's crooked. You can't see it.
Huang just
bought me a shirt,
otherwise I'll be late.
Go.
Professor Mei, you're back.
Professor Mei.
Come in.
No, thanks.
You have something to talk about.
It's not good.
Afraid I eat you?
They're my students.
I know.
I'm not going in.
What did you
just say to me?
Well...
Professor Mei?
I...
What?
Please take it in.
Stay in touch.
Goodbye.
Why aren't you
at home today?
Why did you come to
such a place with me?
I'm not happy today.
What's up?
I submitted a layoff list today
and feel very sad.
It's just the status quo.
The situation of Yu Hai
is also not good.
What we are fighting for now
is not adaptability,
but competitiveness.
I know that.
While...
You should go home
and discuss this with Li Lin.
Talking to a housewife
like me
won't help.
Li Lin is not here.
He went to Beijing.
Why going to Beijing?
To meet his old-time love?
Who?
Mei Yiduo.
Is she still there?
Don't say that.
She's doing well.
She runs
a laboratory in the US.
Are you concerned about
his ex-girlfriend?
Well,
know yourself as well as the enemy.
How can you rest assured that
he meets her?
He's making trouble.
But I don't think he dares
or would do that.
Hard to say.
What do you mean?
Sometimes men can't
withstand the test,
especially in front of women.
I still trust him
in this regard.
You hesitated.
No,
I'm serious.
If Li Lin
had any feelings for her...
Mei Yiduo had been
so proactive back then.
If so, then he won't be with me anymore.
How do you know
what they are thinking now?
How are you doing?
Still acting as a decoration at home?
As always.
Has Huang Sisi been bothering you?
She just messaged me.
That's really too much!
Sometimes men can't
withstand the test,
especially in front of women.
That's why
I want you to
help me find a job,
and see if I can be
a 'flexible decoration'.
I did find one,
but I don't think it's possible.
A clerk in a real estate company.
I think it may be
an insignificant position.
No problem,
can I?
You can,
but I don't think
it's necessary.
Why don't you wait a little longer?
Maybe I can find
a better one.
No, no, I don't want to wait.
It has been eight years,
and I've become disconnected
with the outside world.
I think
it's good to start
from the bottom.
How is that possible?
You learned finance
and used to work in an investment bank.
You dress delicately every day
and interact with elites.
How can you go there now?
No, no way.
The gap is too huge.
It's a waste of your talent.
Not at all.
Just let me try it.
If I really
separate from Yu Hai,
at least I need to know
if I have the ability
to raise two children first.
Seriously?
Sure.
Fine.
I will contact
the senior editor.
Before you go for the interview,
I will ask our company's
HR director
for you
to give you some guidance.
Good.
Come on,
I wish you success.
Definitely.
What do you think Li Lin is doing now?
Just as
what you're think of.
Put on slippers.
No.
Go.
There's no one at home.
Why are the lights still on?
I'm here.
Sweetheart.
Wanzhen?
I didn't lie to you.
Didn't you go to Beijing?
Yeah, I came back at once.
This meeting is a bit hasty.
Yu Hai always has meetings
that last for two days
at least.
I'm not his compare.
Mr. Yu has a great cause.
Alright, you can rest assured now.
I'm leaving.
I'll take you back.
No need,
take good care of Meng'an.
Let me know when you get home.
OK.